Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from Anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MDM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MDM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MDM Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
BedMGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Press to Waiter.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Offer not available in all states.
Terms apply.
See Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to We'll see you and how folks.
It's the old podcast you go to when you want to hear about the horror movies and sci -fi movies and fantasy films and sometimes action and once in a while comedy too.
And if you don't like it, a fuck you.
Let's watch the language it is Christmas.
I believe this episode drops on Christmas Eve.
And that's why folks today we're going to do a commentary eventually.
On a Twilight Zone episode.
Season 2 episode 12.
Night of the meek.
I've actually not seen it.
I've only seen the first season of Twilight Zone, which I know is embarrassing, but I'm working through it.
This is my hands -down, probably least favorite episode ever.
No, Twilight Zone.
It's a touching sort of inspirational episode about a drunk turning his life around.
It opens on a Santa Claus drunk in a bar.
I've said many times in the past, I am convinced that this is what bad Santa was based on.
Yeah.
And they said, well, what if he doesn't learn a lesson?
We just steer into him being a drunk and a creep, but who knows?
But, you know, my Twilight Zone faves are the ones that get a little odd, a little dark.
I was at a, the, the new bar over on Hillhurst here in Los Filos called Atrium.
A little fancy, schmancy for my taste, but they had a great happy hour.
I was meeting a friend, and I got there a half hour early.
So I ordered a drink.
I'm sitting at the bar, and I look up in much like in a Twilight Zone episode.
I see in the mirror, because one of the walls across from me was mirrored.
And I watch an old man fully dressed as Santa with a giant, not just blood red, but damp.
Black eye, sits down next to me, and I see him in the mirror, and I swear to you,
I thought that when I turned to my left to look at him, he would not be there.
And I would only be seeing him in the mirror.
But there he was.
He had a wet damp black eye that was either from getting punched or from falling on something.
And this bar, you know, as in typical Los Filos fashion, you couldn't get a drink
under six bucks, but he kept putting them back.
Wearing under six minutes, mind you folks.
I do want to talk about something truly horrific, and I brought this up in the last podcast,
but I wanted to make sure that Joe saw the video.
Well, bump this up.
This is the scary stuff for this.
This is the scariest of stuff and sort of screaming in as well.
A very quick recap of the story in case you don't know it, but there's a young woman,
17 years old, who accused girls and crashing rider, Murray Miller of rape.
She said she woke up and he was assaulting her.
He's a much older gentleman.
Lena Dunham, because she was working with this guy, was like, no way, I know you.
You couldn't have raped her.
Lena Dunham, feminist extraordinaire, advocate for the downtrodden, takes to the internet
and declares that this young girl, who was also, by the way, half black,
and complicating things even further for Ms. Woke Lena Dunham.
She gets up and says, this woman is lying.
I'm sorry.
This just seems to be one of those cases, one of those three percent of cases,
where the rape claim is misreported because this can't be true.
This guy is too good a guy.
No way it happened.
And in fact, I have proof that it didn't happen.
I can't tell you what that proof is, but I do have it.
Completely discredits this woman's story.
Cut to months later, Lena Dunham writes the worst apology I've ever seen in my life.
Of course, it was entirely about Lena Dunham and her own experience.
And she discusses her own sexual assaults in the article, which made it very gross
because it isn't about you, Lena Dunham.
Not everything is about you.
And she didn't, she's incapable of understanding that.
Yes.
Then she admits in the apology, as like an afterthought, also I had no proof that this
guy didn't do it.
That was a lie.
I made that up to discredit a sexual assault victim.
And everyone's reading this apology and like discuss it.
You got to sit down and read this thing.
If you thought that love actually piece got your dander up, you got to sit down and read
this.
But then came, and I've only been able to watch the one minute highlight clip.
I can't watch the full five minute speech.
But Lena Dunham brings up the mother of the 17 year old girl who was assaulted, who
Lena Dunham publicly called a liar at the Hollywood Reporter Awards and a Hollywood Reporter
event brings her up on stage.
She has, she has a microphone, but Lena Dunham is not allowed to speak.
As Lena Dunham goes through a speech saying, me, me, me, I learned, I learned, I've changed.
I'm sorry.
I want to say publicly.
My favorite line is when she says, I allowed the patriarchy to pollute my thinking.
No, Lena, you just did what you did.
Stop passing the polluted.
Yes.
But your entire brain is polluted by being a rich spoiled bitch.
Now let's, let's complicate it even more.
Yes.
Deadline reports.
Los Angeles DA declines charges against girls writer and EP Murray Miller.
Case has been dismissed.
So here's the thing.
I don't know Murray.
I don't know this woman.
I don't know.
I have no doubt, I have no reason to doubt either of them.
I have, I was not there.
I do not know what happened.
But I will say this.
What really pisses me off about this whole Lena Dunham thing is now you see them.
Yes.
Let's, let's just say for argument's sake, what if the guy is innocent, okay?
Let's just say for argument's sake, what if he's guilty?
What if he's guilty?
She goes out publicly, throws the girl under the bus.
Then when that's, because that's what works for her at the time.
Then when that doesn't work for her anymore, she goes out and throws the guy under the bus.
Correct.
And in either those cases, if he's not in the position that she's claiming he's in, as far
as innocent or guilty concern, what it all goes back down to is Lena Dunham does for
Lena Dunham.
She brought this woman on stage to make herself look good and get her fucking round of applause.
She said the first time, I know he's, I know that he's innocent.
And then later, exactly as you're saying, now I know he's guilty.
What are you talking about?
Well, what's his deal?
You know, talk about playing with people's lives.
Yeah.
Lena, have, here's, here's my problem with the whole thing.
As I said, I have no reason to doubt his accuser.
And I also have no reason to cast aspersions against this man when I don't know anything about
the situation other than the information I've read publicly.
But my point is this, I have a tendency to believe victims as most of us do.
That's a good thing.
I think that we all do that.
But Lena Dunham has, she is removed from that argument or debate or whatever you want
to call it or stance perspective.
She has zero integrity.
She doesn't give, if she figured out the best thing for her to do was go on stage
and bring Donald Trump up there next to her and talk about how she was wrong about him,
you can bet your fucking ass she would do it.
You can bet your fucking ass she would do it.
Lena Dunham, this is not a me too discussion.
This is a Lena Dunham discussion.
She has no integrity.
She sucks.
Her work sucks.
She's annoying.
She's not funny.
She's a spoiled brat.
She was fucking escorted into this business by people that were able to bless her with
exorbitant amounts of money so she could fund her projects.
She's got rich parents as well.
She's got very rich, that's what I mean.
I'm talking about her parents.
She's got extremely rich parents.
She had very connections in very high places.
She grew up next to Merrill Street or something like that.
Where they're very, they're vacation homes were close together.
Right.
This is someone who does not understand a non -privileged experience but pretends that she can
write to it and I really like the first and second season of girls.
The first season in particular, I was like, this is something new, I like what I was saying.
I like the first season too.
And then little by little you're like, oh wait, this isn't a satire of terrible people.
This is just terrible people telling their truth.
I always thought she was like, look smarter than the characters.
No.
Absolutely not.
No, she thinks that's how like real people should act.
Yes.
Like they should be like, you know, worrying about nothing but partying in brown stones in
New York and complaining about how their parents won't fund their ride anymore.
Right.
Like, it's not like, you know, Whit Stillman or somebody like that, like, you know, taking
shots at these people through their work or know a bomb block or something.
Or Bredeest and Ellis, I would also say.
Yes, absolutely.
But for me, the cringiest part of this video was, and I watched this in my writer's room
and people screamed from start to finish, oh, like, oh, no.
And the biggest screams this thing got were when Lena turns to the mother of this victim
who Lena Dunham has publicly called a liar and she turns around and she goes, I learned
through this process, that it's time to cut the shit and put on my big girl pants.
And also cut the shit.
So she's going to say shit, like, I'm still edgy even at a Hollywood reporter event.
I'm going to say shit and put on your big girl, your 32, big girl pants also to, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
And this might come as out of line to certain people.
You know, who does this daughter disservice?
The mother.
You love your daughter.
You stand by your daughter.
Say fuck off Lena Dunham.
I'm not going up there with you.
Yeah.
I don't want to pile on this woman.
But still.
Yeah.
But it's like, you know, somebody went after your kid and then you go up there and champion
her.
Yeah, I find that gross too, but if I got a pick between the grosser of these people, of course.
Yeah, I'm going up.
Lena's the grosser.
You know, it was her idea calling it, hey, you know, it would be great.
There's a Hollywood reporter event coming up.
It like, here's what you should do, Lena Dunham.
Call her up and apologize and let that be that.
That we live in this society where apologies don't count unless they're public for an audience
of people applauding you for making the apology, where I would say that completely invalidates
your apology.
And apology should be, do you want on one, forgive me for what I've done.
And then people will actually watch this thing and go, look how sincere she was.
Oh, look how sincere the actor was.
Yeah.
Some of the best acting I've seen from Lena Dunham.
And then she said, we've laughed together.
We were friends.
You're not friends.
No.
She's a lady you met in a time of crisis because you fucked up and now you got to come
around and fix it.
And you're going to do it on a big stage so everybody can see and pat you on the back
and you can continue to have a career.
You're manipulative.
You suck.
Beat it.
And she won't.
She'll continue to be famous and get you.
She's writing a movie for J .J. Abrams and Steven Spielberg.
Lena Dunham.
Why?
And it's about like a historical event so that it's not even like something remotely in her
wheelhouse.
I hate this fucking business.
I swear to God.
Go read that article, watch at least the minute version of the Hollywood reporter thing.
This article it starts and it's like, we all knew about Harvey Weinstein.
We discussed it over past appetizers.
That's how these things starts.
And she's writing about like, we had to tear down the crinoline walls of oppression and
to stop trying to get raves for your writing when you're talking about rape.
Right.
You know, you've already got a pretty checkered history dealing with this issue.
Drop the fucking, I'm trying to win a creative writing class award.
And if you want any respect from anyone, go away for a while.
Or if you need to write about it, stop acting like you're auditioning.
It's like, there's a line from, I'll do anything, which is a great underrated James
El Brooks movie.
And Nick Nolte says to this woman, he's like, quit posing for this picture of you that nobody
is taking.
Wow.
That's how I feel about Lena Dunham.
Nobody cares, but you just keep shoe warning your way in.
The vast majority of people who hate Lena Dunham have never seen any of her work.
They're just like, ah, you know, she's this, she's that.
Lena, stick to what you're good at.
Go and go to go to a college and complain that the cafeteria's version of sushi is somehow
an appropriational offense against the culture.
Go complain that the fucking Jason Bourne posters on the subway had guns in them.
Stick to what you're good at.
While having a show set in New York in 2011 that didn't have a black person for an entire
season.
I love this fucking shit.
I love this shit.
These people that bitch about, you know, she's, she's a champion against white privilege.
I've never seen somebody more white in privilege in my entire fucking life.
All white cast, there, there weren't black extras.
No.
And by the way, that's an appetite issue as well, who, ah, you know, it's just complicit
in that show.
But, ah, yeah, just, just a world of New York, no different than friends in, in 1996.
Just so sick of this shit.
I'm just so sick of it.
Stop using people's pain to make yourself look better in either direction.
It's fucked up.
It's weird.
And in my opinion, it is as low as Trump separating kids from their families.
It's fucking gross.
It's exploitative.
It's selfish.
It's manipulative.
And it's fucking psychotic.
Lena, your social path, shut up.
Go away.
All right.
Agreed.
Jesus Christ.
Wow.
We came in real hot.
Christmas day for Christ's.
It's, it's not for us, but, ah, we are about to kind of, ah,
head out on our breaks.
We need, we need these breaks.
We're hanging on by a very thin thread.
And we're about to sit back with an old classic.
I guess we should do our movie corner first.
It's only a 25 minute episode.
And this is what's cool is I believe next Monday, and I could, I could clarify this by looking
at a calendar on the phone in my pocket, but I won't do it.
Yeah.
I'm just going to speculate.
Next Monday, I believe, is New Year's Eve.
That's true.
And January 5th.
My birthday.
So next Monday, we, we, we, we, we, we should give you some kind of New Year's evil.
Oh.
I'm not, I didn't make that up.
Somebody made that up.
There was a movie New Year's evil.
We could also do, you know, do our top films of the year, you know, I'd have to really scrape
hard to get 10, but I haven't watched all my screeners.
I like when you scrape hard to get 10.
Just periods, scrape.
I'm a, I'm a scraper.
I'm a scraper.
I'd like to start with, you know, you want to talk about political correctness, something
that gleefully goes in the face of political correctness, and it was a three part comedy
special on Netflix called bumping mics.
I still got to watch it, man.
I still got to watch this thing.
David Tell and Jeff Ross, there's something, Jeff Ross, there's just something about the
guy I've watched, you know, his, his roast, and then when he went down to Guantanamo Bay and
all this stuff he's doing, he really is sort of, he's doing much more to unite people than
Alina Dunham.
Yeah.
By saying horrific things, you know, like things that would get you thrown out of a lot of
places in Los Angeles.
I agree.
And it's more inclusive and there's, there's more warmth to it than anything Lina Dunham's
ever put on screen.
And tell, you know, one of my all time true favorite comedians, he can still land a punch
line like nobody's business.
He seems a little exhausted in this one.
He's always sitting down.
But just to watch these two masters go at it, riff on each other, riff on the audience and
the audience no matter how bad the thing is that's being said, just laughs and laughs and
laughs and has fun.
And it's an equal opportunity offender.
And I had so much fun watching this thing.
They do tiny little bits in New York, like they all go get a sandwich with Gilbert Godfried.
There's a little bit of that comedians and cars bit, but it's only a minute at a time.
It's mostly just stand up.
They got great guests.
They have Michael Che, the most likable I've seen him since he's, you know, SNL is not a
good showcase for that man.
Love Che.
Che.
He's got a sweet spirit.
Yeah.
He was great.
Paul Rudd comes up on stage for 10 minutes.
He's delightful and hilarious.
Nice.
I think my friend Rachel Feinstein is in there.
Feinstein somewhere.
Schumer and Nikki Glazer all take the stage together.
They got, it's just, there's such a fun, positive vibe from it.
I recommend it a lot.
I laughed really hard for all, you know, however long it is, put, put end to end.
And it's probably 90 minutes of your time, but boy, there's some really funny stuff
on there.
Great jokes.
Oh, that's awesome.
I saw, I ran into a tell a couple of times last week.
We did a, we're not last couple of weeks ago.
We did a benefit show together for the great Preston and Steve radio show in Philadelphia.
It was rich, rich, rich boss, a tell in myself and some other comics too.
But we, I saw them there and he was hilarious as always and then I saw them at the comedy
store and he was hilarious.
So I'm happy that that's happening.
I just, I see Jeff all the time too.
Happy for those guys.
They're good dudes.
Yeah.
All right.
I saw, excuse me, first off, I'll start with a rewatch.
Paul Schrader's Dominion, never saying a prequel to the exercise.
I own it.
Never saying it.
I've seen it.
It's one of these things.
I go back.
I try to give it another chance.
This thing is such a piece of fucking shit.
I mean, it is so fucking boring, the CGI in it is so bad and unnecessary.
It just sucks.
The exorcist and the exorcist three are the only exorcist movies.
I mean, it's just, they have tried to revisit this.
The TV shows first season, got us back in the saddle and then they ruined it by going out
of the Reagan -McNeil story in the second season and then it was just about exorcists
and you're like, well, who cares, like, I like this because it was connected to the movie.
Yeah.
You know, it's just, god damn, and it's got Stalin's scars guard, who I love and you've
watched both versions of it.
Oh yeah.
Well, I can't figure out which is worse than the other.
They both suck.
Jesus.
I root for Schrader.
He's either on or he's way off, but, you know, obviously, taxi driver, raging bull, some
xenofliction, which he directed as one of my favorite movies.
The first reformed with Ethan Hawke, I'm seeing get a lot of awards buzz, which I'm very surprised
by.
I thought it was too weird for that, but it's a really great movie that came out this year,
first reformed and it's hitting DVD as we speak.
I mean, look, one of my all -time favorites ever is Autofocus.
Love Autofocus.
Just one of the creepiest movies ever.
I love Autofocus.
Greg Canier, like you've never seen him before.
It's true.
DeFo, you've seen him before.
You've seen this version before.
Yeah, I never saw Dominion.
I will check it out.
I would like to discuss at some point.
God bless.
I saw a rewatch myself on the last episode we talked about.
Can you ever forgive me, feeling like early Woody Allen, and, you know, I said, I think that's
just the Autumn in New York vibe.
They have people in sweater vests and stuff.
I watched one of the ultimate Woody Allen sweater vests, Autumn in New York movies, Manhattan
Murder Mystery.
What are my favorites?
Yeah, I saw it.
I remember, I would rent anything that wasn't rated R. I used to rent six movies at a clip,
and my dad did not want me to watch Manhattan Murder Mystery, and I was like, it's PG.
Back on, and this was right when Woody Allen stuff was really coming out, and he's like,
he's a molester.
I don't want you getting this stuff in your head.
I'm like, dad, I think it's a fun romp.
I'm the last thing in the movie.
We watched it together, and I think he enjoyed it as well by the end.
It's one of his most kind of light, fluffy, delightful type movies.
It really is entertaining.
Fun movie trivia on that film, and why it works so well.
Number one, it's the first thing he did with Diane Keaton in 20 years or something like that.
Number two, the great Zach Braff plays their son.
Zach Braff does play the son.
Number three, that whole movie was a B story for Annie Hall that had to be cut for time.
So it's almost like you're getting a weird Annie Hall sequel or something.
Because it does get into like the strain, there is a strain on their relationship,
as they both sort of take different approaches to is our neighbor a murderer or not.
And then you got Alan Alda coming in, which is in what I assume would have been the Tony,
what's Robert's world over Roberts any day of the week.
I love Roberts.
I wish, he's one of those guys.
I'm like, why doesn't he just pop up in Woody Allen movies or any movies?
It's fucking Tony.
Did he retire?
Like, who isn't going?
They probably got on the ludes at some party in the 70s and killed a woman together.
We have a lot of different time at Hollywood.
My point is it's like, you know, you're making a movie in New York.
You go, hey, I got this like two to two page scene, the Tony Roberts.
You want to come do this?
Like, I don't I never get why does he even act anymore?
That's my question is did he just walk away?
I love Alan Alda in this movie.
The Alan Alda.
Alda's great.
And what I really like about Alda in Manhattan Murder Mystery is the only other Woody Allen movie.
I think the only other Woody Allen movie he's in is Crimes and Misdemeanors.
Yes.
And he is such an, he's hilarious, but he's such an unlikable prick of a man in that movie.
Yeah.
It's fun seeing him be like nice approachable Alan Alda style, like mash Alan Alda in Manhattan Murder
Mystery.
Tony Roberts still live.
Still works was in something called the longest week with Jason Bayman.
I've never even heard of.
All right.
Amityville 3D.
He played John Baxter, the owner of the infamous.
The one from the 80s?
Yeah.
All right.
I've been having Mr. Murder Mystery was in that style that Woody Allen had.
Husbands and wives used it as well.
We're like the cameras just always moving.
It's sort of a, I don't mean he didn't invent this, but it felt like it really influenced
the the indie film movement of the late 90s.
It was a lot of fun.
It was just a funny, really fun movie.
They got a great villain in the guy who plays Hesh on the sopranos.
The guy who they think killed his wife was great in it.
Just a good cast.
Everybody's strong in it.
And I heard from the Wikipedia page anyway.
Apparently, while this was going on, while the whole thing was going on,
and Mia Farrow had them on 2020 and everything,
he's like, I got to press on to make this movie to get my mind off this.
And who shows up day one for a fitting, but Mia Farrow?
What?
At least this is on the Wikipedia page.
She has publicly accused him as everyone knows at this point.
And she shows up on day one because she was supposed to be playing the dying Keaton role.
And she's like, I'm here to get fitted for wardrobe.
I didn't know that.
You're not in the movie anymore, Mia.
And she's like, what?
That's not going down this road.
The uh, the uh, I just, for those of you at home,
I just literally did the sign felt take from sign felt when somebody says something crazy
and he turns his head almost to a 90 degree angle.
We've started a new thing on cool kids where when somebody says something that pisses
his dad off, he goes, I got a pace.
He gets up and paces around and goes, woo, woo.
It's very funny.
My friend Keith Robinson, one of the funniest human beings on earth, who, who had a stroke,
he will often yell when you meet when in a moment like that.
I'm going to have another fucking stroke.
God damn it.
I saw another bad film.
I watched The Vault with James Franco.
I don't think I've talked about this yet on here.
Not even familiar with The Vault.
It's a bank robbery movie where something is a foot down in the bank vault.
Sure.
Something otherworldly is going on down there.
Look, the movie sucks.
It's boring.
It's routine.
You've seen it all before.
Spoiler alert within the first seven minutes.
If you've ever seen one of these movies, you know that James Franco's character is clearly a ghost
that only the robbers are seeing.
And that, of course, is supposed to be the big payoff twist.
And these robbers are actually caught in hell or something or, you know,
they robbed the place and it all went wrong and now they have to relive it.
So I'm fucking shit.
I don't know.
The movie sucks.
Okay.
I don't want to see.
The only thing I ever want to see Franco play dumb is, yeah, is a dummy.
Yeah.
Is a dummy that like, that's like smell my dick man.
You know what I mean?
Like, the guy plays in the interview.
Like, that's only ever want to see him play anything else.
I don't care.
I'm dumb out.
I watched thoroughbreds which came out early 2018.
That's a sequel to Hot to Trot.
Right?
It is.
Okay.
Dabney Coleman.
No, thoroughbreds.
By the way, they pitched Dabney Coleman to the cool kids.
There's a love interest the other day.
And I was like, let's fucking book Dabney Coleman.
And they were like, well, did you see his age?
The man's 87 years old.
Dude, I watched, I looked up Dabney Coleman interviews.
I found TMZ stuff from recently still sharp as a tech.
There's a, there's a documentary coming out about him.
All right.
Maybe we'll get him.
I was just like, Vicki's 65, 87's a big.
It's a big jump.
But he's still, he's still sharp as a tech.
All right.
He's out in front of the thing.
He's like, you got two minutes, son.
You got two minutes and you're failing right now.
Like he's still Dabney Coleman.
All right.
And the trailer for this documentary,
there's a line where he goes,
the guy said, the director says to me,
can you come in and play a tough guy with this?
I said, I'm Dabney fucking Coleman.
That's what I do.
All right.
I'm just happy that he's not.
I was scared he was going to be like drooling.
Well, he was in boardwalk empire,
which was not that long ago.
And he was a commanding presence.
But he did not look the same.
Now, he just looks like an old,
he just got his star in the walk or whatever.
Yeah.
So that you can find the footage of that.
Anyway, all right.
I saw Thura Breds.
It was critically acclaimed.
It came out earlier this year.
It's an indie movie.
Stars Olivia Cook,
who was in Ouija.
She was also in Ready Player One.
It also stars.
She the love interest in Ready Player One.
I believe so.
And yet Taylor Joy,
who was the girl from The Witch
and the girl from Split,
who I like a lot.
The blonde hair daughter.
Correct.
And she was also Anton Yelchin.
It was his last film.
R -I -P.
The movie was compared most often to Heather's.
It is two young girls,
one of whom is a complete sociopath,
much likely in a Dunham
with no regards for human emotion.
Has no human feelings.
And they basically are like,
you can sure get away with a lot
if you don't care about human feelings.
There's murders.
They kill people.
There's a horse murder at one point.
The movie,
a horse murder.
I found repellent.
And as a guy who certainly feels empathy
but kind of struggles to like
cry, you know,
and have these human emotions sometimes.
I thought I was going to really get on its wavelength
but it was a nice reminder
that like, well,
no, I'm not a complete joyless piece of shit
like these two, you know.
I'm far from it and I don't know,
maybe it's just the times
but I did not need to see two young girls
who are, you know,
just miserable human beings
who do miserable things for 90 minutes.
Heather's had a sense of humor
where it, you know,
at least turned the lens on those people
and made you see how bad they were.
This sort of celebrated these girls
and I just found it gross.
It was not entertaining to me at all
and I can't recommend it
even though it was highly praised.
Yeah, I hear you.
And Heather's also has that mean girl's moment
where we're known to ride or realize is
yeah, or the craft is another one
where she realizes like
these people are terrible.
This does not have that moment.
Well, yeah.
All right.
Last but not least,
I saw a dark song.
We were going to review it on here
but now we're not so.
Solid horror movie.
About a woman who has lost her child
to murder, I believe.
If I remember correctly.
And she hires a man
to who's an occultist
to basically help her
conjure the spirit
so she can talk to her daughter.
Irish picture and find
solace in all this.
Yeah, I think it was Irish.
But the actors weren't Irish.
Or they were.
I think they sounded English.
You very remember.
To help but she wants closure with the situation.
Great low budget, one location horror film.
I bet you the budget for this thing
was like a million bucks at most.
It's all shot in in one house.
The acting in it is great.
The two it's two characters.
They're both great.
There's some nice, creepy, scary shit at the end.
And then it's kind of an overall
surprisingly uplifting message.
Which you're not expecting.
So I recommend it.
It's about 90 hot minutes.
You're in and out.
And it's it's worth the watch.
I'll check her out.
That being said, let's get on to our commentary.
Let's do it.
Night of the meek.
This is streaming on net.
I'm on Hulu.
Twilight Zone is streaming on Hulu.
Again, season two, episode 12.
We'll hit play after a one, two, three on play.
One, two, three.
Play.
We are rolling.
Here's the opening credits.
You're seeing the clouds and now the sun.
And a black line go across the bottom of the screen.
I never understood why they did that.
It's an odd choice.
I just put a thick black line across
so the sun can go down.
That's stupid.
Anyway, yeah, I have only seen the first season
of the Twilight Zone.
I have them all on Blu -ray.
They look fantastic.
But I just haven't been able to work my way through it.
As quickly as I'd like.
Well, interesting fact,
if you have not watched anything past the first season,
you've never seen a Twilight Zone
with the classic Twilight Zone theme.
The original, the first season theme is not
the classic one that we all know.
But we open on a, I mean, I'm telling you,
this is bad Santa.
It's a department store manager being like,
where is he?
Where is Santa Claus?
It's not here.
You know, he should have been here an hour ago.
Where is he?
And then it cuts.
And you gotta Santa Claus getting shit fit.
This is the exact opening of bad Santa.
Drew.
You know, he's dirty.
He's pretty gross.
Played by the great.
Where that opening monologue of bad Santa
can still just make me howl.
It is so fucking fun.
I forget what the opening monument,
I gotta watch it again this year.
It's been a joke.
He just talks about what a piece of shit life is, basically.
It's like how it begins.
Uh, the great art carny playing Santa Claus in this film.
Or in this episode and strange.
It's strange seeing art carny in a dark role like this.
You know, he's, he's a fucking mess.
And I mean, and they really get into the alcoholism of it all
because he's got a full sandwich there that he paid for.
And he hasn't eaten any of it.
Right.
He's just drinking shot after shot.
Like, you know, they really nailed what it is.
Now, are you excited about the new Twilight Zone, Jordan Peele?
I'm excited about anything Twilight Zone related.
I hope it's good.
I'm excited about it.
I'm not excited to get CBS on demand to watch it.
Part sucks.
I don't want to support CBS.
And reminds me, Joe,
why did you tell Lesmond Vesitivity?
No, Joe had a little theory that he might have been kicked off my show
because his character was a sexual predator.
And all this stuff that went down,
I just read a huge article about it,
was going on as that show was getting better.
Yeah, I honestly, I think that we're like,
we can't have this character.
I think you're right.
And he wasn't, my character wasn't a predator.
He was just a pervy, he was a horny dude.
Correct.
That it was all consensual, but he liked the flirt and fuck.
Yeah.
And but they were taken this, if you remember,
the execs were coming into this thing like,
that we can't have this.
Right.
And it was like, what?
Everybody was like, what is so bad about this?
It's like a fucking guy that like,
chases Wimley, who cares?
I'm pretty sure that's what was going on.
And he, now this, this came out,
they interviewed people at CBS.
I don't know if you read this.
40 something different people all came far with the exact same story
that he had on the payroll, on call,
a woman who was on call to blow him,
to go into his office and blow him.
And they were all like, I don't know if she was paid for that reason,
but they were like, she avoided termination.
She stayed with the company for a very long time,
because she was his widely known on call.
Can you please come down to my office and people would go,
why is this woman with no ties to the company always in his office?
He was claiming that these blow jobs were consensual,
which probably just means he had some sort of legal document.
But that incident alone, combined with other stuff that has yet to come out,
cost him the $120 million payday he was going to get.
Don't feel sorry for the man, of course,
but he's done and not giving that payday.
He's fucked.
He seems like a real piece of trash.
Here's the crazy part, though.
He was the reason I got the job, if you remember.
You told me
moon vet before we knew any of this shit, obviously.
Moon vet saw your tape, thought you were hilarious.
I think they're going to give you the job.
Yes, I mean, he does, he says say in all that shit.
So I mean, it's so, so maybe my theory's wrong.
My point is I kind of had spirit.
Frankly, he yeah, he was taking notes.
Yeah, this is good stuff.
Anyway,
night of the make people is what we're watching here on the twilight zone.
It's the Christmas episode if you've never seen it.
Do they do other Christmas episodes of twilight zone?
This is the only one that I can remember.
Tell us from the dark side has
one of the best horror Christmas episodes ever of anything I've ever seen ever.
It's called seasons of belief.
And if it was streaming, we would do it, but it's just not streaming anywhere.
We try to do stream stuff that you can stream on a service,
not that we have to pay for to rent or whatever, but it was on shudder and now it's gone.
But anyway, it's about two parents.
One of them is played by the, I forget the guy's name,
but he plays, he plays Beverly DeAngelo's dad in Christmas vacation.
John Forsyth.
No, that's not John.
Oh, that's Chevy Chase's dad.
EG Marshall.
Chevy Chase's dad is not John Forsyth either.
Chevy Chase's dad is played by the actor who played the original Frank Costanza,
who was later replaced by, no, his dad is, I'm sorry, if not John Forsyth.
Not John, that's the guy from Dallas.
John Randall.
What's his name?
It's not John Forsyth.
No, I know who John Forsyth.
John Randolph.
Okay.
Well anyway.
Yes, John Randolph.
So EG Marshall is the dad.
Dig this.
The wife in this thing is like 32.
They got EG Marshall as her husband.
It's got like 78 years old.
They got two six -year -old kids.
It makes no sense.
But the whole thing is about how the parents make up this story about this.
Look, it's bad Santa.
He just fell off the Santa Claus thing.
They were almost definitely inspired by this, I would imagine.
Yeah, now the moms are yelling at him and everything.
Yeah, you know, they made it funny in the movie because it's he pisses himself, which is funny.
Do you just piss on yourself?
Anyway, they make up this story for the kids about this monster called the grither
that comes from the North Pole.
Okay.
And it's a really creepy story.
There's an awesome payoff.
I love it.
I watch it every Christmas with my dear friend, Mr. Pinkstone,
that we often refer to on this show.
Sure, sure.
Every Christmas we hit that up.
I love it.
But this night of the week is not scary.
This is about if you haven't been paying attention,
a guy that plays Santa Claus in a department store that's a complete fucking drunk.
I mean, you take the beard and the Santa Claus job away from this guy.
You got Patty Walsh.
Oh, for God's sake.
You got a guy just stumbling around defending everyone,
drinking his dinner.
I haven't had a drink all weekend.
But here's the thing, or weekend.
Not a huge accomplishment, but here we are Sunday.
You went to the Los Lobos X concert last night.
Anyway, what the fuck is Los Lobos playing with X?
That's a weird combo.
Well, they're both very LA bands.
And X was a X -scene survenka is a Hispanic.
There might be some crossover there.
I think she's sung a song or two with them.
But I've loved X forever, really love X.
And Los Lobos, I like but feel like they
were hurt a little by 80s production.
Sometimes they sound a little too clean or something.
Seeing them live, they were fucking amazing.
Amazing guitar players.
Just killer solos.
I had a blast.
I did get high.
I just didn't drink.
And X fucking killed it like they always do.
It was a hell of a show.
Where'd you do last night?
Last night I stayed in, watched boy erased and fell asleep at 8 p .m.
Wow.
All right, I have residual stress.
I don't deal with the stress as it's happening.
And then when the weekend comes more and more,
I fall asleep earlier and earlier due to the week's stress.
I have to wake up every Saturday and get a script out.
And I feel a lot of pressure and then I collapse.
Okay, that's just what I do now.
Sounds like a lot of fun.
Yeah.
In this version of the drunk Santa in the night of the make,
as you could see here, he's actually remorseful.
Yes.
He's not a man that's given up completely.
He knows he's got a drinking problem.
He actually says to the manager of the store,
who by the way is played by one of my favorite character actors.
I don't know his name,
but he's the guy from, he was in the original odd couple.
I said I had to leave at 12.
Remember I said that when we sat down that guy.
And then he's also one of the greatest golden girl characters ever.
He's the guy that like they find irresistible.
Right.
And they have to fuck him.
Like they're all like they can't.
And he's like this weird little nerd.
I don't remember that one.
Oh, it's great.
Dorothy starts dating him.
She doesn't want to date him because she's like look at this guy.
He's like four foot eight.
And he's bald and he's got glasses.
Like he's like a little weird nerdy guy.
But he's like a sexual dynamo.
Yeah, and Dorothy's like I everything we have.
There's a really funny scene with her and Rose.
She goes, Rose, everything we have is under the sheets.
And Rose goes, what's under the sheets?
And she goes, his cappuccino maker, Rose.
Boy, how many of those jokes do they do on that show?
They're the best jokes on the show.
Yeah, they're very funny.
They lean off of them in the later seasons
because they're clearly trying to make Dorothy less mean.
Really?
To Rose.
But like, yes, she just kind of starts to roll her eyes more.
But those jokes through the first four seasons are fucking unbelievable.
So I was like, yeah, Dorothy, did you have a bad day?
And she's like, no, it was like it's always like the most innocent question.
Yeah.
Would just be shat on in this horrible way.
Yeah, there's the, yeah, there's the one where Rose goes or she goes, so fear.
Are you upset? Are you still upset about Dorothy?
No, Rose. I'm upset because they canceled 30 something.
A lot of shots hit like other TV shows.
A lot of shots of the TV of the day.
I've noticed that.
Some of them I don't even get because I don't know what the show is, but yeah.
Yeah, so no Rose.
The, uh, so the Santa Claus is remorseful.
He's trying to mooch drinks.
He's been fired from the job at the store.
His, uh, he's, he's been cut off.
His credit is no longer good.
He's now walking the streets on Christmas Eve.
Uh, just shit faced dressed up as Santa Claus.
And it's snowing.
It's relentlessly snowing.
Doesn't sound like that bad of an evening.
I mean, it's, it's what I plan on doing this year.
Yeah.
This is what I should do when I've had it with my family on a holiday.
You know, by the time we're fighting by Christmas dinner,
yeah, I should just have a suit that I could hop into and just go outside.
I just walk around drunk.
It's, I mean, honestly, it sounds great to me.
Um, that's what Santa can as except you got too many other drunks, too many other variables.
We didn't do the Santa crawl this year.
We forgot.
I don't think we want to be doing it.
It's, it's taken on a real ugly turn.
It's gotten very fratty, but there was a time when it was fun.
All right.
Now it's like, it feels like Wall Street guys.
What, uh, we need a little more Wall Street.
Yeah, let's Wall Street.
That's right.
Where, uh, when does it happen?
What's the date?
I bet it's already happened in LA.
The New York one, you'll see people bitching about it all the time.
LA, Santa Con, I bet it was this weekend, but let me check.
As if this guy couldn't get any lower in this episode,
somebody just threw a can of garbage out there window from the second story and hit him in the head.
Yeah.
Yep.
Santa Con was Saturday.
But then he turns and he sees the garbage bag has turned magically into a bag of presents,
a Santa sack, if you will.
That's pretty stupid.
And he picks it up.
He has already shown his remorse.
He's got a bag full of presents now and he's dressed as Santa.
You can see where this is going, Pat.
I think I got it.
They remade this one in the 80s, uh, in the 80s,
Twilight Zone with Richard Mulligan.
I love Richard Mulligan.
Yeah.
It made me sad to see him playing a creep.
I like when he plays like a nice guy, but I shouldn't.
This isn't my least favorite episode.
It gets me in the spirit, but I mean, you know, Mulligan's in a good, uh,
Blake Andrews picture called SOB,
starring a topless Julie Andrews.
Blake Edwards, you mean?
Blake Edwards, yeah.
I thought he said Blake Andrews.
I remember skin Julie Andrews is his wife
and she is naked enough.
The lady from the sound of music?
Correct.
We'll look that up right now.
SOB and it's a Hollywood satire where Richard Mulligan plays a suicidal movie director.
And he's doing a sex movie with his wife, Julie Andrews.
But Julie Andrews was and is Blake Edwards' wife,
assuming he's still alive, which I don't think he is.
Blake Edwards always did like a real Randy type of picture.
Yeah.
There was a horniness too.
And skin deep with a glow in the dark condoms.
I didn't skin deep upset me because I didn't like seeing John Ritter play.
Play like kind of like a Bermotharia.
A Poonhound.
Right.
Oh yeah, there she is.
Topless.
That's you know, you don't expect to see that, do you?
You did a Julie Andrews topless image search just now.
Just Google Julie Andrews nude came right up.
I bet that is one of the least searched people.
Although in the season of Mary Poppins returning, I mean.
Well, yeah, I just probably got placed on some real purve list.
Oh yeah.
This purve's typing in Julie Andrews nude.
Yeah, let's send somebody over to his house.
Joey, you're going to see Mary Poppins returns.
I got the screener the other day.
Well, I know my lady friend would love to see it if I might borrow it,
unless you're looking to watch it.
Pat, you can't send it to me.
I don't only can you borrow it, you can keep the fucking thing.
All right.
I have.
She would never had the less interest in a sequel.
I never saw the original.
I fucking love Mary Poppins.
And you know, I'd be lying if I said I wasn't kind of excited to see it as well,
except it has Lin -Manuel Miranda.
And if he plays a rap and chimney sweep, I'm out.
I also heard that the famous song isn't it?
How are you getting screeners?
I'm not getting.
I'm in three unions, pal.
You're in one.
That's the difference between me and you.
DJ as well, or PG and DGA.
DJ, is that why you get the screener?
In the writers, in the actors.
I'm not fucking around.
I want to get into that producer somehow by the end of my life.
Producers gets even more.
But my question is, what's the famous song in Mary Poppins?
I don't think it has any of the same song.
It's an all -new musical.
But there's like the one song,
like there's that.
Jim Chimmyney, chip, chip, and ...
Yeah. And they were like saying like they chose ...
Super galloprazzles against me out of the ocean.
They chose not to use the big one.
I think we should pre -compress.
The birds,
tuppin',
supag,
uh ...
Dick Van Dyck has he playing the same character in this one?
No, he's playing like an old banker.
Why would he not be related to the original character?
sure. So you haven't even seen it. What are you so upset about because this movie is about the
original kids grown up with their own kids now and Mary Poppins comes back. Isn't that the point of
the movie? Maybe Dick Van Dyke plays Bert, but he's a banker now. I don't know. I haven't seen it.
I'm going to look it up. Take the mic for a minute. I'm looking this up because this is going to take me a minute.
I like Mary Poppins. I think that the use of animation mixed with the live action dancing was really fun.
That was your breaking record. The lady who wrote it, that was like what made her say,
fuck off. I want no part of it. Oh, right. I learned that in saving Mr. Banks.
Yes, she was a pretty good movie. I must say about the making of Mary Poppins with Tommy Hanks.
Folks, this holiday season, there's nothing I'm really excited to see. There's usually a
Paul Thomas Anderson, a Scorsese, a Cohen or something. The Cohen Brothers one came and went.
There's the Irishman, I guess, is being released and marched on Netflix. I mean, the movie industry
is going under to say the least. I don't want to watch a new Martin Scorsese movie on Netflix.
I don't want to watch a new Cohen Brothers movie on Netflix.
Here's one for you. Dick Van Dyke is playing the son of the character he played in the original
film. How the fuck does that work? That doesn't really make any sense. I guess it must be 100 years in
the future or something. Oh, I guess he's playing like the kid grown up now. Or something. I don't
fucking know. Anyway, Angela Lansbury is in this too. Oh, nice. I like Lansbury. I did Doug Love's
movies live at Largo a week ago. I went in hard on that Cohen Brothers movie. My buddy Daniel Van
Kirk was up on the panel. He said it was perfect. Come on, perfect. I said, perfect, what? I go
perfectly fucking boring. That movie sucked. He goes, didn't you think it looked beautiful? I said,
hey, Danny, Jenny McCarthy looks beautiful. I don't want to spend two hours with her babe.
Big laugh. Uh -huh. Then a guy started talking about a charity as for Yorkies to prevent them from
being put to sleep. And I asked when they put the Yorkies to sleep, do they just show them the bow to
buster shrugs? Nice. I was ahead of that one, but nice. Well, come on. I mean, it's a good bit, though.
You wrap it all up. He still won't ask me on that fucking show. I think he knows I'd be too good.
I'm sure that's what it is, Pat. I'm sure he's just too intimidated.
He's just always like cross -eyed stone, right? I mean, the man is not a secret. The man loves marriage
you want to. But to, uh, is anyone troubled by it? Uh, it seems troubling when I see him. Nobody
ever has ever troubled by pot, for some reason. Yeah. It is. I mean, people claim for years it's not
addictive. It's addictive. I think it's emotionally addictive without a doubt.
I was, uh, getting my, uh, jizz tested. And this, this is at home, you're just doing a taste test.
Yes. Right. We were, we were kind of doing a base level like just to find out like if we did want to
have a kid, should we do it sooner than later? Kind of situation. And, uh, I went in jerked off in a
room in, uh, Westwood, California. And my levels all came back great. I was honestly surprised.
So I said, Hey, just to ask, I'm curious. I said, I always heard the worst thing for
semen production is marijuana, but my friends who are huge pot heads all have babies. No problem.
Right. And he goes, yeah, he goes, that, you know, whether it was started to kind of keep people off
weed or what? He's like, we've essentially proven that that's a myth. He said, smoking marijuana
is not ideal for sperm production, but neither is smoking cigarettes. Like smoking is just bad for
your blood vessels and bad for everything. You shouldn't do it. He's like eating marijuana has no
discernible effect on sperm production. I was fascinated by this because I've been living a lie.
I lit one up right there on the doctor's office. We celebrated together. Um,
here's where we're at in the show. An old man is asking Art Carney, like, what, what do you want for
Christmas? Right. You've given these gifts away to everybody. Now, what do you want? Art Carney says,
I can't think anything I want. Uh, I think my only dream, whatever was to be the biggest gift
giver of all time. And I think I got to do that tonight. So clearly, this man is about to become
Santa Claus forever or kill himself, one of the two, which I got to be honest. It bothers me a little bit
because he's a fall down goddamn drunk through the whole thing. Why does he get rewarded?
You know, sure. What's his, you know what I mean? What's the takeaway? We should all drink
ourselves to death and maybe some point magic will turn it around. He finds the bag when he's like
shit face trying to get back into the bar. Right. You know, I don't know. I, whatever. So
notice his name is Bert. Have you, have you ever met a Bert under 40 years old?
Uh, I met, I think the first time I met Bert Kreischer, he was under 40. He is no longer. I've never
ever met him before. But he's an old Bert. Yes. Yes. Uh, okay. Was this guy drinking because he
couldn't be Santa Claus? Is that what I'm gonna be honest? I'm not sure that this whole episode isn't just
supposed to be that he's having to like a drunk delirious episode right now. Yeah. Uh, but there's
an elf. He might just be in a men's room pissing on the floor with trembling hands while all this
magic is going on. Yeah. He keeps handing sheets of toilet paper to people. Very Christmas.
Wipes and then hands it to somebody. Uh, but you know, he gets, he finds a sleigh with reindeer and an
elf. Yeah. At the end and, uh, and he, uh, he flies away on their thing. And then, you know,
these two are going home together. You got the guy back now, the sexual dynamo is back on screen.
Right. With the cop and, uh, they hear sleigh bells. Slay bells ring. Are you listening? I
guess the point. He says earlier, like somebody should tell these people that Christmas is more than
barging through the aisles and shoving people out of the way to buy what you want. So I guess the idea
is maybe he's, he might be a drunk, but he's got their, his heart's in the right place. Yeah.
We're everybody else's sober, but their piece is a garbage. Maybe. Okay. Something like that.
Again, it feels very pro booze. Oh, I don't hate that. Folks with one minute to spare,
I'd like to get on with the show. And at the same time on with the Joe, oh, oh, who wouldn't go,
Joe, oh, oh, who wouldn't go up on the house top. Click, click, click. Down the chimney with
jolt. Saint Nick. Rod Sireling signed off a word of the wise. I'll show it in the 20th century. Whether
they're gay, be pediatrics or geriatrics, whether they crawl in their knees and wear diapers or walk
with a cane and comb their beards. There's wonders, magic at Christmas. And there's a special power
reserve for little people. In short, there's nothing mightier than the meek and a merry Christmas
to each at all. Is that even the fame they were saying here? How was a drunk a meek? Well, the meek,
like the meek shall inherit the earth. Like he didn't have any money. He's, you know, he's downtrodden.
I thought the meek meant like weak. It means like the under guy. I guess he's weak. The under guy.
You're not on top. Yeah. You know, top of that bar stool. Oh, folks, guys, that's our show. I'll
be at Gotham Comedy Club next weekend. Come out and see me if you can. Oh, wait, not next weekend. Sorry.
The weekend after that. The first four week in a January. I'll be in Vegas in March. I'll be
in Austin at the Moon Tower Festival after that sometime. Joe DeRose a comedy on Instagram.
Oh, and my fiction is officially running starting in January in Penthouse. Some severe situations.
First story running is Wallace and his checkerboard. When I'm very proud of, I hope you get to read it.
This holiday season pick up a Penthouse magazine and read about Joe's scary stories.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. Cool kids Friday nights on Fox. Also on Hulu.
Catch up with your family over the break. We're coming back big in the new year. Thank you all.
Merry Christmas. Have a good one. See you next time. We'll see you in hell.
It's a cool show.