I'm here for Bett Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bett Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bett Rivers is the place to play in Bett. Bett Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply,
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
This episode is brought to you by US Cellular.
With a variety of options, US Cellular Prepaid makes finding the right wireless plan for
you easy.
That means you can get what you need at a price you can afford all while staying connected,
like two lines of unlimited data for just $60 a month and a free device like the Samsung
Galaxy A16 5G.
US Cellular Prepaid, Terms Apply, see US Cellular .com for details.
This is a Headgun Podcast.
Folks, because we kept you on hold for about a month and a half and didn't give you new
episodes and many of you were just being straight -up dicks about that, but a lot of you were
very nice and supportive.
We wanted to reward you.
The biggest request we get is a return to the old commentary episodes of your.
And tonight, surprise, surprise, surprise.
We told you we were given new episodes every other week.
Nope, you're getting two weeks in a row.
We told you we weren't doing any commentaries in a more nope.
We're doing one right fucking now.
Yeah, so we're mixing it up.
And that movie is the human centipede first sequence.
You all know this flick, we don't need to do a synopsis.
If you want to watch it along with us, we're streaming it from Netflix.
Go ahead and pause the tape now and go find it.
All right, we're back, we're paused up on the IFC opening screen.
Get yourself there.
If you need to pause again, do it.
We're at 128, 10.
If you need to sync.
That makes, that's a better way to do it in my way.
You never did this well back in time.
So I'm going to count the three then say play so one two three play
All right now and Joe you've seen the human centipede am I right only in real life
I've never seen the film adaptation Joe was the tale of one for the bulk of 2013 and
Good eat good eatin' from what I've heard
Um, so I described it, starring Dieter laser that can't be a real, and you know why that's probably not a real name because my biggest question with this movie and this entire franchise is how do you as an actor?
Mom, I'm out in Los Angeles. I know I'm not getting the parts, but I got to stick it out another year. I know I'll get something and then finally that call home.
Mom I booked something I'm in a movie really what's it called the human sense? Oh, it sounds kind of creepy
What's it about? Well, I play a girl whose lips get sewn are you see you're you're missing all these other names
By the way, you see in these names. I loan a sick. Oh, the last guy's name was holy spies
Okay, I think these are all fake names. Look at these names. Well Tom six is the director. Yeah, Tom six is the direct
But I think they're fake names because of that like if I was in this movie
I couldn't tell my parents I was in it. That would just never get told let me tell you why you're wrong
Dietrich laser is not a girl first of all because Dietrich's a man's name no
Dietrich laser is the guy. He's the he's the 70 -year -old man
So I don't think he was calling his mom about anything when he got this the I'm saying I'm talking about the actors at large
I know Dietrich laser is probably
but is that his real name?
I thought Udu Kiehr was in this.
Am I wrong?
Isn't that Dietrich laser?
That guy?
I thought.
Oh no, he's Udu Kiehr.
I thought it was Udu Kiehr,
but I didn't see him in the credits,
but I was looking at you.
I don't know.
I got real wound up on who Dietrich laser was.
My lord, we've botched this already.
It's an awesome name.
Can you stop that thing from bouncing
on the bottom of the screen?
Folks, I have OCD for weird things,
but when when an icon is bouncing on the bottom of the screen, I go completely insane.
I have a quick story about this film. My mom, I was over there. I didn't finish. Oh, I'm sorry.
Go ahead. You call home, and you got to tell your mom, and your dad, and presumably,
grandma, grandpa. I'm in a movie. When can we see it? Well, you can't see it. No, my granddaughters
finally in a movie. I got to see this thing. I mean, what do you do? They wouldn't speak to you again.
You say you say Nana
Open your mouth and I'll show you what this movie's all about oh no and then
And if I feel like I'm being a little too subtle or or metaphoric then you'd shit in her mouth. I got it
I got it so wait why was he he was looking at that how is it still how is it bouncing over the full screen?
We put the movie in full screen the goddamn Epson update for the printer is still bouncing over it
I can't I we just got to deal with it because if I open that I'm afraid it's gonna fuck this up. Oh God
I hate this look at this guy taking a shit
Who directed this Bruno Kirby?
Tom six very close second week in a row Bruno Kirby red is I love Bruno Kirby, but
We he was looking at a picture of a dog sniffing another dog's ass. Are we to believe that that gave him the idea for this?
No, no, no, those were three dogs connected
He's like, I think he's done this.
He's done this on dogs.
It just looked like a dog sniffing on other dogs' ass to me.
In real life, that's probably all it was.
I would think.
Yeah, but this girl's in it.
And she, by the way, they didn't shoot this thing
in Hollywood, buddy.
This was shot.
Canada or something.
No, I think deep, deep, my bet would be deep in Austria.
Deep in the hills of Austria.
Yeah, yeah.
I, yeah, this is, this has got Eastern Europe
written all over it. Strong acting right off the jump. Folks, what I should have probably
said at the beginning is that you don't have to watch along with these commentary episodes
because Joe and I very often don't talk about what's happening on the screen, but I think
you'll get more out of it if you did. But I think some people, the issue we were having
is people weren't listening in their car. They said, oh, I like to listen at the gym and
And I can't because I, you know, you can't please everybody all the time.
And as we're learning, you can't please anyone any of the time.
Yeah. I agree. I agree. Now I guess they're in Holland.
The one girl just said, we brought so and so a present from Holland.
And I believe that they are possibly talking to a grandmother character in this
scene. I think so. Yeah. Cause there's a little bit of a big bad wolf or
Goldilocks type thing or Hansel and Gretel that they're trying to do.
and yeah, Amy is who they were talking to, whoever distant thunder rumbling rainfall, you know,
close caption, I don't need every sound spelled out. You know, I was watching, I watched
all six of the the stand -ups special and I'm not gonna ask your opinion on things, you know,
we're in the comedy community. I'm sure you have opinions, but look, I thought many of my friends
did them. Yeah, I thought a lot of them were really funny and I'm not saying that because they were
I'm saying that because I'm not asking and don't take our an all lack of commenting as a a vote either way, but I was watching Deon Cole
yes, and
the
Close captioning because I was watching it at the gym said
Audience laughs quietly after one of his jokes and I was like I don't need that judgment call from you
Come on, and neither is Dion Cole. Thank you very much. Just put laughter or don't put it. It's a comedy show. We figure they're laughing
By the way
Does that does a deaf person from birth and even know what laughter? It is or I mean they know what it is by definition
They know what it sounds like so is there a difference between quietly and regularly. It's no laughter. They don't joke
Yeah, that's that's deaf discriminatory as far as I'm concerned. I took a screen grab of it
And there's like, there's a classic Instagram coming your way.
So you can see this in action.
Another classic Walsh Instagram.
I'm like that rapper who goes another one after every hit he produces.
I do it on my Instagram's another one.
Here's the one.
Here's the one I'm thinking to do.
And you know the one of, uh, it's a meme.
You know, the one of Patrick Stewart from Star Trek, the big,
that's a popular picture where he's making that what the fuck
face. Right.
I was going to just put, uh, you're in italics.
You were in the emoji movie come on man. That's good because he's in it. Yeah, a little bit of a movie
I mean it it's I
Get the the red I see when I drive down Sunset Boulevard and see billboards for the emoji movie
I know and every billboard for those of you that don't live in Hollywood
I don't know if you have billboards in your town too your town's probably much brighter than the one we live in so you don't have these but
the the fucking
and it's a goddamn movie about cell phones.
The billboard that's on it was an emoji
and it goes, it goes, meet jailbreak.
So like, it's not just emojis now,
it's also just like every aspect of the cell phone.
So, this is a world we live in.
This is, and by the way, the people that make this movie,
I really need to say this out loud somewhere to some of us.
Please.
The people who make this movie are also many of them.
the people you hear mostly on the internet talking about how they hate Trump supporters in middle
Americans, yet they make the product that is 100 % aimed towards the people they shit on all the
time. It's so fucking hypocritical. It's really annoys me. I'm going to get more upset. I believe it was
written on spec meaning it wasn't like a pitch or wasn't like we got to get an emoji movie going.
It was written as a script that sold for $1 million the emoji would be worth so somebody wrote that
That's right that didn't come out of some dipshits in an office. That's that's exactly right
Joe, can I get you to turn this down a little bit because it's distracting to me
You can even mute it the film turn it down. Yes, please
I'd like to keep a little volume because I remember from the old days. How's that good? I'd go down a little bit more
I have a brain that can't really separate things
Just caught a screen cap as I did as well or quick as well to ask all eating when you know and usually I got to tell you folks
Women eat and ask in a movie would usually just just just just light my day up, but in this film it doesn't work
Yeah, it's weird how much more even in the five -ish
Five -ish Finkel even in the five -ish years since human centipede dropped
It's crazy me how much more envogue ass -eating has become.
It's discussed a lot and it's disgusting a lot.
I mean, I get it, I'm certainly not an anti -fan, but boy, is it really hit the mainstream
in a big way?
Yeah, it's one of my favorite old dice jokes is he goes, he brings up ass -eating to a guy
in the audience.
it's the guy groans. Yeah. And then dice goes, oh, come on, you're not an
ass eater from way back. Like it was like a neighborhood game. Yeah. Then he
goes ass eating an art form. Uh, it's a funny joke. Yeah. All right. Uh, but, uh,
he, for an ass eating bit, it's very funny. Sure. The, uh, here's my story about
human centipede. I go home a few months ago to visit and my mom and I are scrolling
through her like neck Netflix queue. Sure. You know, and it's like, you know,
It's like Brian of Frankenstein, Jesus of Nazareth,
the art of sensual massage, human centipede.
Really?
And I go, I go, why do you have human centipede in there?
She goes, I don't know, if I like horror movies,
it looks, I don't know, I might be pretty good.
I go, do you know what it's about?
And she goes, no, and I go, okay.
And she goes, what?
And I go, no, no, I want you to watch it.
I want you to get back to me on this
and tell me what you thought of it.
Sure.
And finally I cave that I was like, mom, this is what it's about. She was like, okay, I'll be removing that immediately.
I watched this with my old roommate and dear friend Jared and I almost didn't make it. I don't do well with gross out stuff.
But at its core, it's a very classic girls lost in the woods, mad scientist thing, but
What I have heard these days, yeah, what I have heard is that two and then three
quadruple the disgustingness they do but also you know two is about a guy wait I
or three one of them is about if you see an all three no I always saw this one
okay but what at some point in this trilogy they come out of the fictional
storyline of the movie and it becomes about a guy who saw the movie and is
obsessed with it and wants to do it yes and then that's three and then you
Do we bowl right who play that's a thing Tom mix no you we bowl who plays like bad
up here who do care yeah he becomes he's in it just as himself so they do like a West
Craven's new nightmare kind of thing except grow closer right I mean I I think like a there's
like a baby who gets run over by a car and shit I just oh stop it I pledge that I would
not watch two or three and maybe we do it as sort of a challenge for the podcast.
I don't want to see it.
You can't scrub these things from your brain once you see them.
I mean, yeah, it's pretty gross.
It's the feeding scene is pretty gross.
I used to hate it in a teen movie when you'd see someone shit for 50, you know, like, I don't
need to see a shit.
I don't need to, like, I'm trying to watch the new season of Game of Thrones.
there's graphic cuts to shit every 30 seconds and I don't need it.
I do enjoy a good vomit joke in a movie.
In real life when I see vomit, I almost vomit.
But I mean, so what's your limit?
Like, stand by me is certainly gross,
but they made it look just unrealistic enough.
No, I mean, I like a zany vomit joke.
I love in bench rumours.
Oh, sure, that's true.
When John Hader shits in the bathroom and he's like,
sorry for what I did in there and David spade walks out
and pukes like all over the door, also another good David Spade one in that movie with Adam Sandler
where they blow up the boats and shit, uh, the run around or whatever the fuck it's called.
And we watched it together. I believe the the run down. Nothing. That's the rock.
The doover. The doover. Yeah. That one where he has the key in his mouth and Adam Sanders like
that was up the guy's butt and he just turns and spray vomit. That was great. Those kinds of jokes
makes me laugh pretty hard.
Both David Spade, interestingly enough.
Yeah.
Now, Joe, you're lost in the wood that starts raining.
Do you ever just run up to a house?
Would you, I can't imagine doing it
because you're just gonna scare the owner and...
I mean, will their car blew out the tires?
I mean, they're in trouble.
They're, they're, so yeah, in this situation I would,
this girl has decided to take her shoes off for some reason
as she walks through the wilderness.
So this is not Udo Kier.
This is Raven Sunshine.
I've lost all track of everything. I just know I know Raven Simone's in this movie somewhere. What is his name? Dominic
Night time
Dominic
Paglasky
It's a very nice Polish man who runs a plumbing business. I'm gonna look at it. He just looks like Udo Kier. That's why that's why I'm mistaken
No, I think that is his name. I feel like I feel like I never remembered I when I saw Dietrich laser
Dietrich laser that's who this guy must be because what would Udo Kier be if he's not this guy?
guy. No, I think this is Udo Kier, so who the hell's Dietrich laser? That's not Udo Kier.
It's not? No. Well, who's Udo Kier then? Oh, wait, Udo Kier is the guy from, uh, he's
in a bunch of shit. Oh, not that guy. Now I know who you're talking about. He's in, like,
UE Bull type movies. Yeah. No, not that guy. Is that the guy that plays the, is that the
I played the devil and plays the devil in Constantine.
Oh boy.
You know, the nihilist.
The guy that's asleep in the pool in Big Lebowski.
No, that is Peter Stormair from Fargo.
Stormair, yeah.
He also played the guy Slippery Pete
who would get the Frogger machine across the street
in Seinfeld.
Yes, he did.
I love seeing him.
And so we're seeing that actor in a multi -games hit.
I know.
It's very weird.
Yeah, near the end there it'd be like James Spader and different. I was like all right. I'm with it
Yeah, there's an Eric Stoltz. I think pops up in one of those. Yeah, yeah real Indy. I like it. I like it
So what I'm curious now you think this guy could I
Mean he's he's on the he's on the cusp
He's on the cusp
Of of creating if finishing his fulfilling his life's work here. He's got already got a guy in a basement
We already saw that right. He's got two chicks in the house. He's got the three for the centipede
He can't even play it not suspicious long enough. Right. He's already looking like a creep
Can you tone it down? Are we cool? Are we to believe that he arranged this for the girls to show up?
Are they just accidentally showed up at the wrong house? No, I think he I think he put a thing in the street that blew their tires
Oh, okay, that's a good idea then yeah
And then, when does the Asian guy enter the mix?
I remember an Asian guy eating a lot of shit.
Or, no, he's shooting at me.
He's like, I'm sorry.
He's the head of the centipede.
Yeah, which is where you want to be
at a human centipede.
People, that's just to put that feather in your cap
for the future.
It's where you want to be, except, you know,
I always feel overly guilty about things.
And that's something I would not shake well.
Amen, but at least you're not doing both.
You got to survive, baby.
Yeah, you know, so then and I want to touch on this and get immediately off of it
My dick if there's folks if someone's shitting in your mouth aren't you wasn't I thought that was funny wasn't I funny?
I'm gonna touch on this and immediately get off of it. I do
If someone shits in your mouth surely you immediately throw up
So then are you throwing up into the ass and is that included in this movie?
I believe it's insinuated. I don't think no, yeah, no, because you see puke come out the sides. Oh God
I'm not going to be able to even look at this. I think you see that
How fucking sick do you have to be is this guy done anything beyond the human centipede? Hey, you know, I'll tell you something
I'm going to walk away from some of you say this guy's name should be Tom six
Like that one. Yeah, there you go. I like that one
Tom six I think has only done the three correct laying on his couch telling him
I don't like human beings. Oh, because he's already drug them. Yeah. I'm assuming he's already drug them.
I mean, these chicks could make a run for it right now, though. I mean, would it play it cool for a minute, buddy?
He has three movies in development.
Two Dietrich laser. No, Tom sex. What are they?
the
one is called enjoy
and that's about a guy who eats shit and the guy says enjoy one is called Tom six and the insanity
of making another movie. A documentary on Tom Six. And the other is called the Onania Club.
That's about a club where everybody's shit. Yeah, that's probably about it. I'm going
to look up what the Onania Club is about. I'd like to know what it enjoys about. I love
it if he's one of these, I love one of these directors who make like the most appraved shit.
They suddenly in the middle of it all, they have like a romantic comedy. Yeah. And they're
Like it didn't do well.
Why did my romantic comedy not do well?
You're like, cause you're a psycho.
Yeah.
And that comes forward in every frame of this thing.
You can't hide it.
Okay.
The Onania Club is a film that will explore the dark side.
No romantic comedies for me.
How weird is that?
He just said that?
That's his quote.
Again, so you and Tom Six are right on the same page.
Oh, that's good.
Oh boy.
It will be a film that will explore the dark side.
I had no romantic comedy for me said six.
I am now in pre -production of the Onania Club,
a very original, highly perverted black comedy
that will shake up the world yet again.
Can't say to plot yet because it's so simple,
but yet so out there.
It's so original.
Did Donald Trump write this?
I'm sure that South Park is going
to make another parody of it.
It's really crazy.
A very pitch black dark comedy with horrific elements.
It will upset a lot of people again.
in. All right. What's what's enjoy about? I'll look at them. Oh, on Ania is a synonym for
masturbation, by the way. So it could be about masturbation. Well, no, but that probably
just means because you're a masturbatory filmmaker. Oh, wait. Oh, not any a club. That's not the
documentary. Sorry. No. Okay. Jesus God. It's God. God. It's, I don't even want to think
about it right now. No. No. I should say. Oh, he also says that the negative, all the
negative reviews of his films only make his cock harder. It's a quote from him as well.
Wait, what did he say? Negative reviews of his film only make his cock harder. There you
go. It's alright. So, so if you're, if you aren't watching along and you want to know where
we are in the film right now, the girls have been drugged. They're about to pass out.
And one girl's desperately trying to make an escape but it's not happening as we all know did they drink the water he presented them with?
Yeah, this is kind of on them. Yeah, he gave them water and pretended to make a phone call. Yeah.
So I guess the idea here is even if they had run for it, they would have collapsed in the woods and he'd still get them.
Okay, but at least they wouldn't be in the damn house. I mean, right, you know,
this one's getting a needle. I guess because she's not taken to the
sedative
Well, he gave her roofies. He said it. He's this isn't one of those bad guys like to tell you everything you just did
Real real self -indulgent guy. Now, what do you think this guy's like in real life?
You know, I don't think he's that far removed from this character
You don't look like that and be normal
There's a guy on my gym who looks exactly like this guy except with like a Rodney Bingen hammer black Poodle
To pay hair who's Rodney Bingen hammer? He hosts the
Local like K Rock show they try to fire him out. You know, he's got like a Poodle haircut
Wait the guy like Rodney on the sunset. Yeah, yeah, can we talk about that guy's creepy level face but with a
Um, a two -pay designed, like he said, give me the Bingenheimer.
This guy for breakfast, because it's a breakfast scene right now, eats a giant can of Del
Monte fruit cocktail, which you find very interesting.
That's his breakfast in the morning.
Yeah.
He doesn't have to eat shit.
He eats the good stuff.
The, uh, that Rodney on the sunset strip thing where everybody's like, this is a crime that
you're firing.
and it's like, I get it, he broke some cool bands and everything.
But at the end of the day, guys, can we stop acting like this isn't just a glorified
groupie dude?
Yeah.
Like he's just like, one of these sunset strip people that just like hangs around.
And he's like, I knew the guy that knew the guy when Kim Deil joined the pixie or what
it, you know, it's like, well, interestingly enough, Joe, the only person I saw saying it was
a crime to fire this guy is something of a groupie himself.
Who's it? Well, I'm obviously not going to say the person's name on here. Oh
Why know who you mean
But anyway, I wish him well
But it's like if you're a 70 year old man
You're not going to be playing on the local new hot music channel
And that and that makes sense. Also, that's not ageism. That makes sense
Be speed 70 and love music, but at some point you have to stop trying to rock
Yeah, it's like just it gets sad after a while. Yeah, that's like how that guy who's the guy that didn't that made the runaways
Kim that creepy fucking guy. Oh, yeah, yeah, he was one of those dudes where it's like he was like 68
He's still like I want a rock baby. Yeah, like just just hang it up dude. Right go listen to rock music enjoy it
Dress cool if you want. Yeah, stop well strutting. It's just weird. I'm at
One James Eha today from smashing pumpkins. Yeah, he was one of the candidates to do the score for the my my show
Very nice guy. I didn't really know what to say. I mean, I always liked the smashing pumpkins
I don't know I at least Corrigan always referred to them as his backing band who played exactly what he told him to play
So I didn't know if it was a touchy subject or not
But he was a guy who
very nice but like could not make eye contact and very quiet. It almost felt like it was from
years of abuse at the hands of Billy Corrigan. But maybe not. And he's he couldn't have been nicer.
A lot of people, you know, are quiet. You think he has ever going back in the band? You think
what? Do you think he has ever going back in the band? I think Corrigan calls says, hey, they're
offering us 12 million to play. Yeah, he's going to go. Well, Corrigan tours with the drummer all the
time, under -spashing pumpkins. He just doesn't use, I didn't know his name till you just said it,
and the girl with the bleached hair was her name. Pass was not that pass. She was in pusifer.
Yeah, perfect circle. And perfect circle. Yeah. Is there's no way we can mute this? Why don't we mute
this? Because I, whereas you have a problem with sound, I have a problem with no sound. I'll get
completely lost even with subtitles yeah I like to have a little sound are you
that distracted listening to to beautiful women tortured and screaming while I'm
trying to talk about James eha it's a little much for me it's look at look at me
you all right can I lower it yes I was looking directly at you because I didn't
want to see what was happening when we moved over to all subtitles I remember
having a very hard time all right like staying in the moment and I was like really
drifting and stuff. Hold on a second. Where is it? Oh, it's over here. Hold on a second.
Oh boy. This is your house, Joe. I forgot. Let's try it there, all right? And if it's still
bothers you, we'll go even lower, all right? Because I'm an accommodating guy. When we get into them,
going like, I don't want to hear shit gurgling sounds while I'm trying to remember in a music
a panic note about being on the bus.
I've got to be honest with you.
I want to hear you hearing shit gurgling sounds.
I mean, I feel like that's part of the joy in this.
I'm really, I'm already just very disturbed
by the whole thing.
I don't like it.
I don't know why.
I don't know how I watch this the first time.
First sequence.
Here comes the, here comes the Asian kid,
Dart and his ass.
Cause I think this first guy dies somehow.
Machinery hissing and beeping.
Again, there's a few things.
I don't know if he would be to die.
Like, okay, so serious question.
they give you the option. This scientist gives you the option. One week in the
centipede or he puts a bullet in your head right now, what do you do? What
happens after the week in the centipede? You're set free and as long as you
didn't somehow die from eating shit, then you're alive. Week in the centipede. I
would ple - I would grab the gun from his hand on my brand's own. I take a week in
centipede. I take two weeks at the head of the centipede one week in the middle. I mean,
okay, let me ask you this. Let's get, I'm sorry for this question.
It's you, your mom and your dad and this guy's base would you stop it? Do you take the bullet and
get in the back of the centipede? Are you so selfish? And I take the bullet at that point.
Oh, my mom and my dad, you think you're gonna say like it's you and like, you know,
Yeah, you know, Dom Deleweez or something, you know, what are you taking the bullet leaving them to centipede it up?
That's their fucking problem at this point. I mean, I you know, I can't do everything here. Right. So let me ask you this
It's you and two close friends. Are you like selfishly clamoring to be the front of the centipede or you like
You know what? You're my friend. I love you a female friend. Let's say I'll I'll take the hit
Or are you saying like you know what you're my dear sweet female friend. I'm a gentleman you get up top
I'm gonna sit in the back in front of her
That's what I would say and as soon as she was out of the room I'd say she really wants for some reason to be in the middle or the bag
She's requesting it like the door clicks and like listen this girl loves eating shit
Yeah, because you're still thinking maybe after the centipede week is over you guys have a chance of
Yeah, so you're being nice to her curb your enthusiasm music starts playing and yeah, yeah, that's how I would play it
Oh, he's fully explaining to them what's going to happen. He did it with the route wallers now it's gonna be for them called it a three -hound
Construction, I will say there's something beautiful about the line three -hound construct. Yes, they were a big band back in the 70s
Yeah, they were real big on the, I despise this guy's scream and South Park parody that really well. But boy, he has a terrible scream.
Like because it's annoying or because it's upsetting all of the above all of the above.
I don't like people screaming and I'll be quiet.
that. I think both of these actors, the two females, came back and also played themselves
in the sequel. I won't watch it. I mean, just now thinking about what I'm about to watch
again, I just shivered. I don't know if you caught that, but I shivered. Look, I owe you
one on this. Look at this graphic. Look at that. I like that he puts the little dotted line
around the butthole.
Joe and I were just talking, we were walking into the building and I commented on how much
I hate seeing the assholes of dogs and cats.
I was looking at Joe's dogs' assholes at the time.
And my cat is so adorable and then you'll just see like this mutant asshole sticking out.
And it's really gross.
I think they should cover it with fur.
My dog's asshole is pretty, it's pretty well contained except for when he's about to
shit.
And then it turns into sort of like all right like the eye of siren on mount doom all right all right
I don't like this stuff
I don't like it
Three -hound
Who was your three -hound construction three -hound construction?
Oh, this kind of speak English
knowledge. No, so he doesn't even know what's going on. The Asian guy doesn't even know
what the hell is going on. He's just seeing pictures that are suggesting some things. He doesn't,
but he doesn't know, but he's lucky. He's at the head of the stamp thing. Yeah. He's at the
head of it. That's where you want to be. Asyamie's triplet connected by the digestive system.
Oh, he's gagging. Okay. Here's the next to the excretion of C. But what does he feed A? I
I forget in the South Park, it was cuddle fish.
But the guy in the front gets to eat normal food.
You wanna be, that's great.
You're in front, you live, you're fucking,
you're moving on from the front.
But you gotta live with what you've done.
You haven't done anything.
You've not requesting to do this.
That's true.
I mean, you know, just,
I guess only in the horror world where you're just trying to up the ante and over extreme
everything.
Does this pitch go over at all?
But I mean, this director has parents, I assume.
Like how do you, face, I guess, you know, pours the same way, but I'd rather say, look, I did
a porno than say, I mean, the movie, here's the thing, let's get into a deeper thing here
with this film.
Yeah, you know, the movie's at best fine.
It's terrible.
At worst, terrible.
My point is, you wouldn't, aside from the content, you wouldn't watch this film go.
This is a well -made movie.
It's a good movie.
This guy really fancies himself out to her.
Yeah.
He really thinks he's like a, what's his face, that God, man, I can't remember anything anymore.
I did Annie Christ and Lars von Trier here. Yeah, here are things. She's like a Lars von Trier
like like would you provoke a two or would they make you think he's shocking?
But it is beautiful. Right. What happened? What happened? What I missed?
What happened? She just tried to run in the needle ripped up the length of her arm and it was really disgusting.
So you know it uh -oh
Look at this. The doors are gone. How are the doors? No, the doors aren't gone. There's a door. There's the front doors. The door is the front door.
or jumped out a window, got damn it, or kill yourself.
That's what I would do.
Throw something through a window, go,
don't listen at the door, get moving here.
Now, Joe, what do you have to say about the star
of the emoji movie, TJ Miller's claims that women
are not as funny as men?
What do you think about that?
We discussed this on emotional hangs,
my other podcast, the other day,
I occurred myself to discuss this and.
My, I did not read the thing.
So my first question was, did he say a thing
where it wasn't that bad and then they took a quote out
of it and it sounded bad and then Kerr was like,
no, no, he kind of said like it was like pretty bad.
And then he like paraphrase what he said.
And then we were laughing because I was like,
it almost sounds like he was trying
to be complimentary, but then he's so crazy.
It came out as a horrible insult, but I mean,
I've kind of started saying like I'm the Lindsay Lohan. I'm the I'm the bad boy shaking stuff up by saying provocative shit. I can't tell if
No, I can't tell if he means it if he's just being a dick, if he's I don't know TJ's nuts. So I don't know. Yeah, I've never had a
Proud with TJ. I don't agree with his statements. Right. I am getting a little annoyed with him in every interview saying
Something fiery that we're all supposed to react to when you're starring in the emoji emoji movie. That's right.
You ruined my pause. No, I'm sorry. Can I do it again? Sure being the bad boy when you start emoji movie
Folks
You see how this relationship goes
Oh God I
Yeah, it's a little fake blood. Well, I don't even into the shitty. I watched it get ripped out of her
I mean, I I got to be in the mood for this kind of shit. I don't who's in the ever in the mood for this kind of shit
Well, it's ironic that I even do a horror movie podcast because I don't really like horror movies, but
Now she picks up the lamp
Yeah, why don't you do that 20 minutes ago instead of sitting in there waiting? Oh, he's gonna break his own
Why is he breaking his own window? You don't have a key
Guys, what are we doing here?
Joe, what do you think about Donald Trump's ban of transgenders from the US military?
Yeah, I think that's pretty cool or I would say it's not cool. That's not cool. Can I tell you?
I have I feel like he's doing I also feel like he's doing it as like a fuck you
Everything he does as a fuck like I feel like he's got his panties in a bunch over the over the healthcare bill thing
And now he's gonna be like, okay, well then I'll do this then
You just be in an ass what it is of course. It's what it is
I
I actually was friends in high school with a girl named Becky, who is now named Blake.
And I would definitely not bring this up if she hadn't been on CNN, so today I talk
about it.
It was very cool to see.
That's cool.
She is on Facebook and etc.
She's a very active part of our military risks her life day in and day out.
I would rather do almost anything than be in the military.
I don't think that makes me a coward.
It just makes me a guy who doesn't give a shit about our country anymore.
Right. Right. But I just wouldn't be good in a combat setting.
What why would we stop anyone? It's the same thing as as the military, but why are we just and if there's not bigger issues going on?
I
Political pockets will get right off of it. It's it's listen. I'll say this much. If you were and I have no
Information to back any of this up. Yeah, but if you said to me by the way, that claim can go with anything we've ever said
If you were saying to me, hey, if you're in the middle of transitioning, X, Y, and Z can happen,
which could require A, B, and C. Therefore, those costs are too much. Therefore, you have to
fully transition before you come in. Then I'd be like, okay, I get, I don't know. Maybe that makes
sense. Maybe that's valid. I don't know if it is right. But to say, no, transgender costs too much.
What medical cost? Like, what medical costs does Caitlyn Jenner have that are so much more expensive?
It's not his reason. He's doing it out of spite. And the military gave that as his reason.
The military is not paying for gender reassignment surgeries. There's no way that's happening.
That's what I'm saying. There's no way. I don't get what the medical thing is.
It's a fake thing, so he doesn't look like a complete monster to the left. But deep down,
what he's doing is his racist speech, his hate speech, his homophobic speech,
is making half of this country or more say, this is what I've been thinking my whole life,
but now the president says it. So I guess I'm right. And he's ruining the country
from the inside out and it wasn't that great to begin with it wasn't and I and I but I also fear
that it's that this is yet another hard curve ball to get everybody screaming and angry as he
goes off and does another terrible thing when we're not looking of course and then I saw both sides
and not that this isn't a terrible thing but you know what I'm saying I do I was on Twitter today
for a split second and it was like opening the book of the dead where there's like screams and
horrific shit, and I slammed it shut, I saw both sides, people were saying this is obviously
distraction, and then we'll trans people don't consider ourselves distractions, etc.
You're both valid folks, we're all angry, we're all on the same side.
If you're angry at Donald Trump, let's just be on the same fucking side, because it's going
to come to us, you know, being cut off from the country and pushed off to our own community,
and I welcome it frankly.
And I'll tell you, when that happens and you got to rely on your neighbors, and all that, right or left, I'm going to be in the community for whites only, and I just want to put that out there right now.
I didn't see it going there.
I'm kidding, of course, before somebody takes that out of context.
I watched and I'd like to recommend a fantastic documentary.
I saw it on ABC on a Friday night and I'm sure it's on ABC on demand or something,
but it's called Los Angeles 1982 to 1992 and it's about what led to the LA riots
and the last hours about the LA riots.
I knew too little about it and I'm glad I watched it and I cried at several points in it
And one was this woman who like you met her today look you'd go this is a lesbian and she makes jokes about it
She's like obviously now. I don't have to tell people I'm a lesbian. They get it by my hair
You know, she said at the time her and her partner were out on the streets
And he was like they're like cocking shotguns getting ready to go into like certain death and he's like look
I don't think I'm gonna make it out of this. I just have a bad feeling. Please tell my wife that I love her and tell my kids
She's a lover. She's like, God it. Then she tells the story about how they start to walk in and she's like, I'd had a
Girlfriend for seven years, but was not allowed to in the force discuss my sexuality. So I just always act like I was single
So and she said my you know pardon was a bit of a jock whatever and she grabs his arm not knowing how he would respond and just said
Look, I'm gay like came. They're getting ready to go into like certain deaths. She comes out to him in 1992
like, look, I'm gay, whatever you think of it,
here's my girlfriend's name, would you please tell her
that I love her very much, whatever.
The guy's like, absolutely, I love you.
Thank you for telling me.
It was like a beautiful, you know,
you don't post this stuff, just telling the story,
but I was gonna get it the other way
and I was gonna, I was getting upset.
Yeah, no, but I mean there are a million stories like this
and he make it, she made it, did he make it?
He, I don't think did make it, but she didn't.
But there are, there are all these stories in there,
all you see is like the guy getting hit in the face
with the brick by looters a thousand times or Rodney King getting beaten a thousand times.
So a ton of great stories from that that were like mind -blowing to me.
There's also footage of like Korean store owners walking into traffic firing handguns,
just like stay away from my store, like shooting into traffic.
Wow. It was a fantastic documentary and nobody mentioned it.
Wow, that sounds weird. I'd like to see that.
I like to if I could it's definitely on hula why I guarantee if I could divert our attention back to the film. Yes, please
Now the girl that tried to make the escape for it. Yeah went into the room
Bruno Kirby started hitting the glass with the car with the gun to break his own window basically
She's not gonna escape. We all know that. Yeah, she ends up in the pool room
She was down in the pool, he comes in with a gun, he announces to her, you are the middle
piece.
Okay.
She says, just kill me now.
He says, I'm not, I'm not going to kill you.
You're going to be the middle.
You're in my middle piece.
Right.
She's in a perfect position to write then, get out of the pool and say, let's talk.
My parents have a lot of money.
Uh -huh.
You put me at the head of this thing.
baby, you're going to be making centipedes for the rest of your life.
Why would she not negotiate?
I think we're giving what it would amount to network notes on the human centipede, but
I think she probably recognizes this guy as somebody who's not open to such negotiations.
He's financially well off.
He's also designed a you know a system where he's going to sew three people together by their lips and assholes
He's probably not open to a discussion lips and assholes famous line from a John Candy movie. Can you name it?
Lips and assholes is from the great outdoors. Yep. Yes, who says it hot about hot dogs? It is said by
Dan Acroid about hot dogs and then who says it's sick the second time?
There's a callback
All right, I don't remember the raccoon rating the guard. Oh, yeah, I forgot that they
were subtitled. That's a great a netbending performance in the great outdoors. Yeah, I
want to check. I always liked at the end when a like the climax of the big fight. Yeah,
when John Candy's wife goes to a netbending, she goes, why don't you go find yourself a washing
first cycle? Yeah. Yeah. That's it. Do you know that they are remaking it with Mr. Kevin
heart, the great outdoors. Ah, no. I did not know that. I don't think that's necessary.
No, but I'll, I'll check her out. I'm not saying I won't, but, uh, well, I am saying
I won't. I ain't nothing against Kevin. I just don't want to see that. Now, Joe, what
do you think? The first one's a great, like a great movie in the sense of like, this needs
to be remade. It's tied to my childhood and I laughed a lot when I watched as a kid. You
watch it now. It's like shooting the bear's ass off as funny. There's also a fourth of
The movie is a horrifically boring teen romance.
Yeah, the pool stick going up or skirt by accident,
which I found arousing, but yes.
You know, because you want a pool stick between your,
yeah, in the Gucci, the old Gucci.
So now he's gonna start the operation.
Look, it's a well -structured film.
Yeah, all the act breaks are hitting at the right spots.
Well, I mean, Christ, you go by a goddamn,
what's he doing with his knee?
the knee. How does the knee factor into a human's outfit? Wait a minute. Maybe that's maybe
that's the bad part about being in the front. Maybe he cuts your you off at the knees. Maybe he
cuts your bottoms of your legs off. We should have paid a little closer attention to him explaining it.
Well, Mr. I want to turn down the volume and talk about. No, I'm glad I did. I'm not that I talk
about Trump because I'm angry but here we are. Should we head into a path movie corner?
Sure. I'm just doing anything to keep from watching this movie.
Snaps, tooth snaps, heighter breathes heavily.
You don't need the heighter breathes heavily.
No, we're watching with subtitles folks.
Yeah, because I have seen one or two things since we last convened.
I had it seen them, but we were out of time and I'd like to share.
Go ahead, Joe.
Oh, you can go first, it's your segment.
Alright
Well, I'll start with baby driver
Because this is the movie of the baby limousine driver Alec Baldwin voices the baby correct boss baby driver. Yes
Now we're just cutting into an ass. Just look at me and talk. Just don't look at it. All right
So yeah, baby driver I'm looking at it. I wasn't at it again. I can't help it. I was excited to see it. I
I feel like Edgar Wright and I would be friends and we have mutual friends, but I love spaced.
You and Simon Birch are very close, correct?
Simon Pegg?
Simon Birch.
Or Simon Birch is the fictional dwarf who died.
The kid who played Simon Birch is dead, but I love that movie.
I love Simon Birch.
He dies in the movie, doesn't he?
Yeah.
He died in real life.
That's it.
Sorry.
What?
Wait.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
It won't be in the final thing.
We just recorded past the outro. It's fine. Just keep talking. You sure this is okay
I don't want to talk now for an hour and then it's not on the final cut. No, this is fine
We just spoke past the the outro thing. Okay, if you guys at home just heard a thing that just went that was a head gum podcast
It's that was an accident, but I don't think they heard that at home
I'm sure head gum doesn't mind another shout out. Yeah, see we're still recording
We're all good, we're all good, we're all good, we're all good, all right.
Yes.
Okay, so baby driver, I'm going to walk you through Edgar Wright.
I thought space was an awesome show, no office, no British office, but a great British sitcom.
I thought that Sean of the Dead is a fucking fantastic movie, his best work in my opinion.
My favorite with a slight edge is Hot Fuzz.
I just really loved that really
But then when you get into Scott Pilgrim
I thought you had a amazing first hour that collapsed. Did you know the original ending in that movie?
They don't get together and when they tested it the audiences are like
What did he go through all that right and they were like okay? I guess they'll get together then I didn't know that now
But I do know from writing a couple of movies. They never like it when the couple doesn't get together
He looks like Christopher walkin' in the weapon of choice video here.
It's like the same shot.
Is that the daddy long stroke?
That boy's that boy's.
Daddy long stroke.
That's my name.
Thank you.
It's gone, dude.
It's all gone.
Whatever info I had up there is gone.
Daddy long stroke.
It's not a bad name.
Anyway, I'm just telling you, I have the world's end, I thought was a bad movie.
And I like them just like hanging out in pubs drinking, but by the end I was like,
what? You know, he has a little bit of a problem sticking the landing for me. He is a visually
fantastic director. He's good at, you know, of course, using music and pop -up.
Can I say my favorite world's end part really quick? Sure. The part, the entire first hour
of the movie, I was like, please, because Nick Frost's character is sober and he's really square.
Yeah. And the whole time, like, please get to a point where Nick Frost has to drink.
Sure, and then when that finally hits and not only does he drink he does every shot on the tray
Yeah, and he's as he's doing them. He just goes
Yeah, yeah, I was I was howling laughing in the movie theater
Maybe I should watch it again. I mean, I feel like I like that movie, but it's it's it's it's it's not it's got problems
It's a weird thing. Yeah, I mean, I just feel like
the movies are unlike anything else and
And I admire that and I admire a lot about them, but they got problems and more as they go now baby driver folks
We have one of the least defined female characters of the past 20 years especially in terms of
How much everybody is monitoring this stuff and how a female shouldn't be like show up literally in this movie
She pours him a cup of coffee
He falls in love with her and is willing to do anything risk his life
His livelihood for her because she's a pretty girl who says hello to him
And they never develop her in any way beyond that and to see people shit on your Lala land or whatever it is
But not shit on baby driver for that is strange to me because I
Know they like Edgar Wright, but he should be held to the same standard. No, I agree
It's a shittily written female character and the other female in it is your standard Michelle Rodriguez tough girl who has nothing to do either
I agree John Hammond Jamie Foxx are bad in the movie. They're bad in it and the last hour of the movie goes wildly off the rail
Jamie Foxx has been off his shit for a little while now like he's off his
Movie's he's been me. I'm like he's off his game
The last one I think I saw was spider -man and it was I was what are you that we saw that with you?
And that is the worst performance of recent years I think
Yeah, by the way, folks, for those of you that are nerd like doing a clumps style portrayal
of a nerd.
Yeah.
It was literally a nutty professor level keeping his tree trunk sized muscles, right.
But he's a nerd for those of you at home.
The human centipede is up and walking and has been constructed.
Yeah.
Let's take it.
And here's what I'd like to point out.
This movie obviously is pretend it's a movie.
But when they shot it at the end of the day, that chick's got to put her face in an Asian
guys asshole. Yeah. I mean, that's all there is to it. There's no way around that. So now let's talk logistics.
Does anyone say to him, you got to really clean out that ass or does he just know?
I would think he knows and I would think there would be some discussions about it.
You would think there would be a crash. This is delicate, but realize here's how we're doing this.
Yeah. I mean, Jesus Christ, that's that ass eating scene in girls where, uh, yes.
Yes.
I forget who the dude was, but he's going after Alison, what's your name, Alison Williams?
Williams is, I mean, he's daughter of noted liar, but I don't like that.
He's face is in her fucking asshole.
Yeah.
I mean, that's it.
Like, and it's, I mean, unless they fucking paint it out like underwear, which I guess
they could do, like, they, they might have to be honest with him.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm ready for another cocktail here.
I mean, you're really nursing that thing over there.
I am because I'm just kind of traumatized by the film, frankly.
Pat also smokes a little reef, which I don't think is something I need to keep secret
from all of you.
I don't think you need to tell them either, but...
I like to put it out there.
Just because as I enter my second drink while you're still in your first, I just like to
point out that you also smoked weed.
Well, then I don't feel like an hour long.
So they don't even need to know we were drinking.
Well, I'm gonna need to walk and make another drink.
I think we've talked about this.
You don't have to mention it, but when Joe and I do this, we have a drink.
It loosens up the conversational muscles.
I mean, let's be honest, we have more than one usually.
Yeah.
And usually the podcast are 45 minutes.
That's true.
I'm going to put my mic down.
Talk to these people about another movie you see.
I will.
And then I'll come back and I have two.
Yes.
But I will say the use of music and baby driver, I saw it on a theater with a shitty sound
system.
in the Los Feliz 3, which is my home theater.
I can't go there anymore.
They're fucking out the sound.
I know that's a pretty Los Angeles specific tweet.
I just said something.
I'm calling what I say now a tweet.
But, you know, it needs to be heard,
I guess, with a good sound system,
but the songs are kind of cool,
but there's also a bunch of songs where I'm like,
you're making a movie with 45 songs, almost a musical.
I don't I didn't find myself dying to get the soundtrack when I left like you see a Tarantino movie
You want to get that soundtrack? I don't know there's there's there's parts about the movie that were kind of fun
But I just thought it was a huge lead down
I don't get the love for it is what I'm saying
The other one I saw that I briefly alluded to in the last podcast was the big sick
Written by our good friends Camelna Gianni and Emily Gordon. I love them both
but even if I didn't, nobody is over praising this movie.
It's very timely.
And at the end of the day, it's a romantic comedy.
I think you could watch with your family.
And it raises some interesting questions very subtly.
It's like political without ever actually being political.
And I thought that was very cool.
I just loved everybody in it.
Holly Hunters, my favorite actress.
She's fucking killer in it.
Romano's killer in it.
But Camel's killer in it.
Camel's great in it.
It's a really effective romantic comedy, and I haven't heard anybody dislike it, so
go see it.
Our friend, Kurt Branneler, who Joe does his other podcast with, is a great sidekick in
it.
It's just a good film.
Now, Joe, you want to take over with a movie you've seen while I watch a man eat dog food that he will soon be digesting shit.
Oh, he makes me dog food appears that way.
So I guess you don't get to eat regular food when you're at the head of the set -up.
But still, I'll take Alpo over shit.
Well, oh god, this movie, why would you do it?
That's not dog food. It looks like it's some sort of steak.
I'm glad they didn't go to the place of like making him eat a fucking burrito or something, you know, like they had some limits.
Let me tell you something. We haven't seen parts two and three. Yeah, that's true.
The doctor evil doctors called the agent man a kamikaze shithole. Yeah, yeah, which is not nice. You know, I don't know where he's getting that from.
I believe that is dog food or it's raw meat raw meat. Yeah, I mean, I don't know the doctors eating that's the sake of the plate that is for the doctor's dinner. Oh, okay, I thought it was for him.
Or is it not look how raw it is. That actually makes me hungry.
That's sick. Oh, yeah, I love. I've never been less hungry in my entire life. I love red. The steak makes me hungry people. Not the not the
uh not the uh shitting. I gotta tell you folks you need to lose uh 20 pounds. Keep this movie on
in your house. This is the shit scene. So if you want to divert your attention to me,
uh I can I can uh you know save you from this. Yeah. What have you seen, Joe? I got one more
biggie here in a moment. I saw some old classics. Okay. Well the first was a rewatch but I just hadn't
I haven't seen it since I was a kid, and I own it on DVD,
but I watched Salem's Lot again.
I enjoyed it very much.
I haven't seen it.
I've owned it for years and never watched it.
Not out of disinterest.
I just, you know, I have a shitload of movies
and I saw that one when I was very young
and well, I borrowed it from you and watched it.
Probably should have done it on the fucking podcast.
That's fine.
It's a little long, but I had never seen it.
But I enjoyed it very much.
I think if you haven't seen the original Salem's Lot,
it was directed by Toby Hooper, Toby.
be. By the way, Hooper, it was made for television as a mini series. It was eventually
recut and shown in theaters. And it was the only television, as far as I know, was it shown
in theaters? Eventually. I was recut. And it was also, I think possibly the only television
movie, I'm sorry, the subtitles just said in parentheses, feces squirting.
What a terrible movie. Go ahead, Joe. The human centipede that was in a cage and everybody's crying.
Yeah, there's a movie I like to put this on every Christmas with the family. We watch this and
you know, and then we'll put on nine and a half weeks right after.
Anyway, so I was the only one of the only TV movies I've ever heard of being recut and then aired and showed on theaters and then also I believe the only TV movie ever to have a sequel that was made for theaters.
So yeah, return to cells.
Yeah, yeah. So it's a pretty, that's pretty impressive and it's a pretty stunning film.
Scariest vampires ever seen in anything like the child vampires are fucking terrifying and then the master vampire. I think his name is
I was gonna say Barnabas, but it's something along. I know that's the dark shadows guy. Yeah, anyway
It's a great flick. It's a slow burn. The DVD has 42 chapters
So it's long but but I found it terribly enjoyable. James Mason is great in it. Yes
So I'd say check it out if you haven't seen it or haven't seen it in a while the other classic
I finally saw from start to finish was puppet master never seen any of them. I got the first
nine puppet master movies in a collection and one collection from a Walmart for four dollars brand new
Now what brought you to Walmart by the way? I was with my dad and we went into a Walmart while
I'll allow it. Walmart has terrible business practices.
I was with my dad and we had to get some stuff for my dog
and we drove by, and I also needed to get some medicine for me.
So we saw Walmart, I said, let's just pull over here,
we'll get everything we need in one space
because my parents where they live, man,
it is 25 minutes between every stop.
So if you got to run multiple errands,
that's that's your whole day.
It's kind of sucks.
So anyway, we went in there and $4 for the Puppet Master Collection, the first nine films,
there were four more after that. I have a feeling around eight, it's going to start to
teet her off a little bit. The quality might start to slip. But I watched
the first one and I liked it. It's kind of what you'd expect if you haven't seen it.
It's a full moon features movie. It's low budget considering. I think the budget was about
400 ,000 for it. But it's fun. Is your intent to watch all eight? Oh, yeah. Yeah. But I mean, I
got to tell you if the first one is the masterpiece. Yeah. But but I've read best of lists on like
bloody disgusting and stuff where the first one is never the first one is never number one on the list.
So I feel like maybe they get better. It's interesting. The puppets look really cool. The stop motion
animation is very cool okay William Hickey plays the puppet master at the
top of the film small role but I always love seeing him you know the the
ancient guy from Christmas vacation ancient guy you know you know all he was
when he died take well guess 80 69 oh wow boy he did not look good 69 this
This movie, Puppet Master was made in like 1989 or something like that.
He died in 1993.
He looks exactly the same, like maybe earlier in the 80s.
Oh, no.
What?
Oh no, oh no.
Oh.
What's he doing?
He's popping pus out of her facial scars, Joe.
Well, Puss wouldn't look like that.
So just remember that.
He also just fed other ones a laxative.
Oh, he did?
All right.
So that is my they might as well just on the burrito gag at that point, right?
Oh God, this is disgusting.
Yeah, it's terrible.
William Hickey, if you watch your in Pritzese's honor, which I think was made in 1985,
so he's barely 60 in that one.
He looks worse in that than he does in Christmas vacations.
So he died of infosema. I think it was a very heavy smoker.
Yeah, clearly.
But my favorite William Hickey world couldn't hear a dump truck.
driving through a nitroglycerin plant.
The blessing.
Yeah, he's very funny.
My favorite, uh, uh, and our dear friend, James Pinkstone,
would, would, I believe agree with me.
My favorite William Hickey role is in Tales of the Darks
of the movie.
Sure.
And we watched it on the show in the cat from hell,
where it's just him in a wheelchair
as like a crazy old man wheeling around going,
the cat is evil.
Yeah.
It must be killed.
He's really great.
that. So anyway, so those were the two that I, I mean, we've only, you're getting this a week
later, but we recorded this two days after we did the last episode. So I didn't have really
a ton of time to watch stuff, but I did check those out. I enjoyed them. My showtime subscription ran
out, so I didn't have any time watching more twin peak steps and I'm behind three or so. I'm all
caught up. I mean, I'm still enjoying it. We can get into it another time. I saw last night
done Kirk, Christopher Nolan, and she did it.
How was it?
Well, I admire that Christopher Nolan finally learned how to make a movie that's under
two hours long.
Yes.
I, I really like the movies of Christopher Nolan for the most part.
I think he's a very fine director.
And I mean, very fine.
Like, good.
Not very average.
Um, he meant, uh, hot like he's attractive.
Yeah.
He's very fun.
That's how Pat describes an attractive person.
She says, that is fine.
Mopping my brow.
Dunkirk is, it's a movie that every shot is just
fucking perfect.
Like it technically, it is a beautifully shot movie
with awesome like aerial action, sea action.
But basically the air portion,
and I don't know how the idiots of America followed
this because I sure couldn't. The aerial portion takes place over one hour, the water portion takes
place over one day, and the land portion takes place over one week. So they tell you that very
briefly at the beginning, like it'll just say, air one hour. But I mean, they keep cross -cutting
between these three things. That's a really hard concept to grasp. So a lot of the movie you're kind
of doing the mental work of like where on the timeline it is.
And actually the three intertwined and then you got it.
But it's a little tricky.
I admired it from a narrative standpoint.
And as I said, it looks fantastic.
You know, there's a butt coming.
The butt is the butt into another man's mouth.
That's right.
Like a centipede.
SPV Herman says there's always a big butt.
He does nothing to make you give a shit
about anyone in this movie.
There is zero character development
Everyone's just kind of a faceless soldier and
Ultimately you wind up even though everything happening on screen is very exciting board. I mean, there's there's under water
There's like scenes where like you know much like the abyss, you know like he's in he is ejector thing doesn't go off
And he's sitting there in the plane and you see the water rising, you know
And he's basically trying to keep his head above water and it should be really exciting
But you don't know or care about this person at all. I found that that was that was my problem with
When I saw saving private Ryan in the theater. I thought it was pretty well done
Okay, and I thought the carnage and the depiction of war was was fascinating
Right, but at the end of the day, I didn't feel particularly attached to any of the characters when people died it whereas
See I that one at least gave you that that thing of Damon and
and they're trying to relay the message and all that.
I got all that, but it didn't mean
that I found the characters more developed or whatever.
But I think the most fast, in my opinion,
the most interesting and attached
I've ever been to a character ever in a war movie
is pile in Full Metal Jacket.
Yes.
It's an enough for you.
Because they take the entire first act of a movie
making you give a shit about this one fucking guy.
I can't hear about him more than Matthew Modine.
Matthew Modine's the goddamn star of the movie.
Yes, that's right.
So, you know, I'd like to see a little more
of the smallness of war, if you will.
Yeah, I mean, clearly, Christopher Nolan
was probably like, I want to make a movie that's two hours
and that first half hour getting to know everybody
would have pushed it to the standard 230
that movies are nowadays.
but I think it really suffered because of it.
You just kind of, you're not really into it.
You're not following the story like you should
because you're just kind of like,
it's just like watching a beautiful documentary or something.
That's what I didn't care about.
Edger tomorrow, like, before the time cruise one?
Yeah, I didn't know.
I thought it was fucking great.
The little you get to know about Tom Cruise
before he's in the war or in the battle,
from his battle, is that you don't like him that much.
And he's dropped in and immediately it's like I don't care. Yeah, I'm not attached to this
And they talk about Emily Blunt and you're like okay, so they've talked about this character
I don't know who she is like I don't fear her
I'm not part of this alien invasion thing that's happening like I think part of why that movie works for me is
I thought it was incredibly well -written and your dog is pulling this out and it may be affecting our sound
Conte stop because it's staddicking out in my ear. What was you want to re -push it?
The headphone was? Yeah
Yeah, sure be fine. All right. It was probably just spitting Tom Cruise brings a whole thing with him
You know Tom Cruise. You know he's the hero
In this movie, it's Tom Hardy who you never know anything about despite me having seen him in 20 movies
He's always kind of an enigma and he has a face mask over him the entire time like Bane
Like Bane.
What's the mask for?
He's a pilot.
So you talk like Bane in it,
and then like Harry Styles from One Direction.
And you kind of just don't know anything about anybody.
And then the actor who I find very boring
from Bridge of Spies, the guy who was the BFG,
the big fucking giant.
Yeah, that big fucking giant.
Why would they name a kid's movie that?
I don't know the terrible either.
The main guy in Bridge of Spies.
Mark Rylance. I'm still shorting out my guy that got nominated. Yeah, Mark Rylance. That guy was BFG
He was also the BFG, and he is also in Duncurt
But I'm just saying these guys aren't like the guys you know everything about you know nothing about them
So you're just kind of like that doesn't help and I don't know Harry Styles was fine in it
They were no one is swearing up and down. He had no idea who Harry Styles was by that, you know
Yeah, yeah, you know what? I buy it too. I was gonna I was gonna take a shot, but I think I do buy it. Yeah now when I was on
two broke girls
at Warner Brothers across the stage across from our stage, I
saw Harry Styles every day and all these people in
fatigues shooting in a giant's this the exact same type of soundstage where we shot a multi -cam sitcom
Well, you know, Dunkirk, I don't know how that happened.
The one direction manager is James Corden's guy.
So that guy like works at the James Corden show a lot.
Okay.
That's interesting.
Isn't that weird?
It's weird.
I don't think it's as weird as me telling you.
They filmed this Dunkirk period piece
that takes place in the sky and on land and Britain
in a Warner Brothers sound stage,
which was just glossed over.
They filmed the interior stuff in the Warner Brothers stuff.
They weren't shooting the beach scenes
in the other sound.
No, there are no interiors in Dunkirk.
I mean, unless we're talking like,
I guess the submarine or something.
Like the interior of the cockpit.
I don't know.
I guess, yeah, probably.
Yeah, the interior of the submarine.
Look, I don't know how special effects work.
But I thought it was kind of interesting.
Two broke curls.
That was that show you were on.
That was the, this was the Thor sitcom you were on.
Well, you've already done this bit on the show.
I know, but I thought of it the other day
and I missed doing it because Cat Dennings was in Thorne.
Yeah, I know. I just think it's funny that a guy's confusion doesn't understand that
two broke grosses and about thores. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It makes me laugh still.
All I can tell you is two broke girls is a show that really moved me into a new house.
That's a crusty the clown line. Joe, I swear to God, now I have no sound. So something has gone wrong.
Something's gone wrong. You have no sound. Hold on. It's been very static and then I went
completely off. Let me just check my still going. Hold on a second. Give me one second.
I mean, this is why we don't do these. These are real endurance tests, guys. These,
uh, are good. We only have a certain area left. Really. Yeah. Okay. Uh, it keeps shorting
in my ear and I can't imagine just your head for that. That doesn't, that doesn't translate
to the list. Oh, maybe it doesn't. I'll look past. Well, it doesn't because you're hearing,
You're not hearing work. Hold on trust me because I haven't heard it. All right. It's not happening. Yeah, you're right
It's just in your headphones. So hold on talk while I do this. Oh, okay
Yeah
Well, I'm going in and out right now
Oh, you think that's it
Better yes, that's it. Nope, it just keeps going in and out. It's very annoying for me
All right, I will
Okay, all right. Oh, okay. You dog fucked us. Yeah. Um, you dog may have a beautiful
asshole, but it fucked us. Um, the most beautiful. Yeah. Uh, well, Joe, I urge you to do Joe's
scary stuff because I have to pay do you have something yeah I believe that I do this sort of
ties into well you know this you know this this podcast guys it covers fantasy science fiction and
horror I've been on a big big retro video game kick last week I talked about the release of slaughterhouse
for the Nintendo switch coming out this well actually when this comes out it'll will have already been
least and I will have already played it to a nauseating length but I don't have it
right now so what I'm going to talk about are two other retro video games that I
have obtained you know what one one because then I can use the other one for
later I bought a turbo graphics 16 recently I know this is sort of a out
their thing, like you might not have an interest in buying a
TurboGraphics 16, or you might not have any ability to come across
one. It's not like they're, you know, just sit in target or something.
I had to kind of come the internet a little bit for this thing, and
they're for retro game collectors affordable,
and that's, you know, I think there are about a hundred bucks to buy an old used one,
which for gaming systems, that's considered affordable.
The games however are not, they are fucking expensive because they are really out of print
and super rare and you know this was a system nobody gave a shit about when it came out.
It competed with the Super Nintendo and the Sega Genesis and it was certainly the in third
place in that race and it faded away pretty quickly as far as video game systems go it's got a very
very limited supply of games that all being said I bought a game for this thing and I can't tell
you the dollar amount that's the Glen Gary Glen Ross thing it wasn't like over a hundred dollars
or anything like that but I paid more for this old video game that I and then I feel not embarrassed to
say, but it's an amazing game. It's called Devil's Crush. And here's why I went
above and beyond out of the pocketbook for this game. My favorite video game of
all time. It is a horror pinball game on the TurboGraphics 16. And when I say
horror, I don't mean just like skulls and shit like that. I mean, satanic imagery,
pentagrams, weird dark monks and cloaks, demon ladies, it's demons, period, it's fucking
amazing.
I love this game so much.
If you have a turbo graphics and you don't have this game, I strongly strongly suggest
you buy it.
It also, if you have a genesis, come in on genesis and I think on genesis it was called
like devil crash or something like that. And then the genesis one is is almost identical to the
the term graphics gets the edge the sounds just a bit better on that one which which I think makes
a difference in a game like this because you're playing pinball you kind of want that soundtrack to
really hit. But devil crash if I didn't know the difference. Joe I'm back. You can wrap this up.
I'm just telling the people about a game that I got.
I mean, even I glaze over on these game segments.
Well, you do, but you're not everybody.
You don't even have the picture up on the screen currently,
for this commentary podcast, which is a new low because you got
scared about your headphones.
And I just try to fix it.
Anyway, um, devil's crush on
termographics or devil crash on Sega Genesis, check it out.
It's in my opinion an excellent, excellent horror video game.
All right, and worth the money.
All right, gang, we're looking at three people attached
at the rectum, trying to escape.
They, I hope you're not watching along with us.
She's starting to, it's starting to rip
either her mouth or his anus.
I believe it's, I believe it's his anus
that is tied to her, tied to her.
Why isn't he in more pain than his anus
is being ripped out?
Here's the part I don't get about this.
They've been attached now as the centipede
for what I can understand a few days.
Yeah, they're gleaming just milky skin still.
They don't have any dirt on them, though.
Everybody's just got out of the shower.
Do you think, Joe, that this was a light fun set
where they laughed at the light in the mood?
I do, you do.
I do, I've heard frequently about some of the more
intense and hardcore horror films that the sets are often pretty jovial because they want
everybody to be enjoying the experience because of the the depths they have to go to when they're
actually shooting. Remember the one you and I saw at the and I want to talk about the horror festival
where they all fuck the dead girl. Yeah see that's the shit I can't deal with I can't deal with shit
like that. I mean, to me, it's kind of like another day at the office, but if the office
is the morgue, yeah, I can't, that's the kind of shit that upsets me greatly. Fucking women
that are dead. Yeah, dead women like, like, this to me is gross, but it's so bad shit that
I don't care. Yeah, what I really do, the corpse sex is a very real problem we have in this
country. And it upsets me. I didn't realize that shit.
Somebody better do something. Um, right after we ban people who want to serve in the
military, folks, I'll get off it. I'll get off it. You think you'd go after the corpse
fuckers? Yeah. You do. You would. Yeah. I got a goddamn corpse problem in this country.
Too many corpses are too good looking. Who's who is the joke about the guy? Oh, already
It's such a good joke. It looks about the guy fucking his parrot got arrested because he's fucking his parrot and he goes
Of all the animals you could have sex with why would you have sex with the one that could tell people that's funny?
Cold on the crashing program and already is apparently
Back in crashes. I guess they're just like I'm happy about that. Let's roll the dice again. I'm happy. He's in man
I'm really happy. He's in I love that guy three of my best friends who I get dinner with about once a month
John and Hayden, who did the Herald and Kumar films,
and my buddy Josh Heild did the Hot Tub Time Machine film.
They have had a wager going for,
I guess I think since they were friends in high school,
they're older than me,
that already language would be dead by his 50th birthday.
Oh, that's terrible.
And if he is alive,
then they all owe the person $1 ,000 who wins,
and they go to Vegas and have like a crazy weekend.
and it's coming up, but they all thought,
when they keep hearing about things getting worse,
they're like, look, they're huge Arty fans.
Okay, they're huge Arty fans.
Yeah, I can't laugh at a death pool about Arty's,
what are my closest friends?
At the same time, they're also kind of like,
of course he'll be dead by 50, it's like eight months away,
but he just keeps hanging in there.
He just tweeted out.
He's cutting his throat now.
Is he killing himself?
I think so.
God, I hate this movie.
He just tweeted out he just had a incident where he collapsed right because of not I don't think
it because of any active abuse but because of abuse from the past right kind of caught up with him
He tweeted out I treated I've cheated the devil for the hundredth time like
You know and I called him and I was talking to him and he's like he's like look man
My doctors and I'm built like an ox so you know, I just keep I'm good
I'm like, I'm like, it is, it is incredible.
Yeah, it makes you really, anytime, like I should
rain things in, it makes me want to go harder
because I, at my worst day, I'm nowhere near the depths
of what I already have.
I told him that was, I told him that once.
I was like, when I talked about this stuff,
I'm sick with myself.
And he goes, why?
And I go, because I can't commit to it, like you can't.
Sure.
And he thought that was funny, but it's true.
Like I look at myself and I'm disgusted.
I just like just just go down the road already. Yeah. Well, you can really do it. I mean you're not hitting some nine to five. No, no, I mean, I'm losing
I'm a fucking boss now. I have to be running things and I hate it. Listen Pat, if I'm gonna dazzle the audiences of the CVS network
You know, and you will you will I just I feel I feel that I need to look beautiful. Yeah, and you do
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Worst of all, he's a quitter. Yeah
Not a fan
Excuse me
Not a fan. Yeah, I was just gonna tell you about what were you talking about a minute before the already thing because I had something to tell you
I don't know, but let me ask another serious question. Yeah you and I I
Guess we've really only been friends about
Three -four years or something three and a half years, but
You know, we're close friends.
I say to you, this movie doesn't exist and I say to you, look.
Before I met you, I was like 25 years old and I just got into some weird shit online.
Eventually, I got obsessed with the idea of making a human centipede.
I explained to you what it is and then I kept these three people in my basement and they escaped
and nobody ever pressed charges and I tell you what I did and everything.
Are we able to remain friends?
I wouldn't believe you
Because you know me to be too good a man. No, not at all. I just would believe I just wouldn't believe you
I'd think you were fucking with me
It would take a lot for you to get me to believe you
Well, assume that you believe me and I'm telling you that this is something I actually know we're not we're not friends anymore
And even if I thought we could be I wouldn't say it
Committing it to recording right now so people could say Joe to Rose the kind of guy that will remain friends with a human
and Santa Pete guy.
You're right.
I just wanna know what kind of friendship I'm in here.
Is it?
You're in a real friendship.
Are you, are you my ride or die bitch?
I'm your ride or die bitch.
Yeah.
Uh, let's say we're out in the streets one night
and you have to kill a man in cold blood
but it's in self -defense and I know it is.
Right.
And the, and the heat's on your tail.
Yeah.
I got your back, buddy.
See, I, all right.
If I'm killing a man in self -defense, then okay.
Why wouldn't I just go to the cops and say it was self -defense because they won't believe me nobody's gonna
Believe this was self -defense. Have you seen the movies? Yeah, you got to go to Bermuda to things cool off, right?
But but not in a way you know what I do on my side of the situation. I'm white. Yeah, boy
So they'll probably be like look we're gonna turn the other way on this one and then savagely beat a
a 14 year old black kid for playing Frisbee too close to a public pool or something.
You're going hard on the, hard on the commentary.
Look, it's a shitty time, you know, to be anyone who isn't a white guy and I have to
do my part to assuage my guilt about being a white guy, because I just feel terrible for
everyone who isn't.
Quite frankly, I'm just, it doesn't mean I feel good for me or the other white guy who's
by the way. Yeah, because you're a hell of a whity. Well, Joe, you're gleaming white. I
know you claim to, uh, you know, to be another, another box on the census form, but you're
a white guy as well. I never had, uh, I don't think I ever got the census. Did they still
do a census? I don't think no. I don't think anybody comes to your door anymore. Did they
stop making census.
The last guy that came to my door
was a kid selling candy bars for his school,
or no magazine subscriptions for his school.
No one ever knocks my door.
And I just crossed over stop making census.
We'll talk in his reference.
Not an LL.
Stop making it, oh.
But not terrible.
I didn't even get it when you said it.
Because it's so accurate.
Yeah.
I thought you were saying literally just saying
like they stopped making the census.
Yeah.
I thought that's what you were saying.
We hear it.
We'll see you in hell.
Would love to shout out the great Mr. Jonathan Demi,
who directed one of the horror classics of all time.
and maybe the best zero killer movie ever made,
sounds of the lambs, as well as, stop making sense.
Maybe the best concert movie ever made,
starting the great talking hits.
It is a great film.
Now you wanna talk about selfish.
Here we are at the end of the film.
Yeah.
Cops are dead, Dietrich Lazer's dead,
the human centipede is in a room trying to,
with their last breath escape.
Why are they dying?
Well, because you wanna talk selfish,
that God damn Asian guy killed himself because the guy kept calling him Mr.
kamikaze and he fucking kamikaze at the end. Yeah. He killed himself and then
these chicks are just so new in asshole. You couldn't live with the guilt
probably, which I get, but you know, the guilt of what? It wasn't his idea. I
don't get that. Joe, if you shit in a woman's mouth, you're gonna feel
something whether you whether or not it was your idea or not. Well, Pat, you're
feel something. I hate to break it to you. I didn't feel anything.
No, don't, don't, don't, don't last Saturday morning.
Oh, I thought you were going to invoke the name of my sweet mother, Jill Walsh.
Um, the, uh, but I'm saying you don't, you, you love these, these, these girls
that hang, man, what are they supposed to do now? That, that, that, here's my
point. I hear what you're saying. Him killing himself was more selfish because
Now they're just stuck to his asshole, but to call the Asian guy a kamikaze and like, you know, and all this and then make him the coward who kills himself
It's also like make him the hero or something
Is this how this really ends with them all attached and
Slowly dying in his house. That's how this movie is gonna end. I thought the one lady got away
All three of them are still sitting there. They keep writing. This is a subtitle right now birds chirping and they always say birds chirping in the day
Nobody needs to know nobody cares. No nobody fucking cares. That is the end of the end unbelievable
I thought the one girl got away, but I guess I'm wrong. Hey look here's a rule if you're gonna make me sit through that for 90 minutes
Give me revenge
Let them
Kill the man. Well, that's not what it's about because Tom six is an artist. Yeah, well
Well folks, I'd say that's our show.
That is our show.
We hope you enjoyed this return to commentary.
I eagerly await the tweets that now say, I don't like the commentary ones, I wish you
go back to the other one because you guys are never happy.
But that's why we keep striving to make you happy.
What is that burst of sound in the middle?
What's that going to be in the blue? It's just that I got this. Don't worry about it. Joe's got it guys
Any plugs
No plugs for me. We are going to be back now in two weeks time
We hope you enjoyed our return and we will see you soon. We will see you in hell
Yeah comedy train festival this week Amsterdam
Where I believe this movie took place
So be careful
Kyle Kinane and I co -headlining four nights. I guess second through the fifth come out and see us cut to you and Kyle Kinane joined at the
We'll see you next time folks. Bye bye