I'll see you at how the movie shall with the movie ho
Today's picture is a little piece of somewhat unseen horror history called the Monster Club starring John
Caradine as our Chetwind Hayes and Vincent Price as Strange Man. Wasn't that his character and pretty much every movie made let's be real. Yes, I agree. It turns out Price's character's name is Aramus Aramus. I don't know if that's ever revealed.
But that's according to Wikipedia. No, it's a film I had never heard of. Joe Bob did it on his show. It's an anthology horror and price is kind of in the connective tissue story.
What we'll get to it. We'll get to wrap around. What was just out of curiosity before we start? What was Joe Bob's reaction to this film?
He liked the picture, but he was also very much on the defensive because he was expecting everyone to not like it. And he said generally people think that these stories are weak, that they don't have good twists and turns, that they're boring, blah, blah, blah.
So he acknowledged that it wasn't really a favorite, but that it had fallen out of circulation and he wanted to share it with the people and probably because it was free on shutter. Let's be honest.
Okay, all right, fair enough. Fair enough. We're going to we're going to get to that and also in coming weeks.
We're hoping, hoping to to review the the new Cronenberg picture, crimes, crimes of the future.
Crimes of the future. And we'd also love to do the black phone. Yes. I plan on seeing the black phone in the coming weeks. It's weird, you know, like when it came out at wherever it was fun, fast or one of the.
It wasn't Sundance, but one of those festivals. It was like this is it was the most I had heard about a big horror movie since like hereditary problem.
Just like with the raves about it and oh my God, it was so scary, whatever. And now that it's coming out, the reviews are all pretty negative.
And I think there's so much of that like black type that carries these movies. Yeah, black phones not getting great reviews at all.
Well, it's got a 80 % on run. I know I'm sorry, that's crazy. I thought, no, it had a hundred percent at one point.
Well, that's what I'm saying is that festival circuit. It was like, oh my God, this is a game changer. But now that it's out, most of the reviews I've seen.
And I follow a lot of film people on Twitter from all different backgrounds. They don't like the movie.
All right. Shit. Well, I want to see it, you know, I am not a big Joe Hill guy. I got to be honest there.
The Joe Hill right it. Joe Hill wrote the story it was adapted from. I don't know that he wrote the film, but I haven't done my research yet for it.
Well, we have a special treat here today.
Speaking of crimes in the future. Rex Reed has reviewed the film.
He's a few grams of the future. Yeah, I haven't read it. Oh, yeah, I sent that to you. Yeah.
I haven't read this yet, but I feel like you don't need to, you don't need to pre read a read. You just need to read a read. It's true.
It's titled David Kronenberg's crimes, the future is a senseless collection of horrifying garbage.
The director's latest abomination is causing audience is to walk out and dress. So he's got a hard on for Kronenberg because he's saying latest abomination that usually insinuates he thinks there are others. Yes.
First sentence of the review. This guy is a wasted time.
Crimes the future is a load of crap.
I mean, at this point, you're not being a professional film reviewer really. Yeah, when you're calling something a load of crap.
I would like to find a more civil way to describe even a sick and depraved barf bag of a movie like not come on, but it defeats every reasonable attempt to try.
Publicity. Oh my God. Publicity. Poopery. Declares it. From the mind of David Kronenberg in quotes. That's your first warning signal.
Just a universally respected director for decades. I know. I've been able to endure a few of his epic horrors in the past, but 90 % of the time I found no evidence of any kind of mind at all.
Still, and what has become a film industry badly in need of triage, TRI, it's just like, you know, like they nurse your wounds. God, I'm stupid.
Wonders never cease. Quick on the heels of its new world premiere a few weeks ago at Khan, where it was shown to audiences who walked out and drove loudly boot and declared unreleasable.
Crimes of the future is now upon us, like a rabid raccoon. Now, Rex, are you expecting us to believe that someone walked into the lobby pointed at the roof and yelled, unreleasable?
Is that, was that person maybe you, Rex? I think they probably did you maybe do that, Rex?
They probably all met up at the critics tent.
And dish the dirt there. Well, I know I must talk on the show about when I met Jimny Glick, when I worked the independent spirit tent, and he came in and made fun of the film bloggers for like 10 minutes.
That's great. Just tore us apart. It was in like a half ass version of the suit, but it was still very funny.
But yeah, you are in a critics tent and the critics, I got to say, by and large, I've had to go to some of these things.
So Rex liked Rex likes Eastern promises, and he liked the history of violence.
Yeah, they're both great, but he says here that it is a crime to see the waste of vehicle more and since time.
And the disintegration of his body and talent in this freak show.
But he's always marched to the sound of his own drummer and you've got to admire his loyalty to the man who wrote and directed this bomb.
He goes on to talk about the plot. We don't need to read that. The movie opens with a mother smothering her sleeping child to death and goes steadily downhill from there.
Oh, Jesus. All right. Well, maybe Rex has a point. I don't know if I want to see that. One scene does not follow another images just sort of invade each other while you hope something will make some sort of sense.
Unfortunately, logic is nowhere in sight and nothing in this movie makes any sense as repellent and revolting as it is. I was astonished to find it doubly boring.
Or Rex.
At the screening, I attended a lot of people walked out, but even more were snoring.
Eventually, it becomes so silly that it sinks into a pandemic of farce. The acting is uniformly dreadful, including Christian Stewart, who plays the head of something called the National Oregon Registry, which sponsors the inner beauty pageant.
A popular event in which people with surgically inserted organs can display their holes, sutures and scars. All right, he might have a point. This sounds insane.
Yeah, no, I've heard it's disgusting, and I've heard very mixed things.
So you can leave this world behind if you eat this. That's another plot point. All right, so he closes out with.
All of the caterpillar paste loopiness builds to a catonic ending, catatonic ending, excuse me, in which the incomprehensible C. Doe, who's a character, I think played by Stewart, I think that's her character feeds Mortensen, the purple candy bar made of microplastics.
Obviously, it's the end of their act, but nothing is explained, including the point of this thing, if there is one, the film has no dynamic, which explains why this little impact crimes, the future is grand.
Oh, boy, is grand, you know, we know, yeah.
That means like gory, like hostile as grand would me all.
All right, to a new level of an uncomfortable gibberish, the kind of self -indulgent IQ wrecking trash on film, for which landfills and garbage dumps weren't all right, racks, Jesus Christ.
Wow.
Halfway through the film, I felt compelled to go up to the projectionist booth, spread my butt cheeks, and shit on the film. That's how bad it was.
That's, that's wild. That's a, that is a heavy review.
Yeah, I mean, what is he writing for at this point, just a manifesto somewhere in a cabin or is he, is he published?
Hey, God bless the New Yorker. Keep, keep it coming, Rex.
But where is Joe, it was a question. Where is he writing? Oh, the observer.
Oh, the observer. I thought you, I thought you said, what is he right? I thought you meant like, what is his reason? Oh, no.
By the way, Joe, what do you think about the observer? What do you think about the decor of my Airbnb looking behind me here? Are you pretty impressed by that?
I don't know why you do this to yourself. You know, you're in a hot city with a hot downtown, you choose to live out in some fucking country house.
Behind me, folks, is the most beige, off -white, gray generic painted wall and on it hangs a large fake silver price tag hanging off of it $9 .99 spoon, like a wall size spoon.
And then above that, another $9 .99 utensil, a giant fork. That's what's above my head.
It looks like the shit the realtor puts on the walls, like when they just need to sell a house. What, what, what?
Now here's the deal. I think I made this clear. I did live in the city when I first came out here. I enjoyed it, wound up drinking too much. There's an enormous tax on alcohol here.
So like, yeah, I'll have a tequila on the rocks, $28. And drinking in the wrong places, man.
Well, no, I looked around, but I have at that time, I had a 45 minute commute to work and back. Now I'm in a four bedroom house.
Two minutes from set. I can go to and from work all day as I please have lunch at home, whatever the fuck I wanted to go home and record a podcast.
And get a lot of use out of those four bedrooms. You get a lot of.
And as I'm built tomorrow night, three of my dear friends from Missouri, if you listen are coming out here to stay in those bedrooms.
And I have invited you to stay in the bedrooms. He gets turned me away.
Men in their 40s are getting a hotel. No, because I've got a house. I understand.
Now the following weekend, I have friends coming out. They are getting hotels and they're staying in the city proper. So they're like they want a party. I get that too.
This is a come out cheer up your friend who's going through a crisis. We play poker. We drink. We have some weed and we have a nice time. You know, that's when you want a house.
We have a big chill kind of weekend, baby.
I'm like Jennifer Tilly walking around in like a leotard and like real tight leggings.
I want to think of it as a different seasons type hang with Alan Alda.
The Ellen Waldo.
And who else was in that movie?
Different seasons is the Stephen King book, correct? You're thinking of the four seasons. Four seasons. God damn it. Yeah. Yeah.
The Ellen Waldo.
A young who plays the my favorite Alan Alda performance weirdly enough is in marriage story. I think he steals the movie marriage story. He's incredible in it.
I never saw a marriage story.
Very underrated film. It's a well, no, it was nominated for a bunch of shit. I just mean there was a backlash to it that I think was unnecessary because I think it's a good movie.
My favorite Alda performance is crimes and misdemeanors by far.
Oh, sure.
And I agree.
If it bends, if it bends, see, it's funny. If it breaks, that's not the thing when he goes time plus tragedy, tragedy equals comedy.
Like for instance, you take the Lincoln assassination. You couldn't make jokes then. It's not funny. But now.
Uh -huh. Uh -huh.
No, it's great. I love it. I'm a fan.
I wonder if he's a pro. I also, and you've made, you've mocked me incessantly. I enjoy him in the film Tower Heist.
Sure. Sure.
Do you think he's a prick? He seems like he could very well be a prick.
Never did anything but really kind things about it. And for funnier die when that had first come out when that was the big thing, the website.
I was a temp at State Farm Insurance at that time. And I realized that I could get in with my key card to a, to an office that looked just like the set of the office on the weekends and film there.
So I just moved to LA. I was trying to make my way in the world. So with my buddy Brian to go I who just got married. Congratulations, Brian.
Who who filmed and edited the short. And then me who wrote and started it and my buddy Ian Friedman.
Yeah.
He was my co star in it, but basically he sat in a cubicle in a tan suit way before Obama.
And then I came strolling through like on my way to the coffee room or whatever and he was like, hey man, how was your weekend of the extension things.
And then I casually dropped that I hooked up with Alan Aldo over the weekend. And he's like, what?
It was super funny. Like to this day. And I said because I wrote it 20 years ago, but it's one of my favorite things I ever wrote and he was really funny in it. And, you know, we played some little shorts festivals and stuff. And it kind of got me my early mark in this business.
But Alan Aldo I was later told had seen the short.
Oh, because for a short time it was posted on his IMDB page is like one of his links.
And he was like, look, getting it set up or whatever and he clicked on it. So I heard second hand or third hand that he saw it and thought it was very funny. And he was like, now are people going to think this is real?
When you say hooked up mean like in sex with the entire short and it was like a nine minute short was me graphically describing the sex with Alan Aldo that we had gone out and then I brought him back to my apartment and we hooked up.
And it's really funny. I don't even know if it's still available online because funny or die went under and I think they revealed to have right wing Nazi ties. But what?
They like they bought oil or something caused Adam McCay to leave the company and will Farrell to leave the company.
So now it has neither of them attached even though they started it, but some scandal involving oil or something along those lines can't do anything anymore can't do anything.
No, I know. So I think it's actually been scrubbed from the internet, but I don't know.
Jesus Christ.
But yeah, it's called I fucked Alan Aldo. So if you Google it, maybe it'll show up any who.
All right.
Any who I realized I only did two on the movie corner last time and it made me sad.
Didn't make me sad at all.
Well, let me get to that other documentary that I wanted to mention. Is this it? Are we in the movie corner? I think so, right? Sure.
I was looking trying to find some more screaming and stuff, but I mean, it's just a slow week, man. Nothing's really going on. It's a slow week, especially in the world of horror.
I don't think there's much going on, you know. Yeah, just nothing, man. Anyway, go ahead.
All right. So I saw.
For the curse of bond Dutch colon a brand to die for. This was a three part. I want to say documentary about the rise and fall of bond Dutch. It amounts to three hours.
Bond Dutch was basically the they started in skater culture, punk culture. Yeah, rose to prominence through trucker hats being worn by Paris Hilton, a national culture and then they imploded basically.
But behind the scenes is a very fascinating tale. A very sleazy disgusting tale.
The kind of people you would imagine would be associated with like bringing bond Dutch to the masses. And it was really entertaining. I had a blast watching it. It's the kind of thing you would have watched back in the day on VH1 as like a really juicy behind the music kind of thing.
And now they're considered prestige documentaries because they're on streaming networks, which is crazy. But I dug it. It's it's got a good kind of soundtrack of that time.
You know, it is a little sad to be watching documentaries about things that took place in your lifetime. It makes you feel very old. You'll you all you young fans will learn that someday.
When you have talking heads reminiscing about something that happened when you were in high school, it's dark. Wouldn't you agree Joe?
Yes, I do. Yeah.
All right. Well, check that one out on Hulu. I dug it. Fun documentary.
I'm going to go all docs. Well, sort of docs. I'll start with Jimmy Savile. I mentioned it last time.
This docu series about Jimmy Savile. And I can't find the name of it because, oh, that there is, it is called a British horror story. Terrible title. But this docu series about this guy, Jimmy Savile, who was a host and DJ and personality from England was hugely cemented at the BBC did a ton of stuff for them.
It raised an incredible amount of money for charity was sort of everybody's favorite man. And then it turned out that he had been doing hard things to women some of them with mental issues and health issues and things.
And it was covered up greatly during his lifetime.
There were a few accusations that sort of came and went, but the shit really hit the fan after he died Netflix did a six part. I think series on this. This is another bit I'm working on is.
This one's not murder, but how many murders is Netflix going to solve via their docu series before we realize there's somehow connected to these things. I mean, it's to me the lid off of everything. It's crazy.
To me, the crime about this stuff is how quickly Netflix became Walmart and just like the lowest common denominator, the documentaries all clearly follow the exact same formula.
And I hate it. Like, even if I'm interested in the subject, I hate that they all look feel sound exactly the same. And you almost feel the gears of the algorithm walking in as you watch this shit.
It's like, oh, that's checking off this box. That's checking off this box. The stand -up specials feel that way. I'm not even going to mention those, but I watched a collection of Netflix stand -up specials this week that made my dick limp.
I'll keep my tongue bit on that since I know many involved, but.
But yeah, this this docu series is interesting. I mean, you kind of know what's up before it's over.
You know, so I wouldn't say that it's a must watch, but, but I, you know, look, it's another fucking depraved docu series where somebody did a horrible thing and it's unspeakable.
And now there's somebody making a TV show about it. So whatever your terms or ethics or boundaries are on that sort of thing, keep that in mind.
The funniest part to me is, and I did not make this observation. I read it from somebody else, but the BBC was was basically accused and covering up these heinous acts of Jimmy Savile. And now the BBC is producing a movie starring Steve Cougan, a biopic about the scandal about Jimmy Savile.
And they're getting criticism about exploiting this thing that happened, and they're saying we feel we feel it's a story that must be told they're justice and this that somebody is like, but you guys were the ones that covered it up.
You know, so, so this is, this is where we're at. Unfortunately, I hate to keep pimping bits here. Sorry.
But maybe just don't over compensate the penance. You know what I mean? Yeah, like, like, like Disney, it's like Disney is so desperately woke and it's like, guys, you're the worst offenders in the game of past racism in your things.
Just stop. You know what I mean? If you're somebody who murders, it's enough for me that you say I was wrong to have murdered.
I don't need to now see you out campaigning for anti murder. You know what I mean? Like, stop it. Like just, just shut up.
Repent. And that's it. You know, so I think the BBC is kind of doing that now with Jimmy Savile.
And it's annoying and it's stupid. And this was the least favorite of the three I'm going to review today. But the guy was a fucking scumbag, you know, yeah, but there's not much more to it than that.
To me, the one if there was something funny about the whole story and there wasn't really, but it was just the fact that every time they put a microphone in front of this man, he says, I basically, I am a sex creep.
I'm a pedophile. Walk up your daughter's daddies in town. And he's looking to lick. And they're like, we just never thought it could have been our Jimmy.
We never thought it could have been Jimmy Savile. And they cut to a clip of him on the evening news. And he's like, where's your daughter's pussy at?
You know, like, it's insane.
It's true that he says, like, he'll say, like, in these interviews, like, we come in, mate, we do a lot of good for everybody. And everybody's happy except for the next morning when the daughter's father's come looking for us.
And you're like, yeah, he's saying it, like, just out in the, I guess it's one of those things, though, where you think he's just trying to be funny.
Like, you think he's a good guy. So you're like, oh, I thought he was like joking.
Like that's inside. Yeah, that's palsy, man, to wave it around like that. But that's what, that's what a lot of offenders do. They get off on the thrill of the, you know, the danger. But anyway, take it or leave it.
Jimmy Savile, a British horror story with the worst title they ever could have given it.
I rewatched the film Game Night, which I think is one of the more solid comedies of the last 10 years.
It's a movie that I could see myself watching. And if I still had cable, anytime it popped up on cable on any plane ride, I always find myself selecting Game Night.
As I did on a recent plane ride, it's perfect for that. But it's also just a really funny movie. It's basically like a perfectly cast episode of a great sitcom. And this is like the pilot of it.
So it's, there's something a little generic about it. Everybody's filling in their role.
But the cast is great. Jason Bateman is always great in this kind of thing. Rachel McCatams, extremely charming. They're great together.
You got stealing the show, Jesse Plemons as the creepy police officer neighbor. I think he should have won the Oscar for that performance, except they never would nominate comedies for that thing.
And then you got hilarious people in all the small roles, Billy Magnuson, Lamor and Morris, Sharon Horgan, a lot of great actors. They directed the hell out of it.
I think it's a very funny, very fun movie. At the end, it becomes a little too much of an action movie makes it feel kind of like those old like ruthless people type 80s movies where every comedy had to end in a car chase for some reason.
But yeah.
But by and large, it's very entertaining. There's a lot of laughs in this movie, a lot of really great one liners. Have you seen the film, Joe?
No.
I highly recommend it, you know, it's like if anybody was going to talk about the better comedies of the last 10 years, I think I would be stumped to be honest, but I got a shout out game night as one that should be in the conversation.
Very good.
My number two.
I can cut me off, Joe.
I didn't cut you off.
Don't you don't you.
He says it as he slugs from a white claw people. This is what we're dealing with here. Dad, he said a few drinks. He's going to get honoring now.
Actually, a white claw surge, which is the new test market for Atlanta white claw where it has more alcohol in it.
There you go.
8%.
I watched finally I watched George Carlin American dream.
I was not as irritated by it by any stretches. I thought I would be.
I do think.
You know, the producers or directors took some liberty in pushing Carlin a little farther left.
Then he.
I think would have liked to have been remembered. That's just my opinion. Maybe I'm wrong.
But I did enjoy the documentary. It was very dark.
A lot about his drug addiction. A lot about his wife's alcoholism. A lot about how toxic their relationship was for many years.
But it did have hope in the end.
And my favorite part was at the end was towards the end when he just started saying to everybody, like, I don't give a fuck if you all deliver die.
And, you know, he was like saying he was going to name his next special fuck hope.
And then they're cutting to these talking heads like, you know, I have a hard time believing he didn't care.
And he's on camera saying it.
Right.
And then going.
At one point he goes, isn't that good, man, that was so real. That's why it's good because it's real.
And then people are still going, you know, I just think that he, you know, like,
I could have done without 90 % of the talking heads in this thing.
But some of the people I really did enjoy watching, particularly Paul Pervenza, who is like, is a great dude and a buddy of mine.
But just really a student of comedy and truly like a comedy historian.
And I thought he had a lot of great stuff to say without any sort of agenda.
I couldn't believe some of the people that weren't in this thing.
Maybe they passed.
I don't know.
But I was shocked to see the absence of certain people. I enjoyed John Stuart's takes on a lot.
And overall, I liked it. I did find it chilling when they cut his words to like everything happening in some of what tragically has been going on in America.
But again, I thought it was way too heavy on the, the right, the evil right wing and not anywhere near enough about all this, you know, all of his thoughts on free speech.
And cancel culture and all that like that, that should have been in there till at the end and it wasn't they they touched on it earlier, but it should have been there in the end.
And I felt like that was that was the producers and directors trying to send a message.
Interesting, but you know, I don't know if entirely appropriate.
In any case, it was a good documentary. I learned a lot about him that I didn't already know and I knew I already knew a lot of it, but enjoyable.
Would I recommend it?
No, I wouldn't, to be honest, it was good to me as a major diehard Carlin fan, but I, you know, my mom wanted to watch it. I was like, mom, I got to tell you, this is not like a light watch.
Like I wouldn't, you know, just toss this on like this is a dark, this is a dark four hours. So, um, you know, that's, I don't know, I can't, I enjoyed it, but I also wouldn't recommend it, which is kind of a weird stance.
I don't know, that's how I feel.
I loved it myself.
I saw on the Joe Bob hellbender.
Wait, wait, is this not a potential for us or no?
No.
Okay.
There's not much to say, really, in my opinion.
All right.
I watched it with Joe Bob's commentary and that's kind, oh my god.
I think Joe just showed me his dick pretty much, folks.
I didn't, I had to adjust the Undy's, I apologize.
Good.
God, I think you came closer than you realized.
Ah, well, it's nothing you've never seen before.
Almost saw Joey's roses in the flesh, folks.
Hellbender is a, there's a Blair witchy vibe to it.
It's extremely low budget.
Christ.
It's in the woods.
It's a lot of pentagrams made of sticks, fab, that kind of thing.
Oh, jeez.
And honestly, if I had just turned on hellbender, I don't know
that I would have finished it.
However, with Joe Bob there to give it context and to have the people
there, I learned that this movie is made by a family Zelda
Adams Lulu.
Oh, this is not Adams.
Oh, I read about them in rumor.
They're very interesting people.
I didn't realize this was their movie.
Okay.
For sure.
Fascinating people.
And, and the dad had been like a male model at one point.
And now the daughter is a young model.
And they're, they act and write and shoot films together.
And having the family as guests on the Joe Bob show was really cool hearing their
takes and their stories made it cool and special.
But that's why I love Joe Bob.
It makes a bad movie way better.
It makes a good movie great.
It makes a great movie incredible.
But this folks, I got to say, if I'm just looking at the facts of a movie,
I'm not too, not too impressed.
But I do recommend watching it with that family.
And it's very inspiring to see what you can do with like just a couple of
your friends and not much money, you know, so the movie itself.
Some cool visuals in it.
Some cool kind of trippy drug stuff, which is even otter for a family to be making
stuff that looks kind of like Mandy in some sections.
But not a great move in my.
Fair enough.
I, my last one is not a documentary, but a bio thing.
I watched from start to finish the offer, which is about to make it.
Do you say a bio pick or a buy you pick?
Is it a bio thing?
Okay.
Did I say buy you?
Are you making a joke or did I really mispronounce it?
I can't.
A little of both.
But I did think it was kind of, it's kind of funny to miss here.
Bio pick is buy you pick.
I thought that was moderately amusing.
You know, yeah, you know, it is.
I agree.
I agree with you.
Just trying to keep it light pepper and light.
Keep it popping.
Keep it moving.
What are some examples of bio picks?
Gatorbait for sure.
Gatorbait to occasion justice for sure.
Uh, I would, I would throw all the crocodile dundees in there.
Just.
They were popping into my mind.
But they never is in the buy you.
Not technically, but he's in swamps.
Night moves with Gene Hackman is definitely a bio movie.
Just cause.
This is some kind of early fish print.
Yeah.
This is burning.
Maybe technically not the bio, but yeah, I hear you.
Just John Candy scene in JFK.
Yeah, he was in the bio for sure.
He was in the bio.
His underwear were the bio that night.
Um, anyway.
It was a big man sweat.
Yes.
Yeah.
Um, I, I, I watched the offer, which is the TV show about the making of the Godfather.
Should I watch this?
Those people keep telling me that, that, that, that it's bad,
and that I should watch it.
I found it too, so I didn't want to watch it and my mom kept telling me about it.
And I was like, all right.
Mom, I'll watch it.
Cause I had the clips I'd seen.
I was like, this is terribly cliched, but whatever.
I'll just watch it.
So they gave me their Paramount.
Log in.
And please tell me you're not taking your hand to your mom anymore.
Joe.
After we talked.
You're not raising your hand to her face.
I will put her over my knee, that's fun, that's fun, but but I said, all right,
final watch. So they gave me their login. And I got to tell you,
the first episode, I was kind of like, right, you know, this is kind of long and
but whatever. And after that, I just was in like, I was hooked. I wanted to see
what happened. Now, is it cliche? Yes. Is it a sort of paint by numbers bio series? Yes.
But are there performances? A lot of fun. And is the story riveting? Absolutely. I'm sure it's
greatly exaggerated. There are things in there that I know for a fact and happen. But Matthew
Good alone as Robert Evans deserves every award possible. He's incredible. Keep seeing it. And
yet I can't imagine a scenario where I walk away saying, boy, that Matthew Good was incredible. But
you're watching it. You're like, Jesus Christ. Like he's him. He looks just like because I admit,
this is my own hang -ups. But I think I was introduced to him when he was like a Jason Maraz type
pop singer who wore like, jaunty hats before he was an actor. If I'm not mistaken. I don't know,
he was ever a singer. Do you just know him as the Thessian? No, I've heard he's incredible in this.
And I want to watch it. But then again, I also just want to watch the two -hour version of
He Done With It. And I also just read a book about this whole period at the time. So it's like
at some point I'm going to run out of my interest in the story. You're in luck. You're getting a
movie starring Oscar Isaac and Jake Gyllenhaal as Robert Evans. I know. But I enjoyed this. I thought
that Miles Teller was great. Juno Temple is wonderful in it. What's his face? His copula is fun.
I really like Colin Hanks a lot. I really like the movie.
Do you have on a BBC play, Joe Colombo? It is cartoonish and over the top, but somehow it makes sense.
It reminded me of Jared Lito at House of Gucci, where you're like, this is insane what he's doing,
but I'm buying it somehow. It was that kind of thing. The air to the Colombo yogurt franchise?
Yeah, of course, of course. Do you have Colombo yogurts at Edmalls by you?
No, I don't. No, I just went along with it. I wanted to guess the end of you. I didn't want to
start yet. I mean, Tara, did you have TCB -wise, the country's best yogurt?
Yeah, but flamingos was a big one where I lived. There was a local chain called flamingos and they
had a strawberry yogurt that I would get gummy bears on. And I'll tell you, man, I would, that would
knock you sideways, pal. Sure, bouncing off the walls.
Yeah, it was really good. I would recommend the show. Why for two reasons?
It's a light, fun watch. It takes you away from the bullshit. It's just a story. They depict the
period realistically. Like, those things I appreciate about it. And secondly,
whether it's in Belish or not, I was just like, I got to stop bitching.
Like, the pressure these guys were under to make this movie, I can't imagine the level of stress.
And they just kept moving forward and got it done. And I was just like, I got to stop complaining
when something goes wrong with my job. Like, I never had to sit down with a mafia member
because they wanted to kill me because I was making a movie that would make them look bad or whatever.
You know, so like, you know, there was probably something more honest about that though.
There was something what? I'm sorry. There was probably just something more honest about it back
then, though, you know, the business, you mean? Yeah. Now, 100 % too faced. It made you want to,
well, everybody's, it's a terribly duplicitous scene in this show. But I will say this,
I said to my mom, I go, I go, mom, that it makes me wish that's what the business was.
Everybody's wearing a suit and drinking all day long and making moves. And it's just,
it's just, it's, it's, it's, I really liked it. I really, really liked the show.
So my thugs up for it for the author. Sounds like this is one offer. You're accepting.
Yes. Which brings us to our, oh, wait, I do have a screen men in.
Yeah. Before we do the movie of the day.
Um, I'm just a live Tyler Christ almighty. Nev Campbell.
Not coming out for scram six. Not coming out for scram six.
Because they apparently made her such an insulting offer.
And I'm with Nev Campbell all the way. She goes, I'm sorry guys. I love all of you. I love
what this franchise has done for me. I love the fans. Yeah. I feel that they are in no way
valuing what I bring to the fridge. It's like, first of all, why are you making another one?
Five was the perfect end to it all. That's it. It's over. They're going to make another one. It's
of course there's another drip left in the teeth. You know, and now they're going to do one for the
first time ever without Nev Campbell. Who the fuck are you going to do a screen without Nev Campbell?
You son of a bitch. Who wants to see what you're going to do? Yeah. Who wants to see how
fucking idiotic are you that you don't have fucking Nev Campbell in your scream sequel? What are you
going to do? To sign on? I'm sure Cox will do it. Our cat and our cat dead die. Well, you never
know in these pictures. Well, here's the funny part. Our cat is talking like he's heartbroken
that Campbell's not in it. Like he's in it. So I'm like, maybe our cat isn't it. I don't know.
I mean, you just know the end of one of these. They're going to take it off and it's going to be him
back from the dead and, you know, they're going to go. They're going to take this all the way down
to Halloween 20 period of time. You know where they're going to take it down to brown town.
Brown town. Yeah. Might be brown town. I just can't believe that you would. It's like undervaluing
Robert England in a nightmare on Elm Street sequel. I mean, it's just so crazy to me.
It's like not paying Crispin Glover a million dollars for back to the future, too.
And then you wind up having to pay him a million dollars because it's sousia because he uses likeness
and he wins and you got to pay him anyway, even though you didn't have him in the movie. You had
somebody way of worth. Rat business. It's a business of rats. Anyway, that's true. There's your god damn
screaming in. All right. Movie of today. That's our thing. It's a combination of a scream and then
like the the gavel that you hear on the news channels. No psycho. No psycho. We got
how I introduced my girlfriends these days. I should meet my new psycho. Her name's Jennifer
Perpet. Okay. She made the news psycho. Okay. I just tried watching Joe dirt to just
the only dirt. The only laugh was I hate to I'm not trying to knock old spade there because I love
a big fan. But the only laugh. I think Miller gets a quip off in the first two minutes and then
nothing after that. Anyway, monster club. Some later error work by the great John Caridine and
Vincent Price for all intents and purposes. This is an early 80s anthology horror film about Vincent
Price playing a vampire. Who is very weak. He runs into John Caridine in the street. He does not
want to he's a he's a he's a he's a courteous vampire. He doesn't want to attack him. He says,
if you would please let me just have a little of your blood. I promise to take you to a really special
place. John Caridine, John Caridine, John Caridine for Christ's sakes. Wash my brains coming unravel.
He complies. Vincent Price only bites him enough to feed not to turn him. And then he takes
him to the monster club a place where monsters hang out. It looks like a third rate version of
the cantina scene in the original Star Wars. It's a bunch of people. It's a bunch of people running
around in static costumes. Oh my God. I mean, we're talking about like masks from the local Walgreens.
Like I mean bad masks that people are wearing at this thing over like a turtle neck and jeans.
Yeah, yeah, that is true. And then Price proceeds to tell Caridine three chilling tales.
The movie for the most part is a comedy including the second story that the first and third stories
are not funny. But everything else in the movie is played for comedic effect including the third
story. Our second story, excuse me. And then there are full musical numbers in this thing by
new wave bands at the time. It makes no sense. Full musical numbers. When we say full folks, I'm talking
first note to last note like you're watching an SNL performance of bands. One of them is UB40
who I didn't even recognize. They certainly didn't play my beloved red red one. But there are
the one that was cool was the stripper song with the animated ghoul where she the stripper takes
her skin off and then she dances around as a skeleton. That is very right. To me, the highlight of the film
and like a real saucy, sassy song, you know, that I enjoyed. A rock band called The Night. Yeah,
they play like the opening theme to Roseanne. Is that right? No. But that sounds like stripper music.
It does. I watch this in a real kind of bad spot. I've broken. I'm on the other side of it. But I
watched this very high and I contacted my friends that I'm on a group chat with and improvised a song
over that stripper song and sent it to them. I might have sent it to you too, Joe. I don't know. It's very
high. Just like disturbing voice memos of in the recent weeks. I don't know what's going on.
I'm recording songs for people and sending them out. But whatever it did, whatever the combo did,
I'm through them. I'm on the other side of a joint life again. But yeah, this movie was to me
a disaster. And Joe Bob kept apologizing for it and I get why? It's an embarrassing movie.
The stories suck. They absolutely suck. Walk me through the stories and prove me wrong.
I will. Just some trivia for you here. Christopher Lee was originally sought for the role of
Chet Wood Hayes, which was the John Karadine part. But flatly turned the offer down simply upon hearing
the film's title for his agent. Peter Cushing also turned out a role. This is saying a lot, guys.
I have great respect for Christopher Lee and Peter Cushing. These guys did not exactly pick
fucking gems all the way through. There are also a number of inside jokes of the movie relating to
Amicus films. You know, you're in trouble when you're doing inside jokes about Amicus films.
I learned about Amicus pretty recently through Edgar Wright's big list of recommendations.
And I watched a bunch over the pandemic. A lot of great anthologies. So I was excited about this one.
But this is the least of them by far, I thought. The first story. Oh boy. The first story is called
the Shadmok. And it's about a greedy woman who's struggling financially, who meets a man who's
who's not physically attractive, but doesn't really look like a monster. It just looks like a ugly guy.
And you find out he's a hybrid creature called a Shadmok. And if you make him angry or betray him,
he will whistle. And if you hear the Shadmok's whistle, something terrible will happen to you.
And of course, eventually. Imagine pitching that. Imagine going into a studio and pitching that.
It's horrible. It's just horrible.
I mean, correct me if I'm wrong. You're right. I can't argue this. He finds out what she's up to.
He whistles at her and it makes her face ugly. Yeah. And then her boyfriend who she's like doing
the scheme with to get to get the Shadmok's money, whatever. That's the whole plan of the thing.
He goes to see her and then he becomes driven insane by the sight of her face. I mean, this is
this is some real paint by numbers shit here. Yeah. I mean, something about the very low budget,
very low -fi effects. We're kind of charming in a ramshackle way. But the story itself was dog shit.
It's terrible. The second story, by the way, the Shadmok, there's a thing where Vincent
Pryce explains what a Shadmok is to David Carrity. You don't know what a Shadmok is.
He's got like a poster and he's like, when a ghoul has sex with a troll, they have a goblin.
And when a goblin then has sex with a vampire, he goes to the whole thing and goes down the list of
monsters to the bottom, which is the least interesting of all of them, which is the Shadmok that
just looks like a person. That scene was so horrible, so horrible that he happened to have a poster
of how we got the Shadmok and written clearly as comedy. Yeah. And by the way, I can't find any
fucking evidence of it. I think they just made up Shadmok. There's no link to it on.
Oh, it was at this point. I mean, again, Joe Bob was really carrying me through my viewing of this film.
Well, not only have I seen this for multiple times, I own it. Now, why did you see it on
like local cable or something? I had never even heard of it. I saw the, if I'm not mistaken,
yeah, you Google Shadmok. All that comes up is the story from Monster Club.
So they made up a monster. Uh, anyway, uh, what's the picture called?
Monster Club? Haas. That was my Christopher Lee impression.
If you need me, I'll be making Frankenstein go to the beach.
Yeah.
I did did anything. They threw at him. Yeah. I'm doing golf sluts for
in the music. Um, the, oh, wait, you asked me a question though. Oh, shit.
Wait, damn it, you said, oh, oh, why do I own it? If I'm not mistaken, I saw this. I,
I used to go to, when I lived in, um, uh, LA, my life was so void of any happiness ever.
You had me, you had me, Joe? I had you. Uh, it's, I would go to, I would go to,
Joe's going to be staying with you boy again, like we're, like we're bulky. Let's,
let's face it, bulky and Larry. Joe, who do I'm on living in my house for a week?
You're more of the Larry, I would say, right? For sure. Yeah. But and you're moving in post
divorce, like this is a sitcom, folks. Yeah. I'm living there for a week. Isn't that how the
other way started? While I'm there, I got a show right down there at the lyric. Oh boy,
end of your street. We're going to get all tuned up that night. You girls want to head up the hill
to my house. And then I can head up your hills. Um, maybe me and Joe, we go pick up some pigs
in the blankets. You know, we, we do, we do it up real nice. You got a couple hot cocos,
you girls cold? You guys cold? How you done? By the way, I want to say what's up to Bob Zany,
who is a cop comedian. And Bob Zany's thing was he would always say, baby,
really loud with a cigar. One of my favorite Bob Zany jokes was he would go, he would,
he would go, ah, my family's fat. I asked, I went to a restaurant or a pig's in a blanket.
They brought me a picture of my parents and bad baby. One liner's like that. I'm a big fan. Anyway,
he, I heard him in an interview, say he opened a McCarrie store and he's selling all these old
collectibles from his collection. Okay. Like old comic books and all the stuff he's collected
over the years. So I went on and I bought an old horror comic from him. And I DMed him. And I was
like, Bob, we met one time. We did Bob and Tom together. I don't know if you remember me. But
anyway, I heard about your McCarrie store. I just bought a horror comic from you. I'm looking
forward to reading it. And he, it was, I mean, talking about perfect. He just writes back, Joe,
thanks for the support, baby. And writes baby, capital B, capital A, capital Y,
dash, capital B, capital B, capital B, capital B. It really made me laugh. Anyway,
I would go to the record store that we loved. Amoeba vintage vinyl. Oh, we have vintage vinyl
sent Louis, sorry. Yeah. And then I would go upstairs. I've already forgotten it. That's how
shitty the new of dammit. It pisses me off, Joe. The new one is so bad, Joe. I would go,
I would go when you're out, when you're out in LA, that's the first place we're going to go.
Please, I'm going to ruin it. I'm going to ruin your day. By the way, Andrew Santino told me he
said that that Vermont is, he's like, dude, all of it is shut down. He's like, public house is gone,
the French place is gone. Like he said, all that stuff is gone. That's sad. Anyway,
I would, you asked why I own Monstro. I would go to Amoeba because it's so nothing to do with
nothing in mind to even buy by myself. I would just walk around. And then I would spend hours up in
that horror section and the DVD section upstairs. And I just saw it in there one day and I bought it
on blind. I saw the word anthology. And I'm a sucker for that. So I bought it. And I remember liking it
for its kichiness and funness or whatever. But upon a second or third viewing, I was like, okay,
this is the second story. See you at least three times. Oh, my God. The vampires is the second story.
Yeah, dumb. This is a comical tale about a family of vampires, the patriarch being Richard Johnson,
whose son, young son, discovers his father as a vampire. And he's in the vampires being
relentlessly. This is how Wikipedia describes it. Relentlessly, but ineptly hunted by a team of
bureaucratic undead killers, the B squad led by pink pickering played by Donald Plezans.
The hunters break into the house and stake the vampire father. So they're like the Van Helsing
bunch. But the tables are turned when the father bites pickering, meaning that pickering will now
have to be staked by his own assistance. A chase ensues and pickering is staked. After the men take
pickerings body away, the timid son of his mother who think the father is dead, return to the basement
to find, it's hard to read this to send. To find the father faked his death using a stake proof vest.
A stake proof vest. Paused to make a catch up. A filled with catch up.
Jesus Christ. I mean, like, honest, and I say this honestly, there are Scooby -Doo episodes with
tighter, better structured, better written stories, better executed kills, the whole night
embarrasing. A stake proof vest. Holy shit. All right. Then it's back for like a nine minute musical segment,
you know? Like, that's how weird this fucking movie is. And then they cut to Vincent Price like dancing
with 20 -year -old girls. That's real bad when Vincent Price is dancing to like a punk new wave band.
Oh, brutal, brutal. Last but not least. Definitely not the best, if this is the best of the three stories.
And it's still sadder than the sham dog. The third one is the one called the ghouls. And that's where
the movie director is trying to find like a new location versus horror movie. And he finds this old
abandoned town where these creepy residents reside. And then he finds out that the story of this town
is that these ghouls went there and made it with the humans and formed this new like sort of
ghoul human race. And now the people that live there want to feast on human flesh, but they've run
out of dead bodies in the graveyard to consume. And it's that's like a cool little horror story.
But the problem is with this one is because they clearly had no budget. They tell that entire
cool story as like somebody's telling the story. And they're showing like still paintings of the events.
So you don't even get to see any of that. And then the big twist is the guy finally escapes at the end.
He finds some cops. And then in an ending that mirrors nothing but trouble,
identically, he's brought back to the crazy town by the cops. So nothing but trouble lifted it's
ending from the ghouls segment of the Monster Club. It's the only story with any potential
and they blow it completely because they have no budget. A couple of cool ghouls in the mix.
For B &R, a couple of the ghouls were cool. And then the movie ends finally with John
Caridine saying, I love your club. I want to be a part of it and Vincent Price says, you already
are a member. And John Caridine says, well, how can I be a member in Vincent Price's because you're
the greatest monster of them all, a human being. And that's the end of the Monster Club.
My hog is not only down. It's going back inside of my body. It's retracting.
Yes. My hog is a dragon in the dirt, folks. I found nothing to enjoy about this, not for its camp
value. Honestly, what I enjoyed the most was probably a couple of those musical numbers,
which were painful to watch. But at least, you know, it was like a time capsule. I don't know.
And I kind of like the stripper song from B &R. I thought the stripper segment was cool.
The stripper Taran offer skin is cool. There was. That's why we said it was cool.
That's one nice thing I can say. But yeah, this one really sucked. Joe Bob didn't even help it
much because he was trying to defend it, but you can tell his heart wasn't even barely in it.
So that's where we're at. Thank you all for joining us.
Joseph, we're doing our show. What is the date again? September 10, I know. September 10.
Yeah, ticket link will be coming very soon, exclusive to the Helian's first,
which, you know, look, it'll probably sell out to the fans of the show completely before it gets
chance to go to anybody else, but, you know, just so you know, that's what's happening.
Very excited about that. So we will see that weekend for those lucky few who get the ticks.
All right, folks, that's our show. We'll be back with some more Flicks next month,
and until then, we'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.