Welcome to we'll see you in how it's the podcast you listen to when you want to hear that sweet
and sour movies. I'm Joe. Yeah. I should have let you start over. That was terrible. I'm Pat Walsh and I'm also appalled at Joe's intro. I'm Peter appalled and married folks.
No one ever made that. Is it even a joke? Like, what if my what if you were a stand up named Peter? Could you call your special Peter comma appalled and married? That's cool title and married.
It should be Peter would have to be married. But yeah, yeah. Is that what you're saying? Are you saying Mary Peter comma appalled and married? Like, yeah, sick. I got I got a lot of jokes about my fucking wife. How about this? Yeah.
Petered. Oh, that's good that you don't have to be named Peter. Yeah, Petered appalled and married.
You redeemed yourself that that's that's really good job.
I was thinking of a bit today, where you say to a guy, Hey, your wife told me she was going to get a tattoo on her boob. And I said, Why are you going to get a tattoo on your husband?
Good. Yeah, that's real good. Thank you. And then laughing joke. Yeah, yeah. And then then she'd hit him with a purse. Yeah. And then lastly, yesterday on taste buds. Sal said, you know, my exercise is routine. And I said, Sal, I've seen your routine. And it's exercise.
Hmm. And it's exercise. I don't Oh, it's exercise to sit through your routine. Yeah, yeah. I see. Okay. I thought that was really good. I just saw red when you mentioned Sal on our podcast. So maybe I didn't hear the punch.
I mentioned you on our on his podcast. That's fine. We've been the established, established podcast. Can you hear that? I hear that. And also you're freezing every 10 seconds. The audio is fine. But I keep seeing horrific freezes of your face contorting into demonic shapes. But the audio is good. The audio is fine. Yeah. I think it's because the fan is on. Let me shut the fan off. Hold on. Talk to the people I shut the fan off. Pretty tight ship over there. We're only going to have one
fan left when this podcast is over, folks. Don't shut off the only fan. Speaking of only fans, I'm masturbating. I'm pretty close to coming. But I think I'll edge instead you ever edge yourself, Joe? I've never done the edging.
You never once have like teased yourself treated yourself like a lady taking yourself to the market.
No, if I'm not going to do it for her, why should I do it for me? No, I don't know. I when I masturbate, it's, it's purely to exercise the demon. I got to get this out of me so I can think straight. I'm not sitting there having a sensual tie with myself.
It doesn't have to be sensual, but give yourself give yourself an edge. I'm picturing you laying back in a tub.
Yeah, with rose petals, much like American beauty. Also with a with a 45 year old man looking gazing down at me.
No, there's nothing wrong with edging. I actually when I was when I first learned about masturbation, which was, I mean, this is bad, but like three years before anything even came out
As I've said on the show, I started quick. Yeah, I had a lot of mojo, as Austin Powers says.
And I looked up masturbation and the first thing I saw was I didn't even have a computer. I had to look at like a boy's guide to growing up or something at the library.
And it said, make sure you don't or there's no need to rush it. People can often feel shame. That was helpful for me to hear as a as a Catholic boy. I always pictured Jesus watching me masturbate sitting at the foot of the bed.
That's the only way you could finish.
Burying his head in his hands in shame at the person I was becoming and coming folks, but the book said
It doesn't have to be a rush. Take your time. And then it went through things you could do. It was like caress your inner thighs, stroke your nipples. Now I don't do any of that shit. I'm just saying you can you can you can keep yourself from coming for like hours and make it feel amazing.
Book for young boys to read.
Yeah, at the library. That is what my parents gave me was like men and women sometimes kiss. It was like very tame. So I had to look up some actual information.
But yeah, little pictures and stuff too. Because I think honestly, the first I ever heard of it was in Needful Things when that teacher jacks off a 10 year old boy. What was Stephen King doing in the 80s and 90s cocaine, obviously, but
He had so many books were like a 10 year old kid was getting jacked off.
It's why I find it so funny that he's like the captain of like the woke ship. Now it's like, dude, you didn't have one book for two decades that didn't have a couple of n bombs in it.
Some kid jizzing on some fucking, you know, like it was ridiculous. It's like, buddy, relax, calm down. We've read the books.
Yeah, I picked up Joe once in my car and I had it set up to the worst sex scene in literature history, which is in Pet Sematary.
When his wife reaches into the bathtub and jacks him off with an oven mitt and he likes the rough feel of the oven mitt and it's read by Dexter, the guy who plays Dexter.
The so like a scene that was already like a ultimate boner killer read by the creepiest sounding man alive. Just, I mean, you get the feeling he's never had sex.
That Dexter's never had sex.
Oh, Dexter, I'm talking about Steve King. Yeah.
Uh, I would like to hear that scene read by
Will, what's his face? The saddest. Yeah, we've talked about Will Patton as the saddest voice that's ever existed.
Yeah, no, I mean, Michael C. Hall is, he was like, she oiled up the oven mitt and gripped his throbbing member.
Just awful to hear, awful to hear. And then you picture Stephen King hunched over a typewriter, clacking it out while drinking like an old Milwaukee. Just gross.
Tabitha waiting upstairs for him.
I'm listening now to Cujo read by Lorna Raver, the old lady from Drag Me to Hell, and I'm enjoying it quite a bit. I've never read Cujo, believe it or not.
The witch from Drag Me to Hell?
Yeah.
I don't know who reads it and does lots of cool voices and she's great.
She's great in that movie. She plays like that gypsy like witch, right?
Yeah, she's excellent in the movie. And then you look her up and it's like she hasn't done much of anything else. I mean, it's kind of sad, but I love her in that movie. That's a great movie to me. I like it to me.
I like it. It's got its problems, but I enjoy it. I don't think it's a benchmark. But we said that last week when we talked about.
We also talked about benchmarks when you get up from your chair and leave it here, we talked about a malignant and you said that it was a worse drag me to hell. And I was saying, yeah, I don't think it's good if you're the starting point is drag me to hell, you know.
Look, I mean, lesser evil dead, you know.
It is, but I love it.
I love fun. The CGI is a great hindrance in that movie.
And it's not needed. And I don't understand why he did so much of it in that film.
Especially the guy who on a budget of $10 can make things look fucking awesome. Yeah, it's CGI is often a hindrance for these people.
Speaking of budgets of $10. Yeah, I'm not going to waste movie corner time talking about this, but I'm now well into season three of creep show.
Oh, I'm not doing it.
I don't blame you.
I'm now at a point where I'm angry.
I'm angry at my favorite movie franchise of all time. This show.
Sucks like if you like I've said before, you could cobble together about four of the stories and it would be a passable third entry into the into the series.
Good enough for me, I guess, but like.
Now the amount of volume that they have. Yeah. And the fact that that number has not gone up.
It's just terrible. It's terrible.
Every episode, as soon as I see Nick Cotero's name underwriting or directing for the episode, I'm like, this is going to be terrible.
Yeah, he did one good episode, which was gray matter, which was the very first story. And I'm absolutely convinced that he because it was his first outing as a director on the series.
That it was really directed by the DP because it looks much better and has much more style than anything else he's doing on the show.
Or maybe he got lucky with the first one and put more effort into it and just doesn't apply the same. I don't know what it is, man, but.
I got a little more money for the first one a little more time. I mean, I, you don't want to sympathize too much because people do amazing work on a low budget, but I feel like shutter.
Has too low a budgets on their projects there. They look bad almost across the board. Their original stuff looks bad. I don't think. See, I don't think they have too low a budgets. I think they're not monitoring how the budgets are being spent.
That's what I think, because in the so I had a meeting once with the guy from shutter.
Frank shutter is his name.
Anyway, but he and I said, I sent him a bunch of my material and I said, you know, I'd love to was when creep show was about to come out or maybe the first season had dropped.
I said, look, man, you know, I don't really do the writers rooms too frequently anymore, but I've always wanted to write for horror. So like.
Would love if you'd take a look at these scripts and maybe I could if you're ever looking for somebody for creep show or whatever. And he was like, well, we don't have writers rooms on any of our shows.
That's not how we we do it here. He was like, we, we just have, we have the show runner and then they parcel out the work to the people that and it's that's what I mean about, like, I don't think any of this is being monitored. And here's why I really feel strongly about that.
The there was an episode this season.
That
The first story was about it was episode two. The first story was about a collector of horror memorabilia and the second story was about a guy being haunted by a demon.
The second story was actually pretty good, but it was ruined by the fact that the demon looked like a man in a rubber suit and it looked fucking terrible. Yeah.
And what pissed me off about that was the first story, which absolutely sucked.
Featured a full stop motion skeleton sword fight like like Army of Darkness style. Yeah.
And I'm like, you guys spent fucking money on that.
And not on making this fucking demon thing look, it is it's astounding to me that Greg Nicotero, a guy that has worked his entire life in special effects, doesn't understand that if you don't wet the suit and make it look slimy, it looks fucking fake.
Yeah, that's like monster 101 shit, dude, like have shit dripping off of it. That's what makes it kind of look a little more real.
Yeah, it's a quick circle jerk before you call out.
Yeah, but two episodes now they've had a guy in a rubber suit playing a monster and it looks painfully fake.
Like it's so crazy if I'm wrong doing couldn't you just put an x ray filter over the camera and had two people fight and then you just show their skeletons fighting.
Well, no, because because the well, I guess you could. Are you joking? Is that a real thing? Although I wonder, it might work. But I may have joking. Yes.
Yeah, I mean, it's like this this whole first episode was our first story in this episode I'm talking about was like was like, this like big tribute to horror history. Yeah, it's like, guys, who gives a fuck about any of this?
I'm not here for fucking fan service. I'm here for you to make cool horror stories that feel like they'd be in the vein of a trilogy of movies I really love. And yeah, out of 20, whatever the fuck 30, whatever the fuck stories, you've managed to do that four times.
And like, eek bye with four story. I'm not even talking about like you had four grand slams.
Yeah, I'd say less the I don't know, I couldn't get into it because of the cheapness. I couldn't help but think with a title as big as creep show. Why not bump this up to AMC AMC and shutter are the same family. You got walking dead a massive horror hit, like, just put a little more money into it and put it on AMC in my opinion.
I think they've got enough money. They don't have the right people fucking calling the shots. They're getting legitimate talent in this thing. It's like, this is not a budget issue. This is a you don't know what the fuck you're doing issue. And unfortunately, it's a big enough title that I guess it's carrying well enough in the ratings that they that it's going to keep going.
But here's my question. Why the fuck isn't Tom Savini involved in this? That's a red flag to me. Tom Savini was involved with Tales from the Dark Side, the movie and both creep shows. So was Romero Romero obviously is not with us anymore. So he can't be involved. And Stephen King has sort of been involved because they adapted one of his stories, but he hasn't written anything.
Joe Hill does a bunch of them, right?
They adapt Joe Hill stories when they've done such a poor job that I'm starting to be like, is Joe Hill a bad writer? Like, like, or do they just not know how to adapt his stories? Yeah. It's just terrible, man. I'm so angry about it. This is how now I get how people felt about the Star Wars prequels, because I liked them. And people would yell at me. Now I get it. I understand now how you felt.
Yeah. Yeah, I watched the latest Joe Bob. I mean, it's, they're getting better guests or bigger guests, I should say. They had David Gordon Green and you're your boy, Jason Bloom. I think they had some really fascinating stuff to say about the movie industry and how they work.
I think that's interesting. But I think you couldn't find a greater antithesis of Joe Bob Briggs than Jason Blum. Like, I just don't. I think he Jason Blum to me is everything. Everything Joe Bob has ranted about, like, you can't make a movie and not show boobs in the shower. You know, like everything he screams about that's wrong with current horror is to me everything Jason Blum promotes.
I hear you. But compared to Hollywood at large, I feel like, you know, he's he's a bit of a renegade. I mean, Joe Bob was calling him the next Roger Corman, which I don't think is accurate.
What? Yeah.
What what he was explaining is that, you know, Joe Bob was like, since you guys do your movies, for the most part for 5 million bucks, why do all these big stars come to you? You know, what what what makes you
a destination for actors? And he said that he pays people off the gross that you find like on variety or on the internet. He says if a movie grosses $100 million, there's a bonus structure in place.
And when the company started, he used to take a picture of himself dropping a check in a FedEx envelope 50k. But basically every
every once it makes $50 million, there's a new structure where every 10 million you make like a $50 ,000 bonus and they pay it and they don't go off weird, shady accounting like how Lord of the Rings pretended they didn't make any money off the franchise.
They go off the box office gross, which is a cool system. And that's why people come to them. And then he said,
it's just it's just very appreciated by everyone. It's all on the up and up. It's above board. And then they return because the sequels make even more money. So I think the actors wind up getting rich off it. He keeps the budgets low. I guess in that way, he's Corman esque, but the budgets are way, way bigger, for sure.
It was an interesting guy. And he said, you know, if you if you do a movie on Netflix, now you do it. This is what everybody's suing over. Now you make a movie, you get paid once, you might make more than you'd make it Blumhouse, but you never get another dollar. So if a movie is like that Sandy Bullock picture, whatever that was rat race, what was that called the one where the bird box or bird box, bird box gets seen by, you know, 100 million people, the guy who wrote the movie, the guy who wrote the movie, the guy who
wrote that makes the same money, essentially, as the guy who or gal who wrote the movie that they bury that nobody watches on Netflix, they get an upfront fee. And that's it. That's fucked up. It really is. So
that is fucked up. Netflix is fucked up. But, you know, yeah, the it's not. I just think I appreciate Blum's intuitiveness and approach. Yeah. And, you know, that that he made it to where he is through a sort of rogue method. Yeah. But I appreciate it the way I appreciate Tyler Perry. I mean, at the end of the day, it's an absolute terror.
Terrible product. I'm sorry. It just is. And with Blum. Yeah, I like some of what Blum does. All right. Well, aside from get out and lash whiplash. They've made some good movies for God's sake. What is the B and then the bonnet? It's like Jason Blum fucked your girlfriend or something. It's come on, man. Some of the worst movies we've ever discussed on this podcast, we're
Blumhouse movie. They make a bad movie. All right. They make a bad movie. It's it's it's they don't make a good movie. You think this Halloween kills is going to be any good? The early reviews are abysmal. Yeah, I mean, that first one wasn't great. The new one, what it has me intrigued is that it's supposed to be just a kill fest like hundreds of people killed, which I'm intrigued by. Did you hear that firemen are something firemen are suing because firemen are killed in this movie?
It's just what's going on again. You ever see backdraft again? It's well, that's just absurd that the firemen suing thing is stupid. I don't know if that's true or not, but it is. It's stupid.
But again, it's it's it's we've talked about it ad nauseam. This Halloween kills sequel is everything that everybody condemned the Halloween franchise for for all these years.
And here comes these guys to the rescue. We're going to reboot and restore and reframe the franchise. And it's worse than anything they've done preceding this.
It just is. It just sucks. It's got no point. It's got no plot. It's got no believability. It's just a kill fest. That's what the last one was. That's what this one will be.
How about we give it a chance? We will. We'll review it. But I get it. Every I think I'm actually going to see it tonight. Matter of fact, every early review, by the way, is saying exactly what our assumption is that it's just like.
It's pointless. It's gratuitous. So I'll give it a chance. We're going to review it. But anyway, I'll say this about a positive, another positive, blah, blah. I think what he does is he allows
artists to do what they want to do, which is cool. Sometimes it works. Get out. Yeah, sometimes it doesn't work us.
You know, so it's like, OK, sometimes it's great. Sometimes it's not. He kind of stays out of their way, which I think is cool.
Yeah, he actually said he never gives notes, which is odd.
It's obvious.
Yeah, so look, he does some cool stuff. I just wish I liked what he did more. And I wish there wasn't such an agenda with every movie he does now where, you know,
you know, after get out, it was we have to make a commentary at all times. And it's like to the point of bad writing. Right. You know, but but what are you going to do?
Yeah, Ghostbusters is also not getting great reviews.
It's got 87 percent. We talk about it's getting fantastic reviews.
I've read nothing but bad. I mean, I'm on Twitter. So that's where I was.
Oh, yeah. Oh, really? The Twitter mom is going to hate on this new Ghostbusters.
It is retribution for the last Ghostbusters.
But I follow a lot of film critics. I mean, I'm not talking about just your average Joe as people just didn't like the movie. I don't know what the time.
I've seen I told you the bad reviews I saw were like, it's too much of a sequel. Yeah. OK.
But I've seen some glowing reviews that it said that like Jason Reitman managed to bring in a new cast that you care about.
Yeah. Also giving you the nostalgia kick that you want.
This is going to the they're they're raving about this young girl that's in it.
Everybody's saying she steals the show and she's fantastic.
OK, I'm excited.
Ivan Reitman said something that made me so excited recently.
He said to see Bill Murray back on set as Peter Venkman and doing Peter Venkman.
Yeah, he was like it.
It was so exciting because he was like, we just haven't seen that Bill Murray in a long time.
And I got like chills. I was like, he's right.
When was the last time we saw just like funny fucking like stripes?
Prick smart ass Bill Murray.
It's been forever. Like, I'm very excited about that.
You see what is I mean, Rotten Tomatoes says 81 percent or 87 or something.
You're right. It's an 81 percent.
The first two reviews of it are not both refer to it as a lifeless corpse.
So that's not great, but yeah, you're right.
Eighty one percent. So people are liking it more than I thought.
All right. Why me? Stinking corpse of a sequel, says the Guardian.
Well, you know, leave it to the Brits.
Yeah. They spilled tea on the review before they turned it in.
Yeah, I I also want to watch this scream trailer.
I think between episodes, you and I should watch it so we have an opinion on it.
But that comes out in January.
I haven't watched it. I already have an opinion on it.
Well, that's your problem, Joe. I don't have a problem.
What else can they wring out of this goddamn franchise?
I mean, I don't know.
And having the cast back seems kind of absurd to me.
It's like my friends work on head of the class or they work in head of the class.
So I'm not saying anything negative, but the on on on while being recorded.
Yeah, I watched the trailer for the head of the class reboot or they showed a scene.
It was a two minute laughless scene.
And they were showcasing the return of Robin Givens
as one of the kids moms.
And I was like, I don't even remember Robin Givens being in head of the class.
And I've seen every episode.
She's on the first few seasons and then she married Mike Tyson.
They have her come out and you hear the fake audience
applause for Robin Givens.
And it's like, oh, boy, like it's it just shows you that
TV executives don't know what people want.
I mean, to think that anyone is clamoring to know what Robin Givens is.
She looked fantastic. I'll say that.
But we're running out of nostalgia when you're dusting off David Arquette.
Yeah, it's a big, you know, I mean, guys, it's one thing to bring back.
I'm happy about like Mark Hamill's resurgence.
And I know that, you know, he certainly didn't have the Harrison Ford type career.
Not that he had a bad career or has a bad career, but no,
I get it. Like Mark Hamill did some some real doozy movies.
And I think a lot of us were thinking we might never see him on this big screen again.
But he came back and reprised
an iconic character in cinema for all of the of the ages.
So it's awesome. And you're happy.
Whatever. Nothing against David Arquette.
But I mean, for Christ's sakes, you know, let's bring back
Jamie Kennedy while we're at it, you know what I mean?
Like, does anybody make an appearance?
I think he's dead. Not in real life.
I mean, in the movies, dead.
Yeah. Oh, you're right. You're right.
He's the one that was like the expert on horror movies. Right. Yeah.
Liver alone.
Still a good job.
Lillard liver alone.
That's in the first one.
Matthew Lillard goes liver alone.
Like liver, it's some it's a bad pun.
I wrote a song and recorded a song with a band I was in years ago
called Bernie, Bernie Head Flap.
And I wrote a song that we recorded called Liver Let Die about an alcoholic.
And I thought that was a very good play on words.
Was it a full on Weird Al style parody?
It was. Yeah.
You can dare to have a drink.
I had Fred from the B -52s come in.
Liver Let Die.
Oh, I didn't even realize I forgot there's a song.
I was thinking of James Bond.
I was I forgot there's the Paul McCartney song Liver Let Die.
Yeah. Then the is is that cover by Faith No More?
No, the guns and roses.
Oh, you're right. Sorry.
You're a big single.
They use that to great effect in Gross Point Blank
for like this the 7 -Eleven that replaces his childhood home.
He walks in there and there's like a big shootout to Live and Let Die.
I mean, guns and roses.
There's a band.
I mean, Appetite for Destruction.
I own an original copy on vinyl front to back.
I mean, it's. It's a fucking masterpiece.
Yeah, that's great.
And then G &R is like, I know what we should do.
Let's do meatloaf style songs on the next rep.
Wow. I like them all.
I mean, look, November Rain to me is probably their their best song.
I know that's going to make a slap you in the face.
You November Rain is a is a masterwork and I love it.
I love the the ending.
But then again, I wasn't you know, I didn't have to watch the fucking
music video 800 times as a kid.
You know, a lot of people have probably different opinions about it.
The second Axl sat down at a piano.
I was like, oh, fuck off, guys.
Like I like some of the usual illusion songs, but.
I did not. I was not a fan of that stuff.
But hey, they obviously made the right move.
Those are considered iconic albums, but.
Oh, just terrible.
It's always a baby.
I mean, I got to find out about David.
Yeah, it's those that leave the exact lyrics.
They were great live, surprisingly great live.
I got to say all that said, I never want to see him again.
Once was enough. I mean, Axl's not in his prime, but they sounded good.
I never went. What can you do?
Nothing.
All right. Should we get to the movie corner, Joseph?
Yeah, let's do it. All right.
I also wanted to say I.
I saw your criticisms, listeners of my solo movie corner.
What were they generally?
Well, generally, I listened to it a hundred times before putting it out,
making sure it's all OK and et cetera.
And this time I recorded it like an hour before midnight at the end of the month,
because I forgot that it was the end of the month
and I didn't have time to listen to it.
And there's a section you all described it in an amusing and accurate way.
It sounds like I'm being kidnapped.
I don't know what happened to the audio,
but it sounds like I'm recording while rolling around inside a trunk of a car.
And I apologize.
But by and large, I thought it sounded fine.
I'm recording you an extra special long one this month,
which will feature all the Daniel Craig bonds.
It will feature a discussion of venom.
Let there be carnage.
It will feature lots of big talk.
So get ready for that.
I got to make it up to you.
The movie corn.
I've seen quite a bit.
I'm going to leave off the ones I'm doing on the other one, but I watched.
Let's let's go with.
The guilty starring Jake Gyllenhaal, it's new to Netflix.
It's one of these basically one character thing, and the rest is like a radio play.
Jake Gyllenhaal plays a cop who is sort of demoted to working the
call in line, the 911 call in line.
And he receives an emergency phone call from a kidnapped woman.
Then the rest of the movie, which thankfully is a tight 90 minutes,
is basically Jake Gyllenhaal talking on the phone.
So in that way, it kind of feels like no problem.
So, yeah, it's not to cut you off, but it's funny you mentioned this movie.
I was at a bar last night and there was a girl there screaming at me
about how much she hated this movie, like screaming at me was hurt.
Well, was her issue that it was a portrayed women poorly or did
you just think that it sucked?
She thought that it was a homogenized version of the original film.
Yeah.
And that it was, it's everything wrong with American cinema and why we
can't do anything right here.
Yeah.
Which she's right in many ways.
But I mean, it was shot, I read up, it was shot in 11 days with the
director, had a COVID exposure and was in like a different building,
directing the film.
And it feels like that.
It just feels like Jake Gyllenhaal doing almost like an improvised play.
There's some fun voices that call in.
It almost reminded me of listening to the calls on Frasier, like your
boy, Bill Burr, you know, they get a lot of people with like good
distinguishable voices, but it's basically Gyllenhaal spends the entire
movie with his arms behind his head to show off his massive biceps and
just talking on the phone.
And it's dull.
I didn't see the original movie that it's based on, but it's just, there's
no suspense to it and the twist is stupid and it's just not a good movie.
You know, I, I, your friend who screamed that she was right.
I don't know why she needed to scream, but I agree with her.
It's not, she was, she was a lot.
She was a nice girl, but she was a lot.
And, uh, to, to a point where everybody was like, what is with this lady?
Just screaming.
She slammed down her glass at one point.
It started because we talked about my first entry in today's movie
corner, a terrible film called the many saints of Newark, uh, that I thought
was decent when I was watching it.
And the more I thought about it, the more I was like, this movie sucks.
Uh, well, everybody hates it.
I told Joe, please don't watch this movie if you haven't watched the
Sopranos and then sure enough, Joe's reading up, he's, he's like, Oh, you
know, he's found out about things that happen like in the second to last
episode of the show.
It's just, I gotta let it go.
He's never going to watch the day.
It's a prequel.
So you don't need to see the Sopranos.
Prequels say you would say somebody watching the star Wars prequels
doesn't necessarily need to.
Absolutely.
That's one of the major criticisms about them is that they don't
stand enough on their own, which I agree with.
You wouldn't say your enjoyment would be multiplied by a thousand having
seen the other movies in the, in the franchise as obviously if you're a fan.
Sure.
But like my nephew, for instance, saw the prequels first and loved
star Wars as much as anybody.
So it's, you know, and he's now 22 or whatever.
So it's like, you know, I don't think there's a, a must to that, but yeah,
obviously there's value in that concept.
That's good.
Did you hear the siren outside?
Yeah, I do, Joe.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
Can anything just be fine today?
We've paused and restarted eight fucking times.
The cop has to do that obnoxious whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Like they probably have somebody pulled over and are still just making
the noise because they like this Christ.
Anyway, he's still doing it.
Anyway, LA is lawless now.
I haven't seen a cop in six months.
I think they're all just like, let them, let them die and playing
board games at the station.
Um, the, uh, so this movie, spoilers, you're going to hear spoilers.
I just have to well acted, beautifully directed, not well written.
Why is it not well written?
I, because it was written by David chase.
David chase, as I said last night is a guy who thinks he's Fellini.
Making Scorsese movies or Scorsese type content.
This thing's got an imaginary twin uncle in it, which is absurd,
which is fucking absurd.
Uh, Ray Liotta at a dual role.
Twins exist.
Yeah.
And made up.
Yeah, no, but Ray Liotta, the most indistinguishable man of all time,
the most incapable actor of playing anything but Ray Liotta.
He can't do anything but Ray Liotta.
And I love when he does Ray Liotta.
Don't get me wrong, but it's literally like Woody Allen.
It's like, and, and then so, so, so Ray Liotta's character is murdered.
And then Dickie starts to go visit his dad's brother in jail that you
have no backstory about, you have no idea of what's going on and who walks
in, but Ray Liotta as a twin brother.
It is never explained.
There's never a line where Dickie says, my God, you look just like him or nothing.
You're just supposed to accept it face value.
These guys were identical twins.
So you go, okay, fine.
They're identical twins.
That's a little confusing.
And then much later in the movie, Dickie goes into a deep fantasy and looks up
and he's sitting alone in the prison, which insinuates this uncle didn't exist.
This was all in his head.
This was a version of his father.
He wanted to have that he didn't have or whatever.
There's that stupid moment at the end where they lock pinkies from the coffin,
which makes no fucking sense whatsoever.
Uh, I know it's metaphoric, but it wasn't real, Joe.
I know it wasn't real, but it makes no sense.
There is nothing in this to make you think that this is the birth of Tony
If anything, you'd walk away from it, going, this kid doesn't go into the life
after this, like it ends with him furious at his uncle and saying, I want no part
of any of this, and then you think that's going to kind of be the end.
And, but then in the last, in the last moment, they play the theme from the
Sopranos, so you're supposed to be like, here we go.
Tony is Tony.
And it's like, it's not at all.
It's a bad movie.
And there's an entire B plot about civil rights and racial tensions in New
York at that time, which was happening, which I do think is interesting that
they incorporated that they do nothing with, they do nothing with it.
The guy says, we're going to start, we're going to compete against the Italians.
We're going to start the black mob.
And they show none of it.
You just see him at the end with money moving into a white neighborhood and
you're supposed to be like, oh, he did it.
I guess.
Okay.
Cool.
Terrible film, just a terrible, terrible, when they're on the phone and he goes
to like it the first time I talked to you.
So this is an interesting, like I said, I had to think about it for a little while.
When the, you know, so David, it's very hard to hear any discussion of
Sopranos from somebody who dismisses it and doesn't watch it and, and hasn't
seen the greatest television show ever made.
It's I can't really engage it.
Although I had issues with the movie myself.
I have attempted to watch the show repeatedly.
I have repeatedly said, I think it's a bad show and I will refer back to what
most people say, uh, that were fans of the show, the first few seasons were
amazing and they lost their way in the middle there, the end of the series was
terrible and this movie, who were you talking to meatheads?
Everybody I know that ever liked the Sopranos says it loses its way in the
middle when it gets into the whole thing about like they they're going to make a
movie and all this shit and the Hollywood, like the comedic Hollywood plot line
comes into it, uh, uh, Tony hallucinating, which I've made fun of
endlessly on this fucking podcast.
Everybody says the finale is terrible.
Nobody likes the finale and you might like it, but you also like the
Seinfeld finale, which is the worst episode of Seinfeld.
I think people have come around on the finale of Sopranos and anyone with half
a brain loves where the Sopranos goes.
It's setting the groundwork for where TV would go for the next 20, 25 years.
It takes a bunch of chances.
There were idiots who were like, nobody got whacked this week, but I don't mean
that, but it's, it's, it's again, David, you gotta watch it.
You gotta, it's a bad show.
The line right at the top that would Chris glam show of all time.
Oh, what does that most, I'm telling you it's the best show I've ever seen.
And I've watched a ton of, I know a lot of shows you've seen, and I think
you're wrong, but listen, you have a soft spot for it.
That's fine.
But I'll say what I said last night, married, married with favorite married
with children, married with children was considered groundbreaking and innovative.
You watch it now.
You're like, there's some funny episodes.
It's not a good show.
It's just was a thing that happened at the time.
That was very different.
I think that's what the Sopranos is and you're wrong.
You're just wrong.
It's not, it's not even a pilot is directed like a film school short.
It's the pilot is the worst episode of the show.
As I told you, although it's still good.
It's a great pilot anyway.
Well, okay.
So then explain to me then, then justify the terrible writing in this movie.
Please talk about the movie.
I mean, to diminish David Chase again, perhaps the best television
writer of all time and of all time.
Of all time.
Yes.
You enjoy luck.
He didn't do luck.
As he did luck.
That was his father.
Anything since the Sopranos.
No, he didn't.
That's that is not him.
Hold on.
I'm going to look it up.
That's the guy who did Deadwood.
David Milch, David Milch.
Oh yeah.
I didn't name him.
That's his name.
I know it's funny.
It's a funny name.
I can't have fun with his name.
The it's just, I mean the, the, the sweeping, everybody hated the Sopranos
after the first couple of seasons is just so dumb, but anyway, the movie.
I'm listening.
Twin subplot either.
I thought Leota gave completely different and great performances.
I thought he was excellent as the kind of softer, he lost like 30 pounds.
So he looked a little bit different.
He had gray hair, whatever.
To me, the one, the first guy was Leota and Goodfellas grown up and kind of,
you know, turned nasty.
And the other one was like a sweet older guy who was very intelligent.
I thought they did a great job of separating them.
And I thought Leota did a great job of playing them and we'll probably be
talked about for Academy award consideration.
Oh, you are insane.
This year, who's better, Joe, who you are insane Academy award.
Because they put them up for supporting actor.
I think he could get talked about for playing the dual role.
I thought it was not a dual role.
It's it's Ray Leota in both roles in one it's screaming Ray Leota and
it's one talking Ray Leota.
That's the only difference.
I thought there was a lot of differences.
And I'd love to hear who your five choices for best twin brother.
I like jazz.
I'm different than the other guy that like spaghetti.
Give me a break with this.
I thought there were very different and excellent performances by Leota.
I would say Dickie's got a chance of the of the nom.
He's really good.
But it's just, it's just a well, what do you make of the fat, the imaginary
uncles, it was come on it.
Look, there's big problems with this movie.
I think, I think a lot of people went in.
I mean, David Chase likes to subvert expectations.
The, the birth of Tony Soprano, I think was used in the marketing.
But I don't know that that was his intent.
I mean, I found it baffling that Tony and his mom, I thought Vera
Formaga was excellent as Tony's mom.
All she was good, better than the lady who played her in the
show, actually in flashbacks.
But that is such a small part of this movie.
And it's mostly Tony trying to get his depressed mom on antidepressants.
I thought that story was great.
But again, what is this movie about?
I, what is this movie about?
I agree.
The Newark riot stuff.
Uh, you know, that's not Chase's Forte.
I get that.
I mean, they're kind of pretending that the Sopranos wasn't just as
wide a show as Seinfeld.
There were almost no black characters of note on the Sopranos.
And these characters all prove themselves time and time again, to be
racist if when Tony's daughter dated a black guy, he was furious about it.
But yeah, that is what absurd, by the way, what absurd, uh, racial slur
that nobody says, did they, did they write in to the, to that thing?
I love at the beginning of the many states when Christopher goes,
nobody made more scuttle.
Oh, nobody talks like this.
The Christopher narration was awful.
I almost was like, I'm not going to watch this and let it ruin my
opinion of the show when the narration in the graveyard started.
I'll grant you.
Actually, the narration was kind of cool.
I just thought it was not well executed.
They use a ton of, of, uh, and words on Sopranos.
They don't make stuff up, but it's like, um, that I think they were trying to
sort of make peace with the fact that it was never a diverse show by doing this.
Uh, Newark riot stuff.
They do mention the Newark riots on the show a couple of times, but
it doesn't make sense here.
You're, you're always just kind of being thrown from story to story without real
cause it lasts exactly two hours, which makes me think there was probably a four
hour version that they tried to whittle down.
Um, but what I, what the one main criticism I see and agree with is that
this should have been a mini series.
I don't think you would have watched it if that's the case, but I think it
should have been chase coming back to do a prequel series, you know, like his
version of, of boardwalk empire or whatever.
Uh, it's, it's an overstuffed movie.
I liked parts of it, but as a whole, I didn't, I didn't love the movie.
I thought that Leota stuff was great and I would've liked to see it as its own
thing.
I thought the Navola stuff was great.
Would have watched it as its own thing.
I liked the stuff with him and his mistress and his wife and all that.
Um, but yeah, it was a little on the nose, a little clunky, uh, the Tony and
his mom stuff I loved, but it was like not enough of the movie.
I thought the ending was corny with a song coming in.
Yeah, dumb.
Well, um, it was, I thought the portrayal of Tony was odd.
It didn't have any footing in one scene.
He was the sweetest kid in the world.
And another scene, he was an absolute fucking maniac.
It never got into why he might be like that.
They, they didn't even tie a parallel between his mother's mental illness and
his apparent, you know, mental instability or anything like that.
This is why I say I take issue with David Chase is the greatest TV writer of
all time, the greatest TV writer.
Then you could say movie.
Would you say, all right, but would you say that about Larry David?
It's like, you know, like Larry David wrote many episodes of one of the greatest
shows of all time.
Do I think that makes Larry David the greatest TV writer of all time?
I think that's, I think, I think Norman Lear is the greatest TV writer of all
time because he's, but I'm saying you have to consistently prove yourself over
and over and over.
I think if you make a show that goes 10 years, that changes the face of television
forever, that changes every show that followed it owes a debt to it.
Uh, and that is funnier than most comedies, better drama than most, or all
dramas, I would say, um, I think it's the best series in the history of television.
But that's a very TV writer, but, but those, those are two different things.
I think this is an interesting nuance, uh, discussion, uh, or discussion
about nuance, excuse me.
You could say, I think star Wars is the greatest movie of all time because it
broke all boundaries and reset the way we look at cinnamon, all these things.
But I think that's a very different statement from George Lucas is the
greatest movie maker of all time.
Those are two different things.
So I just think if you haven't seen all of David Chase's work, which there
is a lot proceeding to the Sopranos, he's written many screenplays.
Yeah, he did Rockford files and all these shows.
You know, I haven't seen them.
I'm saying you do the Sopranos in my opinion, you're the best
TV writer of all time.
I don't think you have to do a bunch of different kinds of shows or anything else.
I think if you wrote the best show of all time, you're the
best TV writer of all time.
So if he wrote another show that you thought completely sucked, you would still
say he's still the greatest TV writer of all time.
That's my question.
Hard to say.
It would have to really suck, you know, to, to, to bring it down.
I mean, he, he had an achievement that to me, you know, the show I'd put beneath
it, Breaking Bad, The Wire, Seinfeld, whatever it's hard to compare comedy and
drama, but I think Sopranos tower was above the mall.
I do.
And, uh, you know, you got some bug in your ass about it.
I'm not going to change that.
You've, you've effectively spoiled major plot points for yourself by watching
this movie and reading about it.
What major plot points?
It's a prequel.
But, but there, there's, there's, you know, Joe, I don't know.
I'm, I'm in a, I am in a prequel series.
You talk to me about Christopher crying when he was handed to Tony or whatever,
like, you know, what, what becomes of Chris, Christopher tells you at the
beginning, what happened to him?
It's his narration and it's terrible writing.
That's like the third to last episode of the Sopranos.
By the way, they put that in the trailer.
That's in the trailer for Christ sakes.
Well, I think they assume that everyone in the world has seen the show that you
talk all the time about how much you hate it when you haven't watched it.
I've watched a lot of the entirety of this.
I've watched a lot of it.
I'm sorry that I won't an entire watch an entirety of a series that
I don't think is very good.
I don't think it's well -written.
I think it's a cliche take on mobster life.
I think it's cartoonish.
And I also think, and I will say this part of the reason you're so
fascinated by it is because you grew up nowhere near any of this stuff.
And I grew up around guys like this and that's not the way they act and
not the way they talk.
I'm sorry.
It's just not.
All right.
I didn't realize you were Scarface Joe.
I didn't say that.
I said, I grew up around people that were, that were in this, they were,
they were in this world.
I'll leave it at that.
And I, I had some firsthand experience with seeing the way guys like this
walked and talked it.
Let me, let me just say that much.
And this to me was cartoonish and it was only made more cartoonish by
every stupid commercial they did.
And I just thought it was corny.
I think it, like I said, I think it's a guy that wants to make art house
film art house films doing commercials.
What'd they do?
You don't remember the Pauley walnuts, like tide commercials and shit like that.
Oh no, I don't remember the slew of shit.
What does that have to do with the show?
I think because in every one of those commercials, it was big pussy or whoever
being like, I ain't no wise guy when it comes to my laundry and it just made
it even more tight commercial, but it made it even more cartoonish.
Show me deserve the Sopranos.
You don't deserve these watch perfect strangers for the fourth time.
That's more your level.
You don't deserve the Sopranos.
Anyway, chase, I see what you're saying.
It, I got you.
You love the Sopranos.
I don't, we're never going to see eye to eye.
Uh, we, we talked about that way too much.
That was basically a full review of many saints of Newark.
We've actually had full reviews that have gone shorter than that.
So let's move to our movie at hand.
The Halloween classic question mark trick or treat spelled like toys are us.
Uh, this is a horror anthology.
It is kind of a cult favorite.
Now I hear a lot of people talk about this as being their, their big Halloween viewing.
They watch it every year at Halloween.
Uh, and I get why it's really fun.
I think it's it, while it's not surpassing creep show, I do think it
is in the same spirit.
It did not get a theatrical release.
Warner brothers didn't like it.
There's lots of rumors as to why, you know, Brian Singer was a producer
and they hated his Superman returns, which lost them a bunch of money.
They're talking about maybe that's why it got buried.
Who knows, but it really found its audience and, uh, it's great because it's,
it's an anthology, but it's also done in an, in an interesting way where all the
stories intersect with each other, kind of like pulled fiction.
It's also like, you don't know what order the stories are in until the very end,
which is a very cool thing.
You see stuff happening in the background of one story that's
happening in another story.
And that's all really cool.
The acting is great.
You got Brian Cox from succession as an old coot.
It's a great part.
It's just really well written.
They took more time to make this something special as opposed to just three
stories and like, you know, some guy in a chair telling you, here's the next story.
The framing device is actually a big part of the fun.
I'm a fan of trick or treat.
They, yeah, they took it a step further than for instance, shutter did with
Halloween adventure doll to usher in the stories each week on creep show.
The, uh, yeah, it's pulp fictiony.
Um, I, I'm a big fan of this movie.
I like tend to like it a little bit more every time I watch it.
Uh, when I first saw it, I years, I bought this on day one, DVD
release on blind, cause this is back when there was no, it came out when
there was no streaming yet.
And, uh, I was so curious.
I don't even think you could rent stuff back then digitally.
I think it was all like, it was either on DVD or it played in the
theater and that was kind of it.
Um, so I bought this day one for like DVDs back then were what?
$25 or whatever.
Um, cause I had heard so much about it and I was so excited about it.
Uh, and I watched it and I really liked it, but I was, I was, I think I had built
it up a little too much in my mind.
And in subsequent watches, I've had the chance to appreciate its smaller points
and, uh, smaller details rather even more.
And this last viewing that I did for, for our Halloween and our review, that
was the most I've ever liked the movie ever, because it really is just very,
very, very well put together and they don't give away every story.
Starts in one place and then ends up someplace else.
They're very good at misleading you to which way the story is going to go.
And I think, especially with the one about the four women, where the
setup is you think that it's, they're going to party and the, the, the sister
played by Anna Paquin is going to like lose her virginity, right?
Uh, and then you realize it's not that it's that they're werewolves and she's
going to kill a man for the first time, basically, um, as a were, as a she wolf.
And they just do a really great job of, of playing that out and, and using
virginity as a metaphor for being a werewolf and everything.
They do that also very well in the, what's the guy's name?
The, the guy from, uh,
well, it was Dylan Baker who's the guy from happiness in arguably the most
disturbing subplot of movie history where he is molesting his son and the son is
like jealous or he's not molesting his son and the son gets jealous.
Uh, he's playing kind of a similar thing here.
He has the kid from bad Santa, uh, who he feeds this chocolate, which he laces
with arsenic, the kid pukes, which is this great kind of gross way to kick things off.
And eventually you learn that this guy's a serial killer.
He goes through this town killing people.
He's the principal at the school and that that's kind of the
most comedic of the stories.
It's his, his son keeps kind of peeking out the window while he's trying to
bury the bad Santa kid and distracting him.
Uh, so that's sort of a more comedic episode, but then the Dylan Baker
character goes in and out of each of the other episodes as well.
He's the guy who puts on fangs and tries to kill pack one and then they
attack him and get their revenge, which is, and they do that.
They do that reveal.
They do that reveal very well.
You don't know it's Dylan Baker until pack when at the very end unmasks him.
And it's a great come up in this moment because he's been so shitty to so
many other people through it.
And they misdirect you very well in his story because as his son
keeps interrupting him, the, the gag is, is you think he's trying to prevent
his son from seeing that he's hiding a dead body and he's cursing about
his son being a little prick.
Yeah.
And whatever.
And you're like, he's got this secret life from his kid.
Then you realize at the end of that story, no, his kid is in on this with him
and he, they're going to carve up the bad Santa kid's head like a jack -o' -lantern.
And he's just, he's just not a great dad because he's, well, because he's getting
his kid into serious at least he's a bad father, but they hide it all very well.
Um, the third story is about the kid, you know, classic sort of tales from
the crypty kind of vibe of kids going to the site, uh, where a bunch of kids
died years prior, uh, in a bus.
That's what you probably wouldn't do today.
Yeah.
It's these parents that unite to pay the bus driver to kill their
mentally handicapped children because they don't want to deal with them anymore.
Uh, so that's a pretty dark story.
Um, and then it's kind of like kids in the present day going to sort of see
the site with a girl who is also, although she doesn't seem like it, she's
supposed to be sort of mentally disturbed in some way as well, but they go to play
a prank on her and it backfires.
It summons the actual kids from the, from the water, from the bus accident.
Uh, that's sort of the longest segment, but I think that one works great too.
Yeah.
And that's that, that's the most straightforward one because it's a
prank, you know, and you kind of know from the beginning, it's going to be
this prank where they're setting up this girl who's clearly like autistic.
Right.
Uh, and, and then you're like, of course the prank's going to backfire on the
prankers and the ghosts are going to be real and whatever.
And then the third story is about the, uh, what is it?
Oh, the Brian Cox one or the fourth story, excuse me, is the Brian Cox one
where he plays a curmudgeoning old man who doesn't, who hates Halloween and
the character Sam Hayne, the little weird thing in the pumpkin hat.
Yeah.
Uh, he goes into his house and terrorizes Brian Cox for not celebrating or
believing in Halloween, which is a cool story.
And there's a twist at major twist at the end of that one where you find
out that Brian Cox is the bus driver that drove the kids off the cliff and
he survives the crash, whatever, but he did this heinous thing.
And then all the zombie kids that he killed come to his doorstep at the end
and you realize they're going to kill him.
What I didn't like about that is there's a weird edit where they show the
picture in the story of the kids.
They show the picture of the kids with the bus driver.
In the Brian Cox story, they show that same picture in his fireplace burning.
The assumption was that Sam Hayne left it there and you realize,
oh, he's the bus driver.
I think it's such a mistake of an edit that they put that picture.
They show you the shot of that picture burning before the kids show up.
I feel like the kids should show up.
They're going to kill him.
You have a what the fuck moment.
And then it cuts to the fireplace and you see the picture and you're
like, oh, he's the bus driver.
Yeah.
I actually, I think Wikipedia actually kind of helped me out on that.
It isn't, it isn't done great.
Uh, I had seen the movie once before and liked it.
Fine.
I think this viewing for me really cemented it as I get why it's this cold classic.
It's, it's, uh, I agree with you that that edit could have been handled better.
I read a lot of the, the troubled production history online and on the
Wikipedia and apparently this thing was, it went through 25 script drafts.
Uh, it went through a million different edits where like they, they tried to
tell the story in a bunch of different ways.
And it, it's crazy to me that this was such a problematic movie for them
because it's great, you know, it, it, it, it's confusing as to why this
was such a troubled production.
There's been a sequel that's supposed to happen for years and years.
And you'd think it'd be a low budget affair that they could do relatively easily,
but it just hasn't come together.
I think it's, um, I think it's, uh, I think it was done as a comic book at this point.
Oh, it was.
I think so.
Yeah.
I think it was hopeless and they just kind of, but here's it's weird.
This movie, even though it was direct to video, it, it, it's so much.
It's it's of theatrical quality.
Yeah.
A hundred Warner Brothers movie.
I mean, you can imagine what the shutter version of this would look like.
And it's, it's a lesser movie to be sure.
But, but, but, well, this is what I was going to say.
I feel like this is the original.
We're one of the original, like HBO max releases.
Do you know what I mean?
Cause like, you know, for all we, for all I bitched about many
scenes you newer, it's a theatrical movie.
It feels like a real movie.
It doesn't feel like some made for TV movie.
Right.
And this is of three actual quality.
It's they spared no expense.
I mean, I don't know how big the budget was.
I'm sure it wasn't huge, but they, they used it very, very well.
And it's got legit talent in it and all that stuff.
And it's, it's just very well done.
And it's kind of like, this is why I remember watching it on DVD and being
like, this is not a direct to DVD movie.
Like this should have been in theaters.
I don't understand why it wasn't bad luck, I guess.
Yeah.
There's stuff about it online.
Like they said, there, there's a few theories, one being that Brian
Singer really shat the bed with Superman and Warner Brothers hated him and did
not want to give him any support at that point.
And then the other is that they wanted to get it away from the saw sequel and
just wound up kind of bobbling it and it never came out, but it is a $12 million
movie, uh, budget wise, and, and it shows it's a good, it's a really
good looking, well -directed movie.
Doherty went on to do Krampus, which I thought was fine.
And he did Godzilla King of the Monsters, which was not fine.
But, um, you know, he wrote X2, urban legends, Bloody Mary.
He wrote Superman returns.
So maybe they had a little ill will towards them at that point.
I don't know, but this is, this is what the guy should be doing.
I mean, this is my favorite of his movies.
And I hope that we get that sequel because I think people are really hoping for it.
And I think shutters should be stepping forward and picking it up.
If they're real horror fans, they must know how much people love this movie.
Um, but yeah, I, I, I dug the hell out of it.
I think I'm going to put it in my, uh, yearly rotation as well,
because it got me in the spirit.
It looks like it's shot almost in the same neighborhood as Hubie Halloween.
It's got the same kind of feel as, as Hubie Halloween, but, uh, it's a better movie.
I'll say that.
Yeah.
My hog is up.
There's more laughs in trick or treat.
Uh, but the, uh, it's interesting.
My hog is up too.
And, and, and Mike Doherty, he said, um, when this came out, he said he wanted to
make a movie, a horror movie that was about Halloween.
And he said, even the movie Halloween is not really about the holiday.
It's about a serial killer, you know, like, and it just happens to take place on
Halloween.
Um, but he was like, I wanted to make a movie that, you know, that was about
stories about the traditions of Halloween and these things you hear about, you
know, and these, these urban legends and whatever.
And he did, and he pulled it off and it's, uh, it's a great flick.
I highly recommend my hog is up.
My hog is up too.
You know, I think that we get a lot of these now, uh, you know, with the
mortuary Academy was a very good one as well, you know, but it, it just goes to
show you how much fun and cool these can be.
If you just take the extra step to kind of link the stories or find some sort of
through line and don't just make it.
Here's a story.
I think that the big, uh, selling point for this is it's script, which is
excellent in my opinion.
Uh, all right.
We, we will be back with a review of the empty man, which is another sort of
lost movie that the theatrical release was bungled and is now sort of finding
its audience.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
You can hear me and Joe on the, we love Val Kilmer podcasts.
I don't know when our episodes will drop, but soon.
And that's it for me, Joseph.
Uh, Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Uh, Joey roses is open and real soon.
In fact, by the time you know, that's not true.
This comes out on the 15th.
It won't be open by the time you hear this, but by the end of this world, well,
our pop -up is open still, but the actual location is we're aiming for Halloween
weekend.
So if you're in New York, uh, that time or shortly after, uh, keep an eye on our
Instagram, it's Joey roses, hard eight.
And, uh, we're gonna, you know, we're promoting a lot and we'll be announcing
the official opening date very, very soon, but it's creeping up.
That's it.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.