I'll see you in thefilm.
How do you do?
What's the bonus at?
How do you do? It's the bonus. April is here. Time for love and a bonus.
April is here. It's the time for love. Spring. Spring time. Spring is
sprung. Spring time for love in Germany. Folks, we're talking today about all
things pet cemetery. We're talking book, audio book, documentary about the
road to pet cemetery. It's called the road to pet cemetery. It's on the shutter.
Yep. We're talking about the 1989 movie. We're talking about that movie's
sequel with Eddie Furlong, pet cemetery 2. And we're talking about the new pet
cemetery film 2019. I mean, let's get into it. This is going to do, there's a lot to
say here. Let's get into it. Let's start with the book. Yeah. Now the book, even in
the forward to the book, Stephen King talks about how he felt he had gone to
far with pet cemetery. He felt it was fucked up. He thought playing around with a
dead kid. Nobody's going to watch this thing. Now this is in the forward to the
book. What does he say in the forward to the book? Shut up, Joe. You know that accent is
just stupid sometimes. It's where I'm from. He was finishing up at book deal.
Like he had one more book to turn in. Sometimes artists are like like musical
artists, like Van Morrison was trying to get out of a record contract and just gave
them the shittiest album of his career. Like fuck you, I'm done. You're gonna have to
narrow that down a little bit. King was like, you know what? I guess I'll do this
because I need to get out of this contract but I don't feel good about it. His editor,
I think, helped him a lot with the book and he put it out but he still feels
conflicted. He still feels it's too dark. I disagree. I mean the book is I think
excellent. The stuff that really threw me this time out was stuff like talking
about the marriage between the couple. There's so much like good stuff like
really well written stuff about the inside of a marriage. Absolutely. That is
completely dropped from every other version of the book but it says so much
about these characters, the family, everything else. It's very well written and
very well done and I know people have talked about the length. You have also
talked about the length of some of his books. You're talking about the stand. You're
talking about it. I think you're right. Pet cemetery seems to be just the right
length to me. Well, I don't let me be clear. I don't think that the pet
cemetery book is too long but I made that argument to you off air. Yes. When
you were saying that you felt that some of the versions, you know, that they
were they were skipping a lot of this stuff and I said look, you know, the book,
he's got, you know, four -page scenes about meeting the family at the airport.
You know, there's there. I don't know that we need all that but but here's the
here's the main takeaway from the book and we've said this before on the show
but it's you got to really drive this point home now that we're going to tackle all
this other stuff. The book is about the sins of the father. The book is about the
dark secrets of men now and I'm let's not get into a whole gender thing here.
This book was written in the early 80s, okay? It was a different time and so
the book really focuses on the secrets and dirty deeds of men that they, you know,
keep from their family or perpetuate in order to try to save their family or
keep their family functioning. Yeah. Which is why the most popular line outside of
sometimes dead is better. From the book is the the the soil of a man's heart is
stonier. He grows what he can and tends to it, right? Which is a play on the soil of
the Macbeth burial ground that serves as obviously a huge component in the story
man's heart is stonier. Yeah, but the point is is that is that you know it's a man's
heart can have you know bad soil or soil that is not fruitful and he kind of
takes what he can that comes out of it and he does his best with it. Which, you know,
again speaks to kind of what takes place in this movie about these things coming
back and being remnants of their former selves and him trying to make it work or
function or whatever to prevent his own heartbreak, his wife's heartbreak and so on and so forth.
That's a huge thing. That's a huge thing and that needs to be recognized in any
adaptation of this book. And it is at times and it's not at other times which we'll get to.
But the book I will also say is it's it's it's thematically it's terrifying. Yeah. And and not
once not once during this because of this theme of what the man is doing for the family or the
father is doing for the family because of that theme. Thanks, Khan. Appreciate it. Good.
But because of that theme, this book never once reads like a zombie story which is essentially
is what it is. Right. You know, and if you watch, you know, there's a great old twilight zone where
like a snake oil salesman goes to this old western town and basically says I can bring everybody back
from the dead that you've lost for free. And then he charges to kill them again. You know, and again,
that never once feels like a zombie story because there's a much heavier theme going on there.
It's not about the dead rising. It's about the regrets and loss and all, you know, all these
other things that have to do with death. And I think those are the most important themes from this
book that that should be upheld in any sort of adaptation of it. Would you agree? Patrick, I would.
I think less so with the first part that, you know, the secrets of men, I feel like that you could
have a version that does not go into that personally. But I think what the book is about at its core
is about death. It is one of the rare horror books that takes death extremely seriously. If you're
talking about the death of a three year old boy, or in the case of the new movie for some reason,
eight year old girl, you've got to take that pretty seriously and they do. I mean, the grief you
feel there is, you know, a two page scene just describing the shattered emotional state that the
mom is in following the death of her son. And which by the way also is wonderfully set up by the fact
that she's she can't deal with death. Yes. To the point where she can't even go to her
when Judd's wife dies in the book, she can't go to the funeral. She has an inability, which stems from
her sister's death, Zelda, to deal with death in any way, shape or form, which is a huge part of the
fucking story. The whole book is about death. How you deal with it. The lengths you'll go to to
bring somebody back, if you could, the anger that goes into death. And it takes death more seriously
than almost any horror book I've ever read. And speaking to what you just said, it even brought her
version of that. Not the lengths you necessarily go to to bring somebody back. The lengths you will
go to to not have to deal with death. Not have to deal with death. Yeah. So I think any version of
that cemetery cannot really do without that. The I mean, they do do away with it unquestionably
in both film versions of it. Well, particularly the latest. And I don't know if we should stick with
the book. Let's work our way up to the movie. Yeah. Let's work our way up. What what what what your
I mean, let's just talk just for fun about the book. What's your favorite sequence? What do you find
the scariest part of the book to be mine, you know, mine of course is the you can't top the Zelda
sequence. Yeah, it's just unreal. It's, you know, there's something about the what the whole way
that's set up. And like I was driving listening to the Michael C hole version. And the man was designed
to read Stephen King audio books. He's fantastic. He does a lot of great voices. He sets the tone
beautifully. But yeah, that Zelda stuff. When that chapter starts, just when it kicks off, you
just feel like the temperature change, like it is so beautifully done in the book and in the audio
book. But it works so well. All the stuff in his mind about it just feels very real. He's dealing with
his family. He's not always enamored with his family. Sometimes he's deeply annoyed in a way that
does not often get discussed, bothered by his family, which I think helps later on when he feels guilty.
Well, that that also speaks to the secrets part because the book, right, it opens with them
making this move for his job. Yeah. So he can in theory provide a better life to his family. Right.
And this huge relocation they've done from a city to absolute rural America. Yeah. And
within the first three pages, he's saying like, you know, he just Lewis thought about I could just
get in this car and ditch everybody right now, including the baby that dies. Yes. You know,
so there's there's a there's a guilt factor there too that when things start to go wrong, it's a guy
going, oh my god, like I took these people for granted. Right. There are many things about the book
that I love the and they're not all horror related like the way they build the really
sweet and loving relationship between Judd and Lewis. You know, it starts with them just going
over there and having a beer every night, but then they're a real friendship develops.
They start to care about each other's lives and families in a way that feels very real and natural.
And just all the character development is done in an excellent way. I thought they deal. It's
almost got blinders on. So you're really just dealing with his family and Judd and his wife.
But that's great. You get to know everybody really well. The backstory between him and his father
and law. It's father and law tried to pay him off so that he didn't marry his daughter is like
such a great detail. It erupts in violence at the funeral. The kids falls out of his casket.
They push each other into this casket. That's a really disturbing and rough scene. Right. And again,
with the father and law, again, back to these filthy things a man will do out of the interest of
protecting someone he loves. Right. In that case, his daughter. But you know, I'm glad you brought up
the Judd and Lewis friendship because it's so well executed in the book. And it is such a key
component to this story because the obvious criticism you would give when watching this is and you know,
they've made jokes about this on I think on family yard of the Simpsons or whatever. It's like,
well, if this place is so bad, why the fuck did Judd show it to him? Right. And the idea is because
they formed this bond that they haven't been able to, you know, Judd Judd very much becomes the
father to Lewis that he never had. Yeah. And Lewis to Judd, the son that he never had. Right. And
here we go again, an older man doing a terrible thing for a man that a younger man that he loves
that he sees his family. That's so fucking crucial. And again, we'll get to it in the way it's handled
in the movies. But you know, there's that great line in the book where he says we're after Judd's
wife dies. Lewis's wife says you should go over and see Judd. He's your friend. Yeah. And he goes,
Lewis had never thought in paraphrasing. Lewis had never thought of it that way. He was his friend.
Right. That was strange. Like to be friends with a man in his 80s, but he was his friend. He loved
him. Yeah. Very important. Yeah. And I mean, you know, this, the big marriage discussion in the book is
basically like the frustration of a marriage is that no matter how long you're with somebody or how
long you know them, they can just be weird one day. And you're like, Oh, I feel distant from this person
because I don't know this side of them or whatever. It's spending that much time with a person. And it
was better than books that have devoted their entire thousand page writing time to marriages. I
just thought he handled so many things so well in this book. And it was in that early, I think just
getting off cocaine stage of his career. No, he's still on it. Still on it. Yeah. Need, needful
things was the first book he wrote sober. Okay. Which was the last at the time, Castle Rock story.
But he was still, he was still deep in it, which is hilarious because if you read about the,
again, the documentary they talk about Stephen King living in that part of Maine at the time,
because he was an adjunct professor or whatever it was at that school. Right. And they said that he
rented a room in the back of the local, you know, the, the, the, the, the, the, the town,
what the fuck do you call that? You know, not a grocery store, but like the, you know, the town shop
where it's like, yeah, it's like you go in and they have everything, you know, where you go, those
books I would have come in, you know, like that place. You know, despite the fact he's living in his
huge house, he needed a place to go right. And I'm like, I wonder if that guy was just like, that was
because he was like, yeah, I got to go get busy somewhere in a room where my family can't see me.
There's a lot in this where, you know, like he's like, he'll have 10 beers, you know, and a lot
of it's just good drinking material and pet cemetery. Yeah, definitely there's an, there's an
air of alcoholism to hate. That's never addressed, but they're just, they're getting pretty stewed on
that porch every night. Exactly. Especially after the kid dies. But if you got to point out a fault,
um, it was, I picked up Joe one morning and was potentially playing this scene in my car.
The sex scene, Steven King is one of the worst writers of sex scenes ever. Luckily, there's only one or
two of a book. I remember speaking of needful things jerking off a lot to this one paragraph in
needful things where the kid fantasizes that his teacher is jacking him off while he's riding on the
blackboard. Just that one scene was enough. This is how, I mean, you kids don't know how lucky you
have it with your pornography. Um, or we, I mean, we had pouring back then. I managed to find it. I
didn't, but, uh, you just had to get a little crafty. I also used to jerk off all the time to this
scene so much so that I sort of remembered the words. It is written so poorly. And when you hear
Dexter, Michael C Hall do it, it's all the more embarrassing. But, um, well, because he's doing the,
the voice of the woman he's going. He's going to see anything you like. Yeah, you know,
it sounds like we could have dinner. And afterwards, maybe I'll be your dessert. Yeah, it'll stop it,
stop it. It sounds like he's almost doing like like a, like a, like a kids in the hall sketch where he's
dressed up. Exactly. It's supposed to be funny. Then the scene, so they finally have their kids out of
the house. And they go upstairs. She gives them a bath and then jerks them off with a bath glove.
And they talk about like the orgasm was so intense. His knees buckled. And you're like, I can't
do this anymore. I'm trying to drive down the street with my windows down. And, uh, it's clear
of her like a second skin. Her panties. And he's clung to her like a second skin. It's like,
you have to picture Stephen King's face in a way you don't with any other part of the book. You
just picture him writing that after he says to, he describes she was quite wet now. Yeah, it's,
it's, there are two terms in a sex scene and a written sex scene that I can never digest. Wet
and hard. Yeah. You know, it's a, it's a clinical way that where you're like, have you had sex,
Stephen King? But, um, you know, I mean, the guy was probably on a Coke bender in the back
of some fucking grocery shop. Right. Yeah. Very minor quibble. I think really this is a,
you know, without question, if you're talking the best horror novels of the past 25, 30 years,
I think Pat Cemetery is on that list. Now, let's agree. Step forward. And by the way,
if you haven't read the thing, man, the audio book is a good way to go over an audible. It's fantastic.
It's really well done. It's, and it's the unabridged on, uh, on, uh, audible, which is the only time
that's ever been released as the audio book. Now, moving ahead, a lot of people have a lot of
feelings about the remake or the, excuse me, the movie, which was written by Stephen King himself,
released in 1989, directed by Mary Lambert, who weirdly had this huge hit,
did the sequel, which didn't make money, but wasn't a bomb. But now, was Pat Cemetery a huge
hit because it was not well reviewed at all. That cemetery too was not the first one. Yeah,
there was pretty badly reviewed. Um, Ebert didn't review it, which I find fascinating. One or two,
uh, Cisco called it sick. He's like, it's absolutely sick and disgusting and they should be ashamed
of themselves. I don't get why they were such visceral reactions to. I don't either. And Ebert
avoiding the whole franchise seems very weird to me because they'd review everything. But the movie
was made for like 10 million and it made 60. That's a, that's a big hit. Okay. And it made 60 in 1989,
you know. So now there was a lot of, this is important to know. I don't mean to cut you off,
but this is important to know. There was a lot of pushback against this movie. The producer,
I'm blanking on her name, but the producer that got this film made, uh, was, was pimping the script for
years. There was a writer's guild strike. Yeah. And they were like, we've got, they're like, only
if we got a script ready to go. And she's like, we do. Stephen King wrote, and even then the guy,
her boss was like, don't bring up fucking pet cemetery. And as she explained, she goes, it was a time
where they thought Stephen King, it was done, which is, which is hard to even imagine. Um, you know,
but it's like, it's like, when you think back to the time when people said star wars was done,
and it's kind of hard to think about right now or, or realize, but, but, you know, so there was a lot
of pushback. So I feel like no matter what this movie did, critically or financially,
they were going to say it didn't work. Mm hmm. Um, which is also why I think the sequel suffers greatly.
You can see the budget drop in the sequel. Yeah. You can see the quality drop in the sequel. You
can see it's not the same care has not gone into it. Uh, let's talk to the original. But again,
anyway, let's work up. Mary Lambert, there are so few female directors, especially at this time,
you pretty much had Penny Marshall. And that's it. And you, well, well, what's her face was, um, um,
um, oh God, I look like a fucking asshole now. Penelope spirit. They, they, they, they, they,
they did, uh, you know, uh, mix nuts and affron. Yeah, nor affron. Yeah. Of course there are a few.
Yeah. But like horror, yeah, horror, you're talking about a 99 % dude, uh, easily at this time,
especially. And not a ton in other films either. Right. Not saying there were. Mary Lambert was a
music video director, which is where horror got a lot of their directors. It's where Fincher came from,
Michael Bay, a bunch of people. But Mary Lambert has a really interesting visual style. She knows how
to shoot scares in a really intense and kind of fresh way. She got a great visual style. Yeah. And
it's pretty much pet cemetery one, pet cemetery two and really nothing of note. And I find that
insane. I think if that had been a dude who directed a movie that made $50 million first time out
of the gate or set a second time out of the gate, I think that person would still be working today.
So that's pretty trouble. That's a good point because you know, I think I think even if even if
even if she got lucky with a movie or two, right? Right. I think she could have at least been a John
Landis. Absolutely. You know, uh, because John Landis is one of these guys where you go, wow,
sometimes it is spot on. And a lot of the time it sucks. Right. Um, so you wonder, is John Landis
good or the people around him just good? Yeah. So even if Mary Lambert was a people around her
just good person, she should have gotten the John Landis shot at this, you know, 100 % like she should
have been given more projects. I and look, she's got 74 projects. She's still directs some television,
but it's really spaced out. And her last like feature film, I mean, you're going back a long ways.
She did like urban legends, bloody Mary in 2005. Like that's a sequel. I haven't even heard of.
So it's happened a lot back then with with anybody that wasn't a white male director. Um,
oh, god, I'm blanking on his name. That is one taken seriously. I'm blanking on his name and I've
met with the man and he's he's great. But well, actually, uh, what's his name that did demon night
and juice? Ernest Dickerson. Ernest Dickerson. It's like, why is Ernest Dickerson still,
why is he directing TV? You know what I mean? It's like, why is he not? And it's the same thing.
It's like his movies were successful. Juice was a hit. Demon night was a hit. Dickerson is an excellent
director. He now look, the TV schedule might be better for people when you direct the TV episode.
You're there for a week. Maybe. Maybe they found there was more money to be made. Who knows? But
Lambert seems very clearly like somebody who just didn't play by the rules or whatever. Right.
And or, you know, didn't have a dick, frankly, but she didn't have that good dick neither.
No, that's true. She did do it. Tales from the crypt that appears at least one. Which episode?
Hard to tell. That's not saying much, unfortunately, because that's a great episode. That was one of
the, well, wow. So here's the thing. That is one of the first of the, that's a first season episode.
So they were coming out, they were trying to come out swinging because the first three,
that's the, that's episode four of the first season. Six, it says, but yeah.
Or six. Okay. So that's the finale. Yeah. The first three episodes of that first season were like
Dante Donner. You know, they were the guys that were behind the reboot or the, or the launch of it.
Yeah. So that's a huge gig for her for anybody because they were trying to, she should have gotten
more shots is what I'm getting at. Yeah. Yeah. No, I, she wasn't treated fairly. And she seems
interesting in the movie and Stephen King met with her and loved her and I'm fascinated by the whole
thing really about somebody like that can just never work again. But Lambert does a great job, I think,
with the 1989 version. It is a surfacy music video, a version of the pet cemetery story. But
she gets great performances out of, I mean, the couple are duds basically. You don't know who they are.
Fred Gwyn is excellent. Could have been nominated as Judd. He's how you imagine Judd. When you go
back to the book, you imagine Fred Gwyn. Yeah. He's perfect. That voice is perfect and everything else.
I put it up there with Christian Bell in American Psycho where it's like, you can't picture Patrick
Bateman any other way. Right. You read pet cemetery. It's like, no, it's, it's him. Yeah. It's
Fred Gwyn. And Michael C. Hall is doing Fred Gwyn. And it's an amazing performance. You buy with very
little screen time. You buy their friendship. You buy their relationship. They don't get into the
marriage at all. They don't get into the family dynamics at all really. Well, they do get into,
they do get into the tension between husband and wife about death. And about her fears of
it. And there are fights in the movie. Yeah. And that original adaptation, there are fights.
They don't, they don't nail it home. And I think they could do it a little bit better. Yeah.
But they at least grace over it. Agreed. To some extent. They, they touch on it. The scares.
The Zelda scene is a, is a slam dunk. Pat and Oswald famously calls that the scariest scene
of movie history. It's fucking terrifying. I saw that movie on video. I rented it with my friend
Brian Peck when we were 11 years old. We watched it in the living room. We had a, we had a big old
wood panel furniture TV set that's out on the floor. We were laying in front of it watching it like
eyes against the screen. That scene came on. We were so fucking scared. We made a pact that we would
stay up all night together. Because it was too scary to go to sleep. And he fell asleep immediately.
And I laid in my bed awake all night with the lights on. Yeah. Yeah. Terrifying.
Pat cemetery. I think there's a lot of people's
kid gateway to scarier movie thing. A lot of people saw it because the parents were like,
oh, Pat, it's fun. And got super freaked out by the movie. Is it terrifying now? No,
it's kind of a kind of a campy fun. It's not 80s cheese, but there is like a layer of like
music video gloss over the thing. But it's energetic as hell. It hits all our most of the key points of
the book. It might not dig into them as well as you want. But the thing is a cliff's notes version
of a great novel. And it's a good adaptation. King wrote it himself. He plays a bit part of the
minister, which is kind of fun. Yeah. It's, it's, you know, it's the weezer cover of Africa.
You're like, sure. Yeah, you hit all the notes like, you know, it's not, and it's not the original,
but you hit the notes and all right, this works. And the movie does, I would say,
give you the same feeling as the book. It's a good adaptation in that way. Although when I
watched it, it felt empty because I was in the middle of the book. It felt very empty and like,
and they could have done so much more, but it pulls no punches. It is intense as hell. They do not
skimp on the kid being a fucking psychopath. The scene of cutting Judd's Achilles heel is still
fucking awesome and scary. It's brutal. Gage dying is brutal. I remember watching that with my,
I remember rewatching the movie that same weekend with my mom. Yeah. And my mom being beside
herself when Gage dies. Yeah. Because you don't, if you don't know the story, you don't see it coming.
Right. It's, it's, and then Lambert does this great thing. I don't, I don't think I've ever seen
anybody else do this where when Gage gets hit by the truck, it's all insinuated. You don't see him
get hit, but you know he got hit. Right. And as soon as he gets hit, Lewis screams no
in slow motion. You've seen that. But, but as he's screaming, it cuts to, it does these flash cuts
of pictures of Gage through his life, like his first Halloween. The mom holding him in the hospital
when he was born. Fucking brutal, dude, brutal, brutal. And the, you know, it is a sort of heart,
not heartless, but a very cold and relentless book. And they don't, you know, they kind of
mash your face and some really rough stuff. He's running around in that book with his son's corpse
for about 50 pages. And it's rough. And it's like worms on it and shit. Yeah. He's taking him out for
drinks. Right. Oh, he's fine. No, he's not hungry. Yeah. It's a weekend. I thought the weekend
at Bernie's turn was a little much, but it was a lot. It was a lot. It was a lot. But yeah, yeah.
He's like, look, I'm not bothered that he's not dead. I'm bothered that he's not 21. I can't
serve him, sir. The movie pet cemetery. It's not the book. It's a good, effective
trash. He's a bit strong, but it's got a bit of a glossy trash factor to it. And I was frustrated
with how surface it was until I saw the new version. I'll say that. Now I want to, I want to point out,
I love the original. Yeah, it's, it's really well done. I love the original, but the main thing I
want to point out about the original one, we will revisit this point when we get to the remake.
I love that when church, the cat comes back, it looks like church, the cat. Yeah, except
it's eyes are glowing and there's something off about it. I like when gauge comes back,
he looks like gauge, but he's a little pale. Something's off. Yeah. That's a key thing. And again,
this or again, that we, I say again, because we talked about this in the it remake with the it
remake, Pennywise in the original TV adaptation was Tim Curry and clown makeup. Uh -huh. That's it.
In the new one, Pennywise looked like a scary clown kid. What's that? And a child. No, no,
in the it, I'm talking about in the new one that Pennywise was a 16 year old kid. Well, yeah,
but I mean, but the fact that they made that they made him look like a scary clown. Correct.
The keyword scary. Right. It fucks with it. Yeah. And we'll get to this in the remake, but
when the things come back in the remake, they don't look like the regular thing. They look like suddenly
a haunted house version of the thing. Right. And it's stupid. Um, but anyway, continue on. I'm going
to get a refill. Sure. Um, yeah. We'll talk about the new one, but Pets Cemetery 2 was also directed
by Lambert King. Not only did not write it, but asked to have his name taken off it when he saw a cut
of it, which I'm sure did not really make the studio excited. But Pets Cemetery 2 and this might
surprise you. This is not a movie with a lot of followers or fans. I thought, again, Lambert's direction
props up a movie that just simply doesn't work. Pets Cemetery 2 was 92. So about three years later,
they're clearly trying to just rush Edward Furlong into a lead vehicle coming off of Terminator 2.
But nobody saw a tournament. This is what they didn't realize until five years too late. Nobody
watched Terminator 2 and was like, I want more Eddie Furlong. Sometimes these movies that are huge,
like, it's like Worthington coming off Avatar another camera movie. Everyone, you know,
idiots, frankly, it's a bad movie, but everyone loved Avatar and it made all this money. But nobody
walked out going, I need more Sam Worthington. And people made that mistake for five years
easy. They were like, must be Worthington. It ain't Worthington. Well, it's also, and I don't
mean, I'm a huge fan. I'm not shitting on the guy by any stretch, but it's the Mark Hamill effect.
Sure. Star Wars works because it's Star Wars. Yes. You know, it's, you know, so it's, you know,
and Hamill, God bless him, like, has gone with the, you know, his road with the punches through
the whole thing and now he's having this wonderful fucking second act that I'm very happy for.
Yes. But, you know, it's the same thing. It's like you love Star Wars because Luke Skywalker's
Luke Skywalker, not because Mark Hamill is Luke Skywalker. Yeah. Not saying anybody could have played it
better. But you put him in something else and you go, well, that's not Luke Skywalker. Now,
what's Mark Hamill as this other guy? And it's, you know, that's the word. And for a long word,
I think they're all very talented people. You do not movie stars. You know, maybe not some,
maybe, yeah, maybe you don't shove them into all these lead things right away. Here's a, I mean,
one sample review of a variety set about Pat's cemetery too. It is about 50 % better than its predecessor,
which is to say it's not very good at all. 50 % better. That's insane. Better Boston Globe says
better entertainment than the first pet cemetery, but more of a remake than a sequel. So that's,
that's madness. I can't imagine anybody saying the sequel is better than the original.
On the whole, it has worse reviews for sure. It's got a 25 % on here. But, you know,
pet cemetery too. I had never seen you can buy it for 399 on Amazon. I was
low -key pleasantly surprised by it. I think a lot of it was how I had heard it was so bad,
some from Joe. But, pet cemetery too is essentially a remake. It's the same story.
A heavy set kid who's really the focus of it more than for a long. His stepdad is Clancy Brown,
who was an awesome actor, you know. Clancy Brown. Clancy Brown, as he does in everything,
delivers an Oscar worthy performance in a bad movie. He's great in it. When he's in a good movie,
he's Oscar worthy. But even in this, you're like, this guy commits a hundred and he's like Michael
Madsen. Yeah. He's like, I don't care if the movie's not great. I'm here to work and he does
it. I wish there was more people like him. Yeah. He shoots his son's dog because his dog basically
interrupts a fuck session with his wife. And the dog gets buried then they wind up spoiler alert,
killing Clancy Brown. They bury him and he comes back. It is the exact same plot. Now, how do they
because I'm blanking, I haven't seen this in a little while. I remember the basic story, but
how do they learn about the pet cemetery? How do they learn to bring the dog and Clancy
up to the Mick Mac? Because they do reference the the creeds from pet cemetery want. They are town
legend. Okay. So people know about the cemetery because those people are like, did you hear what
happened in that house, et cetera, et cetera. So they become like the creepy old haunted house
people they're known about. And that's how it happens. Okay. But I thought that was fine.
The it opens with like a really effective five minute scene. The mom is like an actress in a movie.
Those kind of things were done. I mean, Roger Rabbit opens with an awesome example of that where the
babies like on a movie set. Yeah. That's a magnificent example. This is not a good example. I think
this is pretty bad at the top. You know, it's not. I just like that it started in kind of a different
way. You texted me while you were watching it. You were really delighted by that. But I didn't
it didn't affect me in that way. I I thought it was corny, but that's okay. I thought that Mary Lambert
made this thing something kind of special in spots by doing what seemed to me like a David Lynch type
thing, a twin peak type thing over the end before the credits start. There are you know, the little
circle like if you got a glamour shots photo, it'd be like a photo. And then you'd be like in a
circle in the right hand top corner. They do that. Yeah. They're panning over a forest. And one after
another, you see little iris circles of the characters who have died in pet cemetery too. Right.
Of super bizarre choice. It's it's laugh worthy. It's so weird. And I thought that she should have
cut out the applause bricks behind each picture. And some of them like Clancy Brown is a complete
asshole. So you're like, am I supposed to be feeling sympathetic for him or what's going on?
Right. But I bet it got last in the theater. But it's like that kind of big weird choice
that bothers some people. But in a movie like this where it's just kind of a paint by numbers
scare machine. I like when they do weird shit like that. Well, look, I will say this. This is one
of the only positive things I can say about pet cemetery too. I like the idea that a kid even
though he's abused by his stepfather, excuse me. The child's mindset, 12 year old, how old the
kid is when you're young, the mindset is first, I'm going to be in trouble. Yeah. Second
was justice served. Justice is not in your head at that point. At that point, your main concern is
I'm going to be in some shit. Right. So I like the idea that a kid who even hates a stepfather
perpetuates his stepfather coming back. Yeah. And then tying it at the idea that like, okay,
when a good person comes back from this, they're terrible. What is a bad person like when they come back
from this? Right. That aspect of it is pretty cool to me. Yeah. Not enough to make me
but by the way, he's no different than the good person. He just becomes a zombie. Well, yeah, I just
do anything that interesting. But yeah. Well, again, I'm saying I like the concept. Right.
You know, pet cemetery too to me. Look, I'm not offended by its lack of quality. Yeah. I think it
stinks. But it's a great Sunday afternoon rainy day. Hey, man, I'm I fall asleep in front of the
TV to a spooky flick right now. You know, like that's how it strikes me. You know, they do have
zombie clancy brown rape his wife, which is a thankfully very brief scene, but also a really
unnecessary scene. Well, and here's the thing. It's like it's like in the way that that film is
executed, it I feel I'm saying executed a lot. But in the way that that film is executed,
it is it plays like an unnecessary scene. Had the film been made better, yeah, better written,
better produced, but better whatever. I feel like that could have been a very intense
disturbing moment in the movie, you know, that that maybe would have carried a little bit of value
for the story. But instead, it's like, it's just it's just a shock value thing. And it's just
feels useless to make it even worse. It plays like black comedy. He comes in and he's like,
he's a zombie. And then he's like, Oh, yeah, like it's it's uncomfortable.
But by and large, pet cemetery too is trash. I think Lambert puts it over the edge though. And again,
I think she's the MVP of this early franchise. I think she should have gotten a lot more work and
should still get a lot more. Absolutely. I'll say this to about pet cemetery too. Had it not been
called pet cemetery too. Yeah, probably would have held it held a little bit better, you know,
under scrutiny. What it feels like is like if they were doing a pet cemetery season of Castle Rock,
the Hulu show. Yeah, this season they're apparently doing the misery, you know, how she's got that
backstory where she was a fucked up nurse. That's what they're doing on Castle Rock. I'll probably have
to watch that even though the first season left me beyond cold. Well, I'll say this too. I don't
give a shit about the backstory of the fucked up nurse. That's cool because you don't want anybody,
but Stephen King's version of that story, but also to that's cool in misery because you don't know
what it is. I agree. You see those glimpses of like, wait, what did she do? Yeah, that's what makes it
cool and intriguing. I don't need a season to explain it to. I probably won't watch either because I
don't need to be thinking about that now when I watch misery, which is one of the all -time classics.
But had pet cemetery tube been called, you know, asshole dad that is back from the dad or whatever.
Yeah, you know, it probably would have been a lot more fun. I agree. I thought it felt fun,
a nice addition to the franchise. It does feel like a cheesy remake, but it's got merit. And I would
say folks, it's got more merit than the 2019 version of pet cemetery. And here we are.
Did we touch on everything we needed to from the documentary? Well, I mean, it's hard to talk about
a documentary on a podcast. It's well worth watching. There's a lot of interesting stories. It's just kind
of people believing in the material, the studio, not the second it was a hit. I'm sure the studio is
like we told you that this was going to be great. But it just sort of seemed like a real kind of
home spun production. The documentary and credit again to Mary Lambert. Here's a movie they refuse
to make even during a writer's strike. Yes, we're resisting. She makes it and oh, we need a sequel now.
It's like you fucking assholes. I even with it letting me down. I was very excited about the new pet
cemetery. I think there is no world in which we are not now treated to Melissa McCarthy and Misery.
You know, I think we're going to get all these books again. I think we're going to get Kujo again.
And they know they don't need to put stars in them. And it doesn't matter. And I think it's just
going to keep happening for the rest of our lives. I'd like to see a rebel Wilson Misery. Sure.
You know, a little mad cap action. I went into this excited. I thought there are things to be
improved upon in pet cemetery. And even though I sort of knew in my heart, it was going to let me down,
I was unaware of just how deeply I thought this was the worst king adaptation in a decade. I
thought it was significantly worse than it. More than a decade. More than a, I'd have to really look
at a list probably more than a decade. I mean, this is up there with like, you know, those those
like TV adaptations in the 90s like like riding the bullet that like just like those are better. I think
the stand is a better movie than this. The Gary Sinese Molly Ringwald. I agree with that. I agree with
that. The Stephen Weber shining like I mean, this it was it just such a fucking missed opportunity.
And when you have something like this, it's like, okay, maybe they tried to rush this out on the heels
of it. But this movie's been around since 1984. The book's been around since 1984. Like
how how do they not take a bunch of pitches and just hear somebody who had a lot of passion? Like I
know what to do with this. These guys went in and said, I want to do the book. But I want to make the
daughter die instead of the son. It's like, ooh, that's interesting. It isn't interesting. Now hold on.
That's not a that's not a me too like giving more to women. It's it's not a change. There's nothing
interesting about that change. I got to get a cigarette. All right. I hope you don't mind. I have
so much to say about this. I want to relax. I want to smoke. Can you carry this for two minutes?
Of course. The picture stars Jason Clark. Jason Clark, Joe and I saw in Winchester, which we talked
about on this show. He was the star of a great showtime series called Brotherhood that I've talked
about and recommended a great little two season three season number on showtime. He is a boring actor
though folks. He's just a boring actor. He is equally boring as the guy who played him in 1989.
But man, just give us somebody that puts a little mustard on it. The wife, Amy submits, does not
register at all. She's just not an interesting performer either. And the biggest problem
is John because those two weren't great in the original either. John Lithgow is an actor I have
loved and respected since I was a child. I did not think he was capable of giving a bad performance.
Capable of going a little hammy a little over the top, but I don't mind hammy. He does not seem
to know that the camera is on in this thing. He brings nothing to the table with such a juicy and
delicious character. Now, they did kind of fuck up the character. There's literally no bonding
between Judd and Lewis in this film version. But okay, you don't want to do the main accent.
I think it's a terrible decision, Lithgow, because I'm sure he could do a great job with it. But
fine, what are you going to do to put your spin on it then? Okay, you don't want to do the famous
accent of this beloved and famous character. What are you going to bring to it? This role could have
been played by anyone in the world. And it would have had the exact same impact. Lithgow's
worst performance. And he had to have been directed to just not even try. I bet the studio was like,
just don't let him go hammy with it or something because he is so handcuffed here that he does not
even register as giving a performance. It's pathetic. This movie, whoosh, coming in hot.
This movie to me, when I first saw it, I left going, okay, that was pretty cool.
Then I slept on it. And I was like, that movie sucked the next day. The second you start to think
about any of it, it sucked. It makes no sense. They really play up this thing in the, and I'll get
back to Lithgow. But they play up this thing in the trailers where suddenly the pet cemetery is
this grounds for this sort of ritualistic ceremony that these children conduct every time a pet dies
whatever. And you see it right at the top of the film, these children walking to the grave of
walking to the burial of one of their pets, and they've got the dog in a wheelbarrow or whatever it
is. And they're all wearing these hideous animal masks. And Lithgow goes, oh, this, you know,
it's a bit of a ritual around here with the kids doing their pets die. And that is never called back
to ever again. They do it one time. So let me tell you, I don't understand. I saw that in the trailer,
the kids with the, the masks and everything. And I was like, okay, I may not love where it goes,
but this pet cemetery is going to try something new. I thought they were going to do like a children
of the corn thing or something. Kid cold. Yeah. Great. I'm into it. Let's see it. Then you see it in
the movie. And you're like, okay, I guess it, the exact same thought. Where's this going? It goes
nowhere. It goes absolutely nowhere. This movie to me, look, it's so hard these days. And I know we're
tough on some flicks on this thing. It's so hard these days to, to place the blame when something
like this goes wrong. Maybe it was a studio. Maybe it wasn't. I don't know. But I will say this.
I walked out of the movie thinking, I feel like a lot of it was edited out. The, the top of the
movie shows the Creed House on fire. And they never, and they call back to it at the end. They never
really show why is it on fire? Like what happened? Like it's, it's, it's, Judd saying this is a ritual
around here. It's never explained. It's never expanded upon. I felt like this thing was cut to shit.
Probably from studio notes, I would assume. And I feel like it's an hour 40 at a time when every
movie is 220. And there's, there's so much that does feel glossed over left out. But none of the
relationships are clear. There isn't a 30 second scene where it appears that either parent is even
bothered by the death of their child. So all this amazing stuff in the book and to a lesser extent,
the original movie about grief, death, etc. They're just, I mean, what did they think that we couldn't
handle a parent grieving on screen? How about, how about this too? How about this too? Okay, so at
least in the original adaptation, it starts as normal family moving to a normal place. Yeah. And
oh, there are a few question marks are popping up here and there. Yeah. We'll get to it later.
In this movie, within the first five minutes, you're seeing flashbacks of Zelda,
you're, you're getting the explanation of the pet cemetery because you're seeing a bunch of kids
walk around and bunny rabbit masks. Yeah. You learn that the pet cemetery is on their property,
which it's like, what? What the fuck does this have to do with anything? All these needless details.
And I'm just like, why are you guys rushing to the finish line of this thing? And then it becomes
evident like, oh, because you desperately want to get to the end of the book by the beginning of
act two. So you can then shoot off in this needlessly different direction that adds no value to the
story that brings no more depth to the story. It just becomes this other thing that you don't care
about. None of the kills mean anything. So like, I would argue that the slicing of Juds Achilles
heel and the original. That sticks with people almost as much as Zelda. It's beautifully executed
because you don't want to see him die. And you don't want to see this sweet man who you love die.
By the time Lith guy was muttering around the house, you're like, thank God he's about to die in this
thing. So we don't have to look at him anymore. But they show him, they do these a few times in the movie.
I was, it's so badly done. They do it a couple times. They show you his exposed Achilles heel.
They do a close -up of it. So everyone who's seen the original, I mean, fuck the book. All they
care about is the original movie. Everyone who's seen the original is like, they're going to, okay,
here's the part where they cut it. They cut away and then do this weird edit where he likes and
doesn't really cut it. He sticks like a knife through his heel. Doesn't slash the sheet. She does. I'm
sorry. She's Ellie. And it's cut and edited so chopily and weirdly. You don't even really see her do
it. It's not a cutting of the heel. She just sort of sticks it through his leg because they want
to be different. I'll tell you the, I'll tell you the worst part of that. It sucked. I'll tell you the
worst part of that scene. They do this entire build up about how the return of church the cat is,
is unwanted. And it's an evil cat now, which by the way, when I was referencing earlier,
you know, church comes back and suddenly it looks like it looks like a cat you would buy it CVS for
Halloween. Yeah. It's like, oh, look, it's ridiculous. Yeah. And in that Lithgow Achilles heel scene,
he thinks Ellie's in the house and he's like, what do you do? And Ali, I know you're in here.
And then he looks up the stairs and he sees church the cat and he laughs like, oh, it's just you. It's
like, you've spent 40 minutes telling me how evil and rotten this cat is. He wouldn't laugh. No,
he'd be upset that this fucking thing is in there. And he laughs. And then that's how she cuts his heel.
And then she's wearing a bunny mask for no reason. Because I guess it's got something to do with
the rich. They never explain it. It's, oh, god, it's terrible. And before I forget, how many fuck? Who's?
Jay, what's his name, Jason Clark? Clark. This is like the end of Glenn, Gary Glenn Ross when
Puccino's going, I don't know who's dick. You're sucking on. Exactly. You know, it's like, how did you get
this job? How did you get this job? You fucking child. It's like, who does Jason Clark know that
they keep putting him at the forefront of these movies that are bombing one after the fucking next that
stink? You know, the chap aquatic was going to be the one where he turned it around. That movie sucked.
It's just like Jesus Christ, man. My guess is because it's also like women aren't attracted to him.
Guys don't like him and women are attracted to him. He's the whole not package. Who does he know?
I'm walking out of this movie with my buddy, Brett. We saw it and he's like, isn't that kind of like
weird looking? Is something wrong with him? I'm like, and looks aren't everything. But when you don't
have that much to bring to the table, looks are important. And he just kind of is this zero. He
must be willing to do these parts for less than everyone else or something, which is a smart play. But
he ain't great. And the decision to have gauge who looks exactly like the gauge from pet cemetery one,
who's the boys have a penis girl with a giant guy from kindergarten cop. He's also the kid new nightmare.
He's a great actor. Really good actor. They talk about how the Judd scene and the documentary really
fucked with this kid and like he thought he had actually killed him. I don't know how these kids are
in horror movies and live the tell the tale. But he's like a normal kid now. He's like, he's like,
he's like, it's 30, but he's just like, yeah, how's it this movie? Yeah, look.
They have gauge in this. And as everyone knows by now, Ellie is the one who dies. But
there's no reason for like, I just looked up the writing credits on this and a guy's got story by
story by his Stephen King. You've done the same thing. If you got story by credit by saying,
maybe instead of the boy, it's the girl who dies. Now, there's no reason for this. Any kid under
the age of 16, whatever can only be on set, this limited number of hours. It might be easier to direct
a 10 year old than a three year old, but it's about a billion percent less creepy. And again,
let's let's tip our hats to Mary Lambert once again, that she gets this startling performance out of
it. She is not scary at all in this. They for some reason got a kid who looks exactly like gauge
to play the boy part. Then when they're about to have Ellie get hit by the truck, they do this really
weird pathetic fake out, I guess where gauge is also up by the street. And they keep cutting to
gauge. So you think he's going to get hit, but then Ellie gets hit. And it's like, was that supposed
to be fun for me if I didn't know? Am I supposed to be like, oh, they killed her 80 secrets get
out immediately. But be everything about the choice is less gripping, less scary, less interesting.
That to me is, and I know that I say this because of what I learned from you and dealing with trailer
cuts from the shows you've run. That to me sounds like an idiotic trailer cut by the studio. Yeah.
And in the, how it was supposed to play was you're watching and you go, oh, god, here's where gauge
is going to get hit. And in the last second, it doesn't happen. The problem is they give away in the
trailer that Ellie's the one that gets hit. You know, so there's that speaking of the Ellie hit,
it's sicker to me. It's already a dodgy, dodgy subject of child dying. But the fake out,
like, it just feels disgusting and cheap to me. Sure. And while we're on this,
they show, they show more of the accident than they did in the original. Right. You don't see
here get hit by the truck trailer or whatever it is. But you do see her dead body and whatever.
And you do see a shot of the truck after it's already hit her sort of, you know, on its side on
the street or whatever. Here's your drives me crazy. You're showing a massive tractor trailer,
the trailer of a massive tractor trailer that just slammed into a 10 year old on the street.
She's laying in the grass. There's not a drop of blood on her. And there's the faintest,
faintest smear of blood on the trailer. It's like, guys, don't show it or show it. Because if that
thing smashed into it, a 48 year old, it would be a fucking massacre on the street. So don't show it
if you don't think you can go all the way with it. But if you're going to show it, don't insult
my intelligence that I'm going to think a fucking trailer just slammed into a child. And there's no
blood. It's absurd. Here's another thing this movie does that drives me crazy.
And I say this because I have a dog. And I walk my dog every day twice a day. And often as I walk my
dog, he steps in dirt or wet whatever, you know, mud, whatever it is. My dog is never once left footprints
in my house. This movie relies so much on footprints. Yeah. Where it's like she must have been here. Look,
there's the cat footprint. It's like, what leaves footprints? Yeah. What the fucking,
unless you're walking in wet sand and immediately looking where the person just walked,
who has ever left footprints and anywhere? And then it doesn't clump off as you continue to walk
through the house. It's just, it's just, it's just very, it's absurd. Look, a minor quibble,
a minor quibbles and bits to keep it on pet cemetery. This thing has major fucking issues start to finish.
I had read reports like, you know, like you won't believe how fucked up this version is.
It's so fucking dark, please. Heard the same shit on it. Clearly that is just a publicity machine.
Like you won't believe how dark this fucking thing goes. Every other version of this, including
the admittedly goofy pet cemetery, too, treats this with more impact, more emotion, more
scares, more intensity. You want to talk about jump scares? I mean, one second into this movie,
before you even met the family, it's a truck volume turned up to beyond how loud a theater sound
should be allowed to go. Gah, gah, gah, gah, truck come in, everybody jumps and then cut like,
there wasn't even that usually fun laugh that usually happens after a jump scare because everyone was
just like, well, yeah, you played a sound at the loudest volume anyone's ever played. I'm scared.
You could tell everyone was like, fuck that. That didn't scare me. That wasn't scary.
It was just startling. Jump scares have their place, but it's their bullshit. They have their
place, but their bullshit. Pinkstone sent me a great meme that said, you know, jump scare in a
horror movie. I'm paraphrasing. Jump scare in a horror movie is the equivalent of a comedian running
into the audience and tickling people. You laughed. I must be funny. It's like, no, it's not the same thing.
I don't mind the occasion one. I know we were in trouble. They have their place when this one
kicked off with one and it was a loud truck. When all it can rely on is that it's like, come on.
Let's get back to what I was initially saying about the stone, the soil of a man's heart is
stony or stony. So in this movie, they choose to take the approach that Judd and Lewis
are skeptical of one another that they don't really, they don't, they don't have a friendship. That's
just as plain as it is, unbelievably stupid decision. They have no friendship. So then when Judd,
you asked me what's one of the most lasting affecting parts of that book. I said, the friendship
between Judd and Lewis. So then when Judd convinces Lewis to go to this pet, you're like, what?
What is that? This scene starts. Okay. When church dies, Judd goes,
Judd goes, Lewis, you better come in for a minute or he doesn't even say it like he says,
he doesn't do the accent. But he says, you better come here for a minute. And Lewis literally goes,
what, Judd, what are you doing? What are you freaking my kids out? Like, he's an asshole to him.
Yeah. And then Judd goes, no, you can't. Look, it's dead. And then Lewis goes, oh, God, the stairwell,
a Judd goes, Lewis, we should take care of this tonight. And Lewis goes, yeah, okay, Judd,
he's a cunt about it, right? And then Judd is like, I need to take you to this place to bury this cat
where it'll come back. And then later, when this is like, why the fuck did you take me there? Judd's like,
because your daughter touched my heart in no way that any person has in here. It's like show some of
it. Yeah. Show two seconds. The water touched the heart. Fuck that. Fuck that. So in the book,
the second they land, you got it, you got a great little five page intro, you get the, you get the
family, you get why they're moving there. The second they land and get out, they get the girl gets
stung by a bee. Judd appears, takes the stinger out. He immediately, they're skeptical of him for
five seconds. He immediately wins them over with his charm. And it's like, you can tell these guys
are going to be fast friends. And you can tell how much he loves and cares for the kids, the family,
the wife, he wants them to be happy. And the great line in the original movie is when he goes,
when, when, when Gwyn goes, sure good to see people in that house again, you know, like, and you see,
like, he's this great guy that's just like, dude, like, I'm happy to have a neighbor. Like,
he none of that in this. He does all this and he also has a lovely wife who does die in the,
in the novel. And in the original film, she's not in this. So anything either is, by the way,
the housekeeper, the killer, there's the housekeeper. That was a fine, that was easy to lose in my opinion.
That was a wise choice. Fine, but that's a real dark moment in it. That is a dark fucking moment in
the original movie when she hangs herself and it builds the theme and the tone and the mood
of everything. I didn't mind losing it. I wouldn't mind it losing it from the book either, but
his wife is super important and it paints him in this softer light. He's a man who deeply loves his
wife when his wife dies. That's a very sympathetic moment. He cares for her so much that it's clear
and also decrapes this guy. Doesn't he also too, by the way, in the book, doesn't he sort of
insiduate that he's maybe stepped out on her or cheated on her in the book? Yeah. But again,
speaking to this theme of like, we keep these secrets because ultimately, was that a mistake? Sure.
But I love my wife. That's more in the book. And yeah, and this, you know, he's like, I stepped out
with some, some of the town halls and he's like, but you know, there's certain things you can't ask
your wife to do. You understand? And you're like, okay, this is a weird turn for the book, but
it does. It tells you a lot about this guy. The wife is not in it. So when he comes upon this girl,
Ellie, in the woods, and that's a problematic sentence. Well, yeah, when he comes upon this girl,
Ellie, in the woods, just rephrase that. The mom comes up behind her and it's like, hey,
can I get my fucking daughter back? You old creep? And you're 100 % on the mom side. It's like, yeah,
it's an old man talking to a young girl with no parents around in the woods. It felt weird.
Yeah. And had you not, if you had no familiarity with the book or the story, what's
so ever? Yeah. But then you're in the theater watching it and you're going, no, no, no,
judge a good guy. But wait, why are you making him look weird here? He's not a bad guy. You know,
like, they did that. And the next time you see them, the daughter's dancing. Judds like drinking a beer
in Washington are like, hey, hey, hey, hey. Like, are they trying to make him look creepy?
Because he sure as hell did. And they took away anything that might have made him more sympathetic
or lovable. His wife is caring about the family, his friendship with Lewis, the beers at the end of
the night. I know you're under a lot of pressure. So come over and have a drink to the point where he
kill where Lewis tries to kill him. Yeah. So it's like, did you cut all this out at the script stage?
Or was this, you know, studio director, whoever, just like, let's get this stuff out of there.
It's not moving the story. It's an hour and 40 minute movie. And it's one of the few times where
you're like, this would have benefited so much from being two hours. Now here's the thing to
bunch it out. Here's the thing to they hit this fast forward button on so many of the plot points
from the book and so much of the story from the book. And then they elongate other things that don't
need to be elongated. So one of the great edits in the original movie is Lewis
going to work for the first time and saying like, you know, it won't be a tough day. Don't you worry?
Couple band -aids and bruises or whatever he says. And then it cuts immediately to Pascal getting
wheeled in with his brains hanging out. That's an awesome, awesome time jump in the movie that works
very well. And it's as effective as it is in the book with doing it much more quickly. In this one,
they choose to, again, speed through aspects of the book, jumping right to Zelda almost immediately
and other things, yet they show them at work for a couple days. And then they do the Pascal thing.
It's like, it's like, what the fuck are you doing? And please, please, let's get to Zelda. Let's get
to the Zelda thing. We're saving the worst for last. Please reverse Vanessa Williams once saying
this is, she dies in the whole, oh my god almighty. I mean, this is just the whole
purpose of that existing, that storyline existing in the book and in the original film is because her
her sister Zelda had spinal meningitis. She had become a burden on the family. She had become
transformed into this twisted, wretched monster that the family quietly wanted to die
because they didn't want to deal with the pain of this anymore. And in the book and in the movie,
original movie, she says, how did you know, how did Zelda? She choked. And I let her choke. And I
all wanted her dead. And therein lies the guilt and the fact that this woman can't deal with death
and all these things. In this version, they incorporate for some reason a dumb waiter into the house
where she has to send Zelda's food up. And somehow Zelda, the bedridden girl who has spinal
meningitis climbs out of her bed and into the dumb waiter, which then collapses and that's how she
dies. It is it's it's illogical and absurd from every fucking angle. I mean, I took it that she
fell into the dumb waiter. She can't get out of bed. That forget, forget the falling or they
don't wait. She can't get out of bed. That's the point. We can't get rid of her. That's the point.
I honestly could not believe that when I saw it, but like, it seems like in every because this went
through a pitch, the way these things work generally is that like 10 writers devote weeks and weeks of
unpaid time to fleshing out their take on a project like this. You bring it in and pitch your take out.
Nine of you, you're told you've just wasted two months of your life for no reason and one of you
are told you've got the job. So they go in like, let's talk about Zelda. Everyone's going to want to know
how you're going to handle that big moment. You have to assume when you see this movie that they said,
you know how it was super creepy and effective and we dressed a man up like a woman and the makeup
was perfect and everybody remembers that scene so vividly. We are going to make Zelda look essentially
like a normal woman. I mean, in the new one. Yeah. Her face would just kind of a normal, non -deserving
woman. 12 year old kid. Then we're going to almost rush through the whole disturbing setup of Zelda.
It almost feels like they were like, do we really need this in there?
Because they handled it so stupidly. The dumb waiter thing, it doesn't even make her walk down the
hall up to her bed, which is like the building suspense of this, the scaryness. All it is is just another
really pathetic jump scare. She drops in the dumb waiter. Logistically, that makes no sense. Why does the
house have a dumb waiter? What makes it scary is that she's confronted face to face with death every day
and has to walk into this room. They're adding this layer of her being on a different floor of the
house. Well, the different floor is fine. It's adding this, like, and she even says like, we weren't
supposed to use the dumb waiter. It's like, why is this in here? Why is the dumb waiter in there? And here's
the whole setup. Here's the whole purpose for it. Zelda, for some reason, somehow gets out of bed with
spinal meningitis when she's bedridden. For some reason, crawls into the dumb waiter to get her
food out of it, which makes no sense. And then dies. Then Lewis's wife can go, I think she was still in
the walls. Like, so they could do a literal interpretation of, I think she haunts the walls of the
so stupid. And here's what they missed out on, which is what they always miss out on these things.
They lost, by the way, of a different house. Not the house we're in. Right, right. They lost every
single aspect of the human condition from this thing and what would what would haunts us as people.
Okay, the original Zelda story in the book and they did a good job of this in the original
adaptation. It's like the elephant man. It's like you're seeing this thing that you personally have
sympathy for, but also find terribly disturbing. Yeah. And you have your own guilt with that where you
say, I don't want to deal with this. It's too much. I can't handle it. But this is a human being that
deserves sympathy. That's the point of the original thing where she's saying, I want her gone. I don't
want her in my life anymore. Yeah. And it's that haunting, awful guilt of like, we as people can't
deal with these things that are that are scary to us and frightening. Right. And they lose it
completely in this. And it's just like, I was lazy and I use the dumb waiter and then my sister
fell down the shaft and died. And it's like because some dickhead at whatever fucking studio this was
made from went, you know, she's just too unlikable. If she kills her sister, what does she
doesn't kill her sister? What does she fuck off, man? Like, I mean, part of the reason you do an
adaptation of a classic beloved horror novel, one of the most beloved horror novels of all time
is you don't have to worry about likeability. You don't have to worry about all these things because
it's a proven success. That's why I didn't understand about it. They cut, they stripped away everything
that made that interesting. They stripped away everything that made this interesting. Well, I'll say this
too. As much as I disliked it and had criticism about it, it was 20 fucking times better than this thing.
It is 20 times, it makes you like it more. But this seemed to soften things down in a way that you're
like, no, it was a number one bestseller. We've proven that people are okay with it. The movie was a
huge hit. Just give them the same thing if you want. But if you're going to change things, why change
every single thing you change for the clear worse? Like, how do you defend the decision of what you
did with Judd? How do you defend the dumb waiter? How do you defend so many things in this movie
that just unquestionably make it worse? And if you talk to any horror fan and said, what do you think
about if we do Judd and Lewis aren't friends? Okay, why? No real reason. Huh, I don't like it.
If you're going to go that route, initially, I thought that route was interesting. Where I was like,
okay, now he has a reason to hate this guy for showing him this place. But then you've got to build it
and execute it that way. You can't just go, they don't really like each other, but then he shows him
this thing and he just trusts him. It makes no sense. In my opinion, the movie, the material, the book,
the subject matter is so relentlessly grim and dark that you need in my opinion, that Judd Lewis
friendship, which is so sweet and real, you know, you need Judd to be that likable guy. If Judd
is an old asshole, you're not, you don't give a shit. Here's the thing. You want to go that route?
Here's what you do. Have Judd. First of all, develop a little bit of the fucking relationship
between Ellie and Judd. Right. Show that the parents are weary of it. Yeah. Show that Judd is
actually a good guy that actually does care about the kid. And in this day and age, that seems weird
on the surface, but he's a good guy. Yeah. Show that. And then have Judd be the one that sneaks off
and buries the cat. And then Lewis is like, fuck you. What did you do to me here? Sure. Do it, do it.
That would make it make sense for Christ's sakes. I honestly thought that in the 11th hour, Judd was
going to turn and reveal himself to be a zombie or something. Because I was like, why are they killed
off his wife? Why is he this gruff aloof asshole? And he's not doing the accent. And this and that
and that. Then finally, I was like, I bet he's not doing the accent because they knew that a zombie
version of Judd doing the accent would be hilarious. And that wouldn't be, I started to just get ahead
of it. I'm like, they're trying to make a big change here. And they're keeping Judd on arm's length
so that he can have some big twist. Nope. Well, how about they just made him worse? How about two that
like when Ellie comes back from the dead suddenly, she's able to take form of other people when she
becomes Judd's dead wife. And again, they sort of insinuate that did Judd bury his wife up there.
And they never explain it, but they don't insinuated enough that it's interesting. I thought
though why and could come in in the 11th hour as a zombie, they just didn't do anything. And then you're
sitting there going, okay, so if Ellie can take the form of anybody in the hopes of killing her
family, right to also bury them in the pet cemetery. So they become this big giant zombie family as
they do at the end of this movie. Just do that. Yeah. Why are you playing cat and mouse? Just take the
shape of your father's wife. Yeah. And murder him. Yeah. Or whatever. It makes no fucking sense.
And then as my friend Josh Adam Myers pointed out, I love Josh, go see the goddamn comedy jam if you
ever can. It's a great show here in LA live show, very fun show. As he pointed out, he goes, okay,
so the whole movie ends on we're going to kill a three year old. Yeah, but that's your last note. And
I go, Josh, I got to tell you them creeping up on the three year old, the end when the three of
them are zombies. And now it's gauges turn. I go, I feel like that was the starting point for this
movie. I feel like somebody had the idea, like, what if it ended with you, or you don't think to set
up a sequel, you just think, no, I feel like somebody came in and went, what if it ended with this?
Yeah. Well, how do we get there? Oh, what did this happen? Well, then what did this? And they worked
backwards into a shitty fucking rendition of one of the greatest horror novels of all time.
Literally, the only two things I liked about this and I can't even say liked more. I'll just say I
like, is that ending? I was like, okay, I love the ending of the book. I love the ending of the movie,
which is slightly different than the book. This ending is the kind of horror I like, which is the
absolute darkest of humor. Like when they're walking up to that kid and he's like, hey guys, you know,
yeah, sure, that as kind of a final cruel sick joke, I was like, that ending work, that ending
works for me. The other thing that I liked is that they spent more time with the cat in zombie cat
form. Weirdly, I thought zombie cat was glossed over in the 89 version. Maybe because they didn't have
the effects, but it's such a fun premise and they don't really do anything great with it in this,
but there's more time of the cat being a zombie. And finally, finally, back as we come full circle
to what we were saying at the beginning of this thing, the soil of a man's heart is stonier. They never
that line is said by Lithgow off camera in the middle of a monologue about other where he doesn't
expound on it in any way. So there's no point to it. It's like there's no, there's no, it has no
same with sometimes dead as better is like this like disembodied line. And what I think happened
certainly in the case of man is stonier is they probably screened it probably for Stephen King,
who I think now you give him 10 grand and he goes on Twitter and says he likes something because I
don't think he loves all this stuff. I think he's just old. He's in his 70s. I mean, this guy wanted
to strangle fucking Kubrick for the shining. Now he's going like, hey, it's not my movie, but it's
fun. He's at that age where he's like, I'm not, I got no fight anymore. I don't care. But I
think King Washington was like, you guys got to have the man is man's heart is stonier line in there
and they had Lithgow come in an ADR. I think that's how little thought they gave it. Yeah, it's
is a bad picture. In fact, so too much so much so that this could be our longest episode ever
that wasn't a commentary. It's a it is a movie that if I was not doing this podcast, I might have
considered walking out of I thought it was so bad. And it is a dangerous thing admittedly to like
do that thing. I used to do it when I was a kid all the time, like finish a book the day before
a movie came out. I did it with Jurassic Park and stuff. Let me address parks a good example of a
movie kicking the shit out of the book. But I got to say though, I just listened to the audio version of
how Newman dies in the book. Yeah, and it's it's pretty awesome. Yeah, it is fucking disturbing, man.
Yeah, I mean, really great. Generally, the comparison book to movie,
the book's going to win out. There's just so much more detail. A movie can't do everything.
The last time I really did this was me and my wife read Gone Girl and then we closed the book and
went to see it opening night. And I got I mean, that that that is an excellent book, but it spends so
much time in the heads of these two people. And I didn't think they could do it. Gone Girl is like
240 or something like that. They get every beat of that book. They nail it. It's a beautiful adaptation.
Fincher is not a guy who generally likes to stick to the script or the book, but boy does he.
Gone Girl is a excellent adaptation. It is a a minus book turned into an a minus movie essentially.
This is a a book turned into a D movie. And that is a really heartbreaking thing. And I will say this
too, they're often you receive the criticism as you criticize something like this from people
that go, oh, stop it. It's not going to be the book. It's going to be different. I get all that.
I get all that. But there are basic themes that you incorporate that either translate the point or
don't. American cycle is a great example. That movie is not the book. They made every choice.
Right. That movie is another woman director by the way. Yeah. As you said earlier, Cliff notes of the
book, but the one thing they drive home in that movie. And it's the main fucking point of the book.
Is he crazy? Is he not? Is he doing these things? Is he imagining these things? Right. That that
whole thing is there in that film on the on screen. And none of those basic themes or concepts are
here in this remake. They are there to some extent, at least in the original adaptation. Yeah. But
this misses on on on all marks. It's pointless. Pointless is exactly right. It's like you, you can make
money throwing a title like this on the screen. But why the hell wouldn't you just spend a little
extra time making it perfect? This is a movie adapting a story that millions of people care a lot
about. And it is done with zero care at all. Agreed. I was texting Joe as I watched the 1989
pet cemetery again. Like it was kind of frustrating because I was in the middle of the book. But when
you see something like this, it's like no, no, no. That movie was a very, very good adaptation of an
excellent book. I think I can say this on behalf of both of us, two hogs erected upwards and then
turned down to hard hogs down on this flick. I don't want to be buried in a pet cemetery. And
I'll tell you this, here's a perfect like mathematical equation comparing the two movies. The song
strangely what the Ramones biggest hits that closes pet cemetery the original is the Ramon song
pet cemetery. The song that closes this movie is a cover of the Ramon song by a band called
Star Crawler. And I think that should tell you every fucking thing you need to know because they
could have so easily put together 25 grand and gotten pretty much any band Star Crawler. Yeah,
get Queens of the Stone Age in there. So they totally could have got Queens of Stone Age. I mean,
like bands are there's no way for bands to make money anymore outside of relentless touring and
even then you're touring to break even you dang a little money in front of anybody. You could have
gotten a cool cover of this. This is a movie that just doesn't give a shit frankly. And it's worse
than it. And I hope it's not the second in a long line of upcoming shit, King Remix. And actually
as far as King Remix go, you have to look towards the better ones lately. And those are all in these
streaming space Gerald's game. And you know, that that book seemed unadaptable. But that was done
by people who gave a shit. And this was not I don't think. No, no, yeah. Go watch a 1902. Yeah.
Fuck this movie. And that's it. That's our show. That's your bonus app. Folks, we'll see you next time. We'll see you. And hell.