Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 Plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states
Hello everybody, welcome to, we'll see you in hell.
You know that the podcast is part of the Fangoria podcast network.
That's probably how you found it.
You want some more information on this network, Pat?
I mean, maybe these people want to know about other programs.
Maybe they want to know how to follow this show or find some past episodes of other shows
are our show or whatever. You go to Fangoria .com. All right, how are you, buddy? I'm good, Joe. It's
good to see you always coming in, telling people where they need to go, what sites they need to see.
We get this thing started off hot. Yeah, yeah, yeah, mentioning a website. Yeah, well, it's, you know,
I got to do it. You got to pay the piper. We got to jazz it up a little bit. It's 9 .30
our time. We are in beautiful downtown Los Angeles. I just got out of work. Yes.
Coming hot off a new taping of two broke girls. Yeah. Yeah. Nice to be out. These tapings
used to go till like midnight one in the morning. We're banging them out now. It's a machine.
Who made an appearance this week? Were there any guest stars? Well, there was. It's amusing.
I wanted Joe to play this role of this guy who they have a the girls. I'm sure you already
know the girls open up a new dessert bar serves alcohol and desserts inside the diner
they work at next to the diner but they're still broke yeah well you know you open a
business you sure many businesses go and where they get the money for the business I guarantee
you don't want to know but I will say it's all explained if you watch six seasons of the
fucking show. Any who I said I want to give my Palo Joe to Rosa a role and we had this
role of this very funny part very burned out divorce. He was a former child star who
said his career was briefly sidelined by a 30 year drug addiction. And now he's teaching
bartending school. Right. And I was like, I'd love Joe to do it. My boss loves Joe as
well. She was like, perfect. Then like in the 11th hour, Joe said he couldn't do it. So
we had to get somebody else in. And clearly they just went with a, a Joderosa type. French
Stewart. We've been compared through the years. French. I was supposed to do 30 third
rock. I know. I'm 11 hour six. Yeah, I had to pull out of that as well. French Stewart. I had
only seen him in third rock. And I thought that his eyes were squinty and like that.
and it's just it was a choice he made for the character so and he's also not
like effeminate as he was on third rock. I mean I realized people play parts and
you know of course I what a bizarre choice to make to squint your eyes for a
role and then for the eighth nine seasons that show was on every time you do a
scene you have to squint your fucking eyes. Yeah it's I went through a third rock
phase recently I think I found it on Hulu and I had never really watched it much
when it was on, but it was part of that home must see TV. Sure. I've never seen it. And I know
I'd like it. I like everybody on it. Very funny. Very funny. Everybody hits home runs. I'd say
Lithgow hits a grand slam. I mean, Lithgow in a big broad comedy. There's not much better than that.
Yeah. So, but I looked up French steward afterwards because I said, what the hell is wrong with his eyes
and then learned that that was an acting choice. Yeah. And then just had a great respect for the man
after that. That's that's not an easy choice to read with. He did a very like intense almost
late Pacino take on the material. But didn't quite get across the sweaty loserness that
I knew that Joe would and could bring. Sure. Sure. I'm sorry I couldn't do it. I mean it's
sounded like fun. Yeah. It was a funny part but oh well. I am very tied up with this special
right now. Tell them Joe. This comedy special. My comedy special. Let's do the plugs. We shoot in
I think this will come out just before but we shoot Thursday October 13th in Los Angeles at
the Masonic Temple, the Hollywood Forever Cemetery. If you're in the area and you want to come,
you can get your tickets at blacklistnyc .com, blacklistnyc .com. Go there, click on the shows link,
you'll find my show listed there. I feel that's confusing since the show tapes and the tickets
are available for here in LA, the company that coordinates the audiences out of NYC.
I know, but let's not throw it off. Like even when I saw the link today, I was like, oh, I can't
go to that. It's in New York. That's why I write Los Angeles in the top of the post and everything.
But anyway, I'm also directing the special, which initially I was not and now I am,
Which is very exciting, but it also means
Being at all the scouts and things like that, which is why we had a major scout the exact time of your table read and neither thing was
The time of neither was negotiable, so it didn't work out
I don't want you people to think I'm pissing and spitting it fucking third rock or two broke girl parts over here
I would have loved to have done it. No, and we'll get you back in but
Yeah, nothing ever works out
I like I Joe's special tapes on October 13th so a month ago. He was like you got to keep October 13th free
I flip open my eye cow and from now until the end of time basically I have nothing planned
Not one thing right on my calendar and I zero in on October 13th the one day
I have a little dot in it and my
Girlfriend of many years her father just remarried. Yeah after 20 years a bachelor and
And as a wedding gift to them, I said I would take them to see Van Morrison, who is their
favorite recording artist at the Hollywood Bowl.
That's very nice.
With Tom Jones opening.
It'll be a lovely night.
It's an odd bill.
Why is Tom Jones opening?
I think they're both Welsh, and I think they both get drunk together all the time, but I
love that bill.
It's a strange combo.
I love the bill too.
Wow, I'm not a big Van Morrison fan.
I'd go just to see Tom Jones, I'd be out of there right after.
but I mean, it's an odd pairing of people because Tom Jones's
Vagacy, yeah, and, you know,
He's been worse than his Welsh. Yeah, they're both like Welsh. But like he has like a Welsh accent. Yeah, I mean there
There Irish, which is this very close to Welsh and he's thought Irish Van Morrison grew up here. I never knew that
No, Tom Jones is from Wales and I believe I believe that Morrison is Ireland bell fast. Maybe or something
But anyway, if I was just going to the show,
I'd be like, fuck it, of course, I'm gonna go see Joe stand up.
But there's a hole to do and a dinner.
So I said, well, now is there any chance
you're recording it any time,
other than like seven to 10 p .m.?
And the tapings are at 7 .30 and 9 .30, of course.
But you come after and we have a few drinks.
I come after and we have a few drinks.
Everything's going well, it should be a good time.
I hope you can attend and speaking of Ireland,
if you're in Galway,
I'll be out there for the Vodafone Comedy Festival Halloween weekend and we
will be doing the second ever live taping of an episode of We'll See You In Hell.
Unfortunately, my buddy partner and cram here, Walsh, will not be with me, but I'm
either gonna have various guests or a co -host, but it should be a good time.
So if you're around, come out to that in Ireland. I would skip that one personally.
That's not going to be one of your better episodes of the podcast.
Don't get somebody too good so they're like, ooh, I was going to say no, like Larry
Sanders fear here, you're getting John Stewart while in here, don't get him shitty guests,
that kind of thing.
No, I'll be fine.
Oh, well.
Who could match this magic?
Also the live, you're not doing a commentary, are you?
No, I think we'll just, it'll be the discussion style show.
We're doing it.
they have a they have a moving a moving bus that makes no sense it's a bus
that they did that moves obviously okay that they do shows of and this bus pops
up at different festivals over there so we're gonna be doing it in this this
bus which serves as a moving mobile stage place for shows showhouse Joe I couldn't
have said it better myself I'd like you to sit back I don't like that you're
sitting, I mean, I know I'm sitting forward, but I don't think we both need to.
Quite frankly, we're today discussing a classic film and I, you know, look, I had a bit
of trepidation before the, we started recording here because Pat and I actually agree quite,
quite unanimously, I would say, on this movie as far as I know, but the subject today is
Demon Knight, Tails and the Crypt presents Demon Knight, uh, this movie
will get to the synopsis of it in a second, but I can't tell you
the event that this played in my life. There was no bigger Tails and the Crypt fan than myself
and my dear friend James Pinkstone who we talk about frequently on here. I've never seen an
Epsom. Oh, I own all seven seasons, man. You can borrow any of them from it. Now the the Cryptkeeper
puns yeah they're they're not great they don't even really make sense in some
cases what's the last one of of demon night it's I fuck I said I'd remember it
and I didn't I'm gonna last pun the last pump I mean some of them when he says
I've got final cut you're like all right not checks out but there's some that are
just you gotta realize something by the time you hit demon night yeah you're
pretty deep into the catalog of Kripp Keeper puns at that point. You know that's
like the last pink Floyd album where like these guys have lost their fucking
mind. What is happening right now? So it's you know it's you're pretty far
down the road. They were stretching at that point. You know like you know
welcome to the boovies you know shit like that. That's not bad at all. You know
I back care for some pop scorn, you know shit like that. There was that there was
I can't remember. I'm gonna look at the memorable quotes. Did you watch the lengthy documentary? I gave you on demon line?
Completely blanked on doing it. All right, and I would like to watch it because you also the other night
I said hey, can I borrow a Westworld the movie? He goes, yeah, man, you're gonna love it. I bring it back handed to him tonight
not a week later
no recollection of me borrowing it.
In my defense, the night you borrowed it,
we sat here, we drank two or three bottles of wine.
We had a nice time.
We smoked a copious amount of marijuana.
Easy.
We don't have to talk about all that.
At one point, I said, do we eat one of these edibles?
You said, why not?
I mean, we were in bad shape.
We put on the movie from beyond.
Oh wow, there's one we're not discussing on the show
because we could not finish it.
Well, here's the thing.
We put on from beyond from the makers of Reanimator,
a big, big Reanimator fan of the whole series.
And so we put on from beyond and we're very excited.
We were very high and drunk and thought,
this will be a lot of fun.
We were not enjoying it.
We felt that it was going nowhere.
We felt that we had watched most of the film
and nothing had happened.
And then Pat left and I put up the timer
and realized we were roughly 25 minutes into the film.
So I think it needs to be revisited in a better mental
circumstances.
Sure.
Also, too, we were watching the movie.
We both agreed there had been no credit sequence and that we were probably about 35 minutes
in and then we were six minutes in and the credits came on.
So departed style where it springs up like halfway through the moon.
So we have to, we can't give a fair assessment of that yet, but that night apparently at some point Pat said can I borrow Westworld?
And it was funny because the other day texted me watching Westworld. It's amazing. And I thought, yeah, thanks for keeping me updated, but I don't know why he's telling me that.
Well, no, I'm at the pile of the HBO pilot of Westworld. I thought was fucking awesome, very dark, violent. I loved it.
I really loved it. It's the best thing they've done since that first true detective season and
The movie you know comes off as very sort of
Campy fun in comparison, right, but it was really fun the Westworld movie that Michael Crite and directed which I was unaware
Yeah, I like how they just let him direct all those adaptations of his books and then on Jurassic Park
They were like we got somebody a little bit
Watch us hit this one out Mike now that he's did he step in for Congo?
no no no he was out by that point he had health issues he got real weird about
like global warming and shit yeah he had some dangerous opinions now here's
the thing the Westworld TV show is I haven't seen it yet but it's from the
perspective of the robots where's the movie is the perspective of the
customers well it's one of those who's a robot who's not kind of situations but
they spend a lot of time with Anthony Hopkins and Jeffrey Wright who are making
the robots too. Oh, Jeffrey, right. I didn't know he was in it. Yeah. He's great at Harris.
Great. But Ed Harris is playing the Joel Brenner role, except he's a human, not a robot.
So they mix in humans with the robots in the in the it's too soon to make any sort of
ball or reaction. But I think they're going to be doing a lot of I thought this was a robot. It's not.
I thought this was. But I mean, do you see any of the business in the theme park in the first
episode or is it all backstory at this point. Now you see plenty in Westworld. They don't go into
like the medieval world like they do in Westworld. I thought all that stuff was a little corny.
But when the robot first turns and stabs that guy in the medieval world when they're dueling,
that was kind of like a chilling moment. That was cool. Yeah. But yeah, the series I'm completely
on board, the movie was great. Yeah, the series looks much more slick. I mean, the movie is great,
But the movie is definitely a product tonight of mid -70s science fiction. Yeah
The TV show definitely it's it to me. It's a very similar refacing to
Like what they did with Battlestar Galactica
Very simple. I didn't like the Battlestar Galact. Either never saw the old one and I didn't care
I thought it was boring. I know people loved it. I like the new I like the old one. I
Respect the new one. I I didn't enjoy watching it that much
But which I always felt like I was maybe missing something because some real super nerds that like a lot of the stuff
I like were just obsessed with it. Yeah, but I I don't I mean I thought about it. Just didn't I didn't find it that intriguing. Yeah
Let's let's get back on demon night look demon night. So this one here it is good
Well, what do you know? I asked for a final cut and I got it. He's in the guillotine. Yeah, they cut his head off
It rolls into a basket in the last line of the film as he goes now. That's
in
Territainment
And laughs maniacally. Yeah, so when you're in a theater, do they treat his puns with respect as an audience?
I don't remember there being
I mean look I saw an opening night. It was sold out in Delaware. Okay. This show was big
This was movie was sold out in Delaware. We had to buy tickets for some other movie and sneak in
I was on a date my friend Jim was there too. He we had to split up. We couldn't all sit together, okay
And I remember there being excitement in the theater. I don't think anybody is genuinely laughing at the puns
I think it's right. Well, he's got the way you latch test in the bathtub at the beginning
and he's directing like a movie of his own.
I mean, to me, the John Larraquette cameo at the top
is up there with the Bill Murray zombie land cameo.
Cause John Larraquette, I mean, was still,
you know, you could still smell the fumes
at nightcourt at that point.
Right, sure.
So that was enjoyable.
But, you know, I think I always smell
the sweet fumes of nightcourt.
It's never left my nostrils.
I think people laughed in the way that you laugh at,
Like a Star Wars fan would laugh at C -3PO, you don't really think it's gut -bustingly funny
but it's charming in its own way.
Well on this documentary I learned many things and it's a shame you didn't watch it but
they...
Now wait, should we give the synopsis of the movie first?
Again, yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, we never do that.
Yeah, so Demon Knight was, again, the first of three films in the Tales from the Crypt.
The modern tales from the crypts franchise. I'm not including the films that came out in the 70s
but the basic plot is
William Sadler is this sort of loan
eternal
Gunslinger type warrior. He's up against an ancient evil played by Billy Zane who is the demon knight play on words
K and I G. H. T.
He is the, you know, the sort of leader of the demon minions that ruled the darkness of Earth before God said let there be like.
They get some pretty well done like biblical style flashbacks.
Great biblical flashbacks. There's a lot of blood of Christ stuff in the movie.
And every scene of the movie was filmed in an airplane hangar in Van Nuys, California.
That whole hotel. Yeah, really.
hotel and the medieval time ship.
Really? Yeah, that's pretty amazing.
The blood of Christ is the only thing that can hurt these demons.
It's the only thing that can create barriers that they can't cross through.
By pouring it on the ground, it builds like a sort of invisible wall or whatever.
And William Sadler, in short, finds himself
caught with a motley crew of people
you know Tommy Lee Tommy Lee okay there you go come on man in this in this
middle of nowhere motel you know sort of paid by the hour prostitute hang kind
of place and and it's the night of the big showdown the the reckoning day is
come they had they must face off one must walk away victorious and it all takes
place in this hotel. Billy Zayn's like the head zombie. He gives them all a little demon,
but he gives them all little fantasy flashes, you know, trying to lure and tempt them all the
people there. Yeah, the best of course is with Dick Miller when he walks into that room full
of gorgeous. Yeah, Dick Miller plays essentially Dick Miller in the movie. I don't think he was aware
that they were filming again. I love Dick Miller. Everything he's in though. He's a guy that looks
like he's got a flask under the seat in his car or whatever. But he plays a homeless drunk. And
yeah, his temptation to get where Billy's ain't tries to lure him over to the dark side is that room.
And it's a bar called like, what's his name in the movie? Hold on. The Dick Miller's character's name
is Uncle Willie. So the bar is called Uncle Willie's. Yeah, Billy James is very funny in it.
Billy James is great in it. I thought it had some... it was to me, similar in tone to a movie you
inexplicably don't care for tremors except you know didn't for me pack these scares or laughs of that
film but I did really enjoy it. I think had I seen it when I was in high and high school at a
sold out show I would have liked it more seeing it now I liked it and I have no ties to
tales from the crypt. I saw Bordello of blood by fast forwarding through it when my dad
rented it and pausing it periodically to masturbate. It's a really I've not seen the film. And
those were the Dennis Miller scenes folks. Bordello of blood was a tremendous disappointment
especially in comparison to demon night. That was huge bomb. That was the beginning of the
end of Tales from the Crypt. Tales from the Crypt was delivered pretty much in full for the first five
seasons. Season 6 became very hit or miss and then season 7 has its moments but it's not great
and that's for some reason they moved the whole production. I guess there's a budget thing to
England in season 7. So suddenly now everybody's English. It's like that would be cheaper to go to
which was strange. Well you know it must have been a budget thing because in the opening
in the opening of the first episode of the Seven Seas
and the establishing shots they show of England
or shot on video.
In Westworld, when they show you the three different worlds,
the one they show you the Old West,
which is the set they've carefully built,
then they cut to a painting of medieval times,
a still shot of paint.
They used to get away with you like that in the seventies.
Yeah, yeah.
Just cut to like a drawing of something
and be like, you know, you get it.
this unfortunately was about two thousand two thousand right somewhere in there
the uh...
so uh... but and then after bordello blood came a movie called ritual which
stars uh...
the late jennifer gray
she's alive
i wouldn't know she alive she had a nose job but she has a lot that's yeah okay
so she is alive she's in that movie uh... i only read about that online and though
that as that like even as a theater release was not even called a tale from the
They added it for DVD they yeah came out when it came out on DVD
They tacked on tails in the crypt and and got like it looked like they fished a crypt keeper head out of a dumpster
And then a guy put gloves on from Halloween adventure and they it was the shittiest crypt keeper rendition I've ever seen
Well, it was really bad in demon night which it was a fairly big budget movie like when he walks out and his lips aren't moving at all
And he's talking I was like well, they added see they added CGI in demon night
Yeah, and it's older CGI so it looks a little weird. Yeah, but at the time that costs them some money
Right, and this is a different kind of bad. This is bad where it's like guys
Here's what we got to work with to make it work. Yeah, here's some string and some tape and whatever, you know
Well, the stories they tell on this documentary is guy Ernest Dickerson director who's an amazing director
Kind of a middle -aged black dude. He did like juice
You know he did some really incredible movies and that can can I say something about juice? Yeah
Yeah, Fangoria, that's the parent company, they tweeted out the other day question of
the day, scary a scene in a non -harm movie, my vote was the two -pock hallway scene in
juice.
Sure.
When Omar shuts the locker and two -pock is just standing there, that's a pretty scary
fucking scene, man.
Yeah, I think that's that stuff might have got him into horror, you know, because he comes
comes off as so charming on the documentary and now he does Dexter and the shield starring
C .C .H. Pounder who was also in this thing as well, but he did a great job in it and he was
talking about how he went in there and the guys who were going to make the demons, they
were like, so here's what we can do with your, here's the budget we need for the movie and
the producers were like, okay, give us 10 minutes, say last and he comes back in and they're
like, so we're going to do it with no demons, we're going to do it like where they're like
Yuppies and maybe we'll have their eyes glow red and stuff and he said I can do a cheaper version of the demons
But as a horror fan, you know, it's your standard guy with a huge beard
But the fact that he's like in a Hawaiian shirt. No less. Right. He's like there's no way I'm making this movie without some fucking demons
Right. Well, then you're gonna make him cheaper and he said fine. I think the demons look cool
I love the demon the tricky thing about the CGI in those days is that when you do stuff in studio or when you do stuff
stop motion or whatever, miniatures, it looks better than the early days of CGI.
You just buy it more.
Well, the demons, better than demons from when I can remember our CGI did it.
The only CGI in the movie I believe is when they make the CryptKeeper walk around for
a second.
Well, that's what they did.
They said we're going to get really super skinny people, and then give them, you know, nose
rings and all the shit they did, and they look convincing, they look great.
They look great.
Yeah, that's actually a little fun movie fact.
Again, Fangoria, question of the day.
Scariest, scarriest, sibling character in a movie ever.
I replied, if your answer is not Zelda and pet cemetery,
you're wrong.
Sure, sure.
She was played by a man.
They said they could not find a woman skinny enough
to look that sick if they had to get a guy to do it.
Yeah, maybe the guy they got to do,
the Sloth and Seven, which is one of the scariest scenes
in the history of movies for my money.
I got that jolt's up out of bed.
Yeah, that part's upsetting.
That was a real man, too.
That bad cemetery scene is terrifying, I agree.
It's, it, it kept me awake.
My friend, I remember we were kids.
My friend, Brian Peck, who was a dear friend
of mine in grade school.
Yeah.
Brian, if you're listening, I hope you're well.
I haven't talked in years.
She had a spinal bifida.
Spinal meningitis.
Spinal bifida.
No, spinal meningitis.
It's spite at bifida is a thing that prevents you from
Potentially walking properly. You need leg braces spinal meningitis kills you
I'm gonna look this up Joe. I'm definitely right. I'd like to put money on it. Would you like to put money on it?
I put a dollar on a dollar a dollar
I'll put five dollars on it. Let's put it. Let's put a gram of weed on it
I'll put five dollars on it yet to make it seem like all we do is smoke weed on the spot
That's not all we do. We're not even we didn't smoke any tonight. That's all we do
But let's make it fun $5 the home we're gonna do with that
You know what five dollars and if a listener
Sends us their address. I'll send you the five dollars
That was once Pat Walsh's that's real. I know you five dollars. Thank you. Get us your address. What's spina bifida?
Huh, what's spina bifida? Spina I just said it's like a thing that fucks with your spine where you need like leg braces and stuff
It doesn't kill you though.
What did Zelda have in Patina?
It was meant in Jess, spinal meningitis because the whole idea was it was it was in a time
before they could see this is the reason Patina Oswald always talks about that scene on
Twitter and he always says Zelda the Spina Bifida sister.
Well, I mean, you can blame Patina Oswald for your ignorance all you want, but you're wrong
on this.
and when I searched Spinal Bifida it says I'm just getting a lot of hits on that
too. It's Spinal Men and Jitis and here's doubly why I know because right around
when that movie came out weans, well not right around but a little after weans
chocolate and cheese album came out and it had that song Spinal Men and Jitis on it
where it was the little girl voice going I don't want to die and we always called it
the pet cemetery song we always thought like this must be based on pet
Cemetery all right anyway, but I'm getting in just as many hits on Bifida. We'll do this off. We'll do this off
Well, let's do it on so we can it's a contest all right then just go to the Wikipedia page keep talking
I mean, I I can't I don't know what I can trust here. You can trust the Wikipedia page
Pat Walsh is wrong
Tweet at us somehow get us your
Address don't tweet it out publicly, but tweet at us and maybe we'll DM you or something and we'll send you an official
$5 bill from Pat Walsh's wallet. In fact, signed by both of us. How about that?
That's exciting, sure.
To get the viewers, or the listeners involved a little bit more. But my friend Brian
Peck came and slept over. And we rented Pat Cemetery and we watched it. And that
scene scared the living shit out of both of us. And he fell asleep before I did. And
And I felt just betrayed.
I couldn't sleep.
It was horrible.
I was terrified.
But I'll tell you, I felt like abandoned almost.
Speaking of which, I'm going to send out a tweet now to the listeners.
Send us your questions on demon night now.
Are you done?
Did you fight it yet?
no, no, nothing definitive. I'm sorry. It's definitive. Trust me. It's, I'm right. Look, you're
getting five bucks either way. Okay, but we all know who's right here. All right. I mean, it looks
like in the novel, it's been enjoyed. I assume that's what they were doing. Pat and I was
well, what dearly love always says, Bifida, he must just be mistaken. But that's really what I was
going on. He's absolutely mistaken. Okay. Now, I want to know if you knew this, because
I think I might have a fun fact for you. That from dusk to long. I don't like serious
fact. No one does. Dust still don't. Yeah. They talk about it in this movie. Here were
supposed to be the three tell us in the crib movies. Demon Knight, Bordello of
blood, and Quentin Tarantino's from Dusk till Dawn. That was supposed to be the
first one. The first one. Tarantino wanted too much money and eventually it
went away. So the guys that made Demon Knight, there was it was three guys that
wrote it writing team and then a third guy who they're like we don't write with
him anymore. They cut to this guy and it looks like he's had some real rough
years. He like never wrote anything else. The other two did Kung Fu Panda. So they're
probably billionaires. Anyway, if he's listening, I'm sorry. It's a tough one. But, you know,
they made it pretty clear that like if Tarantino had done from dust till dawn, maybe the
tailors in the crib would have been a big smash. And they would be making one a year
like James Bond, they said also, you know, had Bordello of blood gone first.
It probably would have killed the franchise.
Right.
Demon Knight.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Bordello.
Yes.
Yeah.
Demon Knight did okay, you know, but like barely okay.
And then Bordello of blood tank.
So the whole franchise ended.
But does still dawn.
I don't know.
And no offense to tell us from the crib.
But that would have wasted what I think was a pretty fucking awesome screenplay on something
that maybe didn't deserve it.
Uh, well, I don't know if I had a, if I'd agree with that, I, I think, I think dust
till dawn fits very well into the tails from the crypt, but it's way better written
on that stuff.
Well, I mean, look, there's some excellent, there's some excellent tails from the crypts,
episodes.
Uh, what a ruin the twist, too.
Tails from the crypt, you're like, when are there going to be some fucking vampires?
Whereas if you just, of course, are the marketing ruin the twist, anyway, well, I knew
the twist already.
But I will say that my girlfriend had the dream scenarios of sitting down to watch from Dustel dawn not knowing yeah
I mean seeing that I knew the twist and I still loved it seeing it not knowing the twist. I remember my friend Brian
I saw him at a
Cypress Hill concert and we were both quite high
Right when that movie came out and I said he goes did you see Dustel dawn? I said no, but I knew the twist and he goes
He was very high and he goes dude. I just I just couldn't
I couldn't deal with that man like what the fuck like he felt like like almost like tricked and hurt that they did that to him
I wish more movies would do that when people talk about the ship
You know, I just saw this amazing movie coming out to my buddy Alan produce called Ingrid goes west and it's a kind of a satire about
Social media and how it's ruining society. It was that that movie with
It's Aubrey Plaza. Oh, yeah amazing in it Elizabeth Olson
and Oshae Jackson ice cube sun from straight out of Compton.
I fucking love this is one of my favorite movies of the year.
They're like, you know, I sat down
and we did a notes session.
I was one of the first people to see it
and we sat in this room
and everybody kind of gave their thoughts.
I was going out on my fucking head.
These are people who are in Hollywood, like insiders.
It's not like they showed it in, you know,
bum fuck Iowa or something.
No offense to the good people of bum fuck Iowa.
Sure.
I come from bum fuck Missouri myself.
But like they were missing the point so aggressively and I loved this movie so much and they were like
I didn't really like the tonal shifts of it and I'm like yeah, that's what's great about it
I was never bored. I like a tonal shift. I like when a movie takes me something I didn't know I like a tonal shift if it works
For instance demon night the tonal shifts work very well. It's funny. Yeah, Billy's ain't acts funny
It's scary when the demons are scary, but then
There are other films that try to do it where it's where it's a huge miss so you know
I think a lot of horror comedy sci -fi comedies. They they go too big with the laughs
And then you don't give a shit about the horror or the advice of Versa
but
You know this movie is basically a set set higher comedy that gets progressively darker as it goes
But this crowd is like she's unlikable. Nobody was likable. Couldn't we give her a triumph at the end, you know
It was very frustrating and I talked to my buddy Alan the other day and he's like yeah, you know
We're kind of listening to those notes and trying to decide what to cut. I said if you release it now
You've got one of the best movies of the year right and I hope they do, but I think this is how things get fucked up
Is everybody chips in and I don't know that demon night. I don't know where that would even go today unless it was made for a million dollars
Those movies don't happen really now now now do you think there will be a moment in this
process of this Ingrid goes west release where they'll say a man stood up and said you release this now.
No, and I mean, nobody really listened to me that much.
Okay.
The crowd turned against me when they were like, I don't necessarily believe that these people would be this evil.
And I was like, you live in Los Angeles.
Right.
I mean, people I hate this much every time I leave my house.
Right, yeah.
And I could tell that the crowd was getting a little tense.
It's just some quick interesting stuff about Ernest Dickinson that I didn't know here.
He was the...
Dickerson.
Dickerson, excuse me.
He was the cinematographer on such wonderful films as...
Do the right thing.
Any more if you raw, jungle fever, more better blues, and Malcolm X, which is arguably in
my top ten films ever made.
It's an incredible movie and an incredibly shot movie, of course, as well.
I just got it on Blu -ray for that very reason.
Yeah.
Because I had it on DVD and I went out and bought the Blu -ray because I thought this must
look stunning in HD pad.
It does.
The dude is very, very gifted and now he does a ton of amazing TV, but he's very charming
on this documentary.
If you're a fan of Demon Knight and if you're listening to this podcast, you probably are
The shout, excuse me, scream factory, Blu -ray of Demon Knight has just a stellar hour -long
plus documentary about it.
I just bought a ton of the shout factories, shout out to them, scream out to them, they
do great work.
The scream factory stuff is great, now I'm torn with it, if I may, you know the torn, and
then we'll get back to the movie.
But would you get them to sponsor this fucking podcast so tread lightly?
No, no, no, it's I'm not gonna say anything negative. I'm torn because a lot of the movies. I just as you know, I just
Purchased a VCR. Yes, and right now in fact, we're recording on a Samsung television
That's doubling as the monitor for my computer, but that Samsung television is a tube TV. Yeah, then I bought specifically to hook up to the VCR
So I could experience certain movies with the grainy texture I wanted them to have.
A lot, most of the things that the film's screen factor is re -releasing, they're doing
beautiful jobs with, but they're movies that I want to have on VHS.
I want a grainyist to them.
See, I get what you're saying, but for me, like, I watched Ferris Bueller, let's say, on
VHS, honestly, no less than 100 times when I was a kid.
So when I get the Blu -ray of Ferris Bueller and I see it looking like it came out yesterday, I
Have gas before it's like holy shit because you get to see it in a new light
Well, but we're talking about screen factory movies not Ferris Bueller's not screen factory. They do the same thing
I mean they they take these movies that through the ravages of time will have looked pretty granny and shitty and
Make them look amazing. I like when a Blu -ray preserve some of that grain as well
Well, but when you really clean up something I've seen a bunch and they could look like a new movie
That's a me is what a blue rise all about here's of course obviously obviously, but here's the thing
There are certain horror movies. I like to experience that way and other ones
I don't for instance I today I went and bought on iTunes. I bought all the phantasm
Films okay HD. I'm going to see fan I didn't get for ravager
I'm gonna go see that this weekend in the theater you should come is it coming out here come it's playing
I think for three days because it's like on iTunes already. Oh, well, it's
put it over at the Egyptian. I know. Well, we're me and Matt McIntyre. But I think
it already played are going to go see it this weekend. So you should come because
then we could do it on the podcast. I watched one and two with my buddy and I was so
horrified when I was a kid. I had not seen many horror movies and I was like, I don't
want to do this anymore. They're great. But I just the reason I got them all on iTunes
say it was because the JJ Abrams right frame for frame remaster came out and I
I thought, well, I'm not going to watch the first one remastered and then the other ones
nod.
It's going to look dumb or the other ones not HD.
But phantasm is a movie where I thought, that is something I want to see in Blu -ray.
There are a lot of black and white landscapes.
They're in that funeral home for quite a bit.
It's a lot of marble.
It's a lot of very primary color stuff.
So I thought, that will look very cool.
Yeah, but
Something like for instance Texas chainsaw massacre. Yeah original. I don't want to see that on a Blu -ray
I want to see that with I want that to look like I found a videotape in the mud somewhere and I put it here in the machine
I hear you and I just bought you know something that was offered like a 4k
Thing that they just came out with of Texas chainsaw masker
Now I've seen I've seen it granny so many times. I'm excited to see it in 4k
But I bet I bet even the best possible print of Texas Chancel massacre
Looks pretty dingy. There's no way you make it look incredible. Well, that's yeah
I mean, it was you know
It is what it is at the end of the day and then I also got on shout factory Chancel massacre 2
Which I watched once when I was not granted. I used to be a real pussy sure still am to some degree
But horror doesn't necessarily bother me as much as it is a day when I was a kid
But he a mind when I was like 13 showed me Chancel massacre 2
So I was sickened to my stomach, the guy scraping his brain with that hanger or whatever.
I was like, it has stayed with me now for 25 years, it ruined me.
It's got some gross parts, those Bill Mosley scenes are pretty nasty.
But I bet now it'd be, because I've heard it's funny.
It's without question or horror comedy.
And Dennis Hopper it is most coaky.
I mean that I think that's right before the break right yeah that's before he got sobering said
I got to make a movie about cops yeah, yeah, yeah, but
It's it's a pretty insane movie, but it's a horror comedy would always upset me was Toby Hooper has been quoted as saying
Texas chainsaw master two is what part one was supposed to be but we didn't have the budget
And I think part one is such a masterpiece it upsets me to think that any of that was accidental or not on purpose
I think, I think that the reason text transomaskers still horrifies is because it feels like a VHS you found in a swamp.
Right.
I think that it was so cheap and like they didn't quite know what they're doing, they're rushing to do it.
Some movies have like a haunted quality and some movies try to do it and don't get there.
Sure.
It's the movies that are truly disturbing are the ones where they happen into something that really fucks with you.
and that's for sure as Texas Jones. Now let's get back to demon night in a new
segment that we call gripes and swipes. What? This was not discussed. I know I
just thought of that just now, but it does sound like a segment title doesn't it?
What were your gripes with the film? Because I really don't have any gripes and
swipes. Well, you know, I think for what it set out to do it was super fun. I
in the thing she's I mean she's still amazingly hot but I mean she's that's
like that's like the peach just came off the tree yeah oh man it's a
Georgia son I mean that's Jesus you know that she's like a peak physical
condition in that film I tell you I'm watching this thing thinking you know I'd
love to put one in the pink it too and the stink it you know what I'm saying
Oh boy, there you go.
Tweet that out as when you hear this, I'm sure you will.
Thomas Aiden Church, I thought was great as a scumbag in it.
I love a movie where a bunch of people band together.
Much like Tremors, which again, it's just baffling that you
didn't enjoy.
It's not baffling.
I've explained, I don't like dirtworms.
I don't find it's them to be a scary monster.
So then that's the, once I don't care about the monster,
or then everything else is, you know, superfluous.
Yeah, I mean, I liked that I don't have any real serious
scribes with it either, although, you know,
I didn't love Demon Knight.
I thought it was a very fun, solid movie.
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
I'm John Lithgow bringing it back to Lithgow.
I've never seen it.
So this thing, I had already seen it when I was a kid, but it's Di Palma, who I love.
I had seen the Di Palma documentary, which I really love.
And they talk about Raising Cain as being like this really lost classic.
And some guy online had read.
That's a Palma movie?
Yeah.
I never knew that.
Written and directed.
After Bonfire The Vanities, he was like, ooh, that better.
That's a Di Palma movie.
Yeah.
I never knew that either.
That bomb so hard, he's like, I better do something low.
But that was out of that wasn't to Palma no territory. No, but your Tom Hanks territory. No, absolutely not right very very weird
Decisions or choices. Okay, sorry some guy in the Netherlands a fan of Dupalma
had read this like
See in an interview or read an interview with Dupalma where he was like raising cane
Here's the script I wrote. It was in a completely different order completely different structure
We didn't think it worked. The studio didn't like it. Nobody liked the way we set it up
Here's what I wanted to do and I regret that I didn't even though the movie was successful
So this guy in the Netherlands
Edited the movie together right exactly how De Palma originally wanted it. It's very different all the scenes are there
but they're in a completely different order and I watched them both one is kind of a fun thriller the original way it came out
The other way that he redid it is fucking awesome. Okay, and like what a what a dream for a fan. So then De Palma saw it
loved it
halted the release of the Blu -ray and insisted that they put this Netherland dudes cut on the Blu -ray now without
spoiling anything. Yeah for me
What are the differences between the two jet broad broad strokes here?
The differences are the film is structured in a completely different way and it starts out as the woman's story, the liturative itch's story, and like this creep kind of muscling in on her and she's not the guy she married is who she thought but at first she's just like carrying on an affair, you know it's very romantic, and then you realize there's this creep in the background.
The original way it's told comes from the point of view of Lithgow from the jump.
You're like, this guy's crazy. There's not a lot of surprise to it.
It's kind of by the numbers deal.
The final shot of Reisencane, both versions, is, you know, like the best of Hitchcock.
It's an awesome shot. I thought that if you do rent it, honestly, and this is rare,
the the I guess you'd call it the Netherlands dude cut is the preferred version
okay they call the directors cut on the Blu -ray but it's it was edited by
some dude and it's a great you know if you got the editing equipment tinker
around with some of your favorite movies maybe you'll get them a new release now
I will check that out uh speaking of which uh along similar lines the
The Exorcist III Blu -ray is about to be released.
I'm very excited about this.
The first movie, Joe, and I watched together.
It is true.
Who knew this is where it would lead eventually?
I don't know who's releasing it.
I don't see Scream Factory.
It is Scream Factory.
It is Scream Factory, OK.
The Exorcist III Blu -ray is being released.
And for fans of that film, you probably
are very familiar with the fact that there
was a William Peter Blattie cut that followed the book
more and was I guess perhaps a little darker. It's a pretty fucking dark movie though to begin with.
That was lost in the fire or whatever. But this new Blu -ray is going to have that cut on it
that they've assembled together with, you know, outtakes and B -roll and whatever the hell else.
So I'm very excited for that. I put that on my mom asked me what I wanted for Christmas.
That was one of the things I asked where if she doesn't get it for me, I might throw a temper tantrum.
do they make it all see I what I used to hate in the early days of DVD was when
they would say like it's I remember it with Alien 3 which is not a masterpiece
by any means no it's not they're like here's the director's cut of Alien 3 so
he's sitting down to watch it you know like okay he notoriously battled with the
studio there's an amazing documentary on the Alien 3 Blu -ray about how like David
Fincher just screaming at these people and disgusted with the studio and on
So I'm like, I would love to see Fincher's cut.
I love David Fincher, and you sit down to watch it,
and it's like a flip book of drawings appears.
I don't think that's what this is gonna be.
I hope not.
I know one of the big, the biggest view
between Blattie and the studio was the studio
was like, you have to have an exorcism in the film.
That makes sense.
And Blattie was like, but there's no exorcism in the book.
I guess to the end of the book that's not there.
right and they were like yet to have it so that drastically changed the ending
of the movie but I will say this I love the movie as is I look forward to seeing
the new cut the exorcism sequences the least interesting part to me the
entire film yeah because it feels like it feels like do you know sort of do
diligence at that point in the movie like the truly scary stuff is the
innovative stuff that bloody does earlier on that we hadn't seen before and you're
I'm not going to get exorcism scenes scarier than in the original
exorcist. No. So I don't think you ever could ever have you
watched the new actresses show. Not yet. It's gotten rave reviews
and I'm curious to watch. I mean, look, the fact that Fox is doing
it as a good sign, Fox isn't scared to throw their nuts out on a
table now, which is nice. I'm not an American horror story fan.
I think the show has potential. But yeah, I just can't wait to
It tries way too hard to shock you with sex stuff and it's just kind of annoying in childish to me
But I love the first one and then I watched like my my girlfriend loves it
I watched the first one or two of every season and I'm like that life's too short. That's what I did
I was glued to the first season. Yeah, and then the minute spoiler alert if you haven't seen it the minute it becomes
Beetlejuice yeah, where it's like we need to scare people out of this house, right?
but I was like, this is the fucking ending,
it's Beetlejuice, that annoyed me.
But I said, all right, I'll give the next season
a shot anyway.
And every season except the newest one,
which I haven't seen any of, I've watched the first episode.
And without fail, there's a moment where I'm like,
why are you trying to show,
it's like a child trying to shock me
with what he thinks he's allowed to say.
Yeah.
So in the firm, in asylum, it's the girl with the guy from, what's that band, the band,
the guy that's in the band, that's in like the sort of wrap around story.
Oh, more in five.
Adam will be.
Yeah.
The part where she's like, if you go in here, I'll let you do put it in my ass.
You're like, yeah.
Okay.
Channing Tatum's one.
Uh, that's Channing Tatum's wife.
I didn't know that.
Jenna Dewam Tatum.
There's the thing in the circuit in the freak show one where the guy with the flippers is
prostituting himself to finger women. It's like I don't it's too much. I don't need to see this
I agree and no woman
No matter how depraved is like yeah, I want to get flippered in my in my puss
Well apparently these fucking depraved chicks wanted to any final thoughts. Oh, go ahead
Well, have you seen the Paul Schrader exercise? Yeah, you must have I own both versions thanks to you Pat
wash, gave me the blue race set. I own them too and I've seen neither of them. I've seen both of them. I
bought both of them separately on DVD and I've watched both. In my opinion neither are very good.
Shrater 1 is a bit better if I remember correctly but neither are very good and it's very
unfortunate because it's a case of great writer, great director, great cast, you know you got
guard in there playing uh father is it father Mary and I guess is the older
president uh you know this is the exorcism that scarred him for life this is the
one he's afraid to revisit in in the original film it's just got all the
makings of a great movie and it just doesn't just doesn't work I don't know
what it is boring is piss oh yeah uh exorcist two is very bad very bad and man I
really tried to hang in there. There's a couple cool scenes. I actually like that
sort of dream machine scene that everybody shits on. I thought that was kind of
cool. But Exorcist 3 to me is wonderful. It's a breeze very cool. Wonderful film.
I just saw you know to do my little wrap up on the movies I've seen. I saw a
Paul Schrader. It was supposed to be a double feature with Taxi Driver up the
Egyptian in the sound broke. It was an evening of Nicholas Cage, Paul Schrader, talked after
this movie. It was called Dog Eat Dog, Willem Dafoe, Nicholas Cage. Movie opens. Willem Dafoe
has a mild disagreement with his heavy -set girlfriend. Stabs were repeatedly killing her. Her teenage
double date with our friends Vince and Georgia Georgia left about an hour into this thing uh I thought
that this was Paul Schrader's best movie in years probably since affliction which affliction is a
fucking amazing movie if you haven't seen it with Nolte and Coburn some of the best acting ever but
doggy dog was a blast it was insane it was very violent Nicholas Cage uh was awesome to foe was
awesome. Cage gave a talk. He was as crazy as you'd want to be. We were talking
before this podcast started. The first thing Nicolas Cage said during this Q &A,
somebody asked him a very simple question and he goes, you know, I was in
Marrakesh working on a film and like the crowd was just kind of like laughing
like, of course you were in Marrakesh working on it. And of course you're
answering the question this way. Yeah. And the best part was he goes, now the
The rave scene, the song playing in that rave scene was written by my son, who's here
tonight. Was his name Weston? I don't know. You ask me like, this is common knowledge.
He's like, he looks like a Rob Zombie character, like long hair. He looks like a wrestler with
like, I make up on. And he goes, my son wrote the song. It's every actor's dream to appear
in a scene where your son has written the music for the scene. So that's something anyone
would ever think of. Sure. And the sun sitting in the audience, I think Weston cage. He goes,
I love you dad. And Nicholas Cage goes, I love you too son. A huge sold out crowd watching this
moment. Completely insane. Paul Schrader was hilarious. In person, the movie was great. I saw other
people. Chris Kelly's movie, a very funny writer for SNL. Extremely emotional movie. I haven't even
heard of it. It's a, you know, a very true story about his mom dying of cancer.
His mom's played by Molly Shannon. It's Jesse Plyman's. All right.
Uh, movie was amazing. They do something with the song Drops of Jupiter that is
one of my least favorite songs ever. Right. I won't ruin it for you, but they do
such an amazing thing with that song that it's one of my favorite things I've
ever seen in a movie. Okay. How they use it throughout. Um, again, uh, one of the
best movies of the year. Other people, great little indie movie, extremely
depressing of course but also very funny. I saw Snowden, Oliver Stone Snowden. Zero
interest. So boring. I thought the documentary about Snowden was fucking boring. I don't
necessarily think he's a hero or a villain. I just don't give a shit. You know, I think of course
people are invading our privacy because the world is collapsing into the sea. Right, you know,
I don't necessarily give a shit. Oliver Stone kind of treats him as a hero. Cage was in the
Stone as well cage was in that to very restrained his hair is insane at this point. He looks like he's had a facelift or something. Right. Stone's not great.
I saw our masterminds. What do you mean? Is this all you do? No, we're talking over since the last month, but okay. All right. Masterminds. I mean,
The Gallifinacus wig, you know, everybody in that movie is fucking funny.
I love the director, I love gentlemen Broncos, very underrated, and of course he didn't
pull me in dynamite.
He does someone click a great movie.
It's very bad, and everybody in it is funny and trying, but it's a great like true crime
story that actually happened, and he's got everybody in like Prince Valiant Wigs and pants
suits and stuff, and then they show you at the end, which was a mistake, Gallifinacus
with the real guy and it's just like a normal hick yeah like why did you make
everyone look like beyond cartoon right right right that one was a bummer and
then I saw Sully which you know straight forward an old -fashioned entertainment
I enjoyed it I would see Sully I haven't seen it yet it's they'll send the screen
in your watch it it's 90 minutes Hanks is great my favorite part about it you
can't spoil Sully you know what fucking happen with Sully but they do this
They end it with like a golden girl's blow like a sitcom ending where they'd all like pause freeze -frame
They're taught they're doing the hearing I think they're all laughing for the end solely this very serious very serious movie and at the end
Eckhart they they asked them. They're like well, you know
We apologize you guys obviously did your best this hearing is adjourned right and
And they're like do you guys have anything else that you'd like to disclose or say at this time is that is there anything?
You wish you'd done differently about that fateful day on the Hudson and
Eckhart goes well there is one thing I would have done differently. I would have done it in July and
the entire room
laughs
Explosively they cut back Eckhart's laughing like
ha ha ha. Hanks looks over at him and Hanks is shaking his head like in slow motion like
you old hilarious son of a bitch and then the credits roll. I love it. I cannot believe
that they ended solely with that but they do. I love it. That's like the ending of a like a Rodney
Dangerfield movie. Exactly. That's great. But so you know it I like how he's would make some movie.
It's very straightforward. He does one cut of everything obviously but I will tell you now the
movies I saw go on lights out thoughts huge disappointment okay huge
disappointment my god that movie was was just given accolades I was highly
disappointed yeah Nicholas Cage I saw the trust today very good I I
recommended highly I thought it was very funny okay and I enjoyed watching
Nicholas Cage sort of downward spiral slowly through the film it reminded me of
Jerry and Tom the Sam Rockwell Joe Montana film which is one of my favorites. You got to see that movie. That's a movie. I
Saw the Phantasm remaster wonderful looks beautiful looks gorgeous buy it if you're a fan. Don't rent it just buy it and
Finally Blair Witch which I'm gonna bite my tongue on because I feel like we're gonna probably
Yeah, I was supposed to see it this weekend and didn't so no comment yet on Blair Witch
but it's coming. Folks, that's your episode. I don't know what else the hell you
else you want. That's an hour. Where do you want from us? I plug it away,
Patty. Well tonight, and unfortunately this isn't going out live, but tonight I am on
drunk history telling the story of Buster Keaton. So it's the second episode called
legends and an aired on October 4th, you can catch it in reruns or Hulu or whatever else.
I think Hulu, it's a week after. Tony Hale, Buster from Rest of Development plays Buster Keaton.
Billy Joe Armstrong, the lead singer of Green Day, Portray's Charlie Chaplin.
I have not seen it. I'm going to leave this podcast and rush home and watch it because I can't tell
you how much anxiety it gives you to know that all of your friends and family have seen you drunk
on television and you have not seen it. So I hope that I did well. But on it
before it all worked out, I'm sure this did as well. Very good. Again special
coming up October 13th go to blacklist blacklist NYC dot com for tickets 730
and 930 taping at the Masonic Temple at the Hollywood Forever Cemetery in Los
Angeles. And I will be in Galway for the vote vote of film comedy festival
Halloween weekend, again, doing comedy shows, but also doing a live recording of
an episode of We'll See You In Hell, which has been a presentation of the
Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail, executive produced by Ken
Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment for press opportunities advertising in
queries, and info about We'll See You In Hell and all the other shows you can
contact Ken. It's Ken at Fangoria .com. Thank you. Night y 'all.
You