I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, we'll see you in hell back for the fourth and final installment in our December series of
episodes. A Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year, as that approaches. I hope it is happy for you.
We're here to talk about Nosferatu. Correct. Another Dracula movie.
Yeah, we'll get there. But yeah, a much more traditional Dracula movie than I'll say I was expecting.
I was surprised myself, given that it's Robert Eggers, I thought maybe it was going to be some
strange metaphor for Dracula or something like that, but it's like, no, it's Dracula.
You know what's weird about this movie, I won't get into the movie, but just the promotion around it,
I, did you ever think you'd see a Robert Eggers film getting like, like promo swag in the theater?
Like, you know, they're like, come on in and get our coffin bucket for your popcorn or whatever,
you know, it's weird. Yeah, it is weird, and I think that because they're doing that, people
are going to be very let down by the movie, because it is not a commercial popcorn movie.
Yes, it is the standard retelling of this tale, but like, its methods are not, it's not the commercial
movie of Bram Stoker's Dracula was, you know? No. I watched mine on a screen, or my buddy saw it
theatrically, and he said that the audience laughed hard the entire movie. Laughed? And I was like,
I didn't even find it to be campy or anything like that, like The Lighthouse is a much funnier movie
than this. And he was like, no, it was mocking, this is stupid laughter. Really? From an LA crowd,
which is weird too. It's like, all right. I'm surprised to hear that. I'm surprised to hear
that, but we'll get into it. In the meantime, Pat, what are your, this is probably going to
come out before Christmas, so what are your Christmas plans? Well, Joe, I'm going home to
Missouri. Tomorrow morning, I go to Kansas City. I'm going to my friend's Christmas party there,
and then me and my buddy Mike are driving home to St. Louis, where I will spend about a week,
see my friends and fam. Yourself? Pinkstone and his wonderful wife, Jessica. Yes. Are coming in.
Love Pinkstone. I don't know, three days before Christmas, and staying with me for the duration
of the holiday. They're here till the 26th, and we're spending Christmas morning together.
Yeah. You know, waking up the three of us, giving each other presents, and then departing to
the horrors of our own families to do that sort of thing, and then regrouping that night again to
what I can only assume will be get shit faced. So I'm looking forward to it. They get in
on the 22nd, so some quality time. We'll eat a lot of bad food, meaning bad for us, not delicious
food, but bad for us. We'll listen to a lot of music. We'll play a lot of video games. We'll
and I'm very happy about it. I love it. Maybe some year I'll come out there. I'm always looking for
something to do at Christmas. You're welcome any time. You ever want to come spend Christmas with
me? You say the word. That's an open invite. All right. That's an open invite. Maybe we could do a
holiday special, get a film crew out and just me and you spending a week together, a reality show
about it. Get a rent a crane, crane shots. Yeah, no, I'm excited. I love Christmas. I kind of like
the whole traveling and craziness of the airport shit. For the first time in my life, the Burbank
Airport, the best airport in America has opened up a Missouri flight, and that's changing everything
for me to not have to go to LAX tomorrow morning is just a dream. I got a 15 minute cab ride to go
to like the world's smallest, chillest airport. It is the best. Yeah, I have San Diego at the end
of January and I'm coming, you know, I'm flying out for it, but I realized that if I want to put LA
around San Diego, which I probably will, I'm going to go from Austin instead of Pennsylvania
and I can, I cause I'm going down to Austin for New Year's and I can, I'm like, Oh, I can fly
direct right into Burbank from Austin and it's like three hours. Oh, what a dream. Yeah. You know,
Burbank, I just flew to Vegas out of Burbank with this girl I'm seeing and we, they let you
de -board from the back of the plane, folks. They let you board and de -board on the front and back
to make it go faster and smoother. And have you ever experienced that at any other airport? And
why not? Why the fuck not? Yeah. Vegas has figured out a way to sexualize even the flight
experience. Exactly. You can take it from the back or the front, however you like it. Yeah, exactly.
What's your poison? If you do live in Los Angeles and you're a single man, I highly recommend the
Friday 5 PM to 9 PM flight to Vegas because it is all strippers and just gorgeous, gorgeous,
gorgeous women. The flight is that long or you just mean fly in that window? If you leave between,
yeah. If you leave basically in that like 4 PM to 9 PM, they're all going to Vegas for the weekend
to strip and then they come back on Monday. After I've ever spoken to any of them, I just
admire them from my seat creepily. One of my movies for the movie corn today will
tie somewhat into Vegas. Okay. And I'm very excited to talk about this movie,
but I'll hold my tongue until then. Is it leaving Las Vegas? No. No, it's a much dumber movie.
But - Is it the hangover? No, you'll see. You'll see. I forgot, we forgot to watch the Superman
trailer, but I - Yeah, we did. I do have a news psycho kind of trailer. I'm assuming I saw that
you didn't. Okay. Because I feel that you - actually I'm shocked I didn't text you about this. Did you
see the trailer for - I know your friends are involved in the show. I'm not going to be an
assault, but - Okay. Karate Kid legends. They had nothing to do with that, so you can speak freely.
I have not seen the trailer. Is it - I don't get it though. I'll say that. Is it Jackie Chan and Machio?
Yes. So isn't the Jackie Chan Karate Kid a standard remake of the original and not a continuation?
No, and I will tip my hat to them for this. I saw it. Figuring out how to fix that issue.
The big thing with the Karate Kid remake was it wasn't karate, it was kung fu, and everyone was
like, why is this called the Karate Kid? This doesn't make any sense. And everybody was like,
why is Jackie Chan not playing Mr. Miyagi? Like, why is this called this Karate Kid? It's not the
same story. And now in this, it's the Jackie Chan character seeking out Machio. He's got a new -
the Jackie Chan has a new apprentice. Jaden Smith is not back. Big surprise.
Jaden Smith was - I don't know why they made the Karate Kid a fucking dick.
Jaden Smith was worse than the bullies in the Karate Kid remake.
If you think he's a dick in that movie, why don't you watch his interview that he just did where he
builds people beds and he puts a note in the bed frame, which is fine. You're like, that's a nice
thing to do. And at the end of it, he goes, I am a carpenter. I make things with my hands. That's
what I do. Like, he says it like he's throwing the mic down. It's like, you know what? Smith family,
we've had enough. Enough. Have you seen that legendary interview with him from maybe five
years ago or something where he's like, you know, he's 16 or maybe even younger, 14 in the
interview. And he's like, I'm just like, like, have you ever been like talking to somebody and
they're like, I want to talk about this movie or I want to talk about this song or TV show. Like,
can we talk about the geopolitical situation in America? You got to watch this clip, Joe.
He's talking about like fellow 14 year olds talking at lunch. And he's like, why can't we
meet the Smiths? I'd fucking watch that in a heartbeat.
Myth reality show we got was Will Smith getting back into shape and crying
because he couldn't lose his COVID weight or whatever. It was like, that was
one of my favorite cat Williams jokes ever though, is when he talks about the interview
where Jayden Smith said, when I turn 18, I think I will cut my dick off.
And cat Williams be like, and he said, it's so gangsta. I had to respect it.
Yeah. Chris Rock was on, he hosted SNL this weekend and look, I off it while watching
baby girl, which I'll talk about. We've, we've talked too much, frankly, about Nicole Kidman's
face on this show and it's not fair. Chris Rock has had extensive plastic surgery now.
You think?
Joe, watch him on SNL. Here's the only reason I say you think. I've met him many times in real life
because he's around the New York comedy scene. So I've sat close to him, whatever. I'm not being
diplomatic. I've never, there's never been a thing about him that made me go, he's had work done.
This is new. It's not.
Okay. All right. I'll take a look.
Uh, yeah, he, it's almost like a, a new skin or something. Like it was very odd and off -putting
and I, you know, I confirmed with friends who watched us and now they were like, oh yeah,
some sort of weird face situation or something. But, um, he was funny. He had a really good
monologue. Um, the show itself is just rarely what you want it to be. Oddly weekend update
remains the highlight. Like it's always got good jokes and you realize how rare it is to find a
day's world. I'm relieved about that because weekend update is where the people I'm friends
with reside on that show. So you can keep saying, yeah, I'm relieved about that.
And when they do the, that bit, which is like the, it's, it's such a genius way to get really
edgy R rated comedy back on television, but they do that bit where Colin has to read three jokes
written by Che and vice versa. And Che writes jokes that make Colin look incredibly racist
whatever else. Um, it's a great bit. They do it once a year and it's funny. And there's always
a sketch that's good. You know, I think that show suffers from the person deciding what heirs,
Lorne Michaels, a 80 year old man who hasn't suffered a day in his life. It's like that
should not be the man picking your comedy. Watch, you should watch the clip of Jim Brewer
on Rogan where he talks, this is an old clip, but where he talks about the experience at SNL
and Rogan in turn talks about news radio. Yeah. And so, so they start by talking about it
and, and Brewer's like, yeah, it's not a friendly environment. And Rogan goes, yeah, it's weird.
He goes, when we did news radio, he was like, they were the nicest people on earth. He goes,
everybody was so nice. He goes, Dave Foley would be like, what if you said this and that would be
funny or give this joke to that person. He goes, everybody was trying to help each other. And he
goes, he goes, Phil Hartman turned out to be a wonderful guy. He goes, but it took months for him
to relax. Yep. And then he said, finally, one day Phil Hartman was like, geez, you know, this is,
I was just so used to SNL. It was so mean and so competitive and so vicious. Like I've been so
and like, he said, he finally opened up, but Brewer talks about like peep, they're, they write on a
server. So the head writer and everybody can see what you're writing in real time. And he talked
about like, that sounds terrible. They had to write some shit on paper to get to the good stuff.
He told you, you can't be thinking like, you can't be thinking about that. That would drive me insane.
So he said, he told the story. He was like, he was like, you'd be writing a sketch and the head
writer would come in and be like, Hey, I saw you're writing this and this. And he goes, just so you
know, I'm doing that already. And like just, they would steal stuff and whatever. And he talks about,
he talks about somebody stealing his sketch. He goes, because he goes, the strategically,
what you would do is if you had a big host coming in, you'd say, I'm saving my A plus stuff for that
show. Cause it's going to get your most eyes on it. And he said, he was holding a sketch for like
Joe Pesci or something at the time. And he said, somebody came in and he said, somebody came in and
goes, the example he used, I don't know if it was really, no, no, I think he said this was really
what it was. He said the sketch was Joe Pesci reading, I don't know, green eggs and ham or
whatever to a bunch of kids. And he was like, and the joke is, is it's Joe Pesci and he's being
iconic about the children's story. And he goes, they go to the table, read. And then before he can
pitch another staffer goes, I have a thing. It's Tony Montana from Scarface reading books to children.
And Brewer said he, he like took the guy in a room and was like, I will knock your fucking teeth
down your fucking throat and screamed. And this is the part where I wanted to stand up and cheer.
He goes, I'm not from the writer's world. I will fucking knock you out. I was like, yeah,
that's an awesome thing to yell at somebody. But he said when he quit, the reason he quit was
because he saw the writing on the wall. He knew the end, he knew they were going to cut him.
He said the head writer, I forget who he said it was hosting. Oh, it was Matthew Broderick.
Yeah. And he said, he wrote a monologue for Matthew Broderick and he goes, the strategy
with SNL is you want to write for monologue and weekend update because if your stuff gets,
it's a different group. So if your stuff gets in, it stays in and you shine and they can't fuck with
it. Whereas with the sketches, they can fuck with you. So he goes, they wrote, he said he and somebody
else wrote a monologue for Matthew Broderick. And then the head writer also wrote a monologue
for Matthew Broderick. And at dress rehearsal, Matthew Broderick goes, I know you want me to do
yours, but Jim's is better. I want to do, it's funnier to me. I want to do his. So they did
at dress rehearsal and it killed. And he said, and then after dress, the guy came up to him and he
goes, listen, I know that yours killed and everything, but we're going to do mine.
Despite what Matthew Broderick said. And Jim Brewer goes, I'm going to go talk to Lauren.
And the guy goes, no, you're not. And Jim Brewer said, because there was this thing where you can't
go talk to Lauren. And he was like, I don't care anymore. I'm not scared. I'm going to go talk to
him. And he said, he went and talked to Lauren Michaels and he said, Lauren Michaels said to him,
Jim, you're too nice to be in this business. And he was like, and I gave my basically gave
his resignation. Cause he was just like, this is it. They're going to fire me. That's the end.
And that's how it ended. Like, you know, too nice to be in this business is a thing, man.
It'll kill you. I've seen it. It did. It nearly killed me at a few occasions.
The, I only kind of tell my funny celebrity stories about SNL, but the overall vibe of SNL,
I was there for six months in a, you know, in a low role, but above an intern,
I was always around the, the hosts, the musical guests, the cast, the writers,
and they're all dying inside. And some of the most talented, funny, gifted people in the world
will come up to me and be like, did you hear if Lauren said anything about my sketch? Did Lawrence,
when Tina, when Tina came by, did she say anything about my sketch? And you're like,
dude, I remember, you know, I love Rachel Dratch, but like you'd see these people like crying
because like they thought they did bad at a rehearsal or whatever else, or they'd bomb and
it's rough stuff. There's no reason for a job to be like that. There's no reason to make people who
are, you know, older than 20 years old, stay up all night, two nights a week writing and leave at
seven in the morning. It's just, it's while Lauren goes home at 10 PM, you know, meanwhile, we would
watch the dress rehearsals live. You know, they bring it up. They have a whole different audience
for the dress rehearsal and the live show. They're three hours apart. So the dress rehearsals, two
hours, the live shows, 90 minutes. Every single week, the funniest sketches, the hardest laughs,
the most, cause you know, SNL does have great comedy writers there, despite these sometimes
not great comedy on the show. Lauren would never pick the sketches that were the best, the funniest
and arguably the funniest and best sketches because an 80 year old man's opinion of comedy
is not only out of touch, but it's wrong. Your opinion of comedy is wrong at 80.
You shouldn't be doing it. Yeah, I don't, uh, it does not seem like a pleasurable experience.
You can't not care when you're in the situation. You know, I remember, yeah, I remember Karen, uh,
Karen Kilgariff said to me once about a writing job she had. It was after we both did Pete's show
together and had gone on to different writing jobs. And you know, we would, we would commiserate
about the headaches and trials and tribulations of a writing and a staff job or whatever.
And she was on a job and she goes, you know, you always say to yourself,
it doesn't matter. I got hired. They're paying me either way. I'll sit in the corner. I'll write
my little jokes. And if they use them, great. And if they don't, who cares? I'm still making money.
And she goes, and you can't do that. No, your brain will not let you not care. And she's right.
It doesn't matter. It's, it's, it drives you crazy. It just drives you crazy. It's a weird.
Well, so there are people who don't care. You don't want them on your fucking staff. I'll tell
you that much. And a lot of the time, the people that don't care get ahead because, oh yeah,
they're, they're, they're deemed easy to work with or whatever, you know? And yeah, you know,
well that's what, you know, I, I had very few breakdowns while running shows. I had many at
home alone, but I would just be like, you're, you're talking to me like, I don't deeply love
this show and want it to succeed. You know, I'm not against you. Like the, the, I, I desperately
want this show to work and be funny because my fucking name is on it. But also like,
I, who cares more than the person running the fucking thing. And it was always this attitude
of like, you're trying to do this. Or we think you're trying. I'm like, no, I'm trying to make
it good. And it's oftentimes the others, the other side is not, or, you know, they're just not.
Tires, Tires was the only show I ever worked on. And it was probably due to the fact that it was
a bunch of guys that were not brought up through that system. And had to have a -
That was always sunny too.
Yeah. They had to have a writer's room because it was union rules and it was,
it was their first foray into it, whatever. It was the only writing staff I've ever been a part of
where it was very much, we know what you can do and when we need you to do something, we will ask
you to do it. We are not going to waste your time making you spin your wheels and be busy,
do busy work and, and whatever. We will employ you to do what you can do. And it was very
straightforward. And that was the only time I'd ever experienced it like that. Every other,
and that's not me knocking Pete's show. I had a great time on Pete's show, but Pete's show
was a different story because I was, I was a monologue writer. That was my job. It was very
cut and dry. But other shows I've staffed on, not that they were all bad or not that they were all
great, but there was an element of you're here. We have hired you. Therefore, if you were not
doing something, every waking moment that you're here, we're wasting you or whatever. You know
what I mean? And I don't think that's the best way to do it. I think you got to treat it like
it's the X -Men. This guy's good at that. Have him go do that. This person's good at that. Have them
do that. You know? Yeah. The issue is, and we experience, I mean, I experienced this,
you experienced this a little too, cause you were insecure about it, but it, there's a, there's a
thing you're not, you don't want to do and you're not trying to do as the boss, but you, you do it
a hundred times a day. When you say you're good at this, you should go do this. A writer who is
naturally a insecure and often mentally damaged person goes, well, he doesn't think I'm good at
anything else. Or like, you know, I would say you two are great, you know, go do the jokes or
whatever. Then he'd be like, so do you think we're not good at story or what? And it's so competitive
and you know, everyone's trying to get in good with the boss. It's like that, that stuff ruins
writer's rooms immediately. And you can try to, just like what Karen's saying, I would do a
speech every year, like an hour long speech of like, here's what we're not going to do in here.
And you wind up doing it by week three. Right. You know, it's like guys, we all know how much we
hate in a writer's room, how like gossip destroys the room and like, you know, when the boss leaves
and everybody starts talking shit, like let's just not have that environment here and voice problems
and three weeks in you're doing it. Everybody's gossiping and closed doors and whispering and
everything else. Yeah. Human nature. Yeah. Unfortunately. Yeah. It's not great.
But yeah, the always sunny guys, when they were hiring in the early seasons of always sunny,
which is when I worked there, they were actively looking for people who had no
TV writing experience. We don't want somebody who's learned a bunch of shitty habits to
come in and make more formulaic TV, you know. Did you see, by the way, sorry, speaking of formulaic,
or maybe not, well, I don't mean that, well, I'll just say, did you see the new Mission Impossible
trailer? That's another new psycho I forgot to mention. Not only did I not see it, I'm surprised
they have one ready to go. Is there a stunt that can compete with driving off that cliff?
I will tell you, this is why I said speaking of formulaic, I turned the trailer on thinking
this is going to be the most formulaic thing ever because I really didn't like that last one. And I
think they've run out of gas in this vehicle here. This trailer is fucking awesome. I was like,
this looks fucking awesome. And is there a stunt? There were like four things in the trailer where
I was like, is this the big stunt? Like Tom Cruise is doing so much. It's a scene where he's like
hanging on the side of an, I know they did the airplane thing in one of them, but there's another
airplane or helicopter thing where I'm like, I think he's really doing, it looked nuts. I was
like, this looks awesome. Simon Pegg is claiming that this is like, this is it. He's like, we are
going out with a massive bang. Like this is the last one. That's what they said. This is supposed
to be it. Cool. Yeah, a friend of mine who listens to the show was pontificating the other day that
may be the best franchise of all time. And it's hard to argue because of how many there are and
how they're all good. And the worst one is like still way better than average. And it's called,
so the last one was called Dead Reckoning Part One. This one is called The Final Reckoning,
which I think they retitled it that instead of Dead Reckoning Part Two,
because Dead Reckoning didn't do as good. Well, I thought just to imply like, this is it guys,
the final, you know. But you know, it's the usual suspects. It's Chris, well,
no, it's not the usual suspect. Wait, yes it is. It's not Macquarie?
It's gotta be. No, it is Macquarie. Yeah, he, but he's,
yes, he's directing. And then I guess he co -wrote with Eric Gendresen? Gendresten?
Gendresen? I don't know. He wrote, he did Band of Brothers or whatever. All right.
And yeah, it's Macquarie, you know, who's, well, Brad Bird, wait, he's part four Brad Bird. Part
five is where I thought the, I thought the series was solid up until that, but then five,
Rogue Nation to me is where it's like, holy shit. That was -
I mean, it kind of became a different franchise there, but I, having just rewatched the entire
series, one is fucking awesome. It's a Brian De Palma movie. It's not, it's not these current
ones we get, but it's great. Two, the weakest, the John Woo one still has some fucking cool action
in it. Three has Philip Seymour Hoffman as the villain and it's great. And then I don't,
you know, the other ones all kind of blend together for me, but in this way where they're all
just uniformly excellent. They're just a different thing than that first trilogy, I think.
Yeah. What was four?
Like really, to me, the last four or five could have been one big long great action movie,
Ghost Protocol is four. And to me, it's, it's pre -McQuarrie, but to me,
Ghost Protocol is where the franchise shifts. Yeah.
The first, the first one, well, the first one is extraordinarily different. The first one is a very
much a Brian De Palma movie, like you said, but it's, it feels like Brian De Palma doing a serious
take on an old, sometimes campy, but beloved TV show. Two is like classic mistake of big or
better sequel that this doesn't land and spins off the rails. Three to me feels like a reset.
And then four to me is where it's like this, the story we are in now to me is set in four.
Yeah. And, you know, and there are elements of it in three, but to me, four is really where it's
no, this is where it becomes what this franchise really is. It's kind of a miracle that Mission
Impossible didn't kill off James Bond. Cause when you look at it as like, when it started out,
it was going to be like a competitor to James Bond. Like we got a new spy in town. He's younger,
he's hotter, and we're going to have some big action set pieces, whatever the James Bond formula,
but they very quickly started kicking the shit out of those Bond movies. Even the really good
Daniel Craig ones. It's like, they can't, they can't hold a candle really. And Macquarie's career
is interesting because he, you know, he wrote Usual Suspects, of course, but he was like slipping
in a huge way. Like, I don't know how he got the reins of this franchise, but he's done such an
excellent job with it. Cause he did Usual Suspects, then he wrote and directed The Way of the Gun,
which is kind of trashy fun, but like didn't do well.
The dialogue in Way of the Gun is almost unbearable.
It's too Tarantinian. Yeah. Then they let him do Valkyrie, which he did not direct, but was okay.
His next directing thing was Jack Reacher, which kind of bombed, but it was okay. And then suddenly
he gets the reins of this franchise and that's, that's what he does, but he just found his niche,
I guess. And you wouldn't necessarily think from Usual Suspects that his niche was going to be these
insanely, you know, jaw -dropping action sequences. So kudos to him. Cause that was the whole appeal
of Mission Impossible early on is it was going to be a different director each time and give you a
different stamp. So it was DePalma, Wu, JJ Abrams coming off Alias. And we're like, okay, like,
let's see his take on it. Brad Bird. And then they just decided like, no, we're set. So I kind of
missed that different director every time thing, because that's kind of like watching an anthology
movie. It's kind of a fun way to see how people interpret the same material. I would have loved
to see Tarantino's Mission Impossible, which he flirted with for a little bit, but I'm glad it's
I will start with
Carry On, my nicest surprise of the week.
There have been such a glut of Netflix action movies, usually starring one of the Chris's
and on a gray poster, you know, on a plane that's going down. Marky Mark has made like
plane thrillers for Netflix in the last three years that nobody knows about, even though they're
always the number one movie on Netflix. Like, it's just where these talk about the opposite
of Mission Impossible, just junk, shitty movies where they pay a star $20 million to do a paint
by numbers action script. And I guess somehow they break even on Netflix. I don't watch them. I just
stopped at a certain point, The Gray Man and even Gosling did a couple of them. You know, they just
bleed together and I don't watch them. This one only jumped out because I saw Jason Bateman
in the cast. I love Jason Bateman and outside of Ozark, we haven't got to see him do his thing
really in a long time. So I was like, you know what? I'll check her out. Carry On is a really
good, really well written, really well acted and directed and fun action movie. I liked it a lot.
It stars Taron Egerton, who played Elton John in Rocket Man, which I liked as well.
It stars Sophia Carson, who I'm unfamiliar with, but I wanted to make out with as his wife.
Logan Marshall Green, who I love. He's kind of the poor man's Tom Hardy. He pops up
in a small role as a detective and then you got Jason Bateman as the villain. So for the first half,
you got Bateman talking to him, kind of like how Jeremy Irons does in Die Hard 3. So it's just
Bateman over the phone, but he's got a perfect phone villain voice. It's amazing Bateman has
not played more villains, but he is great. His voice, you know, he's got such a sarcastic nature
that him fucking with somebody is funny and entertaining and you believe it.
And then Bateman's in it more than I thought. He pops up and he's actually a physical presence
in the movie for quite a while as well. It's a great cast. It's this guy,
Jean May Collette Sarah, who's been doing all these Liam Neeson action movies. He also did Orphan
and then his career kind of took a wild departure with Black Adam, which lost, you know,
a billion dollars or something. So he's gone back to his roots, a small little thriller.
Clearly he's more comfortable doing that. I love these movies. This movie is basically
Die Hard 2. You know, it's an airport set action movie. There's lots of twists.
They never get too ridiculous for me. I loved it. It's really, really fun. You know, it's a Christmas
set action film. I would have rather seen it at the theater, but I dug it. It's well worth checking
out. Get some use out of your Netflix subscription for once and check out Carry On. Joe? Well,
by the way, I didn't even say what it is. It's nerve gas on a plane.
Okay. So it's one of those classic speed type movies under siege that came out weekly in the
nineties. And this would have fit right in, but it's a B plus better than average example. It's
a film tangentially related to Vegas because it has to do with porn and the porn awards.
Bucky Larson, born to be a star.
Saw it. I've seen it. Folks. Wait a minute. Stop though. Oh, it's Dickie Roberts' child star.
Yeah. That's the David Spade one. And this is? This is Nick's full title again. Bucky Larson,
born to be a star. Okay. I didn't know born to be a star was part of the title. Stars Nick Swartzen
as a buck tooth kid named Bucky from the Midwest with the Fargo accent,
who is a cashier at a grocery, a bagger at a grocery store, who,
after going to his friend's house where they're going to watch a porno movie and have a circle
which he's unfamiliar with how to masturbate and his friends have to teach him how to do it.
They watch the movie. He realizes his parents are the stars of the movie
because they were porn stars in the seventies and he never knew. And instead of being mortified
by this, he's enthralled and he realizes his calling in life is to become a porn star.
The problem is, is he has a micropenis and ejaculates before the woman even touches him,
but can ejaculate bucket loads of jizz and can ejaculate multiple times, which makes him a star.
It is an insane movie. Is it a good movie? No. Did I laugh my ass off?
One thousand percent. Sometimes I remember texting a friend as I was watching it,
saying like, cause he's a big fan of all the Sandler, the Sandler verse, all the, you know,
he'll watch, you know, bench warmers three, they'll go deep. And I was like, look, man,
this is probably maybe the worst of the Sandler verse, but I have been laughing real hard
throughout. It's just fucking funny. It's really funny. It's one of my favorite things
when a comedy does this, when a comedy just goes, let's just make the stupidest movie we can think
of. Every dumb joke we can go for, let's go for it. The amount of stink and stench jokes they make
in this movie, Stephen Dorff, who plays the evil porn star at one point refers to Christina Ricci's
vagina as her stink garden. Ricci's in this. Ricci's the love interest. Holy shit. Don Johnson
plays a porn director called Miles Deep. Clearly before he had his comeback. Yeah. One of the movies
he directed was called P .U. in the good way. I mean, there's a movie in it called Welcome
to the Stink. I mean, it's just so fucking dumb. I laughed my ass off through this entire movie.
And then the scenes where Nick Schwartz and his master, he goes into a commercial audition,
he doesn't understand that there's a difference between regular movies and porno movies. He thinks
it's all the same. Uh huh. And he goes into audition for like a Tide commercial and starts
whacking off because he thinks that's what the audition is and everybody's screaming.
It is an insane movie, but boy did I enjoy it. And I, anything, Nick Schwartz in anything to me
is usually magical. Like, there's very few things. That's why I'm very pumped that Swartz, I used to
love his Comedy Central show, that man that used to make me laugh. Yeah. But he is playing Sandler's
Daddy in Happy Gilmore too. Oh, that's awesome. He's got, he's like the second lead. So that's
awesome. I'm pretty pumped about that. That's great. Yeah. Cause I saw that standup clip of
him where, you know, it's semi made the viral rounds about three months ago or something where
he had an off night and it wasn't crazy, but he kind of got belligerent with the audience. Now
it's like, Oh, I hope he's not losing his mind or something. But no, he doesn't. I know the clip. He
doesn't get belligerent. He talked about what happened. He said he ate edibles and they hit
him and it was too much. And he's not belligerent. He's just being like, wait, so what's up? So
what's going on? He's just not, he's not doing well performance wise. Yeah. Yeah. And the crowd's just
like screaming at him and he's, and then they just take them off stage and he's like, yeah,
sorry about that guys. Yeah. Which, okay. Who amongst us? I watched on Disney plus Elton John
never too late. The tagline is he risked everything to find himself, which is kind of ridiculous.
But I love Elton John. I have always loved Elton John. My family has always been big into Elton
John is just music's always been around as I think most people would say his music is part of our
society. You know, what, what I loved about this was an opportunity to see him performing a lot
in the seventies and performing like, you know, like he's doing Saturday nights, all right for
fighting, but it's like seventies coked out rock Elton John, which you never get anymore. But like
him fucking kicking the piano bench, like Jerry Lee Lewis and like bashing the keys and going nuts.
There's some amazing performances in it, but then also what just, it kept blowing my mind again
and again and again that this man was the, he as at least according to the documentary, the biggest
rock star in America for at least a five year period. And he is constantly wearing the most
flamboyant and ridiculous clothing I've ever seen in my life. So at one point wearing a Donald duck
costume. Yes. He is not bald, which can be a cool look. He's like 40 year old male pattern balding,
you know, like big clumps of hair missing and a big sort of alien looking head. So it looks even
worse and he is destroying. And then when they cut to the audience, it's like young hot girls
screaming and losing their shit Beatles style. Yeah. And that is the conversation I am really
looking forward to having with my mom when I go home tomorrow is I want to know like,
what did people think of Elton John? I asked her this when we watched Bohemian Rhapsody together.
I was like, so did the guys that loved how hard Queen rocked, were they just in denial? Were they
pretending? And I really want to know just what the vibe was with Elton John. Was he a sex symbol?
Were the women there like, I want to fuck this guy. I'm going to ask all these questions because
that's what this movie raised in me. Frankly, it was a different time for stardom.
You simply can't be a star now and look like that. It's not possible. I always found him fascinating
because he looks like your dad or something. Not your dad. I'm saying a dad. He looks like
your uncle that comes over for the barbecue and brings a mini keg or whatever. And he's a rock
star. It's the oddest thing in the world with Elton John. In his absolute prime, you will not
believe the hair on this man's head. You just won't believe it. But that's what I loved about
weirdly. That's what the movie was about to me, is that in this era or that's what I took out of
it. That's not what it's about. But in this era of most celebrities have to look amazing.
In this era where it's not enough to look as jacked as Harrison Ford did in Temple of Doom,
when he takes his shirt off and he'd been working out for months to get that physique.
Now he would look scrawny. Now we got to be the rock. Now we got to do Zac Efron. We got to be
times have changed. And I think what's scary about that is that we're going to miss out on
the next Elton John because he looks like Elton John. Yeah, that man would not, I guess he'd have
to write songs for other people. And then that's okay. And I guess what's his face? What's the
redhead guy's name? He's a pretty good example of like a Ed Sheeran. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ed Sheeran, I'm always often mesmerized by how regular he looks, you know? I always say -
So maybe it could be done. Maybe I'm wrong, but it's such an exception to the rule.
Well, it's like we talk about with actors. It's like Giamatti got in under the wire.
He was the last like Mathel type they were going to let in.
Yeah. And I think the movies are so much more boring now for that reason.
Speaking of Mathel types, I watched -
Well, I was going to finish my little review here, Joe. I was just talking about that one
aspect of it. But the movie itself, I listened to Elton John read his own audio book and I
fucking loved it. He tells this whole story. It's amazing. Rocketman, I thought was a great
sort of musical retelling of his life. The problem with this movie is that it's basically
doing an album by album. You're like, oh, this is great. We're going in depth on Elton John's
career. They stop going in depth on his albums in like 1978 and he's got 40 more years of a career
to go. So I know his later stuff wasn't as beloved or was, you know, but like they don't even go into
like the Lion King and shit like that. And you're on Disney plus no less. So it's a weird sort of
half finished documentary. It felt a lot like the Beach Boys one and the Jim Henson one where it's
Disney plus. You are a streamer. Get back, prove that people will watch the Beatles sit around
talking for eight hours. It's going to be one of your biggest hits. So why not give us a full
fucking four part Elton John documentary or Beach Boys or Jim Henson? We care. We want to know more
than just the bare surface minimum about it. So as much as I liked the documentary and seeing all
this live performance, it's an hour and 45 minutes and you don't feel like you could get a full
picture of the man. It's him narrating at his age now with his kids and his husband as he prepares
for his last show at Dodger Stadium. And there's some great stuff there, some great reflection,
some great looking back on his life interspersed with some, some cool footage, but give us the full
version or give us the option. Say if, Hey, if you kind of want the overview of Elton John's life,
Wikipedia page, watch the hour 45. But if you want the full thing, here's an eight hour version.
Isn't that what streaming is supposed to be? That said, the movie is moving. I liked it. If you're
an Elton John fan, watch it, Joe. Well, I'll call an audible here. I was going to do a Walter
Mathel thing, but I'll do something different given what you're talking about. Cause I didn't
even think to talk about this, but I watched on YouTube a documentary about Phil Collins called
Phil Collins Drummer First. It is two solid hours and it is a sit down discussion with Nick Collins,
who was the, who's Phil Collins' son and an exceptional drummer who played drums on the
last Genesis tour because Phil Collins, because of a spinal injury or condition was unable to
play drums at all anymore. And that last tour, he had to sit in fact in a chair and sing
cause he can't, I don't think he can stand and he's got trouble walking and whatever.
But the, this documentary was about how Phil Collins before anything was an impeccable
drummer. And in one of the greatest drummers of all time and how much his drumming influences had
on music production and drummers in general. And they really get deep into the early Genesis stuff
where Peter Gabriel was still the lead vocalist talking about how much of Phil Collins drumming
in this art rock band was influential on metal and what metal drumming became like him using
double bass drums, meaning literally two bass drums. The gated sound effect that he puts
on the, his drums that he's known for, obviously most famous, that drum filling in the air tonight,
that sound becoming a sound that people mimicked and wanted to also do. And then them just talking
about the stages of the band and him going from the drummer to the lead singer and also still
playing drums in the band, all that he's produced with other artists, they talk extensively about
that drum fill and in the air tonight where he's just like, he's like, I didn't sit down and try to,
I didn't think of like, this is an iconic drum fill. He's like, we did a bunch of takes and that
was the one that worked best. So we used it. And then people started to say to me, he talks about
drumming on a Tears for Fear song that he got hired to do. And they're like, okay, so at this
part, we want you to come in and do like the in the air tonight thing. And he was like,
what do you mean? Just like a big fill? And they're like, yeah, yeah, like you did in that
song. And he's like, he's like, so, you know - Was it Head Over Heels? Because that sounds like it
has the in the air tonight. No, it's a song I don't remember. It wasn't one of the
big songs. Okay. I mean, maybe it was, but it wasn't a single that you or I would know.
Anyway, and they get into a solo stuff and they even start breaking down some of the solo stuff
that sort of gets dismissed because it's in the poppier years, obviously, of Phil Collins. And
they talk about like, how booming and awesome the drum parts. There's a part where his son just is
playing the easy lover drum part without the music. And you're like, this fucking rips. Like
this guy is, you know, it gave me, I always really loved Phil Collins and really loved Genesis,
but it really gave me a heightened respect for him and what he's done for music,
what his talents are. It made me go back and start fishing through the older Genesis stuff
because I was always more of a fan, not the latest era Genesis stuff or the, you know, like -
Can't dance. Like I like that stuff, but like, you know, there's a real sweet spot for me with
them, like with the self -titled and Abicab, where they're not quite invisible touch fully pop yet,
but they're also not like doing seven and a half minute art rock stories about a kid who dies,
then his spirit comes back through the radio or whatever. You know, it's a really, really
interesting thing. And it's really nice too, to watch him reflect, talk about his life,
and accept where he's at physically now and stuff without it being like this tear jerking,
overly emotional experience. Like he's not there to make you feel sad for him or to say,
my plight and it's been tough. He's there with very few regrets, no regrets, even says at one
point. There's nothing I wish I would have done that I didn't do or things I thought I should have
done differently. He just talks about his career and he's very pleased with seemingly all of it.
And it was awesome to see. It was really cool too, to see how proud his son is of him and
what his son learned from him. And they're just interviewing drummer after drummer after drummer
in this thing, a lot of talking heads and everybody from drummers of all different types of bands,
from metal to pop to whatever, that just have such respect for this guy. It's really, really cool.
I really enjoyed it. And especially as a drummer, I thought it was an awesome documentary.
And it's two solid hours, man. When I first clicked on it, I thought it was going to be
this little seven minute thing. And I was like, holy shit, this is a full feature length movie.
I don't know why it was only on YouTube. Yeah. I wonder why they wouldn't sell it to Netflix.
As I don't remember, maybe somebody in the archives can find out which episode it was,
but I met Phil Collins once and told the story on the show. I will not tell it again, but he was
insanely nice and stood up for me. And I liked him a lot on the set of the Tarzan Broadway musical,
where I was a PA. Folks, my third is called super slash man, the Christopher Reeve story.
And I will be fully honest with you. I am not really a Christopher Reeve fan.
Superman is, though it seems the original Richard Donner Superman,
was before my time. I was not born in 1978 when that came out. And I liked Batman way more.
I just always did and still do. I don't really care about a great looking guy in tights
who never does anything wrong. It's just not interesting or compelling to me,
which is my issue with a lot of superhero stuff. Christopher Reeve was the perfect Superman.
We've been chasing that high ever since. I didn't realize how tall he was. And I guess he was kind
of scrawny when he got the part and kind of had to bulk up for it. I enjoyed watching this.
It's tragic what happened to him. It's tragic that the most notable or memorable thing about
other than Superman is just that, that he was paralyzed. But the documentary is very sweet.
There's a lot of time with his family. They go out of their way to make sure we know that
this was not a perfect man in real life, especially with regards to women. He had very
serious commitment issues and some infidelities and things like that.
But at the end of the day, it's not really a warts and all thing because
there's not much bad shit to report about Christopher Reeve. For the most part,
everyone talks about what a lovely man he was. They talked to Robin Williams and Whoopi Goldberg
and all these people that were his friends in college and later on in his career.
And everyone just seems to be very inspired by him and love him and talk about
how he dealt with what happened to him, how he overcame it, how he became a great advocate
and spokesperson. And it's a good documentary. It's solid. It's about as much as I was interested
in Christopher Reeve. That's what I got. I learned a little bit. And if you're a fan of the man,
I would recommend it. Joseph? So I will do the Walter Mathau movie
since I mentioned it. I watched, well, it's not a Walter Mathau, it's an ensemble movie,
but I watched Hanging Up. I remember that being terrible, but again, maybe time's been kind.
Well, I watched it because I was on a Nora Ephron kick and have started to also explore some of the
Delia Ephron stuff. And it was sort of part of my Thanksgiving holiday watching. Nora Ephron's got
a couple bangers that come out every year at Thanksgiving time for me or during the holidays
in general. And this was one I'd never seen, but it starred Meg Ryan. The thing that attracted me
to it first was that, well, I've never seen this and it's a Nora Ephron movie that she co -wrote
with Delia Ephron. And it stars Meg Ryan, like I should see this. And then much to my surprise
and delight, it also stars Diane Keaton, who directed it, which I didn't know, and Lisa Kudrow,
great, and Walter Mathau. And it's about Walter Mathau being a father of three girls
who is slipping into Alzheimer's.
And it opens with him being brought into the hospital for some care and some testing where
he's going to stay for a certain period of time. Meg Ryan is the daughter bringing him in,
and you start to learn about the family. She's got two other sisters.
Lisa Kudrow is a sister who's an aspiring actress who's on a soap opera, and Diane Keaton plays
the oldest and very successful, most successful of the three sisters, who has her own magazine,
like O, she's like an opera type or something. And Meg Ryan is the one that's caring for the
more than the other two. And you learn about their estrangement from the father,
why the other two aren't around. And then you see a series of flashbacks where Walter Mathau
is a bit younger, and they're all a bit younger. And you learn about the relationship and he's
an alcoholic and he's a bit abusive and verbally abusive, whatever, emotionally abusive,
and a very flawed man, but at the end of the day, it's their father and they want to care for him.
And the sisters reforge their bond as family through this crisis with their father's illness.
It's very funny at times, it's very sad and almost disturbing at times.
It's not a great movie, but it is definitely within the emotional tone of a lot of the
Nora Ephron and Delia Ephron stuff. I have to think that it's somewhat autobiographical. I think
it's based on Delia Ephron's novel. Yeah. But I was like, there's a sister who's wildly successful
whatever, I'm like, this is clearly Nora Ephron. And she's being a sport enough to be in on the
joke of the other sisters making fun of her being the famous one or whatever.
And it was a very beautiful movie at times, maybe cry at the end and I'm a sucker for this kind of
in most respects, in the moments where he's charming and fun and whatever,
he's straight up Walter Mathau. I mean, there's a part in the hospital in the beginning
where he like gooses the nurse and he's like, he can't help but let that Mathau,
I'm not saying the goosing part is Mathau, I'm just saying the way he plays the scene.
And I'm like, this is funny, even when he's playing like an alcoholic, like rage addict,
the Mathau shit still comes out. So, I don't, Adam Arkin's in it. It's a good cast. It's a
very good cast and it's well directed by Diane Keaton. It's not a bad script. It just doesn't,
I don't know, it's missing something that I couldn't quite put my finger on.
But it's good. It's a good movie. Remember, it got terrible reviews at the time.
Terrible. Yeah, I don't recall specifics, but I don't remember liking it.
I'd say if you're in the mood for, and it takes place, the holidays, the flashbacks are all
over holidays through the movie. So, there's like a Thanksgiving flashback. I think there's a
Halloween one and then there's a Christmas one. So, it plays into the holiday season.
It's about family, three of our most charming and talented actresses alive, and then Walter
Mathau, and it's all right. It's an all right little flick.
Folks, let's get to the picture at hand. We are talking about Nosferatu,
directed by Robert Eggers, who brought us The Witch, The Lighthouse. What was the other one?
That's it. No. Yeah. Those are his three. Oh, the Northmen. Sorry, the Northmen.
Yes. Okay. So, I fucking love the Northmen. We talked about that on here.
Nosferatu, I would say, is shot more, I would say, of those three, it's more reminiscent of
the Northmen, but without that movie's sense of like bat shit weirdness, you know, kind of
stone or heavy metal. I remember that movie ending with like a warrior riding a unicorn
into the sun or the moon or something. I'd like to rewatch it, but I like that movie.
This is a very, as I said at the beginning, surprisingly to me, very straightforward retelling
of the Nosferatu legend. It owes a lot to Coppola's Bram Stoker's Dracula, which I am
prepared to say is my favorite take on the material. I think it is the best Dracula movie.
Me too. And I think people are starting to acknowledge that more and more. I don't know
if it's a younger generation coming up or what, but I've been seeing that opinion more and more
online and it's cool. Coppola's, let me just say this, Coppola's movie, and I hate to knock the
guy, it would be perfect if it wasn't for Keanu Reeves. Keanu Reeves is the weak spot in that
and he's fine, he's good enough, but if you had had a Nicholas Hout in that role,
in Coppola's thing, this would be to me at like Godfather status in the Coppola canon of films.
100%. I laugh out loud every single time when Gary Oldman comes in looking like he does in
that movie with the buns on his head, a thousand years old, and Keanu looks over at him, his face
has not changed, and he goes, call Dracula. It makes me laugh so hard because it's like he
couldn't have been directed. Like when you see him, you have no reaction, Keanu. That could not
have been the direction. It's like, dude, what are you doing here? Yeah, if you ever watch the
behind the scenes stuff of that movie on YouTube, it's great. Some Oldman blowing up, yeah. Yeah,
Oldman in the full makeup. I love when you see this, when you know they're shooting and you see
how fast the guy can slip into the character and then it's him just in the full makeup being like,
well mate, then what the fuck are we doing then? It's very strange to see, but it's very funny.
Well, so here is my issue with this Nosferatu and I think, you know, my guess, my estimate is that
Coppola made Bram Stoker's Dracula when he was around 60 years old, a man who could have just
been retired and resting on his laurels, and that movie is so inventive, so visually inventive.
He does so much, you know, going into past film technology. There are scenes, I forgot about this
till I watched it again recently, like the little like practical effects he does throughout this
movie are amazing. And I think this movie is super influential as well, Bram Stoker's Dracula.
So why is Robert Eggers a much younger man kind of coming up in his career who's done all these
visually exciting and experimental type movies? Why is he now at this stage of the game doing kind
of a very traditional, at times a little dull retelling of this story? It reminded me of
one of Herzog's Nosferatu because it's the same movie.
Like the rats are what I really remember about Herzog's Nosferatu, just like the rats in every
scene and they had like thousands of rats shipped over to the set. And there's rats in this one too
and it's like, are you trying to shout out a few of your favorite movies? Or are you trying to
give us your own new take on the material? I would have much rather it been his own take on the
material. This felt very, I gotta say like basic to me. It wasn't taking enough chances. The only
chance it takes is it gives Dracula a big Freddie Mercury mustache, which is a choice.
Well, I think the interesting thing is the Herzog version, he changes all the names back to the
he makes Dracula, Dracula, he makes Jonathan Harker, Jonathan Harker, whatever. Eggers,
which this was supposed to be Robert Eggers' second movie. He wanted to do this after The Witch
and then he couldn't and now he's doing it now. But Eggers clearly is making
a remake of the original film, of the original Nosferatu film. I mean, he keeps all the names
changed, all that stuff. And I have not seen that silent film in a long time,
so I don't remember if all of these elements are just in that or if they're elements from the book.
Is he remaking the silent one or the Herzog one?
He just said, I'm remaking Nosferatu, so I don't know. I don't know if he made which he...
My point is, I don't remember the silent one enough to know that if these things he's doing
are things he's taking from the Herzog one or if they're things he's taking from the original one
or that they both took from the original one, because Herzog is a remake of the original one,
or if they're things that Eggers and Herzog both took from the book,
that the original silent movie didn't have in it, I don't know. I did think
that this was more visually interesting than the Herzog version.
Sure, yes.
I thought it was certainly creepier. It was very creepy, which was great at times.
It was very well acted. My biggest distraction, and you've already mentioned it,
was that they made Nosferatu look like Vlad the Impaler, like all those old pictures you see,
drawings of Vlad the Impaler. He's got this mustache, and the mustache was taking me out of
it for two reasons. Number one, Nosferatu's body is rotting, which they show many times,
when he feeds, you'll see his back and it's got open... It's rotted. You can see organs and shit.
So, it's weird that he has hair growing too, on top of that, which is just weird.
And then secondly, this is going to take me into Jeepers Creeper Zone.
What's the... The vampire is grooming his mustache?
It's not like...
Carefully, precisely grooming his mustache, yeah.
Because they show at one point that he has some hair, but the hair is like strands
and remnants, like other parts of his head have rotted away or whatever,
but then he's got this mustache that's perfect, and you're like,
he's trimming his mustache? I don't know. It was very, very distracting to me.
And it also made him look less scary, like a vampire with a mustache, it's just not scary
looking. It's, you know, I don't know. It would have been...
When it's like moving towards the camera, like floating over you like,
with the mustache, you're not scared. It feels like you're getting molested, if anything.
Bill Skarsgard plays Count Orlok, which is Dracula, much like it. It's a performance
where it's like the voice is modulated. There's a lot of CGI. So,
it's like we don't even really get Bill Skarsgard. He's this weird actor that I feel like I don't
even know, even though he's played these two iconic characters, because he's always getting
help from other sources. I don't know if he's not good or what, but certainly not a memorable
Dracula compared to the other portrayals we've had. Lily Rose Depp plays the bride, you know,
was Isabelle Hubert in the original... Not Isabelle Hubert, Isabella Johnny in the original art
song. Lily Rose Depp, I only know from A, being Johnny Depp's daughter, and B, the terrible show,
The Idol, where she was naked for seven straight hours. And she's good in this. She's effective.
You definitely buy that she's in this weird love triangle between Nicholas Holt and then this
dark force. And that triangle playing out is the most, I thought, successful part of this.
It worked for me. It was spooky. It was scary. It made me feel bad for Holt getting cucked by a vampire,
you know. I enjoyed myself. This is a story that works. There's a reason a Christmas carol has
been told a hundred times. It works. But my only real grievance is when you get a guy who I consider
to be a really exciting film artist who's done three really, really interesting movies and visually
spectacular movies. I just wanted more. My expectations were not met, but I certainly
enjoyed the movie. I'll disagree. I thought that the only reason my expectations weren't met was
because, again, the look of the vampire wasn't as scary as I wanted it to be. I mean, that original
silent movie, it's so scary looking. Yeah. And I guess they tried to make it where he could almost
pass. See, when they first started, I was like, I guess they're making it so he can almost pass
as normal in the shadows. But then they kind of blow out of that and he doesn't care about trying
to be normal. He's just a monster. So I was like, well, then make him a monster. Just make him
scary. So that part I didn't get, and that took me out of it a bit. I thought visually it was
stunning. I thought it was very well directed, very well paced for the most part. It could have
been 20 minutes shorter. And emotionally, I was invested. I was pained for Nicholas Hout's
character. Yeah. This is a thing that always confuses me with the Dracula story, is, excuse
me, the love interest, the Anjanu is always, I guess it's supposed to be a little bit of both.
Maybe I'm just dumb, but it always seems like the Anjanu is always like,
he's seducing me and I hate it and this monster has a grip on me. But then it always seems like
she's into it and whatever. And I get that that's kind of the point is like, it's a spell.
But in this particular story, she's very aware of that. She's very aware of the
connection between her and this thing. And she doesn't like it
to the point where she's willing to sacrifice her life at the end of this
to save the day and kill the vampire. But there's this scene in the middle of this thing
where she's confessing to her husband, I have had visions of this guy my entire life and he's been
seducing me my entire life and I hate it and this and that, whatever. And then in that scene,
she's then giving herself in the next breath over to the vampire and then she starts trying to
have sex with her husband and he's into it. And I was just getting confused. I was like,
I don't know what's going on. Is she part of this or is she not part of it or is she a
victim of this or is she not a victim? It got a little convoluted for me and I thought,
here's the point. Well, the point I'm getting at is this. In that scene, I just was like,
I was like, this scene is confusing me now where I'm losing the thread of what it is they're doing.
And it did, I know you're making a joke, but it did kind of give me the impression
that it's like, guys, what you're saying is that the woman is manipulative and is into this.
I took it as this guy, Count Orlok is irresistible is how I took it.
He's disgusting. Yeah, but for whatever reason, irresistible.
This dynamic plays out all the time in real life, you know, why is this woman going out with this
hideous troll and they have a weird pull, a weird control, you don't know.
But then I was also mad at Nicholas Howt's character when she's like,
as she's like on her knees, like having like spirit sex with the vampire that when she turns
to him and like, is like, have sex with me now. He does it. I was like, no, don't do that.
Be like, what the hell is wrong with you? I have some self -respect. What are you doing here?
I don't know. It just bothered me. I mean, look, pussies pussy, Joe, but no, it's a folks.
It's weirdly, yeah, it's a horny movie, a horny take on the material.
Um, I don't know, man. It never quite clicked for me. Of course,
Willem Dafoe is running around in this thing with an accent. You knew that.
You knew that before you bought your ticket. That's another part that confused me.
When, when Nicholas Howt realizes that the secret plan is she's going to seduce Dracula now,
he's going to go to her, she's going to have vampire sex with him all night until the sun
comes up and then he, and then, and then he'll die. Right. That confused me for two reasons.
Number one, when Nicholas Howt realizes that that's the plan and that's what Van Helsing
or whatever his name is in this was up to Willem Dafoe starts laughing as if to be like,
we tricked you. And it's like, you wouldn't be laughing. You'd be pleading with this guy.
Like this is the only way to stop this plague that he's brought onto the whatever. Right.
Then the other element in that was if we burn the beast's coffin, he can't return to it to sleep.
And it's like, well, that's irrelevant. He never tries to return to it because he has so much sex
with Lily Rose death. The sun just comes up and he dies. And I'm like, what did you have to burn
his bed for? That never even came into it. Whereas in Coppola's, they're racing to get back to the,
he's racing to get to his coffin and they catch him outside and trap him from getting inside.
And that's how he dies. And in this, I was like, I just don't, but again, I was like,
I guess they're going really close to the original material. And that's the point of this,
but I never read the book. So I don't know. I tried. I read Dracula ages ago. I mean,
and we've had how many versions? I mean, if you want to count fucking Nicolas Cage and Renfield
and all that. Speaking of Renfield, Ben Mendelsohn, I guess, gave an interesting
performance as Renfield. Was that what it was? Ben Mendelsohn? No, that wasn't, no, that wasn't
Ben Mendelsohn. That was, I don't know who that guy was. Help me out. Help me out. Who was he?
I never saw him before this movie. So Aaron Taylor Johnson plays
a dude in this. Who, by the way, as I was saying earlier, I don't think is a great actor.
Aaron Taylor Johnson has several scenes in this where you go, he's acting right now. He made a
decision that he's going to like get choked up on that line and it's very obvious. Like he's,
I thought he was out of his depth here. I really did. So wait, we're not getting a, who, wasn't
that Mendelsohn? Help me out. Who plays Ralph Innocent? Who's Ralph Innocent? Simon McBurney
is who you're thinking of. I don't know who that is, but he was the Renfield character.
Aaron Nock. Okay. And it was Tom Waits in Coppola's. The best Renfield ever is Tom Waits.
He's awesome in it. Ralph Innocent was great as the doctor.
Yeah. I mean, it was pretty good. I mean, it was, you know, it was well put together. And I,
this is a movie, I will say, I feel like if I watched it again, I might like it more.
I just don't see that happening. I came away without like one super memorable image or moment
or anything. And I just, I was sad about that because I love Eggers and I wound up with Eggers
on my face. I respect Eggers. I don't love them in the way you do. I think the lighthouse is an
interesting piece of work and it's very well made. It's not something I would ever watch a second
time. I did not like the Northmen, which I made very clear on here for reasons. I stated at the
time, I won't go back into them. The Witch, I loved the first time I saw it. Upon second watch,
I was bored to tears. I think Eggers is a good filmmaker. I don't think he's for me.
Whereas Ari Aster, I think is a complete fucking hack. And it was also not for me. But the only
reason I bring him up is because the two of them are sort of neck and neck as the new
arthouse horror guys. True. Yeah, this, I don't know where this goes. I mean, my thinking is this
is not going to have a huge audience. They're releasing it at IMAX on Christmas day. And I
just can't imagine it being a big smash hit, but maybe I'm wrong. It's got no star power,
no star power. It's a Dracula movie and I just don't see it being a smash personally. I don't
know why. Last year, the big hit was Anyone But You, a romantic comedy on the beach.
So like, they learned nothing. There's no romantic comedy coming out on Christmas.
I thought, I would say Steeler of the show goes to Lily Rose Depp. I thought she was great.
I thought there was a lot of emotional investment and demand on her required for this part. And I
mother should have played Keanu's part back in the day. That would have been awesome. Yeah. Oh,
wow. And I think he was with Ryder too. I bet you they offered it to him and he couldn't.
They must have, yeah. But I thought she was great. And I thought that,
like you said about Billy as old Drek there, I think he was good. It's hard to tell because
you're like, is that his voice? I don't even know. Yeah. The voice is kind of cool.
Very cool. But yeah, it's not, you know, you don't feel like you got to know this Dracula
in the way you do with every other one. Yes, there was a -
I agree. There was a distance, you know, people complain about the Coppola thing
that they add this back love story to the movie that's not there in the book. And it's like,
yeah, but guys, that is what justifies the entire story. Him seeing the picture of Winona Ryder
and realizing she looks just like the love I lost where I was betrayed and all this stuff,
and she killed herself and it was the worst thing ever. And that's why I'm cursed because I cursed
God because of it. All of that is what drives the whole story. And it makes perfect sense.
And then you're in, you believe in this. They eventually explain what their connection is.
It's pretty thin. It's just like, she is one of the gifted that is able to see to the other side
or what, you know, and you're like, yeah, okay, she's the only one. Like, there's like, I don't
know. And I do like the detail that he was sent there purposefully by the Renfield
parallel character because it was requested by Dracula because
I mean, no, no, that doesn't even make sense. I was going to say because he has to get to the
girl, but it's like, he's Dracula. He could just get to the girl. Why does he need the guy sent
there? Why does, by the way, why does Dracula need to buy a house?
For being a centuries, literally centuries old story, tried and true. This movie is super
convoluted and confusing in spots. Like just things were not landed properly. I don't think.
But do you have an answer to my question? Why does Dracula need to buy a house? Why can't he
just go and unleash the plague on the city and just kill everybody and take the girl?
He does not need a house, but I always think of Dracula as being sort of upper crust and elitist
and wanting to show off his wealth and taste and class. That's why I take him for doing that.
They repeatedly say, why do you want such a decrepit old house with all of your money? They
never. Because it's spooky. What? I mean. He's tugging at his tie. Is anybody hungry?
Tell you what's scary is this real estate market. Am I right?
You know what? This movie makes no goddamn sense. Maybe I'm out. I don't know. I thought I
kind of liked it. The more we're talking about it, I'm really confused. If you're wine drunk
at 9 PM on Christmas day night and your cousin's like, Hey, I got to join out in the car. You want
to go see Nosferatu? Yes. Yeah. Go, go see it in the IMAX. I can't even say I didn't like the movie.
I enjoyed it. And my hog is for the most part up. I'm not sure I'm going to be able to maintain
this erection, but it's for the most part up. I liked the movie. I just wanted more and I feel a
bit let down by it. And the more we talk about the story, I realized he convoluted a perfectly
workable story and made it less workable. Well, my thing is, is did he convoluted or is it just
because the source materials from the 1800s and it didn't really make much sense to begin with?
Perhaps. This is why I think every time people complain like, well, that's not like their book.
It's like, well, maybe the book doesn't make any goddamn sense and people have to make it make
sense. Right. Yeah. So yeah, my hog, I guess in the spirit of the holidays is up enough,
but in the spirit of New Year's Eve, the balls are dropping and I don't know that it'll be up
for very long. But yeah, I agree with Pat's take. If you have a chance to see it, see it.
And I think if you're in the mood for just some spooky visuals, you'll have enough fun.
Folks, we'll be back in January with movies yet to be picked, but as always, we appreciate your
support. We appreciate all of you during this holiday season, as we always do, but at a little
extra love to you and yours at this time of year, we wish you a very happy, happy holiday.
Happy holidays to all. Merry Christmas. Happy Hanukkah. Happy Kwanzaa. Happy whatever else
you celebrate or if you don't celebrate at all. Thank you for your continuing support.
I will be doing the Pat's solo movie corner sometime between now and New Year's Eve,
probably closer to the holiday. Merry Christmas. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.