I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell. We're back to talk in the month of, oh Christ, what is this? Is this, what are we in? March? This is March. Yeah. So we're in the second half of March, and we're here to talk about here. Oh good, Joe. Thank you. On the spot I came up with that. Joe's been texting me all week. Can we record this? I got something really hot I want to kick off the show with.
And now we know what it was. Now we know the answer. You know the answer. You know the way I do it. Did you know this, Pat, about here? I actually took several notes on this movie. This is one of the. Rarely do I take notes for a review, but I do when it really hits me in a certain way. Here is one that I took notes on. But the thing I want to say now before we get to the review. Did you know this movie is based on a graphic novel? I did. I haven't read it.
But I did know that. I just want you to imagine going to a comic book store. Standing before all the thrilling books you could buy. Batman, Tales of the Crypt, Alan Moore's Swamp Thing, Frank Miller's Synth City. And you go, you know what? Give me a copy of here. Yeah, I bought a Daniel Klaus graphic novel once. I'm a big Ghost World fan, and I like his work a lot. And so once in a while it will recommend me a graphic novel. And the one they think that I'm going to
love is called Mouse M -A -U -S. Oh yeah, people love that one. And it's like mice as Nazis, or maybe it's mice as Jews and cats as Nazis or something. But I don't care how powerful it was. I liked it better when it was called An American Tale. OK? And then I liked it even more when it was called Five Goes West with Jimmy Stewart. I think his last performance was Jimmy Stewart in a Five Goes West. It is a sort of wild.
thing to take the Holocaust and say, but what if we did it with rodents? It's wild. Wild movie. I mean, I learned all about immigration from that movie. There are no cats in America and the streets are paved with cheese.
Oh, you're talking about Fievel. Oh, you're talking about Mouse. Mouse. I think you're supposed to say it, Mouse, as in like. Mouse. Yeah. Like Kinski. Here is a Jesus Christ. I mean, I mean, at least Ghost World's funny. Yeah. Oh, you hate it here that we're getting to? Most people did. No, I'm just I'll get to it. But I'm just saying I just can't imagine where you're at. If you're like, this is the graphic novel I want to read. Well, not everybody jerks off to the riddle.
In their free time, you know, sometimes people grow up. I mean, at this at that point, go read Pride and Prejudice. You're you might want to graduate to books at that point for sure. I'll grant you that. Yeah, it's just odd. It's the weird thing to read in comic book form. What is the best graphic novel?
I my money always goes to. Kingdom come is tremendous. You know, the killing joke is tremendous. A death in the family is tremendous. Well, mine are all Batman ones. Batman. The long Halloween is tremendous. Like those are all very, you know, pretty resonant.
Story stories for me. They were they're just tremendous story. You know, Alan Moore wrote The Killing Joke and Alan Moore also did Saga The Swamp Thing, which is the best comic book series I ever read. I did not do Watchmen as well.
Yeah, Alan Moore did Watchmen. I've read Watchmen and then Frank Miller did Dark Knight Returns and Sin City. And, you know, those two guys were like the two titans of comic books. They were, you know, they were forces to be reckoned with.
I had a meeting at Jason Bateman's production company the other day and I met with his head of development and having a nice conversation with her. And I was like, who is this woman? I've never heard of her. And I looked her up. I'm not going to say her name, but her father, the director of Sin City.
That's right. Why don't you want to say her name?
I guess I don't know why. Why? You can easily look it up. But yeah. And then I had this weird thing now because it's the same thing as like, like there's all these things now that are just bad that weren't bad before. So I wanted to bring it up. But then she's a nepo baby. And that's a big problem.
You can't you can't call somebody out for that. So I just let it go but I wanted to say like hey
But you probably have some cool stories, you know, sure
You want to hear a hell of a story? Yeah, of course. It's gonna knock your socks off
I'm literally wearing
Underwear a white fruit of the loom t -shirt and socks so I could I only have those socks to lose anything else goes
I'm good. There's gonna be partial nudity. We're gonna have to change the rating of the episode
So I was just over seas
With Shane Gillis. Yeah, Shane was playing some
massive rooms some arenas in
Manchester Dublin and London
Big shout outs to everybody that was on that tour Chris O 'Connor
The whole crew Shane's whole crew everybody was the fans that came out
Everybody the whole experience was truly
Truly amazing truly wonderful. I'm so proud to see Shane doing that such a fun thing to be a part of
It was a really really amazing trip
So the last night we were we were in London and we did a show at the o2 arena which was insane and
Yeah
Sitting in the green room. I think I can talk about that. I don't think this is talking about school. I
This is fine. Yeah, I'm sitting in the green room and you know
there's some people coming through the green room that we're at the show where I'm like
Holy shit. All right
In walks
Fucking no Gallagher
It's a big one
Walks up to Shane. He's talking to him. He's all smiles. Uh -huh
Thingy or whatever the term is but I got to tell you this not that but okay, I'm sitting there
He's talking to Shane. They're standing in front of me. I'm sitting on the couch. He turns and looks at me and
Goes Pat just took off his headphones and walked away
I'm right here. I know I'm kidding. Yeah, no, Gallagher looks Joe
He looks at me and goes he goes, ah mate
You're fucking amazing. I was like
Well, nice to meet you sir, I think this is fucking crazy and we talked to
Noel Gallagher for 30 minutes
Wow was he as cool as he seems he was the nicest man ever told us some really funny Oasis stories. Yeah
And then when he was leaving he said to me
Shane's gonna come to one of the shows if you want to come just let let him know and he's got my number
You should come to one of the show. I was like
Yeah, I think I'll be there. Mr. Gallagher
Where are they playing the garden? I?
Think I think on the moon and they're gonna tell advise it down here. So I don't know
They're coming over. They're doing
15 shows here in like six cities. Yeah
I was I have multiple friends obsessed the one who lives in New York always sees him at Sonic watching World Cup on
Sunday morning at 5 a .m. At a bar. I'll see him. So he must have at least a place in New York
Yeah, he's he seems cool as hell he was super cool. I saw I just saw today on I
Guess it must have been fucking Instagram reels, but it was
There was a picture of it, but it was Noel saying that he had talked he had had a dinner with
Robert De Niro and he hit it off so well with him and he was like
I mean this this is like the ultimate for me and we talked he goes this dinner went on for eight hours
We're doing drinks and we keep talking we're talking about our his whole career and my whole career and everything
And he said I've never felt so cool in my life and at the end of the dinner Robert De Niro stands up
And he was my friend. It was great meeting you gives him a handshake and brings him in he goes now
Tell me one more time. What was the name of that band? You said you were in he had no clue
He just thought it was some dude which makes De Niro even cooler because he just talked to someone he thought was a
Shoeshine boy for eight hours. Yes. I agree. I absolutely agree. Um, I
I did I think successfully make him laugh at one point because I said I go so you're coming to the States
You're doing like 15 shows and he's I was like, that's it. He's like, yeah
And I go how many did you do in Europe like 20 and he's like, yeah at that 20 and I go
That's the way to do it I'm gonna do that I'm calling my managers tomorrow I'm going guys I'm not working for the next 10 years
And then book me 12 arenas. Yeah
Do dial tone
Did I guess it's an odd question to ask but does anyone know if he's speaking to his brother until the tour starts are
They like trying it out first. He he seemed like he was he was in good spirit
You know, he didn't my suspicion is that they can is that they hang out at holidays and they're totally cool and they get
A beer together and stuff and a lot of it is drama
I don't think it's like Morrissey and and Maher who despise each other and won't work together
I get the feeling that they're okay behind closed doors, but I got the distinct impression
I mean look he wasn't sitting I wasn't going so tell me what the deal what's the deal?
but like right I got the distinct impression the way he was talking about the shows like just he was just talking about them like
Yeah, yeah, we're doing this. That should be cool and whatever
I
Was I thought the same thing?
I was like I bet they're just like brothers that fight and like also know how to capitalize on it. Like let's fucking
Look take it into the press. No hard feelings and it'll be really funny. Yeah, and who cares, you know, like yeah, so
Anyway, he was super super nice man. He was super nice
Wild though real wild just a real unexpected
Yeah counter and then and then me and Shane and Chris O 'Connor drank 9 ,000 beers after that
to calm down
It was a fun time though man shout outs to everybody over there man, what wonderful people overseas I'll tell you Walsh too I
To different people while I was there
This country we're in is just sick
I was like you guys I go you guys still have a sense of country like there's camaraderie over here
Like yeah, you say the wrong thing the whole arena booze together
You guys are still with each other on stuff. Like this is a disaster over here
It is and I think more and more that thing that unites other countries will be their hatred and mockery of us
Yeah, and and it's it's deserved
Yeah, I say it'll I say it's so often that I'm probably going to be detained soon
But how is no one blowing up the country right now?
Like it is time it's prime time baby you want your head to spin I saw a video
Two days ago. I sent it to pinkstone. I was like you want to be even more confused with everything
Here's Tucker Carlson saying the perfectly right stuff about Palestine
There's a video Tucker Carlson be like
Whenever children are being killed that is not a win. We should not be bragging about that
I'm sorry Ben Shapiro is offended by it like
Every comment under it is like I hate this man, but man did he nail it way to go Tucker
What is happening right now the more the more of that we can get the more of people like
Saying something surprising the more we'll remember that everyone has different opinions and that's good
Yeah in a week, he'll deny that he ever said it. Yeah
It'll be like what's the fuck it's a bald -faced lie that was AI I keep that's a big thing
you know, I knew it was coming but the amount of conversations that I have listened to on
Instagram over the last couple weeks and gone
Holy shit, is this real then you go to the comments and it's 300 people going. Holy shit. Is this real?
No one knows where it's rough, dude
And if this was like a you know a conversation between Vance and Trump behind closed doors and if they were impressionist
They were amazing if it was AI it was amazing
It wasn't gussied up to the extent that I thought it might be satire
I was just like this is chilling and it sounds very real, but I have no way of knowing look AI can already
Perfectly mimic and
Create Morgan Freeman
Like I see video after video of Morgan Freeman narrating things that he didn't narrate. So if they can do that with Morgan Freeman
Trump is a no. It's like going up to an it's like going up to rich little going
Can you do Trump and he's like, can I do it? Of course
You'd never ask yeah, so like it's it's
The the impressionist knows how to do Trump without question if it's got a good Morgan Freeman down. Yeah, so it's frightening
Rich little I had a friend who saw rich little like within the year
Like he's still doing a residency in Vegas somewhere like in some some mop closet somewhere. Yeah, he's still out there man
It's wild. I mean he's still doing like Nixon, you know, like
He's still doing like Churchill
Yeah, let me see rich. Let's look this up rich little he looks good looks exactly like he always did showtime Joe
630 p .m. Wow the hard out at 730
we're at
Canada or Vega Laugh Factory at ooh, you hate to see this the Tropicana
that's
honestly as far as comedy clubs in
Vegas goes that's that is the oldest one like that is a sort of notable club
That's where dice was playing when I was out there
So yeah name a person or celebrity and little can drop an impersonation his Reagan
Sinatra and Kermit the Frog are legendary
All right, man. I promise you I I know rich little more intimately than most men
Not it not on a personal level. I just mean his work. Yeah
I promise you his Sinatra is not good. There's no way he does a good. So do you consider Piscopo great?
Do you consider Hartman great?
Nobody the only person that ever did a really truly great Sinatra now Piscopo and Hartman's are funny
But they're caricatures and really what all they're doing is this voice. Yeah, you punk
They just they do a deep voice and they say crazy shit and it sort of sounds like him
But not really Hartman's doesn't really sound like a bitch. Just really funny. Harmon's is great. Yeah. Yeah, it's just funny
I got chunks of guys like you and my stool. It's it's a man. Yeah, it's the comedy is amazing
Yeah, but Toby Huss is the only guy that does a truly like Toby Huss
looks and
Truly sounds like Frank Sinatra. He used to do it on MTV
They would do these promos where he would do Sinatra singing modern songs
Yeah, and he would be like come as you are and it he sounded exactly like it was wild how much how good the impression was
And he was just where was he doing this bit MTV? Oh MTV. Okay. Yeah, remember in the in like the 90s
There was that resurgence of swing. Well, obviously sure and then like Tony Bennett had a video on MTV
Yeah, it was during that
Yeah, I had his his unplugged album. I was into it. It was good. I
Talked about seeing him here on the show didn't I with his daughter opening?
Yeah, you said the daughter wasn't great, right?
She was terrible and she was clearly taking him out for one last cash -in before he died
He was he was beyond senile and she had to have known that it was her father
But it was him and a pianist and he's like, you know, this first songs about the time
I took a little trip to San Francisco. Nobody claps. I left my
Song songs are all two minutes so it ends and then he's like next up
He's a little song about my time in San Francisco
Kept going and going every time the pianist would go Tony Tony
No, Tony Tony
Little sad, but he sounded great, you know couldn't turn it off
Yeah daughters backstage, you know laughing with a cigar in her mouth, you know pulling in 20s into a bag has a bubble bath backstage
It's in her rider, but she puts it under Tony's name. Um, mr. Bennett, here's your bubble bath my what?
Who are you and who am I? Yeah, I love bubbles, baby
All right good only bubbles. I like a champagne is
Baldwin's Tony man Baldwin's Tony Bennett is kind of the definitive very good
He does a very good Tony Bennett
very watch the premiere of that show with him and his wife that he had to do because he's run out of money because he's
on trial for murder
What is this? What is this world we live in and?
He a I believe their love is real. I'll say that I like them as a couple
But I'll say this
She breaks his balls to the extent that the Baldwin I thought I knew would have thrown her out a plate -glass window
But she's clearly domesticated him, you know
Or else the world has broken him down to the point where he doesn't fight back anymore
Well, did you see the red carpet video?
Saw that there's a lot of moments like that on the show. So it didn't surprise me much but like he'll
He'll be like doing Tony Bennett around her and she won't even acknowledge
He's doing a bit like forget forget your wife not laughing at you
I mean she won't even give him the time of day and it's like there are cameras on you like
Your husband is doing a very funny bit
Laugh at him. This goes for all you up you people in marriage is out there laugh at your fucking spouse
We're all the only audience they got he did kill somebody so maybe she's maybe she's on a jokey mood. Oh
No, she makes plenty of jokes and he laughs at hers baby in that first episode
Is that the one where he starts telling the story and she's where he's like and I go in the locker room and her ex -boyfriend's
Dick is the size of a clarinet
No, that's that has not been on the show to my knowledge. That's no that's a clip from the show
He's he tells a story about how she was dating that baseball player he like goes in the locker room and he's like
You know, he's like they're all naked and I look up and here's her guy
He's got a clarinet hanging from his crotch and I'm go and I go. Oh, I see
Like these two are coming unglued
Why would he go see her ex -boyfriend in a locker room, you know
Pat that wasn't the question I was asking. Yeah, I'm always that this is why I'm a hardened police detective
I always ask the follow -up questions. I was asking
How is this the man from Glen Gary Glen Ross? Yeah
Well, she she does that her and the kids will show him pictures of himself from like hunt for red October and be like
We want this daddy back and he's like brother. I want it back, too
Unfortunately, it was 30 doughnuts ago
Keep talking for a minute because my mic stand is gonna fall off. I gotta read just keep talking for a second
I gotta reattach this. Okay
I always feel like Garth and Wayne's world when Joe goes off the mic
That's what that's my probably my favorite bit in Wayne's world because it's such a perfect and specific
Character beat is when Wayne leaves him alone for 30 seconds and it's like just vamp and Garth's immediately like oh god
And starts to panic it always makes me laugh had a friend the other day said he didn't think Dana Carvey was
talented and he actually put him in the bottom ten of all -time SNL people and
It was nearly a friendship ender. I wound up getting way too angry about it in a way
I usually don't let pop culture get me these days, but I went off on him. I was like and he was telling me
Here's the other thing
No disrespect to Mikey day. I know he must be a great writer. He's been writing on SNL for ten years
Said the man's never made me smile and he goes why think Mikey day is way funnier than Dana Carvey
I almost lost my shit
You people don't respect your elders
although there is something to be said about the cast when you're a kid being the cast that sticks with you and
Dana Carvey Phil Hartman all those guys were really my my cast leading into Adam Sandler Farley and all them Hartman
Yeah, I think Harvey's untalented. I'm like I was just like fuck you man
What were even his movies now, all right, if you want to talk about his starring efforts
They weren't good, but he is amazing in the Wayne's world movies and that's enough for me
Nobody's starring efforts from SNL were good
There were a few I
Gotta tell you I watched 15 minutes of the ladies man the other night and I was dying
I thought that movie sucked but but here's the thing that well
I remember when that came out and everybody was like I can't believe it. There's a good SNL movie
They were talking about ladies man. Yes, I remember that was like the reaction to it. Like my friends were like, dude
You wouldn't believe it. It's actually funny because all we had it was we were inundated
With Rob Schneider just just disgrace after disgrace. Oh, yeah
I'm not I'm not totally disagreeing with you that there were a lot of terrible SNL movies, but there were there were some good ones for sure
Now I actually
Because my dad was always a an alcoholic anonymous 12 stepper type. He really loved Stuart saves his family
He loved that character Stuart Smalley and the movies pretty good
It's like it's more of a drama than a comedy and that's what kind of sucks about it
Is that it's a serious drama with this giant broad sketch character in it. So it's kind of awkward, but it is good
It's it's a good dysfunctional family movie for sure. It's a drama
I mean, yeah, because you know because it stars Al Franken that nothing can be funny starring Al Franken boy
I agree. He's just that's my my friend was going off on Dana Carvey to such an extent that I was like
Are you thinking of Al Franken? But no, he wasn't
Yeah, the
That's a crazy thing to say about Dana Carvey. Oh speaking of funny SNL guys though, man. Kyle Mooney got me
He got in what
He's been doing this press thing of like I'm putting out a music album
It's called the real me like I saw a poster but no material like this is now
He made a video for a promo video. Yeah, and in the video you can tell he's not being totally serious
Right because he keeps like as he's talking about how music is his life and it's what he truly wants to do over comedy
He keeps getting phone calls and then like walking off screen and then like you'll
They'll do like the capturing from afar shot. Yeah, you hear him being like I'm not a clown anymore
I don't want to be and you're like, he's clearly joking like, you know, but
But I did think like no he's just making a funny video for his music album, right?
but then the album came out and like
you know, they're like these articles that are like like AV Club was like Kyle Mooney shocks the world with deadly serious music album and
I was like
What the fuck?
Like what is this? Like why is everybody freaking out about Kyle Mooney's music album? Like I'm sure it's good
But I mean God people are saying it's like a game changer and all the shit. I was like, so I went and listened to it and it is
fucking ridiculous
Yeah, it sounds like he recorded it in 10 minutes
Like it was making me laugh so hard at how
Half -assed he made it sound on purpose
And I was just like this fucker got me man. He really got me. It was really funny
I only see him with Heidecker now and Heidecker Heidecker's music thing is serious
Yeah, I never know what to believe there by the way, Joe
Speaking of some scary stuff. I sent Joe Joe and I both loved the band pavement and
There is a trailer for a movie directed by Alex Ross Perry who has done really good movies that I like super low -budget indies
He did her smell with Elizabeth Moss that I really enjoyed
Wait about like a poor way to love. What's that? Wait a minute
Elizabeth Moss is in a movie called her smell
Big I'm astounded. I'm serious because this is a woman that I've said frequently throughout her career
She looks like she smells to me smells. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, wow, that's wild. Okay. Yeah, she's basically playing Courtney
Love it's like an out -of -control grunge singer. It's a good movie
super uncomfortable, but I saw the trailer for this pavement biopic and
It looks so terrible. It looks like an indie walk hard, but not funny. It's not a parody. There are no jokes in the trailer
There's no wink
But Tim Heidecker is in it and comedy people are in it
Joe Keery from Stranger Things plays Stephen Malkmus, but it's a band with no drama
There's no story, you know
There's no like juice and and you know, there's of course a little bit of fighting and stuff like any band
But there's nothing to tell a story about yeah
So I sent it to my friend who I know is obsessed with pavement and he looked into it
So now I guess it's some sort of Andy Kaufman thing
Here's what it is. You can go watch the trailer. So it is supposed to be funny
Here's what it's supposed to be for those not in on the bit range
Life is a fake pavement biopic conceptualized by Alex Ross Perry as a part of his film
Pavements from last year, which I had no idea that even happened which was trying to be a simultaneous
earnest documentary of the band
While also being a look at their new original musical theater show slanted
Enchanted and this is the third portion
Which is a riff on the modern post -bohemian rhapsody state of musical biopics
It's not going theatrical I don't know when it will get a home release but Joe Keery gives a heroic performance
heroic
Well, is that supposed to be funny though? No that that line is not I don't know where my friend even got this from but
It's part of some sort of
three -piece
pavement art exhibit and
I maybe it is a sketch
Maybe it's supposed to be funny
But you have to give your audience a clue that they're watching a comedy or it's technically not I would say
Yeah, you know, I look I've I've made my public complaints about high decker before and it's not his project but
It you know that that that's all there's a camp of guys
Where that's all they do is like it's like I'm gonna do a thing that I know is a joke
But it won't read as a joke to anybody else. It'll just read as awkward and strange. It's like
Yeah, I get the the I get how that could be funny. But I think a lot of the time it's just like
Okay, I guess like there's one of those guys in every comedy writers room and they never get anything on the show
they sit and make fun of everyone else in the room and how hacky their jokes are and they make fun of
TV in general and
They're so cool and they're checked out and at the end of the year. They've contributed absolutely
Nothing that made it into the show
That's my take on those kind of people
I
had a you ever have a friend just use a giant word out of nowhere and you you just kind of
Hate them for it like a word. You don't know. Yeah, what's the great? That's the great. There's a great Seinfeld where George
He drops the big word and I so how long you've been sitting on that chestnut
That's basically what I said to my friend
But I sent my my buddy Brian this thing about I sent him the pavement thing and he goes I got the impression
It was supposed to be a parody of those
Hagiographic musical biopics fuck without jokes and I go
Hagiographic is this my dinner with on crack. Yeah, what the fuck are you never heard that word in my life?
It means excessively flattering and idealizing in case you were wondering. Oh
God, that's
Disgusts me. This is this is a guy I've known 20 years just dropping hagiographic into a text
I would find that word arrogant printed in in the liner notes of a criterion release
It would make me angry if Woody Allen was saying it while walking down a Manhattan Street
With who's that guy with the horse teeth? I would find Tony Roberts. Yeah, all right P horse teeth. I would find it
Too pretentious shall we get to the movie corner BT dubs? Yeah
Okay
Yeah, in fact, I'll start us out with a biopic a musical biopic that I couldn't believe existed yeah
It's called girl, you know, it's true it is the biopic of Milly Vanilla, yeah
Pat I got to tell you this thing front to back was a solid piece of work. I'm shocked. So I'm saying that I thought it was
gonna be
ridiculous, but
It actually is a movie or what?
No, it was like a real movie that came out like two years ago now ten years ago
this would have been on VH1 and it would have been ridiculous, but
That was actually they seriously committed to making a biopic about the scandal of what happened with Milly Vanilla
Why it happened how it happened the lip -syncing scandal if you don't know anybody listening Milly Vanilla were
They became a global sensation. They were huge
they had four massive hits from their first record and
The the biggest being girl or the first being girl, you know, it's true blame it on the rain
Baby don't lose my number and then there was one more. I can't remember
Baby, yeah, don't forget my number girl, you know, it's true and baby
Don't forget my number they sampled the same exact breakbeat that was first used by Eric being rock him and paid in full
Yeah, they put the breakbeat in both singles back -to -back single. I mean, it's it's insane. But anyway
And it came out that they had lip -sync all the songs and it was back then that was like as bad that
This thing went down like the Cosby reveal like in the 90s like now
People only only Monica Lewinsky can I recall taking a worse beating at that time?
But it's very well acted it's an interesting story you do give a shit about the two of them you feel kind of bad for them
You know cuz at the end of the day you're like these guys are young
They're like 22 year olds and they get swept up with this whole thing and
It's like, you know, of course man. They're kids dude, like whatever so
But I thought it was I thought it was cool and I actually learned a little bit about the music industry that I didn't know
Like some some information about who they were working with and who those people worked with and how they did the songs and stuff
it is absolutely of
Of caliber or better than like Bohemian Rhapsody was and it's about Milly Vanilla story
Shouldn't have been called girl, you know, it's true though. It should have been called
Blame it blame it on the rain. I feel like was a better
Well, why not call it girl, you know, it's a true story
Or how about just you know, it's Mary I guess you can't do that girl the girl and girl
I'm not 50 % of your audience calling it girl, you know, that's I'm saying it. That's the part that throws it off
I don't know. I think blaming on the rain would have been
A bit better. But anyway, it was a good movie, you know, I'm not gonna tell you to run out and watch it
But if you catch it check it out, I think you'll be shocked at how interesting it actually is
Any stars in the thing Peter Gallagher as an agent or something
Surely you got David Krumholtz as the guy who buys their rights and sells them to cheese or something
He played that nine movies in a row. I don't think I
Don't think anybody not that I remember. I don't think anybody
I mean, I'm sure there are people that have been in tons of shit, but I just you know, nobody where I was like
Oh, there's you know
Dame Edna playing, you know, one of their moms or something, you know
Not it not probably the piece of casting they needed to secure funding was a Dame Edna
Yeah
In every one of these you your way that you think at any moment Steve Coogan is gonna show up as some sort of
He's another guy. He's always in in pops up in a suit as a guy that's making a thing happen and it's not right
Yeah, I feel like he and that's probably why he remains funny
I feel like he's probably got a nice bit of money, but he's also not loaded like a big star, you know
he's still doing a
Alan Partridge podcast so there's probably not a lot of dough and I think he's made a lot of fuck -ups in his life as well
Yeah, be drug days. I think makes him all the better all the funnier
I think all that stuff in the trip is like sort of based in reality of like he's got
Divorces or alimony or whatever and he's like, yeah, I need to make fucking money man
Like I I've I saw the first two Paddington's I don't I I truly don't know if he's in them
But my assumption is he's in one of them
Anytime you get a bunch of British actors together
He's gonna come in and say a few lines and he's gonna elevate the movies in
Speaking of Paddington, I thought of you because when I was in England, I tried finally for the first time ever marmalade
Yeah, it's fucking disgusting. I
Mean, isn't it's made of what apricot?
Listen, yeah, you're gonna have all the thoughts. I thought oh, that's like a peach jelly
Delicious put that all over my biscuit. Yeah bite into it. It's just bitter. That's gross
Well, everything tastes terrible and in the UK everything they've good Indian food strawberry jam was nice. I
Saw okay, let's just get right to it. Ladies and gentlemen, I saw a picture called better man
This is the 2 hour and 15 minute biopic of Robbie Williams
Where Robbie Williams is portrayed by an animatronic chimp?
Now were you confused with this like you were with a different man where you thought Robbie Williams
The chimp was playing Robbie Williams. You didn't know who was or did you figure this one out?
I figured this one out with the help of Wikipedia
but
What's weird is they're using essentially the exact same technology as Planet of the Apes the new ones
So it looks exactly like one of those apes. So like they do have a really kind of cool idea
I guess it's certainly a novel idea insane idea. It's an insane
Okay, we'll call it what it is, especially with how expensive this movie was but
They don't it's just a regular looking monkey that we've seen a million times in this Planet of the Apes
so it immediately becomes less interesting and less novel, but
It truly is as advertised you do not see Robbie Williams face for 2 hours and 15 minutes
From him as a boy in in London town all the way up to the finale
he is a monkey and
All they do to explain it is he says like, you know, I always did feel like I was
You know a bit of a cheeky monkey
That's really all they do to explain why they're doing it. So
He's wild, you know that I guess that's what it is. He gets into drugs and so forth
Here's what I did like about it and there were things I liked about it
The only reason I watched it a some of the hellions were like you got to see this thing
but a lot of people critics and friends were like look, I don't know what to tell you it's fucking good and
Can't go that far but
It's if it had been a straightforward biopic of Robbie Williams
I mean even less people would have given a shit about this movie. Robbie Williams is not that interesting
What's interesting about the movie is he's an asshole for the entire running time. He is never nice to anyone
He has an asshole dad who only comes back into his life because he's famous
And at the end, you know, they sing my way together a monkey and then his human father
Which is also not explained because nobody else in the movie is an animal
But they sing my way together and I was watching it with a buddy of mine
We were texting while we were watching it and kind of making fun of it
but also kind of liking parts of it and
Our biggest issue with the thing is when I finally looked it up on Wikipedia
Most of the songs are not Robbie Williams songs
Hmm, like my way is they're doing covers of stuff and they're doing some original songs the movies from the same guy who made
Which I liked about the same I thought it was a solid musical, but I don't like musicals
It's I don't know it wasn't boring it was a biopic about an asshole and to me
That's more interesting than a biopic about a person who's who's nice to everybody. He's mean to women. He's an insane narcissist
He recognizes that he's obsessed with drugs. He's mean to his family
Alienates everyone and they don't even redeem him the real Robbie Williams in real life is married to a famous British comedian
All right. I don't know. She is British, but she's a comedian and actress
she was on the blue the woman on the blue -collar comedy show believe it or not and
He's married with kids. He's calmed down. He's sober. He's happy. He's at peace. We never get there in the movie
They stop when he's still an asshole, which is I don't know
It's not a great movie, but I liked that about it
I liked that it had the balls to show the guy as a prick and I also liked that it was rated R
I don't know how they sold this movie a rated -r musical starring a monkey about a guy. Nobody knows or likes
There's a scene where he gets jacked off and comes the monkey a
woman jacks him off folks
So look see it it's not quite the the like
Curiosity you might be thinking like wow this movie's crazy other than the monkey thing. It's just a biopic
But a pretty good one Joe
I'll only do one more on a stick to my theme, which is movies. I basically I watched on the plane
Yes, two of them are ones. We will review one being here
and the other two
No, three of them are ones will review and then the other two
Were the one I mentioned and then I watched this movie the critic
Which is not a live -action
Version of the John Lovett's cartoon, right? It's a new new were film starring Ian McKellen
About I guess it takes place in the 30s and it is about an aging theater critic
in London in
You know if in as I said, I guess the 1930s or something like that anyway
The premise is
He is a very very powerful critic. It is back when
The the pen of the critic and the words of the critic could make or break your career quite literally
Gemma
Artur tin Artur tin, I'm not sure how to say the name pronounced
But I think that's our archerton is probably what it is. She plays an actress that he particularly dislikes and
He repeatedly bashes her and it is hurting her career
He then amidst this she confronts him and asks him to stop and amidst this happening
He gets caught with his boyfriend slash assistant
Committing a quote lewd act unquote in the in public which at a time when homosexuality
Homosexuality is illegal
Because of this he loses his job
But he also finds out that his editor or the owner of the paper
Is married, but he is quietly obsessed with
Gemma's character
He then orchestrates this scheme to get Gemma to sleep with her boss in order for him to get his job back and
I
Don't want to tell you all that happens
Because it is the type of sometimes I'm okay with talking about spoilers
Usually in the main movie that we review every week
because
You know, it's just easier to talk freely about the movie, but sometimes I'm okay with it too because I'm able to
Use them to further my point or support my what is what it is
I'm trying to say about the movie. Sometimes I avoid spoilers not just out of respect for you watching it
But also because I can't do it justice. There are a lot of things that happen in this
Due to the wheels he puts in motion. I guess you could call it a thriller
It's not great, it's pretty dry. I was invested I cared
Yeah, I cared about what happened
I thought it reminded me a lot of that movie he did with Helen Mirren
where like he marries her and then like is gonna take her for her money and
Then who Ian McKellen? Oh, yeah. No, I know what you're talking about
It was kind of like that. We're kind of like the movie. He did homes where he played like the aging shirt
Sherlock Holmes. Uh -huh. It's like one of those things
You know decent production value
and and very well performed
and quite tragic ultimately, but I
Enjoyed it. I enjoyed it. It didn't get very well reviewed
But I would say to you know, if you like that sort of thing check it out
It feels feel like this would have been like one of those like masterpiece theater
Movies of the week back in in the day it was directed by a non Tucker who?
He did shop girl, I guess which is the Steve, you know, the adaptation of the Steve Martin of shop girl book and movie love them bull
He did leap year
It was terrible unwatchable. He did red writing the year of our Lord
All three red writings are awesome. Check them out. Okay
Hillary and Jackie
Decent
Yeah, I don't think I've seen any of these. Anyway a British dude. Yeah
It's an interesting movie I
You know Ian McKellen you can only go so bad with Ian. I mean the guy is just a fucking powerhouse
He's right. So I enjoyed that pupil was never released on anything but DVD because of its controversy
I have to assume that was the reason because not only was that Bryan Singer
But there was an added controversy of him shooting the boys in the high school shower sequences too long and too naked
But I still have my app pupil DVD. I still think it's a great movie despite its controversies. I never saw it
That's that blows my mind Joe. I
Didn't have any interest
You're a Stephen King enthusiast. You got Ian McKellen Brad Renfro
Well, you did it somebody said the deadly words to me
About a Stephen King movie, which was it's not a horror and I was like, oh, I don't care then
It's about the horrors of man. Yeah
By the way on our next episode we got to talk about Darren Aronofsky's Cujo, but we'll do that next time
I
Watched I'm out here in Atlanta and I'm getting I'm getting homesick. I'm missing my lady friend and I'm doing some binging because
When you don't drink and you don't have any vices going on then you got to have something you got to have something
Was that blats blame it on the rain. That's why that's in my head
got to blame it on something I
watched two seasons of Severance in about a week and a half and
It's not because I was addicted. I felt like I was taking it like medicine. It is
Unquestionably one of the better shows on TV. I don't watch a lot of TV these days. I recognize its quality
but
Man, is it just not fun?
You know like the world imagine the world of office space. Mm -hmm
Except it's not 80 minutes and hilarious. It's
10 hours or 20 hours with both seasons and then we just turn the dark filter on
You know, it's so it's not only at a boring office a drab office
it's also super dark and it just gets oppressive, you know, and I'm getting off of a 16 hour day of work and
sitting down to watch people be miserable at their jobs and then when they get out of work their lives are miserable at home and
I get that that's kind of the point that you're always kind of trying to escape this other side of yourself
You know and nobody's truly happy at home or at work or whatever
But I feel like the show just started with a guy taking a bong hit and being like what if
You know, it's a great Twilight Zone premise or it's a great. It's a great pitch for sure
What if like you you could shut yourself off when you're at work and you were two different people?
Love it and then naming them innies and outies helps clarify it
I found it
The the times where I found it difficult to follow were the times where I was not confident
They knew what they were doing and I don't think they did there was some of that in a show like Lost these puzzle box shows
sometimes
have to kind of
Start moving before they know exactly where each piece is gonna fall
But as soon as I start feeling like you're just pulling shit out of thin air
It's real hard for me to commit to like six seasons of something and I feel like Severance is gonna be on for a very
long time
Lost people forget was 22 to 24 episodes a season for six seasons
So there's so much more material and of course, there'll be a few more duds with a show like Lost
but
Severance to me there's just too much
Time wasting going on, you know every show it's every show anymore
It's every show every show these things don't need to be this long and this big
This this should have been a movie and especially, you know with with how expensive the thing looks and I'm sure is and I was
Talking on with Joe on one of these episodes about how they threw out an entire shot season of the show and started over
But they brought in the house of cards guy the guy who ran that show and I was like, yes
That's what they need a classically trained guy who can do setups payoffs twists turns and bring it into this really cool
World I love it because the first season was too much just vibes. So now we're gonna get story
But they're still doing this shit. They walk into a room and there's like 20 baby goats
What's the deal with the goats and then everyone on online? What's happening with the goats?
I'll tell you what's happening is they said wouldn't it be weird if they opened a room and there were goats in there and
Then they have to spend the next 18 hours teasing it and then you finally find out I'm not gonna say it and and it's
Exactly what you thought, you know, it's some lame pulled out of your ass explanation and
That weird for weirdness sake stuff on these shows it gets them away with so much
They get to just say well, maybe we'll tell you what that was about in 48 episodes
Well, maybe we won't and also there and also too
It it goes it that's without a doubt an executive note. We want water cooler moments
Let's put let's plant things in that are gonna make and it's just so stupid
It's a shame and and look I recognize the quality of the show any show where John Chaturro and Christopher Walken are in a
Romantic relationship where they can't they can't kiss but they're in love with each other
It's got great stuff in it and the actors are excellent Zach Cherry who was on crashing which Joe and I wrote for he's a fucking
Really great new character actor. I love that guy
Everybody's good Ben Stiller is a really strong director as are the other people he he assembled
But it leaves me too cold and the five of my friends who watch the show all of us have said we're not coming back for season
Three it's like it just never lost gave you that human element that emotion that kept you coming back severance. Just keeps me at a distance
And it frustrates me because I like a lot about it
Let's get to the movie
At hand which is here
And you know, it is it's got some elements, I guess of
Sci -fi there are dinosaurs in it
Fantasy, we don't normally do these kind of movies, but it's Zemeckis
and I was just honestly happy to see Zemeckis trying again, which
After his last several is a big deal. I thought here was at very least an interesting movie
Joe walk us through the plot. All right, the plot is there's a plot of land
And uh, they show you what happens on that plot of land mainly within the walls of a small house that gets built upon it
over the course of
Many many years starting with native american settlers or not settlers, excuse me native americans and then just
Then at time
I thought this movie fucking sucked
I thought it sucked. I'm getting frustrated even trying to explain it it time jumps
The focus is is the family of tom hanks and robin wright
They're the characters they play
And the trials and tribulations that they face from as from the time of being a young couple up through old age
um
It repeatedly jumps out of time
Uh to different periods to show you things
I guess it's sort of interesting to realize when you get into the concepts of like deep time or whatever
that once
uh, native americans walk this land and you know and try a tribe lived here and now people do and
once uh
A director named robert zemeckis thought this movie needed a storyline about the guy that invented the lazy boy living in this house
I'll grant you that's fucking weird
Yeah, uh now look, I don't know how much this is bobby z and how much this is just the graphic novel, but
The the time jumping all around is confusing
The period piece dialogue is literally written
Like a john lovett's snl sketch
From the 80s. I mean, it's it's ridiculous, man
They'll they'll go back and like it'll be like a guy in a powdered wig
Being like i've had just it just up to me britches hearing about ben franklin
Yep, there's some of that. Oh you go now. That's terrible. Love
It's so it's it's literally written like this like the way i'm trying to make up how I think an english person would talk
In whatever year it is, uh the 17 whatever that
It's it's just not
It's just not a good movie, man. It's just not good. I don't give a shit
Paul betty is walk paul betty plays tom hanks's dad in this thing
I don't know that we've quite landed quite what it is. You haven't mentioned tom hanks robin wright or paul betty
So yeah, I said their family they're they're them growing old in this house
Well, yeah, I mean but the the essential gimmick of the film is as if you're watching a play that never changes
You know the curtain never goes down basically. It's it's one shot of a room
and
You know we we watch that from dinosaur days that plot of land to a house being built
To all the people that live in the house throughout the years
up to
modern day
Tom hanks and his wife robin wright
Tom hanks's father is played by paul betty his mother played by kelly riley and at this being zemeckis
Of course, they do some digital de -aging and stuff
But the main people we're focused on are the is the marriage of hanks and robin yes
Uh tom paul betty who I love is one of the most miscast roles I have ever seen
Yeah, i'll grant you that betty is walking around this thing
It feels like a 16 year old has to play the old man in the high school play
Or julia garner and wolfman. Yeah, he's hunched over
He's doing this gruff voice
Are you extreme? He's clearly british like he screams british
And he's the only one in the movie that they didn't digitally age. They just put him in old man makeup
So it is painfully obvious when you've got smooth face. Tom hanks talking to paul betty in like elephant man
Prosthetics, it's ridiculous. It's fucking ridiculous
By the way gang if you're gonna de -age de -age the voices people sure
Yep, got tom hanks and his 72 year old voice coming out of an 18 year old face. It looks insane
Well, they're gonna be doing more of that the brutalist was controversial because ai got made their accents, right?
I don't know if you heard that controversy. No, but ai tweaked their accents. So then when adrian brody won best actor
Everybody was like, hmm
Um
Look this movie was written by zemeckis and eric roth eric roth is one of the most celebrated screenwriters in the world
He did forrest gump the insider munich benjamin button star is born remake dune the new dune
Um killers of the flower moon, even though scorsese just admitted that the draft they used was written by paul thomas anderson
Do you know that?
I didn't but didn't uh david, uh, what's his face also write this?
Um this movie
Is it just yeah didn't david? Uh, the guy that wrote crystal skull david, uh
No, it was just roth and zemeckis. I'm looking at it right now. What am I thinking of? I don't know. Um
david kepp who wrote jurassic park and shit, too, but um
Yeah, I mean look
I'm a massive zemeckis fan. I thought zemeckis was basically like spielberg jr
And his credits are incredible and i've been watching the guy just fall apart
So here to me represents a guy trying again
With a movie that's using special effects for a purpose and not just to jack off and try new expensive technology
I know the movie is very corny in spots. I know the movie is sloppily written in spots
Um, and I didn't care about much more than the tom hanks thing. The rest just kind of played like a gimmick
But maybe it's because I was a guy who was in a house for 10 years
With my girlfriend who became my wife who became my ex -wife and then lived in there alone
It spoke to me and by the end of the thing. I had tears in my eyes. I gotta be honest
um
Sometimes something will sneak up on you. I don't know it got to me
but
And by the way, I forgot the tom hanks. They're not the final family to live in the house
Um a family moves in after them
Uh that they also explore which just makes it more confusing
Oh the black family. Yes, and in the most tone deaf
Liberal misfire i've ever seen in recent days
they give
The only family to have a maid is the black family because because the the bleeding hearts of liberal hollywood want to prove
That that everybody can do it, too
um
Which is fine. I'm obviously not condemning that
But they make the maid the most racist stereotype ever of a hispanic person
She's like the family guy made. Yeah, it's insane. She literally at one point goes
Oh, dios mio. Yes, like exactly this
Is bat shit
This is why and I obviously we've talked about how they got way too crazy with you have to be this to write this
But this is why 80 year old
Insanely wealthy men should not be writing something like this without some help from a younger person
um
But real quick
After I want to hold your hand which is on criterion and is a fun little beetles movie
Zemeckis did I just need to shout this out. It's the same thing with rob reiner. The run is is so amazing
Used cars a fucking hilarious movie with kurt russell and jack warden
Romancing the stone back to the future who framed roger rabbit back to the future two back to the future three
Death becomes her produces trespass with iced tea
Forrest gump produces bordello of blood
Contact what lies beneath cast away?
And then we just fall apart. It's the polar express
It's bail wolf
It's a christmas carol with jim carrey
Flight I liked with denzel and good. I purchased it yesterday. It's a good movie then we got the walk
The three which was sort of cool the 3d guy that walked between the two buildings allied which is like just lame brad pitt and angelina
Welcome to marwin one of the stupidest movies i've ever seen with steve carell the witches
Three times worse than welcome to marwin awful film
Pinocchio which joe saw and I did not
And now here he also produced joe's precious demon knight and a bunch of other horror the guy's career
Is is sad it's just a baffling and sad career. It's a guy who got way too obsessed with technology
You could say the same about james cameron. I don't I would much rather have
Five new james cameron original ideas than to be spending the next 20 years of my life watching avatars
These guys just disappear into effects and it's a bummer
Here is more of the same
It's more effects
But I gotta say it had a low -key charm that won me over and at the in the end
The the emotion is what got to me. I couldn't disagree more on both things you're saying
I think zemeckis's career dies after back to the future one
I think wow
Look hits or not far as gump sucks that movie sucks. Look i'll grab I need to see it again
Back to the future two is not perfect back to the future two is not good. It's an enjoyable sequel
Three sucks
You you like what lies beneath I find it to be a slog
After back to the future i'm like get me to flight
And then get me out the door like this is like
I don't think the guy what death becomes her is passable. It would have been a better just episode of tales from the crypt
Um, well, you know, he had a big hand in a lot of tales from the crypt
He was one of the five producers the powerhouse of the five
I wouldn't I wouldn't mind you putting a little respect on the man's name. I do respect him
But I think he's had far more misses than not
um
He's just benefited from
uh six box office success, but I mean
this thing
Look man, here was my biggest issue with this. This fucking movie was tone deaf as I already pointed out about the hispanic maid
um this whole movie
reeks
And i'm not one to usually go on about this sort of thing
But I will this whole fucking movie reeks of white privilege
It's people in their living room crying
That the house they have isn't good enough
That I never this is a real thing. I never saw paris in the spring
Yeah, robin wright starts crying on her 50th birthday. I never saw paris this. Hey, fuck you lady
Go live on the street
Fuck you
Uh as far as I can tell the point of the whole movie is
You'll compromise and never do what you actually want to do in life and then died riddled with regret
And they make this point so many times in the movie with so many
paper thin fucking characters
Bitching about their life not being what they wanted it to be
That in the final scene of the movie, they actually have to have tom hanks's character say I have no regrets
Because otherwise you'd be sitting there going well, what are your regrets now everybody else has had regrets through the entire fucking movie. Yeah
it's
Excuse me. I work myself up into a hack. Um
I think this would have been a passable short film
I think it was an interesting experiment
And I think if you do want this to work as a feature length
You put sean penn and robin wright in that fucking house and that's the marriage I want to watch
For three hours guy doing tying into a chair setting her on fire
Um, I will say this and I know we're wrapping up but
Looking at his producer credits outside of um
Tales from the crypt this man
Has bad instincts
He did house on haunted hill remake with jeff rush
13 ghosts remake ghost ship, which I remember being just fucking awful
All three of those are interchangeably terrible bad. They are they're really bad. Yeah, uh gothica terrible house of wax
terrible with paris hilton god
Uh the reaping I don't know what that is mars needs moms. You do know what the reaping is
The reaping is the hillary swankard movie. Oh, yeah sent her out of the business after winning an oscar. I saw it
Yeah, um, he did produce matchstick men but like
These are these are rough. These are pretty rough. He did the public eye with joe pesci the frighteners, which people like I didn't like
Oh, it's not it's not a great run. There's no real big hits in his production. Uh roster even forest gump
The book was completely panned if you read about the book the book was panned right and for some reason
I read the book at that time
He was like this will make a good movie and he got lucky with it
You know
He does have good instincts. They let him take these giant swings and his he does not have like the spielberg touch clearly
Uh folks, we'll be back with a review
of
The speak no evil remake. Yes currently on peacock
Starring james mcavoy the most jacked jimmy mcavoy man that you don't think is jacked man ever
Yeah, I think he got jacked for the picture, but he he looked good
Uh, we'll be back
We will
Uh see you on the internet at see you in hellpod on instagram. I'm at the patrick walsh occasionally on instagram joe
Joe de rosa comedy on instagram. Come on out to phoenix this weekend
If you're in phoenix, who are there tickets available folks come get your tickets, please
I'll be at the desert ridge improv. Please come on out. I've got other dates passed then in uh, stanford connecticut
uh
In april, I think i'm in stanford. Yeah
Uh, and then i'll be doing some other stuff into the summer different cities
I'm kind of blanking right now where i'm going to be but go to joe de rosa .com for show dates and ticket links
Uh come through joey roses if you're in new york get a sandwich have a drink
Uh, and we'll be back with speak no evil. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell