I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell And when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say I'll see you in hell, you know I will
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
folks it's we'll see you in hell kicking off august with the ep we have been teasing for some time now
long legs a24's latest no it's not a24 it's who neon neon oh which means a24 passed I uh I tend
to love neon they they make really weird they did titane you know they do weird cool shit I like them
we'll get to long legs you know I thought it was a24 they keep comparing it I keep seeing articles
that are comparing it to um I'm blanking on the movie but the the headline will say like
long legs box office at whatever the fuck million beating a24's highest grossing
horror movie indie horror movie whatever the so I was I was like oh they're they're
a24's like outdoing itself well they're highly competitive the two uh you know they're definitely
neon is is the number two I'm sure they get a lot of runoff from a24 but they both look they they
curate great stuff they for the most part have at least interesting films I give them kudos
even though a24 movies have their own wheelbarrow full of cliches and stuff that gets old fast
they're they're churning out for the most part original low budget films that's what we always
talk about wanting on this show so it's hard for me to be mad at in a24 I I haven't said anything
yet no I'm well aware I'm just stating my opinion I know you have stuff coming but I could I could
hear the anticipation in your voice that I was going to say something I wasn't pressing up against
you I'm stating my own opinion because they're they're an interesting thing I mean they're
now they're they're making huge movies they're making movies with the rock and they're starting
to become bigger and before you know it there will be no a24 stamp of quality um what is the
rock movie they're doing they're are they doing red one no they haven't gone that far off the
one of the Safdie brothers which I think is kind of a tragedy that the Safdie brothers made
good movies building up to great with good time building up to their masterpiece with uncut gems
and then split up I don't really get that as they're as they're making it big but it's one
of the Safdies I don't know which one is making a movie with Dwayne the rock Johnson as a MMA
fighter this famous you know had a legendary legendary difficult life I don't know who it
is the machine I think his name is it's a Bert Kreischer biopic with Dwayne the rock Johnson as
Bert well it could be less it could be a little less a24 going more mainstream and a little more
the rock going like you know Bill Murray into Wes Andersonville or whatever you know yeah maybe
that's what it is a little harder for a body like the rock to make that transition into indie
filmmaking into quirky Wes Anderson you see him in a boy scout uniform yeah um yeah um all right
I had a little thing I wanted to share that I thought would be fun on the last app and I forgot
so I'll do it here today Joe I think you'll enjoy this a little bit give it to me daddy uh
so Deadpool and Wolverine
has set a record for the most uses of the word fuck on Disney Plus or certainly will when it
drops on Disney Plus so and they make countless jokes in that movie about you know we're we're
saying fuck we're doing pegging we're doing all this stuff that's crazy for Disney etc
um Deadpool and Wolverine has 118 uses of the f -word during its two hour and seven minute
runtime with a few tossed off during that surprising post -credits scene which I didn't
see did you watch the post -credits scene no I looked it up in the theater and it said it's
nothing the scene doesn't tease anything it's just a joke that hinges on a joke from the movie and
I was like all right I don't just sit to the credits for this I hated that fucking I forgot
to say I couldn't tell they were being ironic or not I know with the Seinfeld thing the time
of your life that wasn't ironic at all there wasn't a joke in there it was I thought I thought that
was dead serious I felt like the fact that they were using time of my life and Seinfeld famously
used it and people kind of scouted that they were making fun of that I thought I think they
meant it just because there was no wink and it was all just straightforward material
I didn't mind that even as a guy who I've seen all the x -men but I have no big big love of them
or anything I thought that was kind of nice but what was interesting to me is that not a single
person in the entire and the AMC 16 and Burbank has these massive theaters some of the biggest
I've ever seen not one person outside of me and my date stood up when the credits rolled oh yeah
yeah couldn't believe it there's not somebody in there who's like all right I don't give a shit
what they do here after the next seven minutes of credits everybody stayed it's a new thing
well um that was anybody the whole audience said I got up and I said we got up as well
and I as I walked out I went bad bad get out your shearers and start you know scalping people well
you're a sheep aren't you um all right so 118 uses of the f -word however it still comes up
way short this is on the Hollywood Reporter by the way when compared to some other incredibly
profane f -bomb hall of fame classics here's how the Deadpool and Wolverine swear jar stacks up
against other famously potty -mouthed mainstream hits so I've got the top eight here Joe okay
and I thought it might be a fun little kickoff activity for you to guess what might be
these top eight a few will be obvious but I just want to hear what your thoughts are
Scarface is in there right Scarface is number eight you might do them in order
uh Scarface doubles Deadpool with 226 Jesus Scarface is the low ranker on the list that's
tough is good Scarface also we we all act like uh this is the first time we've ever talked about
capitalism in film and it cites here as one of the most famous lines from Scarface you know what
capitalism is getting fucked 1983 same year as risky business so clearly that was on people's
minds in 1983 as well uh and we could have stopped it then but folks we didn't and we never will
we didn't start the fire as Billy Joel said but we're not gonna put it out is Goodfellas on the
list Joe it is that is number no what you know what it's not yeah which is insane it must be
number nine if it's not I thought I always thought Goodfellas was high on the list
I'm already let me ask you this Joe what if there was a movie that was
like Goodfellas but 45 minutes longer yeah casino but um yeah I guess that extra 45 is what gets
him across the finish line in the fuck yeah casino is number three with a total of 422
okay well I got casino uh Scarface
yeah gee that's I'm out I got oh wait wait wait Big Lebowski
Big Lebowski surprisingly is number five certainly the top comedy on the list um
I got I don't know give me a hint sure um you're leaving out
one of the biggest directors of today who's got two back -to -back on the list
um one of your and my generation's kind of biggest directors Christopher Nolan
no he doesn't know Joe you know he doesn't hit it's not like well if it isn't fucking Oppenheimer
one of the biggest directors of his day uh oh Kevin Smith
no well no but a good guess on the list at all he's not he's not but it's a good guess
um I don't biggest directors of today not Spielberg obviously not Nolan not uh
what if I told you it's a director whose use of language not only profanity has been extremely
controversial Tarantino correct you got two back -to -back at number seven and eight
Jesus well I'm sorry six and seven six and seven one I gotta be honest I don't
remember any Tarantino movies being that fuck heavy uh I gotta tell you I just saw one of them
and I'm kind of like I didn't think it was at this level it didn't feel that excessive but
is one of them once upon a time in Hollywood no sir you're going real early in the career
all right reservoir dogs which I didn't think was that fuck heavy dogs is number six with 269
fucks really and pulp fiction is seven with 265 so very very close to each other pulp fiction
having a lot of f -words in it it's weird well again it's a full hour longer than reservoir
dogs so it's much more impressive how many they packed into dogs over um I you know David Mamet
could be on this list and I bet you some of his movies would stack up but just weren't considered
I mean the movie hafa they say fuck so much in it yeah I mean this claims it's it's the kind of
definitive list but I do feel like I've always seen good fellows on these lists and so forth so
it might not be 100 accurate but they do have the counts here um I'll just do them for the group
fill you in on the last couple you missed number eight scarface number seven pulp fiction number
six reservoir dogs number five big Lebowski number four was the biggest surprise to me
it wouldn't that's the one I would have missed straight out of Compton
has 392 f -bombs god I should have guessed you know with 422
uh number two so very surprising as well even though I just mentioned it uncut gems is number
two what 560 fucks in it what I think to me that movie is so riveting and so draining and
suspenseful that maybe you just don't notice but that one would not have occurred to me
for uh 560 and number one with 569 uh which again it's an it's a full half hour longer than
the wolf of wall street
uh yeah that's a heavy one yeah that the numbers in that one were probably probably upped by the
long coked out improvisations you know where you're just going to be saying fuck a lot
uh interesting list I thought
any hoot I'm looking that where did you find that
Hollywood reporter as I think I said twice
well let's come on come on too early by the way it's very early I was just about to comment on
how early it is it's seven o 'clock my time a .m. and I just slept a nice eight hours I went to bed
early I woke up I have not even gone to the bathroom yet and I'm marveling at how my hair
looks my hair didn't look this good when I went out last night how did I sleep seven hours and
I'm I mean I got the Conan O 'Brien quaff going here you do that is weird you didn't do that on
purpose Joe I didn't touch it um are we still talking about your hair folks oh uh I um I
I would call this an almost emergency episode of the podcast uh I wanted to I saw this movie
last night I went to a 9 45 p .m. screening yeah at the movie test and it's a bit of a special
episode because I am going to forego my movie corner today and do something we've never done
on this show which is read the rex reed review of the movie we're long legs before we review it
was he a fan we'll get to it Pat I need I need now to read or hear a positive rex reed review
and see what that looks like does he have them yeah we had we I've read a couple on the show
like oh he loved this remember the one I read where I was like he loved it but
it was just him complimenting other movies he liked yeah yeah um but we'll get to that but I
went to see this movie last night at 9 45 p .m. at the worst movie theater on planet earth
the movie tavern uh why do I keep going back to the movie tavern as much as I complain about it
well because it was playing 15 minutes earlier there than the theater I wanted to see it at
and I was supposed to be uh in the office today and we got called out for you know at the last
minute this morning to work remotely so you know I thought I was gonna have to get up early and
drive and whatever so I wanted to get home as early as possible uh I went straight from a
dinner with some friends to see long legs at 9 45 now I won't get into the movie yet but I will
tell you about my movie tavern experience I've complained about movie tavern before on here
if you're unfamiliar it's a you know it's a it's not owned by the same people but it's a variant
of of alamo draft house it's a you know you can get food while you watch and there's a sports bar
in the is it a true variant meaning like they own it or just they okay they ripped it off sort of
only because you just did this to me I literally said it's a variant it's not the same owners or
anything well no but I'm clarifying variant I'm asking directly after you said it now what do
you mean by variant that's we're off to a rough if we're already poking at each other like this I
feeling this review this review could hit uh oh no no no this isn't gonna be me uh raving about
the the plot intricacies of long legs but I definitely I can tell I liked it a lot more than
you did um anyway yeah by the way before you so when you go to the movie tavern you know we've
we've complained about how these these dumb trailers where Nicole Kidman comes out and goes
movies yeah yeah the party to go to the movie the movie tavern they don't do those what they do
do though is the owner of the movie tavern chain comes on the screen and goes you know folks I love
the movies and it's great to go to the movies but that's not all we do here at the movie tavern
we've got a bar and the bar isn't just good for having a drink before or after the picture you see
the bar is great anytime come in and watch sports it's a great sports but where are you at in life
if you're going into a movie tavern I was just not thinking about how how sad I'd have to be
to do that and look this this could happen Saturday it's very much a possibility in my
life that I go and drink at the the movie tavern so I'm sitting there the movie hasn't even started
the trailers haven't even started yet I'm already furious yeah there's two guys down from me
facetiming in the theater people are straggling in late everybody's sitting down
everybody as they soon as they sit down they start adjusting their chairs repeatedly because
it's the reclining chairs every chair at the movie tavern makes like a Dennis drill noise when you
adjust it so every time you just there it goes yeah like that trailer start because everybody was
late the waiter now has to take all the orders during the trailers yeah I tell you what Joe we're
getting people walking in 10 minutes into the movie when it starts 35 minutes after the show
yeah it's crazy what are you doing see something else it's crazy waiter is standing
fully erect full volume oh okay just stay I know it's a problematic phrase but he's standing
fully he's not doing the squat like hey what can I get you folks which is how they used to do it
yeah he's just standing up and he's like so would you guys like to try a bacon cheeseburger tonight
you know I'm like this is fucking insane this is insane our specials are this is happening
Deadpool of tomato soup uh this is happening I'm not kidding into the opening of the movie
yeah this is still happening so I'm furious uh by the way too here's another thing I love about movie
trailers now please take notice people as our society crumbles of the sprinkled in commercials
for ai that are now before every movie with the competing companies being samsung meta and I
apple I think is the third one it must be uh it's insane and every commercial is a kid with his
phone and them telling you how great ai is on your phone and what I don't know how many fucking
warning movies they had to make about this and we're still just zoom it just it's gonna happen
there's no that shit doesn't happen at amc that does that shit doesn't happen at amc um well I
gotta find an amc Nicole and honestly it's because Nicole wouldn't allow it she would never allow that
we um the uh movie starts throughout the movie people are adjusting their chairs
yeah because grown fucking adults can't sit still sit and I'm talking every six minutes
it's literally like planes trains and automobiles yeah I want to start screaming sit stop with the
goddamn seat it's it was crazy I was so fucking angry and I don't think it tainted my opinion of
film and I'll get into that when we talk about the film but it was just
I mean you know we were locked in our homes we said god we just want to get out in public again
this is no way to live we're out in public again and I don't want to leave my house I just I'm just
yeah the problem is I think it made it it made people way too comfortable out in public
um you know when I go to a movie here in Burbank it's a lot of pajamas a lot of crocs a lot of
flip -flops I'm not saying you need a three -piece suit like it's Vegas in the 50s or something and
we've lost the magic of going to the cinema I'm just saying people are like the guy next to me
the other night his water bottle had fully tipped to the right from its holster its thing so it's
Indian style furiously texting for the first hour of Deadpool and he's got his water bottle
like on my lap it's like I'm covered in trash almost and I hear you I don't want to go out
anymore either and we we ourselves have become so comfortable with the home life that we're
we're much less able to adapt to the animals of society now so it's really bad on both sides
we can't we can't be around it and also everybody else doesn't care anymore guy two seats down for
me yeah uh mid movie pulls out a plastic bag now much to the movie theater's credit they let you
kind of bring your own stuff in now even at the movie tavern they're not policing some kid had
an outback bag in there uh so we've been in a place where they serve food I brought a coffee
and they weren't like you can't bring that in the movie theaters it used to be
gestapo -esque when you tried to walk in with a bag of m &m's or something they were like
get out leave it you know it was like at the airport going through security but so so I
appreciate that they've leaned off on like let people bring a fucking bag in whatever be cool
great this guy until you get until you smell hot fish yeah that's as I did the other night
some guy like with scallops on a piece of aluminum foil yeah kid pulls out a bag from you know
cvs or wherever he bought bottles of water from and he's taking the bottles of water out and
it's full crinkle it's just like can you try to do it quietly can you try to do it quietly
it's just insane every seat somebody was doing something shitty it's just god damn it man
may have affected your enjoyment a little bit joe but um I hate when somebody is trying to like
open a starburst and if they were just sitting at home it would take one second but they're
trying to be quiet so the opening of the starburst takes three four minutes of crinklin that annoys
me but at least they're trying to be respectful sure you know what I mean uh you know so
who's the kid from uh I played uh Freddie Mercury what's his name rami malik rami malik
pinkstone told me once he saw a meme of rami malik's face and it just said rami malik always
looks like he's trying to quietly eat Doritos during a meeting yeah I buy that that man uh
deeply unsettles me in everything he is in uh yeah he's something anyway the tavern experience
I'm not trying to knock a chain I mean they're you know they're doing their thing and it's
but it's just like come on guys like god damn man yeah it was annoying anyway did you get the
you mentioned meta in there did you get the email out of the blue that you have to sign up for a
Facebook account or they're gonna completely remove you from this $400 purchase you've made
the oculus no because I don't have the oculus because it was stolen when my apartment was robbed
so I do have the oculus $400 bought it over the pandemic admittedly I don't use it near as much
as I did over the pandemic if at all but I get this email and it's like um you have to now sign
up for a Facebook meta account otherwise you won't be able to use your oculus system three four years
after I bought a $400 item it is now decorative because I refuse to sign back up for Facebook
I listen here's what's fucked up I was talking to uh friend uh comedian Tim Dillon the other day
a very funny man whenever you talk to Tim it immediately devolves into apocalypse talk
you know you'll Tim sure you'll be like I'm thinking about buying this car and he'll be like
here's why you shouldn't okay let me tell you what's going to happen oil is running out
and then you're into some dark dystopian whatever so anyway he uh we're talking about it we're
talking about how the United States is moving towards a society much like China or or you know
Asian society and I talked about hey in China it's weird they only have one app that does
everything because the government is like monitoring you there and I said to him
are you seeing any of these commercials that I'm talking about for AI I said to him I go
people think it's a small thing that Facebook bought Instagram and that whatever and then
Instagram now is pushing you over to meta yeah it's all in one place that's not a small thing
there's something behind that and then of course you see the commercial where they're talking about
AI it's crazy like it's it's just crazy they they slowly are ushering us
into this one corner and they're and they start introducing these new things and then you begin
and every one of these commercials by the way it's not like is an AI fun it's like look how
useful it is for you to exist as a human being it translates language for you so you can talk
to people when you're in a country and you don't speak the language it's like there were apps that
did that yeah you don't need AI to do that it's wild man it's wild we're and you're talking with
Oculus they're going to force you to everything you do now when you sign up to a website or
whatever subscription whatever nine times out of ten they're saying you have to download the app
yeah and then all these apps are getting shoved under the umbrellas of one company
and then they're making it more and more mandatory and every time you do anything on your phone it
asks if it can track you it's wild man this is this is no good this is no good yeah i think i
talked about on here how the the parking meters are going app based and you have to sign up and
give credit card information to pay like a dollar 25 on a parking meter and you're sitting there in
the hot sun entering information you know it's so annoying and uh what's sort of more disturbing
about it is that these places then have your credit card information and your email and you
have no idea what these companies are as much as i hate it when i am telling a lady at bank of
america what my social security number is i at least feel safe but i can't tell you how many
get an email where it's like there's been a security breach by parking apps .com and just
so you know every piece of your information has been stolen and i'm like i don't even know what
this is it's something i signed up for on like a sweaty afternoon because i needed to park quickly
and they've they've sold my info to hackers it's it's terrifying yeah and then also in pertaining
to the movie we're talking about today now much like long legs if you want to make a movie about
you know a detective investigation yeah into a murder mystery you got to set the goddamn thing
in 91 right because it's like you just do this you just do this and this and you'd figure out
that and whatever you know now because of uh the way everything's interconnected and by the way
from the producers of megan oh god this trailer for this fucking movie where it's like the alexa
oh yeah it's the same story it is yeah except it's a device
well he probably said we're gonna make this goddamn movie he goes give me an ai megan
and then went back to jerking off in his oculus yeah did you see the trailer for the movie i'm
i did yeah it just looks i mean to to be honest it looks like something that would be going
direct to dvd in 2001 it just looked very generic and they updated whatever it's always like whatever
the world is kind of scared about becomes the new villain these things but ai is trying to have it
both ways we got like that creator movie that lost all that money about the horrors of ai and the
lot so it's like well you can't have it both ways here you can't use it uh in everything you do
and then release 200 million dollar movies critiquing it but they do that's i mean it goes
back to what you said earlier look at the you know studios even in the 80s making these big
budget movies about the horrors of capitalism there's nothing more capitalistic than the
studio system you know yeah that almost reached its nadir if you if you'll allow me the most
pretentious word i've ever used i think that reached its nadir with don't look up the adam
mccain netflix picture that probably cost 400 million dollars telling us how greedy and obsessed
with destroying energy and the environment we are and then you've got like an elevator operator
played by arnold schwarzenegger because they have to cast every tiny part with the biggest star in
america um it's a it's a crazy time no other way to say it but and i don't know if i was clear
it wasn't like you have to sign up for meta facebook to keep using the oculus it was if you
don't sign up by june 15th which i didn't then you can never use your oculus again it's crazy
so i just threw that money away and then obviously you know i'm not going to put forth the time or
energy to sue or something but it's like they've they definitely figured out how to make that an
unsuable offense but that should be something where the better business bureau gets involved
i mean that's insane we'll sell you a product and then a few years later you can't use it
we change the rules it's crazy it's crazy um do you want to i want to read the rex read before we
like right before we do our review if you want to do a quick corn um last night at the american
cinema tech of which i am a member they are doing a donald southerland tribute they're very good
about getting like great lineups for actors very shortly after they pass and you get to see kind
of all their best stuff um southerland's got some fucking hits man and i love the guy i don't know
if you've seen this clip going around on tiktok but it made me love him times a thousand i've never
really seen him interviewed as just a dude but there's this clip you know it's probably around
hunger games era he's like 65 70 or something and it's anderson cooper and he goes uh now i heard
that your mother was highly critical of you or something like that and have you seen that
clip joe i don't think so oh man it makes me cry every time and southerland goes yes anderson that's
true uh you know i can still remember when you start to go through puberty and you start to
wonder you know am i attractive and will women find me attractive and i said mother do you find
me attractive like am i handsome and she paused for a long time anderson and she said and then
he's starting to say what she said to him and he gets emotional the tears don't show but he can't
talk for like 10 seconds which to me is always more painful when they get kind of stuck an older
man like they're not going to cry but they also can't talk for a second always destroys me and
goes she said to me your face has a lot of character donald
and he was like a kid so uh he's sitting there and he's clearly still traumatized by it and
anderson cooper goes donald he's like you don't still think about that do you like does that
still affect you and he goes you know anderson only for the last 60 65 years uh has that bothered me
and he gets the big laugh you know and he pulls himself out of the emotion of it but
what a fascinating dude and as i was watching him last night in ordinary people i'm like
i guess i never i always kind of thought he was a good looking guy but when i was watching him in
this movie circa 1980 i was like boy yeah i mean no movie star looked like this man that's for sure
certainly not at that time um but what an actor him and mary tyler more also at her best ordinary
people one best picture famously over raging bull which everybody considers some big scandal
raging bull is a better and more important film but ordinary people is really excellent and
it was also interesting to see kind of the very early days of therapy being accepted
as a way of dealing with trauma that it's it's timothy hudden as a young boy whose brother dies
in a boating accident and he tries to kill himself which has happened before where the movie starts
and it has put his very waspy non -communicative upper crust family on high edge so they were
always kind of this like my family like a lot of families everything appears okay on the surface
but nobody's talking about shit and then if anything big happens the family just completely
implodes because they don't know how to deal with it that's what the movie is about
um it's based on a great book it was the directorial debut of robert redford who did
a really excellent job you have judd hersh as the world's like most lovable therapist you love this
guy um it's timothy hutton in a lot of good sessions with hersh great acting all across the board
um but the mvps are really southerland and more who are like at the beginning like you think this
perfect couple and by the end you realize they're just barely biting their tongue and not saying
these horrific things to each other which feels very true of a lot of marriages and families
unfortunately uh i loved ordinary people i saw with friends and i was right as the end was coming
up where southerland and you know and his son like movie just ends with them hugging each other
and saying i love you there's nothing fancy about it there's no great line at the end of it
but it hits so hard when southerland's like i love you son you know every person in the theater is
just like uh you know dealing with their own shit about their parents it's that kind of movie it's
a beautiful great movie i love it joe i'll be seeing that film uh at a review uh at my local
theater the films of dina manoff
it starts with an empty nest retrospective and uh yeah yeah i um yeah she's it's weird he directs
the women in the movie to be kind of nuts you got elizabeth mcgovern being real wacky as a love
interest and then man off is super manic and then winds up killing herself but um it's a you've seen
that movie right joe yeah i i saw that movie in i had a theology teacher named mr dowd he was a
great guy yeah but he he showed as my favorite teacher i ever had well one of my top three
because i had a few teachers i really appreciated but mr dowd was awesome he was the theology
theology teacher excuse me but he would show his movie sometimes that had nothing to do with
theology one was ordinary people sure he also showed us threads at one point that's right so
this guy was depressed he would know he was he was the greatest dude he was so funny and he was like
jovial and whatever and i i felt like he just felt like you know these films are close enough
to being on you know religion is supposed to teach you about life i guess and these films teach you
about life yeah uh threads was a wild choice though like for sure yeah but uh but yeah i did
see this movie i i enjoyed it and it's the film that sort of redefined mary tyler moore to the
american public you know because up until that point she was you know she was not just trophy wife
in terms of looks but like dream loving doting caring wife on multiple shows
well they're not no mary tyler moore she wasn't a wife but she was like the sweetest woman alive
and then when you look back to dick van dyck she was like every man's fantasy wife basically yeah
and in this she was reintroduced as a dramatic actress um you know good man she's great she's
amazing man she's amazing um anyway go ahead go ahead i'm i'm gonna i just got my read to read so
sure uh i re -watched lady blade directed by gretta gerwig and it's interesting with gerwig i
did not love barbie i really did not like her version of little women and it's not a misogynist
thing i actually love the book and i love the winona rider little women i just didn't like her
on it and i was just kind of thinking about her and i was like what why don't i like her stuff
like i i should i loved francis ha i love that movie but um i wanted to give lady bird another
spin i saw it in the theater i remember absolutely loving it and i loved it again it's if here's
something i i almost never say on this show too short uh it's 99 minutes or something and i feel
it's just this too brief portrait of these people because they're so fascinating it makes you realize
how little character development is done in most movies when you see something like lady bird i
really loved it and i think well when i read up on it on the wikipedia apparently she had a like a
three and a half four hour script of the movie that got whittled down to this um and i say she
whittled a little too far but i think i don't have the time or patience to do it but i think when
you write the four hour giant epic version of it like a lot of tv shows make you write the bible
where you write what the entire world of the show looks like and it takes a lot of time
i think it's what leads to the really great character development that comes out if you
really understand everybody and their worlds it can be a great exercise so that's what this movie
felt like to me that in a novelistic way she had spent a lot of time with these characters and
stood them and they're probably based on her family and friends as well but it's set in
sacramento where she grew up sure sharonan i fucking love her i love hannah i love brooklyn
i love this movie lori meckath excellent oh yeah it's such a beautifully written role that i'm so
glad i didn't go for a bigger actress they went for the best actress because she's perfect
um great drama great coming of age stuff should make it feel like your own story even though it's
not and there were many times in this where i couldn't tell lori meckath apart from my mother
they looked and acted and spoke so much alike it was crazy uh tracy letts as the dad is the
best character in the whole thing he's everybody's kind of dream dad he's so sweet and funny and then
you find out halfway through that he's super depressed and then in a scene that had me balling
out of the blue he goes into interview for a uh computer job and he's miserable that at age 65
he's trying to re -enter the workforce and everybody the guy that's interviewing him was like 22
and then he walks out and sees his adopted son in the lobby waiting to go in for the same uh
interview and he hugs his son and is like you should get it you know best of luck to you and
like letts needs the job to like keep his life afloat but in that moment he's like more more
concerned about his son the movie is just full of very beautiful small moments like that you got
lucas hedges as her boyfriend who is gay in a great little mini c story you got tim chalamet
and the only funny performance he's ever given where he plays like the uh high school douche
the very specific high school douche who's obsessed with like books and and and french
culture and stuff like that um i love this movie it's one of the great coming of age
stories of all time i would say it's really really well done and then my third very brief i saw
uh to die for the new 4k criterion with nicole kibman i love nicole kibman in it she does comedy
so rarely and i think she's really funny in this um however what she's doing in this nioe watts
does better i'll say that nioe watts came in is like i'm the new younger australian hot blonde
and i think nioe watts is better than nicole kibman if i may uh especially at playing this
ruthless cutthroat part but to die for is about a uh a weather woman very pretty uh she's married
to matt dylan and she basically seduces a high schooler played by joaquin phoenix who looks
literally like a child in this movie it's hard to even know it's him um but she hires joaquin
phoenix who she is fucking to murder her husband matt dylan casey afleck is also in it as sort of
a cohort partner in crime iliana douglas plays matt dylan's sister you got the great dan hadaya
in the mix as dylan's father and then stealing the show obviously an actor who i've loved for
my whole life but i've never seen him be this great in a movie he's a great comedic actor but
never seen him just be perfect um in a he's funny but he's also just perfect it's wayne night folks
newman oh yeah um and he's in so many of these 90s movies basic instinct and jurassic park of
course he pops up he's always good but um this is his best work like playing a character not
playing newman and to die for is a lot of fun it's gust van sant it was written by buck henry the
legendary writer of the graduate it got all sorts of awards attention at the time and it was super
ahead of its time in terms of uh going after the narcissism of people on social media which didn't
exist at the time but nicole kitman is definitely sort of a precursor to that type of personality
who's obsessed with himself interesting movie super entertaining fun comedy but you know is it
one of the greats was i surprised to see it get a 4k criterion yes i was i don't think it's the
classic it's made out to be but very good all right there you are uh okay mean old bitch
yeah rex reed here's his review ready yes i told matt mccarthy last night when i texted him
i said the uh i said do not read the rex reed review before you listen to the episode because
i'm going to be reading it i said do you want me to give you the title of the review he said no
save it and i said okay because it might be reed's best title ever okay and we've heard some doozies
yeah long legs is a stupid zero star dumpster fire that's the come on you you can't use dumpster
fire anymore come on now rex rex rex rex can do whatever he wants as far as i'm concerned
under that it says the worst thing about the movie is nicolas cage and his most hysterical
unhinged over the top performance since he played dracula like a vaudeville act
he's off to the races yeah is that referring to renfield yes okay uh here we go rex says it's
summer when multiplex marquees are bloated with hunks of junk
one learns through experience to expect mediocrity at the movies what one does not expect is a load
of total trash full of gimmicks instead of ideas stolen scenes from other movies instead of
originality amateurist posturing instead of professional performances clueless meandering
instead of organized screenplays and pointless confusion instead of one clear -eyed direction
every negative just listed is glaringly evident as part of the incomprehensible gibberish that
makes a crummy horror flick called long legs not only the worst movie in the summer of 2024
but one of the worst movies of all time right they gotta put him down i mean this guy's old
at this point you can't say every movie is one of the worst movies of all time and this clearly
isn't um he goes on to say there is no plot but basically it centers on a now wait a minute see
you've got somebody's got to poke back at him of course there is a plot rex um well i will read
this part because it'll save us the time of rehashing what the movie's about so so again
folks i will say this now if you haven't seen it and you want to see it there's going to be a
lot of spoilers here uh and this movie does have things to spoil so that is by the way that's
always the case we're always going to have spoilers in here we try to warn you but that's
always going to be the case you can't be mad at us for that i know but i just try to respectfully
remind everybody um i hear you i'm just telling them don't get smart with me down the line
i hear you all right he says there is no plot but basically it centers on a rookie FBI agent
named lee played by a charmless actress named michael and fashion imagine she's in starbucks
got a little coffee oh a new review a charmless actress she spits her coffee out uh she's
fashioned in the style of clarice and sounds of the lambs played with much more force and individuality
by jodie foster lee is also a psychic he's right there i mean christ the parallels between this
movie and silence of the lambs are glaring and annoying because the director talks about them
all the time but man does it suffer in comparison and man does she suffer in comparison and i like
her as an actress but come on well this movie i'll give a few thoughts as i read this about
the movie yeah the silence of the last thing is spot on this movie long legs plays plays like
os perkins was sitting around going but i want to direct silence of the lambs they're like well
he can it was already made and he goes yeah i'll do a thing with a psychic i guess well if you've
seen him interviewed about it he goes like all like i wanted to make silence of the lambs like
that was my number one talking point with my crew and we were all always on that talking about that
he goes but was i ever did i ever once think about the sounds of the lambs while making long legs
not once bullshit i don't buy that i love yeah it's like dude you you probably put screenshots
of it up and show them to your cinematographer and that's okay people do that don't let's not
pretend that you yeah you know i want i set out to make silence of the lambs but i never considered
that once we were making it you're lying uh lee says here i'm sorry reid says here lee our character
is also a psychic duh uh whose boss assigns her to the case of a mad serial killer called
for no explicable reason long legs fair point massacres entire families with daughters who
have the same birthday as lee uh parentheses you don't have you don't need to see sorry you
don't need to have seen a dozen serial killer movies already to know this means lee is targeted
for the next victim there is no mystery about long legs suspense wanes in the first scene
a sort of prologue to the rest of the movie in which lee dredges from her subconscious the memory
of a horrifying childhood visit to her home by a creature called long legs who has some
kind of relationship to her abusive single mother long legs is played in drag
well that's an interesting that's really funny he's not in drag i have seen or i saw one review
uh a gay friend of mine who went after this as being anti -trans i didn't reach out to him but i'm
like the nicolas cage character is not trans no in fact he said what appears to be and it's hard
to see where cage's face and the characters begins and ends but he's appeared to have had a lot of
plastic surgery and he dresses sort of effeminate but he's also like obsessed with glam rock and
i don't think he's trans or in drag i didn't i gotta be honest with you i didn't even find
him to dress effeminate i took his odd look in this yeah to be a guy that had uh altered his
face to look like the t -rex album cover i think so yeah mark bowlin or volk bowling yeah is like it's
it's it's a saturated picture so his face is overly whited out from in a black and white photo right
i was like oh he's supposed and then they play t -rex for the movie and he sings t -rex so i was
like he wants to look like that cover of the t -rex album anyway i've also and i'm sorry to interrupt
again but i've seen him described as being um an ex glam rocker the character and i'm like i think
you're making that up too i don't think that's in there yeah uh he writes here nick's character is
also a satan worshiper parentheses double duh i can't disagree with you rex i can't disagree
with you by the way with the psychic thing yeah you know there's only two more paragraphs here
but let me just say this you you know your movie's in trouble when your opening scene after credits
is blair underwood as the head of your branch of the fbi saying to the main character so you're
psychic that's gonna come in handy i was like this is what do we wait this is where we're
starting i know it's um at that point i thought maybe this is some sort of spoofs not the right
word but maybe it's some sort of knowing wink to all these procedural movies and it's going to do
its own thing but there's a little bit of like it's almost like in beveley hills cop when they go
into ash and he's like downing pepto bismol and like you gotta get out there whatever that they
were kind of winking at the cliche but that's not the case with long legs it's just bad writing
i will give it that it's just and i gotta tell you that psychic thing and we can get into this
i was like well that's gonna pay off at some point and it doesn't really she's just psychic
when you start really peeling back the layers of this bad boy this is another one where when i go
see it again i'm gonna go oh no no no it's gonna be a quiet place all over again where i'm like no
this has huge because they were there the first time but i found enough to like that i sort of
looked past its flaws but you're absolutely right the psychic thing doesn't really play in
and um i've got my own little thoughts on on the lack of payoffs to all the setups in the movie but
i'll let you finish the read of course so uh while lee busies herself forming clues in groups of
and deciphering codes long legs is arrested so that's the basic plot these families are being
murdered by their fathers they can't prove that long legs is in the house they don't understand
how this is happening because he's leaving these letters but he's never been in the house yet these
fathers are killing their families they've got to and he's sending these letters you know zodiac
style that have these codes to be deciphered or whatever uh long legs is arrested but before
anyone at fbi headquarters can question him about his motives he smashes his head to hamburger meat
at the interrogation table teeth fly blood splashes all over the room faster than the plot
and long legs dies but the massacres continue lee's mother heads the heads the long list of
red herrings as an eye -rolling religious nut who also has tied to the devil worshipers parentheses
say what
yeah again he's got a point he does my my buddy bridger weinger uh who has a very funny podcast
he's very funny on twitter comedy writer but he had a really great one -liner about this movie
after he saw it which is um i love how nicolas nicolas cage needs uh somebody who everyone will
trust to do his bidding so he goes after the natural first choice a retired nun who makes
creepy dolls in a basement or whatever it was a very fine not doing it right but the movie is
just glaring holes that that a studio really should have stepped in and said hey you got to fix this
well yeah they they set this mother up like the mom in carry yes where lee is calling her mother
her mother keeps being like did you say your prayers it keeps the devil away so then when
you find out that the mom is involved with long legs and she in fact is the one she's not murdering
but she's delivering these dolls which we'll get into that cause the families to murder yeah it makes
no fucking sense anyway oh rex rex's next sentence none of it makes a great deal of sense but it is
constantly savagely and intensely gory gloomy and so mystifyingly preposterous that they seem to be
making it all up as they go along long legs is a bit of a gasoline fire with a new match lit every
minute again he's got a point they keep introducing these twists and layers and it's it's over
complicated it's convoluted the ridiculous script and paralyzing direction are both by os perkins
the son of the late and versatile tony perkins rex come on let's not put tony as a director above
os yeah true come on uh considering no because perkins did psycho what three didn't yes os is a
better director and writer and i love tony perkins as an actor but but i i i don't i don't i don't
they're both very talented yeah um uh you you'd wish some of his skill would rub off on his son
he writes jesus christ dad to say there is no evidence in the loopy long legs that os perkins
has inherited any of his dad's understated cinematic abhorrence to be charitable he is
careful not to reveal more at any time than lee figures out for herself and there is some style
the dark foreboding but in my opinion even a hair -raising creep flick needs logic and this has
none it has it is never clever it is never clear what long legs motives are what the supernatural
under turns have to do with the serial killings and even less with how and why the slaughters
continue after long legs is dead yeah that's a great point which we'll get to the best thing
the film is the grim lighting and camera work agreed which is set which which set its ghoulish
mood and never brighten its consistency the worst thing is nicolas cage and his most hysterical and
unhinged over i said that already the film's ponderous third act in which everything comes
together in a tsunami of delirium is nothing less than moronic in the end you're left asking more
questions than anyone involved can or will ever answer zero out of four stars
i mean i think he's way too harsh but i don't disagree with anything he's saying about the
plot and the story of this movie i really don't um and i have my own huge issues with it
um i want to get bridger right i looked up his quote here which is i like how nicolas cage says
it has to be somebody people trust and then it winds up being the classic person everyone trusts
the nun who randomly shows up on your doorstep to tell you that you won a lifelike doll
i knew he had a much funnier way of saying it but um funny that's true i'm gonna quickly read my
letterbox review of this movie and that'll tell you where where my head's at mine's much briefer
but here we go um long glags
all right just an incredible look and vibe to this movie i had a blast and i wasn't bored for a
second i'll take something like this over the vast majority of modern trauma horror however in all
caps how are you going to create a truly great horror villain have him beautifully brought to
by cage and one hell of a makeup department create one of the all -time classic intro scenes
for that character give him his own killer t -rex soundtrack be savvy enough to keep him off camera
most of the running time jaws style so we're even more on edge only to have him recruit a nun to do
his bidding yeah it's like if freddy krueger said yes i can murder teenagers in their dreams
but i'd prefer to compel a neighborhood mom to handle in fact i think i'll just detach these
iconic footlong claws for the evening maybe start watching that new season of the bear
that's exactly how i felt about this movie was the opening scene where they keep cage's face out of
frame it's so simple i have i've never seen that trick where you're just like seeing something at
an angle that obscures his face so unsettling so weird so creepy kicks right into that awesome
t -rex song to kick off the movie and i was like oh yeah we got a classic here boys yeah i was so
pumped i really do love t -rex i have all their albums i love t -rex constantly so i was like
i'm totally on board and they do he does perkins does such a great job i think cage does a great
job he's over the top but it's nicholas cage i was so into this so on board i'm like okay the
influences here are three of my favorite movies ever prisoners zodiac sounds of the lambs it
really wears its influences on its sleeve movie looks a lot like prisoners in terms of its visual
style yes and you just realize as it goes i'm i'm in the hands of a master director these scenes
are super tense they are perfectly framed shot just you hear you heard gassed from time to time
it's a film town but some of the shots in this movie are truly something else and look amazing
but boy it's that chameleon thing you need to recruit somebody else to help you with your
stories uh because you feel his grip and his control just being washed away with everything
until to me it was as big of a change in the movie as like moholland drive when they go into
that little box it becomes a whole new movie yeah a much darker more intense movie as soon
as nicholas cage does that where he bashes his face into the thing which i thought was a
fucking fantastic scene by the way great scene um i was like shit i didn't expect it you know
we haven't seen much of cage so the whole time you're expecting him to be chasing her in the
act and when he kills himself at the beginning of that third act you're like well what the hell's
going on at that moment i think everybody in the theater was like oh okay here's where the big
twist comes in it's like when jodie foster is at the wrong house in silence of the lambs one of the
great movie moments ever and you're like oh no so that happens you have that great feeling of oh no
what's going on what's going to happen and then what does happen is so beyond unsatisfying and
just so not good and nonsensical and one of my least favorite things that these type of movies
do and they do them rarely by the way because it's always a gamble that never pays off you
don't introduce a supernatural angle an hour into a straightforward procedural well but they don't
but they don't introduce it an hour in they introduce it in the opening scene after the
credits in fact in the opening scene when she points at the house and goes when they're after
the the the first family of the dad that killed everybody yeah she just points at the house and
she goes it's that house there oh yeah yeah and then blair underwood goes so you're a psychic
how did you do that wow well look i'm like what psychic shit i don't necessarily consider
supernatural i don't i don't necessarily believe it either but i'm talking particularly about the
phantasm orbs and the doll's heads that control people's uh minds so that's a gun style yeah
that's the thing that yes it is sort of like making gun that is the thing you find out that
these dolls are being delivered to these homes for whatever reason and something's afoot with
dolls there's a scene in forensics in the in the crime lab i mean god damn it's so lazily written
where the guy dissects the doll and yeah silver ball out of its head and he goes that's the brain
it talks and you're like what the fuck is going on i don't understand like so then you find out later
nicolas cage somehow plants evil into these dolls or messages that speak to people into these dolls
and the dolls pollute the brain of the father of the family they're delivered to and then that
makes the father kill the family okay great fine but then nicolas cage kills himself and as rex
pointed out how is anything bad still happening right if he's dead now you could argue because
the last doll was already poisoned by nicolas cage and that's what's happening i guess that's
what's happening but if nicolas the whole reason the mom of lee is helped by the way played by
alicia wit who as far as i know is like 43
couldn't i i slid my phone out to do the discrete lookup i was like that can't be alicia wit
but she is like 43 i went at growing up she was in all these teen movies were the same age i mean
there nothing about it makes sense um so but to rex's point so now nicolas cage oh wait you so
could argue that the doll was already possessed and so he's dead so it doesn't matter but then
alicia wit's whole motive for delivering these dolls is that long legs let her daughter live
and the deal was if i let your daughter live you have to deliver these dolls for me and and have
others kill okay yeah but now he's dead so who cares and then when the daughter tries to stop
her mom in the end she ends up having to kill her mom because the mom wants to keep carrying
out the work but it's like no the bad guy is dead right and then the nun says hail satan after
through the entire film she has told her daughter to pray to keep the devil away none of it makes
any fucking sense and yeah it's like was so was she did nicolas cage's influence over her over these
last 30 years even though she's 43 years old did his influence over her make her steadily become
evil over time i guess that's what we're supposed to take away and that she was lying to her daughter
and saying like you know she's the devil she lies whatever that's what i that's how i took it but
doesn't mean i'm right and all this stuff it's not the movie's lynchian in look and feel and tone
but david lynch has such a complete mastery of what he's doing you might not get it but he gets
it and so you go along with him this guy is really just kind of throwing weird shit up at the camera
and seeing if it sticks and when stuff doesn't land it's not because this movie operates in a
dream state or a nightmare state like lynch's stuff it's because he doesn't seem to know how
effectively tell this story this i think why me and other people joe and other people are so
frustrated about it is that what's strong about the movie is very strong and it's the case with
all of osgood perkins movies and i'll go through them when we're done doing the kind of summary
here but he's got this problem every time it's beautiful movies with chilling memorable images
that pop up but on the whole you're like just get a writing partner dude you can't do this
yeah there it was very beautifully shot it was very well acted even i hated the main character
it wasn't her fault she did a fine job it was written poorly i can't stand the brooding
stoic detective i was just like oh god come on guys it felt like seven uh
uh it looked great i'm sorry quick pause again when you say it felt like seven
the this movie wearing its influences on its sleeve like there's a scene where she goes over
to meet her partner's family and it's like that is seven you know it's like there there are so
many moments in this where you're like but that's this it's a pastiche of all these movies um and
they're better movies so you just wind up going well i wish it was like those movies it's it's
it's true detective it's it's it's we've seen it a million times the cop that's got the family
that lives the sort of traditional life and is a by the books cop with the new recruit or partner
or whomever that is distant and distracted and and preoccupied by her past or his past or whatever
we've seen it um whatever that's fine but it's just i i i felt that this veered into our gento
territory and i've complained about our gentle before the best of our gentos work it looks
beautiful it's scary in moments it's shocking in moments it's visually stunning but when you try
to piece a story together you can't there's not logic and here's the thing with lynch
who goes full till art house boogie okay that's a different story if you want to be samuel becket
and create absurdity then create absurdity but this movie is not striving to create absurdity
it's striving to pull you in to a detective story it wants you to follow the procedural and and and
the mystery and when logic goes completely out the window i'm just going what the fuck am i
watching and by the way when i say logic i'm not even going to nitpick at supernatural and all that
stuff it's it's lazily written in the sense of guys you've got a room full of detectives standing
over two dead bodies that are filled with maggots because they've rotted away in a bed for a month
and nobody is covering their face right nobody is covering their face because the stench is unbear
everybody's just standing there talking like they're in a starbucks it's ridiculous
come on guys put a little thought into the making well then you can you compare that scene to its
identical counterpart in seven they do the exact same thing in seven when you walk into that room
where the corpse is there are a thousand pine tree air fresheners hanging from the ceiling
and then still everyone in the room pukes covers their mouth hardened detectives etc it's it's
weird it's like this guy watched all those movies but was like i'm not going to go the extra mile of
like speaking for five minutes to a policeman to find out what their job is like like everyone is
just acting like he put every movie he's ever seen into a blender and then just kind of threw the
they're acting like movie characters but they're acting like copies of movie characters
because he didn't do the research the person who wrote the movie he's ripping off did the research
well i also have a real problem with
compensating for lazy writing with quirkiness yeah so when they go to to the insane asylum
whatever it's mental hospital because there's a girl that has survived one of these killings
and she's in this facility now and you find out they find out that long legs has visited her
and they go to the director of the facility and they're trying to find out the identity of this
yeah and and the the the the director of the facility is it's it's it's like a it's like rip
taylor he's in like a purple suit oh he's like yeah and he's like this is wild you know and it's
it's so campy and then they go did you check the idea of the visitor and he goes well we don't
that's a good idea i guess we should and it's like guys come on man come on come on like this it's
lazy having having the crime lab director be quirky and be like this silver ball is the brain
and as a means to not convey any real information yeah it's just it's just lazy writing um because
there's too much focus on you know somebody a friend of mine said something very interesting
to me recently and i'm not saying this is what os os perkins is but he said he's a writer and
he said you know man i'm i'm kind of getting tired of all these movies directed by commercial
directors they get these guys that direct a bunch of commercials and then they have them direct a
movie and they think what works in a commercial makes for a good movie and it doesn't yeah stunning
visuals and whatever are great for a commercial in a movie you have to capture what you're trying
to do in the movie now he does capture that in this uh with mood and whatever but i've said it
million times before if you want to direct a music video go direct a music video that's all mood
and you don't have to worry about story this you need to worry about story and i i just don't get
again i feel like he was sitting around saying i want to make silence of the lambs i'm not allowed
to so i'm going to just copy it to an extent and add all these elements to make it my own thing but
those elements don't fit together that the scene you want to talk about logic
long early in the movie long legs goes to the main character's house yeah and she sees him
inside her own house yeah and then just goes back in the house and just sits there
reading the letter he's left her doesn't yeah i found that nuts too secure the home doesn't go
onto the phone immediately to the fbi guys he's he was here yeah there's no there's nothing she
hides it she never reveals it to to the team um and i and you could say well because he says in
the thing he threatens to kill the girl if she were come on guys this is stop it's 19 the movie
takes place in 1991 i think he's not watching her with cameras it's not they don't have the
technology there's privacy in this world that this movie takes place in she would reveal this
and she does it and then that's there by the way just as a red herring so you go is she long legs
is she imagining this and then and then she's not and then you're like well then if she's not him
then why the fuck didn't she report all i don't know man i don't know when i went to the uh
box page now there's an image of this woman in a bra and panties cutting her stomach
open and you saw it last night i'm realizing i remember seeing that but i don't remember what
it even was what what is that scene i don't remember that a good looking a good looking
lady in a bra cutting open her stomach with her she's tracing a stomach or tracing a knife along
her stomach i remember the scene i just don't remember what it was i don't remember that
all right um i mean and that's that's weird because you saw it last night so also too also too
there is no mission of the killer like now i get it he's a killer but
aside from the fact that he's trying to on the calendar create
the symbol that means six six six or whatever with the dot the two triangles or whatever
i guess that's enough i don't know but i also really hated again lazy right writing
that lee can just like immediately she opens the book about the devil to the exact page
as she's trying to decode what's going on and knows exactly what symbol she's looking
for whatever there's that terrible scene where there's the the the it's the asian lady is like
the book of revelations and then lee goes revelation there is no s and and then she
starts reciting it and then it cuts it does the the reaction shot of the asian lady and the asian
lady like makes this face like oh i'm embarrassed this girl knows her stuff and it's like guys this
is fucking lazy this is fucking lazy and this just isn't how this interaction would go then also
blair underwood later in the movie gets more and more indignant about how nothing mystical or psychic
or whatever exists you know like this is the guy at the beginning that says he thinks it will be
yeah so i i just again looked great very well acted poorly written i did like cage and cage
the one thing he did really well was cage's character he just looks some his face looks
off somebody on rotten tomatoes said he looks like mickey rourke which is funny because he kind of
off he's doing something yeah you know is it plastic surgery it is it that growth hormone that
makes your head big that that fighters take sometimes but the point is is like they did
that very well you know for years in different horror ideas i've written and stuff i've put
the concept into it of not being able to see a character's face but seeing enough of it that you
don't that you know you don't want to see any more of it and they did that with cage in this they
did a really good job of like something's weird about this guy i don't know if i want to see his
face um so so that was i'm trying to compliment it that was very well done like again i can't stress
enough i thought it was amazingly directed and after that opening cold open i was like this is
all right this is going to be pretty awesome i'm excited and through the first act i was interested
and even with the psychic stuff i was like okay i get it she's psychic he's psychic
a psychic after a psychic that this is interesting i don't know that i've seen this
okay i'm in i'm listening i'm watching right and then as it went and just there couldn't be anything
lazier than worshiping the devil it's like come on guys the the devil what are we what are we doing
here what are we doing yeah i don't know i'm the old the old osgood parkins um he he made hansel
and gretel came out in 2020 pandemic movie a lot of raves about the look of it i saw it myself
i feel even stronger that that one is a movie that's style over substance it's not a good movie
did we do that one on the show i think we did and i i enjoyed hansel and gretel um he did
i am the pretty thing that lives in the house which i think we also did
or gretel and hansel excuse me gretel and hansel um and he did the black coats daughter which i
very much enjoyed but which also kind of didn't stick the landing um long legs not only his
biggest hit by far but like one of the biggest indie horror movies of all time he's going to
have quite a career now i know he's good friends with old jordan peale uh he appeared in nope as
actor uh and his next project is stephen king's the monkey yes which i believe is which that's a
short story from which book i don't recall skeleton crew skeleton crew um yeah it's i really
hope at some point old osgood just directs somebody else's script um because
he's an excellent director he's just not a good writer and tone is not really his thing you know
that well the tone it that's a very unsettling uh horrific tone of dread throughout the movie for
sure but then yeah these characters like the the guy at the morgue and etc what this movie might
feel like to people 20 years from now is how like a season of the witch feels to us or something
from the 80s where you're like this is ludicrous but there's a charm to it the things that do work
are creepy and fun and you sort of look past the rest of it because it's an old movie but i think
this movie needs 20 years of like uh you know of just like time being kind to it because right now
for as big a business as this movie is doing everybody walking out of the theater behind
me was complaining about the movie oh really yeah oh that's interesting and complaining about
the ending and and what the fuck even happened there at the end and whatever else um because
you show up for these things not every movie requires uh a definitive here's what happened
ending unless you're doing one of these procedurals you can't put the people through all this and not
us what happened at the end of the fucking movie and by the way prisoners seven zodiac they all
have brilliant endings zodiac doesn't know who the killer is but that's what the movie is about
you know that's the theme of the movie so that's the issue is he's following in the footsteps of
these great movies but those great movies knew what they were doing and how to end them and
um every piece seemed like it led to the next piece and so on and so forth
this just it lacks control maybe doing the stephen king story will be good for him because he's
got a framework but then again stephen king's stories are often ludicrous so who knows well
also um you know the the we left out one of the big twists that's
and you know keeps nicolas cage keeps referring to the man downstairs you think he means the devil
right uh you realize at the end the man downstairs was nicolas cage because he's been living
in the mother's house that that's his lair she wakes lee the main character wakes up in the lair
at the end before she goes to try to save blair underwood's family and you're like oh she's in
the long legs lair how did she get there and then she walks upstairs and it's her mom's house
and you're like so he's he's been living with the mom and again it's like
uh okay i guess but by the way completely silence of the lambs the entire end of silence of the lambs
is the reveal of the wrong house yeah and it's the basement in the other house or whatever it's just
a variation of that but you talk to your mom every other day and you haven't gotten a hint
that there's a man living in her house you know uh yeah because you haven't visited her
yet you call her and they sort of try to implicate that she or imply that that that she doesn't
see her mom a lot and it's like no she does she calls her mid investigation
like two times in the movie she leaves like a crime scene to call her mom yeah
i don't know and the mom's not aware that the daughter might be
this might be the the big case she's working i don't know i don't know it was it was
i knew i and and i say this to the audience because sometimes people will comment on patreon
that i'm too hard on things or a little close -minded or whatever and i'm i'm aware of my
i'm aware of who i am i'm also aware that when i hear everybody praising something i start to
you know the antennas go up and i start to move a little in the other direction just organically
i'm aware of that but i will say and i don't think i was wrong and i said this on the podcast
everybody saying before this movie was released it's the scariest movie of the decade no
immediately i'm like we we've got a problem here this is just hyperbole everybody has to
speak in hyperbole yeah and there's so much of that hyperbole before you can even see the
goddamn movie that it can't you can't help but have it influence how you're going to go into it
yeah and truth be told it's not a particularly scary movie it's not like that kind it's scarier
than all of it or less scary than the other movies we mentioned you know there's a feeling
of dread but there's not a lot of like ah or on the edge of my seat type feeling so the devil
shots were scary which ones the devil shots yeah like when it shows the devil behind her when it
shows the devil the the thing in the cloak like that was like that's scary all right that's cool
yeah i mean i don't think rex reed is anywhere near accurate when he says that this is one of
the worst movies of all time it is nowhere near one of the worst movies of this year
it is also not one of the scariest movies of all time or of the decade or probably even of the year
it's a beautiful movie to look at and that was kind of enough for me a lot of times that's enough
for me on a first viewing of a movie then it either becomes a classic to me or a movie where
i'm like oh god like what was i thinking this will be a what was i thinking movie for sure
because even with my very negative review of it or my questioning review of it i gave it
four out of five stars which is like a b plus and i stand by that because i had a blast watching it
however from any sort of story plot logic standpoint it really falls apart
and the the problem is you get the feeling he was trying to make it make sense that that's
you know like that's not lynch's objective is to give you a traditional whodunit he doesn't give
fuck blue velvet is not about well who cut off this ear you know it is but it ultimately doesn't
matter this movie sets up a we've got a big twist coming and you won't believe who's doing these
crimes and then when you find out you're just like no dude no and that's a problem with these
movies where the reveal is kind of everything so now here's the thing i would give it maybe a
a two and a half to a three out of five stars that's what i get that pull you know based on
just the craftsmanship yeah not the writing but just the visual structure of the film
you know you compare this to what like smile 2 looks like yeah it's it's no contest this this
will visually without even seeing smile 2 i promise you this will beat it in the visual
aesthetic department however i'm willing to bet you smile 2 will have a more coherent plot
whereas this does it i wish we could get both together more frequently we just can't smile 2
by the way if you didn't know anything about the original smile you'd think the trailer for this
fucking thing you'd think it's just a movie about people that smile at you yeah i'm like guys maybe
tell the audience what the fuck is going on here and could you care any less than now being about
lady gaga style pop star like who cares anyway really that's becoming uh a real go -to in horror
oddly enough there's all these stalker movies i'm seeing tonight the new chameleon where heart net
is at a taylor swift concert basically but he's also there with his daughter and he's a serial
killer and i don't know what that's even about but i'm gonna go see it supposed to be good people
saying it's chameleon's best in a very long time so we'll see all right um anyway folks my hog is
down for uh uh down bashing its head down into a table repeatedly until it's dead yeah or long legs
outside of the the direction and uh director of photography work that was done in it
and my hog is up i had a really good time with the movie i do not think it will stand up to repeat
viewings i'm not entirely sure it stood up to one viewing but i do think that the visuals vibe nick
cage that character um the just the general fun of the movie makes it unquestionably a hogs up kind
of picture but with huge issues of course so let's let's say that i'm my hog is erect
but it has an std is what i would say it's infected fair enough uh we'll be back with
deadpool and wolverine after that i think we'll have uh maxine and probably fall guy or maybe
line will if i if it's great then let's do it that's it folks we'll see you next time
and we'll see you in hell