I'm here for BetRivers' online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of BetRivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great!
And the same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool.
A blackjack icon, a moneyline icon.
A roulette icon.
Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, BetRivers is the place to play in Bet.
BetRivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus and President of West Virginia.
Void were prohibited.
Terms and conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -GAMBLING.
Hadaday presents, in the red corner,
the undisputed, undefeated, weed -whacker guy!
Champion of hurling grass and pollen everywhere!
And in the blue corner, the challenger,
extra strength, Hadaday!
Eye drops and work all day to prevent the release of histamines
that cause itchy allergy eyes.
And the winner, by knockout, is Hadaday!
Hadaday, bring it on!
We're back, we'll see you in hell.
Episode 2.
two. Number two. Episode two. This is a big one tonight.
Nightmare on Elm Street. Nightmare on Elm Street one episode two. Directed
by Wes Craven. The movie, not the episode. He also directed the podcast tonight. He's
not happy with our performance thus far. Get out of here. Come on. We're thrilled
to be here doing this with the Fangoria podcast network. Newly launched Fangoria podcast
Cast Network a proud moment for both of us. I'm Joe DeRosa. I'm Pat Walsh. Thrilled is
extreme for me. I'm I'm having a nice time. I wouldn't say thrilled. Fair enough. I mean
you want to bite the hand that feeds. No absolutely. Listen. So we're we're we're
jumping right in. I feel like you know we open the series with children of the corn
and now the second episode we're going right to nightmare in Elm Street. I don't think
it gets any more classic horror than this. It doesn't.
We discussed doing leprechaun. Pat made the point of he didn't want people to think it
was a thing where we were just making fun of movies because I don't think anybody thinks
leprechaun is a great horror movie. No. No. But we wanted it to be. You know what
I mean. Yeah. We wanted it to be. I wanted that remake
that new one that came out to be awesome. The new leprechaun.
Leprechaun Origins. That happened. Oh yeah. I didn't know about that.
I met Ricky Gervais once on a radio show and I said why of all the things you made fun
of on life's too short did you never make fun of leprechaun.
Yeah.
And he was like oh man I'm sure we did it was just probably got cut.
Okay.
Fair enough.
Anyway.
He cackled like a mad man and told you he didn't believe in God.
Yeah.
Let's fire it up.
I actually get tense when we're talking and you haven't started it.
I don't know why because this goddamn Apple TV, you know, it does this on and off thing.
Yeah.
All right.
So we'll count to three and then say search.
And that's your cue to pause the podcast.
Search for Nightmare on Elm Street on your whatever
your device for streaming is.
You know, these are all movies that are on Netflix
Insta.
You can go ahead and search for it now.
You don't need to count down to search.
Well, let's just wipe your ass for you.
You know, let's give them.
To find Nightmare on Elm Street.
We'll say play.
You do a play and then immediate pause.
We're all on the pause screen.
And then we go one, two, three play.
Yeah, but they need time to do that.
and it might not be fast enough so what if they weren't let's just give them a
countdown let's just count down everything you do all right here's the
countdown for you to go fine when you hear me say search you pause it you go
you find it whatever one are they pausing the podcast so they can go find the
fucking movie just let them go do it one two three search like a like a dog Joe in
morning when he wakes up I have before he brushes his teeth I have to come over and go one two three
brush and then he brushes now just in case you got confused because Pat talked through the part
where we're supposed to say we're back we're gonna give you another chance one two three search
we're back okay here we go we're back uh you've unpaused uh now uh this is how we do this you
hit play and when it gets to the first frame of the screen you of the movie you
hit pause again and the reason we do this because load times vary right am I
over explaining this I feel like it couldn't be less complicated but being
made more okay well I'm trying my best what do you want me I just feel like
people are gonna get confused I worry about that too all you're doing
everybody and I think we might have to adapt this for a future one is you're
going to hit play and then hit pause.
So now we're all on a screen that has like one second
or two seconds on it.
Right.
Because everybody's load time is different.
That's where we do that.
Everybody's load time.
Everybody's Wi -Fi is different.
You have time warning.
You're going to be waiting 30, 40 minutes.
Oh!
As you would say.
You're going to do when we count down one, two, three play,
we all hit play and now we're going to watch.
OK.
So now you've got it paused, hopefully, at this point.
I hope so, or else.
I mean, if you don't, I don't know how you hit play
on this podcast.
OK.
So here we go.
Joe on play one two three play and it's playing. There we go. We got new from New Line Cinema
New Line Cinema is on your screen. Hopefully we're all in the same page. And the thing
I think you're missing Joe is that they don't need to pause the pocket. They can look for
the stuff while listening to what if it takes a while. What if you're dealing with a slow
man. I mean I think that's all I'm saying. He's always got to quit. Now I'd like to
start with something completely unrelated. In the last episode we talked about how much
of a disappointment the poltergeist remake was right and we both speculated that perhaps
the new vacation would not be up to par. It's got a I believe it twenty six percent
on right to bearable views and Joe and friends I'm here to tell you I just came
from seeing it and it is extremely funny the vacation remake there are a lot of big laughs
in it here the fuck out of now whenever they go for a huge like a set piece a huge over
the top scene those don't really work but everything else works and I'm going to confuse
it even further by telling you I didn't love Ed Helms or Christina Applegate in it but
I thought the movie was really funny I thought you were going to go into a thing about
the nightmare in Elm Street we're gonna get there okay but I thought it was very funny
and the kids in this remake are so fucking funny the little kid basically the one gimmick
is that it's a younger brother bullying his older brother I funny I thought those parts
in the trailer were funny that's how you sound that kid cracked me up a little kid
in that movie both of them were great and the movie gave me a lot of laughs and I'm sorry
I spoke ill of it and nobody's telling me to say that I promise. Then why is it getting such bad reviews? I
think critics
Just kind of generally hate comedy. I'd love to sit next to these people and see if they truly didn't laugh throughout the movie
I can't believe that you're telling me this movies. All right. I'm gonna believe it. Listen here's where I'm gonna believe it
Terminator Genesis as we talked about the last episode terrible reviews. Yeah terrible rating
I loved every minute of it. I might just start going with the opposite and round tomatoes is usually if you really read the reviews
It's like oh this is a good review and they're putting it as a bad or vice versa, okay fair enough
But I'm telling you right now. It's very funny. I usually go by what Richard Roper says
My big Richard Roper sure. Well, he's a very insensitive film crew
If you're watching the film along with us, which you know, you don't have to do
I guess we should have mentioned that at the top. I forgot to but
You know, you don't have to watch the movie along with us
You can just kind of listen to this
But if you are watching she's walking through some pipes now
I'm having anxiety about it or Rick Shane just just went off. I'm having anxiety about the fact that we didn't tell them at the beginning
They didn't have to watch the movie
Do they yeah, we have a we have a whole description up remember. Oh, yeah, that's right. Okay good enough good enough
I worry about everything. Here we go
I wish we had slammed Peter Travers because he's a far worse critic than Richard Roper. No, I I really meant what I said
I like Richard Roper. I like him too. He's a very like man of the people type. Yeah, I loved Ebert
Ebert's my favorite of all time. I loved Ebert. There's there's no better film critic. I don't
know if I'd be doing what I'm doing with that. Here's my favorite Ebert review. You're ready.
Yeah. He said Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of
the Crystal Skull loved it. He said was it as good as the first one or the second one
of the third one. I don't know. That's like asking me if I eat four pounds of sausage.
Which pound was the most delicious?
Oh.
Well, I'll tell you that fourth pound was not the most delicious.
You should have a little better memory than that.
It was a great analogy.
My favorite Ebert review is of a horror movie.
M. Night Slamalons, The Village.
And it's such a funny, perfectly written review,
and I urge you to look it up online,
because I won't do it justice.
But the final paragraph of it is such perfect, funny,
trashing the movie comedy writing I loved it what did he say we'll see I just said if you
should probably look it up so I'm gonna botch it but the gist of it was it's the kind of
twist that make I'm gonna botch it it's the kind of twist that makes you wanna I'm gonna
botch it look at how you're saying you're going to botch it as if it was smooth sailing
up until this point you forced me to say it when I said god damn it Joe now here's
Just a part that I'm glad you asked that question.
This is a thing I was always slightly confused about in the original Nightmare in Elm Street.
Are these children dancing and singing really there or is she dreaming this right now?
Because look, this is reality.
And they shot that in a very ghostly way.
Yeah.
Are they supposed to be the girls that Freddie molested?
Well, they never say molested in this original.
That's something they more clarified in the remake, which I enjoyed.
I know people say it sucked but it did suck.
To those people I say you didn't see parts four, five and six in the theater like I did.
I mean it was just nice to have a scary Freddie back again.
I was happy about that.
New Nightmare was good.
Did you like Freddie versus Jason?
I like it now.
I had to watch an interview with the director who said he wanted to make like a classic
monster fight movie like a Godzilla versus King Kong like over the top crazy whatever
once I saw that and understood where he was coming from with it I was like okay now I
like it right but I had to see that because I went into the theater again opening day
and from the minute in the opening monologue where Freddy goes then they forgot about
me and that's a bitch I was just like what is he gonna surfboard right now I never
liked his wisecrack. I went into Freddie versus Jason thinking it was a legal thriller along
the lines of like Kramer versus Kramer and they would each have attorneys and maybe it
was a divorce case for custody of the kids. That's the other kids that they would molest
or murder. The last two these children. Yeah. Going back
to vacation for no reason since this isn't a vacation podcast but when you watch the
new movie note that there's a bizarre obsession with pedophilia jokes like there's 80 of them
and they're not all great no wonder why they wouldn't take some out it's a little weird
who's making the pedophilia jokes they're everyone everyone in the movie is basically
hinted at as being kind of a pedophile want to make note again second episode in a row
strong pedophilia theme I'm telling you once again it's on the brain vacation and watching
watching a movie about a pedophile. One of the most famous pedophiles ever.
He's not quite a pedophile in this one. What are you talking about? He's a child murderer
in this one. They don't ever say the pedophile thing.
Sure they do. Don't they? No. They make a point to say it in the
remake and if you watch any behind the scenes stuff with the remake they say like we wanted
to make him even more unlikable so we brought out the pedophile undertones.
I thought for sure they did. I mean I guess the assumption is in this
that he is. I mean. Yeah.
Yeah. You know Johnny Depp here. Seventeen. I think his age is gorgeous. He's just beautiful.
Yeah. Now he looks kind of like Stephen Tyler floated
up on the beach but still beautiful. He looks like Stephen Tyler got raped by
Stevie Ray Vaughn's scarf collection or Stephen Tyler scarf collection. Both Stevens big
on scarves. Yeah that's true. Now which of these two were you more attracted to Heather
Langenkamp or I don't remember Tina's real name but the blonde. I think I'd go with the
blonde. I think she turns me on a little bit more. It's a little of a pixie vibe. No I
always loved Langenkamp. I liked her on a ABC TGIF sitcom called Just the Ten of Us.
Yeah. About like a family of basketball players.
Yeah. That movie. That was a coach. That sitcom was shot about eight years after this
and she played a character two years younger. Yeah that's true. Which always confused me
But I did like it's been off for growing pains. That's true. It was a good show. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, and then now scream which we also took bandied about
Viewing and talking about tonight and which will in the future, of course we will but scream I guess clearly
Those are lots of this movie directed by the same guy and they found
The exact same person Skeet Ulrich to play the Johnny Depp
Like you wouldn't you wouldn't know they were different men at that time. What happened Skeet Ulrich?
Where are you don't know I guess maybe because his name was Skeet and then when it hit the
rap world his name basically represented coming on some.
It's one of my favorite Hollywood minute jokes by David Spade.
It was when he was big and they put a picture Skeet Aldrich and he went hey Skeet Johnny
Depp called he wants his DNA back.
Yeah I love the balls of David Spade like really not not having any sort of film
career at that point just taking on the hugest people in Hollywood.
Got in trouble for it.
I admire the balls.
I know I did.
Trouble for it.
Yeah.
Murphy.
But it's great stuff.
It's great stuff.
It's the good stuff.
It's the old stuff as they say.
Now your favorite nightmare on Elm Street is this one.
Yeah.
I mean with our question number one in my book is the best.
I think number three is the second best and I think seven is the third best.
Seven is new nightmare.
I've only seen one two three and new nightmare and I've seen all the modern day ones that
I thought we're all kind of trash to get some fun moments but it's not a great movie but
I put it above five and six without question. There's a great documentary about the whole
franchise that discusses the intense homosexual overtones in Nightmare on Elm Street too. Yes
and I got to tell you they weren't far off. It's like there's a really interesting thing
going on there and it's like not that suddenly done either. No no it's written or directed
by a gay guy. I think a gay guy wrote it and there's a tremendous documentary called Never
Sleep Again on Netflix where he's like laughing like yeah I just thought it was fun to put like
a lot of gay undertones through the whole thing. Oh it made the movie a blast to watch.
I like it. Wow they're. Yeah you got that fucking gym teacher that's like I'm going to make
you do laps at midnight because you caught me in a gay bar now hit the showers and then
Freddie chooses to whip him. Yeah. Like whips him while masturbating or something like that.
The one part I didn't agree about it with was when they go in that documentary they're like
it's clearly a gay metaphor when he could run. He's with the woman that he loves and
he leaves her to run and retreat to his friend's bedroom. Yeah. I was like well he runs away
because he's going to turn into Freddie and kill her and he's terrified right and he goes
to his boy's house like that's what any guy that age would do. I think he also though has
like a pretty lengthy choreographed dance in his bedroom. Yeah that ends with him popping
a cork as his dick. There it is. There it is. Yeah it's a it's a it's an enjoyable
film though. The part with the bird bursting into flames is pretty crazy. Yeah I remember
of that and then the end is the standard house party actually horror movies don't give you
a lot of like house party getting attacked by a killer.
Wes Craven says in that documentary that was the part where he realized that the he was
like they blow it it's off the rails why is Freddie appearing in real life.
Yeah there's something like if there's that many people around you're not that scared
because it's kind of like well at least you're there in it with people and then watching
it you're like well they're not gonna he's not gonna kill everybody.
By the way, if you're watching along with us, Rick just came inside of Tina.
I mean, he might have pulled out.
We don't know.
He might have had a rubber in those days.
They're wondering who Rick is.
He's the guy that you can't tell if he's Italian or Puerto Rican.
He's just kind of right up the middle there.
Maybe a black Irish.
Nobody knows.
Sure.
Is there some there's a little nudity in this, I think we were bemoaning last
night the lack of nudity in the horror genre, which I think is a real shame because
Because you could always count on teen movies and you could always count on horror movies
and now neither neither and usually they're PG 13 in both cases.
I watched mirrors this afternoon starting the Great Keep for Sutherland and you see Amy
Smart from the back naked.
I remember that.
You see your butt.
I mean it's just a tremendous shot and I was by myself it was three o 'clock in the afternoon
and when they showed her ass I went ooh nice.
Which should mean.
I'm really glad I missed that.
Yeah. I should be never allowed to be to date ever again. It's a fairly real creep. Oh nice.
Oh nice. Now don't say that in real life when you see a when I see Amy Smart naked when you're
making love to Amy Smart who would not be doing anything particularly smart that night.
I'll tell you that much. Look at this hospital blanket they have on the bed.
This is bright is crazy blue hospital blanket. I
Want to say last night. I said I made some remark that I didn't know if any girls would be listening to this podcast
And I want to retract that it was a very sexist and stupid thing to say and I know many girls who watch horror movies
I don't know why I said it can't believe that's the thing you're worried about
After saying that the happiness is a tremendous film a lot of people think happiness is a great film
Films can be good about difficult subjects. I just want to mark two episodes in a row
So lots of pedophilia talk and talks of the gay undertones in a horror movie because last
night we got into the molester that made powder and fun house or fun.
Was it fun house or was it.
It was called the fun house for Francis Ford.
I believe.
Oh no.
What's the movie Sam Rock Sam Rockwell is very has a very early film.
That's a horror movie.
It's not fun house though that I do not know.
I can't remember this one of my favorite parts of the movie when Freddy comes through
the rubbery he makes the wall into like a latex just really great cheap well done
special effects that don't look cheap as compared to our last one the children of
the corn look at that that looks perfect and you know this movie had no budget
yeah it looks real as shit and children of the corn decided to put like a
sticker over the screen to represent a man turning to fling but by the way
Hey, this whiskey I picked up today is delectable.
What's the name of it?
Let's give him a shout out.
I can't remember.
I left it in the other room.
Papa Bourbon's Drink Hutch.
Something like that.
I think a whiskey Dix O 'Hallohan.
Yeah, I've met him once or twice.
Good guy.
Great whiskey.
Sure.
Any, you think there's maybe doing a little Christ
symbolism with Freddie coming out of the wall
in front of that crucifix?
I don't know what it would be.
And I'm not smart enough to speak further on that.
But maybe they are well is that Ernie that cookie jar is Ernie, right? Yes, that's an Ernie cookie jar from the back
I never noticed that good. I absolutely good. I I think the I don't think that's Christ symbolism
I think it's supposed to be the symbolism is he knocks Jesus off the wall like
God can't protect you
Sure sure when he comes out of the rubber wall. Is this a look you like the the lady in a dress shirt and no slack
Does anybody not like it is just fantastic. Is anybody complaining about this look?
Here comes doesn't happen much in my
Day -to -day life, but it happens in movies all the damn time now if you're watching along with us
And if you're not to worry it'll be described
We're about to see a shot and it's the scariest Freddy has ever been and will ever be they will never make Freddy scarier than this moment
Tina's now in the alleyway. They stole that shot from Paperboy the video game. Yeah of a trash can live trash
Yeah, yeah, well, it's like the park coming up where the guy in the boombox makes a car crash happen
Yeah, exactly
That is the scariest thing ever the long arm Freddy and he's just pretty laughing like a witch
It's so fucking scary and it's something that it would happen in a dream where you'd be like
This is God puts the claw over his face there's that look at the way he's running yeah
Oh, it's so scary and he's just toying with her. That's what the great part is
There he goes. He disappears reappears in front of her
He can catch her if he wants but he's gonna have some fun with it now going back to paper boy the video game. I
But can we just can we point out this part? This is the second scariest thing
Cuts the fingers off and green slime jizzes out of the fingers should have been thicker and plus here
well sorry Pat that it didn't more closely resemble actual come I apologize I do come
green well do you ever see the watch Vince Vaughn movie I sure did I think you like that
quite a bit more than I did I loved it but my favorite joke is when the Indian guy is
rubbing the green slime between his fingers and he says it does feel like come the taste
the color of the texture and it's bright green. Yeah. And then you find out later as an alien
you're like oh it's yeah. Right. Alien come. I remember that show. Great show. This is amazing
special effects right here. It is similar to the Joe Beth Williams and poltergeist being
thrown around. Very simple. Anything. Anything hotter than Joe Beth Williams and poltergeist.
We didn't touch on that last episode. I used to really I would like I would be
like this is gonna be my wife.
I would like her to be Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist.
And any more of a dad than Craig T. Nelson?
I know.
And what I also love is that that movie's PG
and the parents are getting high up in their bedroom.
They're sitting in bed getting high.
I love that about Poltergeist.
I'll tell you what my dream is.
You know, Sam Rockwell was in the Poltergeist remake.
Oh, and in that one they drink a half a glass of whiskey
instead of getting high, by the way,
I wish it tells you everything you can know about the remake.
Yeah.
Here's my dream.
I want to make a coach remake starring Sam Rockwell now.
Okay.
Well it's coming back to TV.
I know.
Let's get to success.
Let's get Sam Rockwell in there.
Now who's playing Dobber?
Dwayne The Rock Johnson?
I put Dwayne The Rock Johnson in the Dobber role.
I put a tanning Chatham in the Dobber role.
Tanning Chatham?
I think you're done drinking.
We're 20 minutes in you just said tanning Chatham.
Oh Channing Chatham sorry.
great. That's great casting though. You know it's good cast. I'll see if Tanning's available.
There's Michael Jackson from the beat it video just hanging out in the my take on Channing
Tatum has always been that both of his names sound like things you'd call your taint. Yeah
I could see that. We did that as I wrote that as a joke for
the Pete home show. Okay. Did they deliver it. Yeah. Oh baby.
Lick my Channing or like my and then again then she goes what do you mean he goes you
know what I mean my tatum classic dirty stuff. So ladies out there if you ever consider having
sex with Joe just know he might say things like lick my Channing referring to his taint
and he also upon seeing your butt might go. Oh nice. So Nancy is now in the police station
with her parents played by home over Jones. John Saxon John Saxon from enter the dragon
in fame and early clinging to his hair and a woman who is the most melodramatic actor
of all time I've only ever seen her and I mean this is just yeah look at the just weepy eyes
he looks like Petunia Pig from the Looney Tunes or something you know Petunia Pig
Porkey's girlfriend who's girlfriend Porkey's like the Minnie Mouse you know Daisy Duck
you're blending all kinds of cartoon worlds right now saying they all had their girlfriend
and then Petunia Pig was the girl. Okay. They're all boring bland characters. Unfortunately.
Okay. This guy should take some of his eyebrows and put it on top of his head. I love John
Saxon. Do you ever see under the dragon? Of course. And he's in Rambo, right? No, you're
thinking of Richard Crenna. No, I'm not. I think John. I know who Richard Crenna is,
but I think I think he might be in Rambo. But maybe he's not. He's in Rambo. I thought
he was. Well, I love John Saxon. First blood. Same old. I can't remember the
line that he says to black belt Jones in in Enter the Dragon but it's great look at this
lady hitting the Vodka at seven a .m. There's something me and this lady have in common
anyway back to paper boy the obstacles in paper boy it's like trash can lid guy with
a boom box you know rabid dog then don't forget rabid rabid just a dog yeah and then within
in seconds you're face to face with the grim reaper. That's quite an escalation of
obstacles paper boy. I don't know. Is this a bit. I don't know if it is sounds like a
bit to me. Send this to Jerry Seinfeld. Have you played this paper boy game. You seen
this thing. Then shows up the grim reaper. I remember encounter this guy many times in
my paper. I said five minutes ago I'm dealing with a can of Sprite now I'm face to face
with grim death. I like I don't know if any video game has and you don't know who that
guy is standing against the tree. Is he real. Is he not real. Is it in her head. Is it not.
He's just a dude watching her man like in any dark. But now he's gone. I'll jump the
Italian and or Puerto Rican kid. He's got her in the bushes now because shirt and a leather
jacket. Here's what happens if you're not watching
with us. Tina my favorite girl is now dead because
Freddie killed her with his long arms and her boyfriend that just inside of her just
before that happened. Right. A boyfriend here played by a young
lies in Manelli. They think that he killed her so he's on the
he's on the lamb if you will yeah from the cops so now he's trying to tell Nancy he didn't
do it but of course the cops show up because her dad's a cop and they're gonna he's some
for some reason barefoot wearing old Navy jeans no shirt barefoot and a leather jacket
he's dressed exactly like Stanley Tucci wasn't that Levi's commercially did all those years
ago. I know that's a deep cut people but trust me it exists. Tucci in the south. There's
a Stanley Tucci Levi's commercial. It was just one of his first acting jobs. It's out
there. Guys got a body like a rock. Okay. I wouldn't doubt that. Now this is what I was
going to ask was wait a minute. Oh paper boy. It wasn't a question was what I was
going to say about people with. Yeah. I don't know that any video game. Look oh
And by the way, that's the lady from something about Mary and son of a Mary and now insidious
and now insidious.
Yeah, she got this role and the insidious role because her brother Bob Shay is the head of
New Line Cinema.
But I think she's a great actress in her own right.
I love her to pieces.
And in Kingpin.
She's fantastic.
I love her to pieces.
And I'd like to have sex with a young Lin Shay here.
I would absolutely like that.
I'm not going that far, but I think she's a handsome woman.
I'd like to.
I would enjoy that.
She's mousy.
I like it.
Sure.
Okay. Great. Now, by the way, third recurring theme,
Kingpin, two episodes in a row.
I, well, you figure a movie is at least 90 minutes.
I'll never go 90 minutes without talking about Kingpin.
Sweet, sweet Kingpin.
Look at his shirt that this kid's wearing.
Yeah, it looks like a stained glass window.
He's a, look, he's a guy that likes a party.
Right.
He's the guy that has a donkey at his party in the 80s.
Do you remember here, now this should be a segment on the podcast.
When was the first time you saw this movie?
Do you remember? Oh, yeah, man. I was I was 11 years old and I was obsessed with it
Okay, it was the greatest thing I'd ever seen. I mean, this was my godfather at 11 years. Oh, okay
Nancy's friend Tina just showed up in a body bag and I think if I'm not mistaken a worm is gonna come out of her mouth in a minute
I think so we're a snake of some kind
Now see because of my fear of VHS horror boxes and the fact that I was not allowed to see R -rated movies until I was actually
17 years old, which really don't care for my parents doing that to me, especially since
I was obsessed with movies my whole life.
Sure.
I don't think I saw Nightmare on Elm Street until I was about 17 years old, and I thought,
this is pretty scary, but I had it built up in my mind as though it was going to ruin
my life.
It is a scary movie, for sure.
Well, thinking I like about 80s horror movies, you get to notice what have different clothing
styles were back then.
It's crazy how much things change in so little amount of time.
Nancy's dressed like my Aunt Rita.
Well, some of these outfits are kind of big in hipster circles,
like where we live here in the Los Angeles.
Nobody's wearing a pink sleeveless sweater.
You can see it out there.
With a collared shirt and khakis, baggy khakis.
This lady shows up in the documentary.
The Where's Your Past Lady?
Yeah, she's not great.
No offense.
She's great right here when she turns into Freddie.
Yeah, I take it back. She's pretty good.
Yeah, she's awesome.
And there's leaves in the hallway when Nancy starts dreaming.
This is, this is, this is what makes this movie so great.
He adds these, West Craven was so good at adding these elements to the set.
The different sets that really made it feel like a nightmare.
Like in the beginning you see loose cattle running for no reason.
Yep.
Through a watery like boiler room hallway.
She's in her she's running through her high school now the hallways are all dark
there's leaves blowing around Freddie has the extended arms these are these are
very specific qualities of nightmares and I think that's really what gave this
movie yeah I mean I've seen it a bunch and it's always feels kind of fresh to
me too why do you think because this movie I think cost something like five
million and made 50 or something like that you know horror movies usually make
good money. We can look it up. Why aren't more horror movies. Good. Well it's. Do they
feel like they'll just make anything now and they're all kind of the same and why can't
like everyone's scared of stuff. Why can't you put your own personal take on a horror
movie and make it good. It's my philosophy that horror most of the
time gets the porn treatment and they say well as long as you have your money shot
it's who cares yeah and the money shot in a harm movie is a kill and I think that just
like with porn you know there are the Burt Reynolds guys from Boogie Nights being like
I want to make a film oh look Fred he had maggots coming out of his body there are those
Burt Reynolds type saying I want to make a film and I want to make something truly
erotic and then there are other guys saying it doesn't matter yeah have people fuck
on camera for as cheap as possible and that's all that that's all anybody cares
about. So the best example of like a porny type or movies like the final destination series
where it's just kill kill kill but those are really fun. Yeah. Put the time and they have
a clever kill you know at the very least. I like that series. All of those have really
good kills. Well this is why I can't believe that you're a fan of the Jeepers Creepers
franchise. Look maybe I'll rewatch it. I really enjoy
Jeepers Creepers. Please don't rewatch it till we can rewatch
it on here because I just I'm dumbfounded that you thought that movie was good.
I don't know sometimes I just happen to be out of the house, you know when I go to a movie. I'm like, yeah, I like that
What it came out when we were like?
17 or so now it came out when I was living in New York, so I was 23 years old really liked it
I don't know what to tell you. I had a nice time
Freddie also in these in these original films had a much more pervy sexual vibe to him. Yeah, does he not later?
now later he's putting on sunglasses and eating pizzas and shit and he kind of lost like what
made him a creep isn't Roseanne in like the fifth one she's in the sixth one okay they
play crazy people in the town all right yeah it's Freddy's dead is an abomination I mean
it's you know I still watch it yeah because it's just you know it's it's bad fun but
like and you also own and I guess must enjoy the Freddy TV show right I own every episode
okay it's a shit show that's Joe you do you like the show no why do you own a fucking
terrible friend of mine to me this okay I'm a completist yeah I enjoy the fact that I
own it yeah and I enjoy watching it with people to be like look at this right but it's you
know so I for camp fact value I enjoy it but no it's I can't stand by it in any way
Is it he's haunting a new person each week or are there is there a cast that we follow or what goes on well
You know how everybody who is a fan of nightmare in Elm Street thinks you know if they only would do this without Freddy
That's who that that's who the shows for he's in like two episodes
The other ones are just like about people living in nightmares
And that's it and he's England in the other ones. He's he hosts all of them
Okay, but it's literally he's like the creep keeper. Yeah, and then there's two episodes that the fruity character is actually in you think and even those aren't that great
Huh, what what kind of house you think England's living in like is he doing all right?
He's gotta be man. I mean it's it's the money. He must have made off of this thing people are often wrong, you know like he probably made
50 ,000 for this and then by the end at the very most he's getting a million
in you know and that that money is twenty five years old at this point.
Well look let's I mean here's the thing there's they couldn't do this series without him.
So there's no way that by the third movie he wasn't like go fuck yourselves if you want
to do this this is how the shitty contract where like here you're only going to get X
amount of dollars no matter how many times we do well let's let's look up Robert England.
Celebrity net worth is there any reliance on this.
How do they know it on celebrity network?
I know that's why I'm asking is this in any way reliable or is this just a chit show?
I think people would be a lot more upset if everyone knew exactly what they needed.
Fourteen million.
I'm getting fourteen million.
I'll buy that.
How much do you think you made for the adventures of Ford Fairland starring Andrew Dennis Clay?
I mean look even if you make scale on a movie like that the unions make sure that you get
your residuals and stuff.
that movie made money even though it was wasn't as big as it was supposed to be. Yeah. You
know that's true. So I mean you know I I I'd imagine it was pretty decent. I'd imagine.
Yeah. What I love when you go back and watch documentaries about old movies which I always
do if they're available on DVD. I love that shit. Yeah. The make like the making of right.
It was a good name. It'll be like it'll be like it'll be like Ford Farrell in the
adventures of creating a movie. Yeah. Exactly. Who framed Roger Rabbit? I'll tell you who
framed the movie Roger Rabbit, the people who shot and directed it. Like, wow, that's
the title you went with. Anyway, I love how, especially like in this, like I watched a
lot of this night right now, I should documentary. It's about eight hours long. It's so long,
but everybody in it. It seems hurt that their character what they think I don't know how they
went ahead and made Nightmare on Elm Street for without janitor number two is like janitor
number two's opinion right you know everybody in it is like I was shocked that I wasn't
asked back right as though people are wondering what happened to like the guy who died at
the end of Nightmare on Elm Street eight right and this is such a great shot Nancy's
in the bathtub legs I mean that's a poster right there that's a claw coming out they
they did this in the remake I was very happy that they paid tribute to the sea and the remake
and they didn't really change it. Okay maybe I do want to have sex with Nancy as she lays
their spraw spread eagle in a bathtub. Oh nice. Tasty. Oh I'm kidding come on. Bath pillow.
Who has that bath pillow in the tub with them. Well although let me ask you this. Shell
binder. Look at the towel. Look at the bath. Look at the sheet.
they're all that same color of blue is that telling me anything. I mean I don't know does
blue signify evil or something signifies maybe it signifies Friday's coming because so far
every time we've seen blue Freddie shows up. Well let's look that up. I like this scene
a lot. Yes it's great. Great scene. Look at the little nudity right there. Once again
getting pulled under water in a bathtub and it's an endless bottomless sea. I mean it's
good it's good nightmare stuff I agree they know how to do this what I and I know a good
nightmare because I wake up nearly every night nearly screaming because I have night terrors
you do about me I do every night like I'm in a horror movie and go I'm not looking
forward to that when we're like the odd couple and live together you mean like in three months
when my house is foreclosed. Well join the club on that one. I was I have it happen a
whole lot and it's not a it's no way to live. I don't know what it says about me but I have
a real problem with it with the night terrors. Yep. You're about the third or fourth friend
of it. Look there's another town and the bathrobe is blue and the hand teller blue. All right
this is what I think on that color coding movies. This is what I found ready. Let's
see if we can make any link here.
Blue symbolizes trust, loyalty, wisdom,
confidence, intelligence, faith.
You just looked up what does blue represent in general,
not in this movie?
Yeah, but I'm saying let's.
Oh, all right.
I'm sure Wes Craven didn't go, I'm
going to, the door is blue to the house,
the front door is the same color blue.
I think I really made a big discovery here.
Blue symbolizes trust, loyalty, wisdom, confidence,
intelligence, faith, truth, and heaven.
in. Yeah. Heaven. Yeah baby. Blue is considered beneficial to the mind and body. It slows
human metabolism and produces a calming effect. Dreams. Sleep. Dreams. Yeah. Blue is strongly
associated with tranquility and calmness that is it has a meaning. The people it's it's
featured every time the people are having nightmares being killed by Freddy because
It's calming it soothing it makes them go to sleep
that's
That's very interesting. I think that's what it is. Yeah, very excited about that now here Skeetal words comes in this exact same way on screen
Does he really yeah through the window Johnny Depp's coming through the window of Heather Lang and Cap's bedroom
Yeah, he's climbed the thorny rose bush vine outside of the house
Now when I was a kid the only way I could watch already movies was if they were on channel 11
He's got blue sweatpants on now. I've made a really great discovery here
This is nuts
It's all over the fucking
Who on John or Heather let's pretend I'm talking about Heather
Heather also has like a giant mosquito bite in her forehead or a zit or something she does
But I like that they left it there. That's like in the witches of Eastwick
there's a scene where Michelle Pfeiffer is a huge cold sore on her lip really and it's
real and the director was like no leave it because you're you're sickly in this scene
and that makes you more human and she went with it you know who that director was George
Miller director of Mad Max he did witches of Eastwick you sure did I mean which babe
and babe pig in the city yeah only the second one yeah I had a tweet once I'm looking for
a babe in the streets and a babe pig in the city in the sheets. Yeah. Yeah. I mean I still
think that's funny. I mean I mean I I would have went like this. I'm looking for a babe
and by that I mean a pig in the city. Sure. I would have went like that. All right. Probably
less fun. She looks I think it's tighter and that's how you get to it. You're connecting
had somewhere in the one seventy eight faves right now I guess America thought differently
all right sorry George Miller now which is which is of each Eastwick yeah which what bothers
me is it was witches of East End the TV show in any way link to it no not linked at all
they just ripped it off like that yeah embarrassing I I was just about to say and now she's gone
But Langenkamp looks exactly not it looks exactly like it gives me a very similar vibe to Jennifer
Jason Lee in like fast time which came out the same year.
I mean Jennifer Jason Lee there's another one just just smoking 80s hot.
You know Joe these these women have lives and personalities.
It's not just you know pieces of meat.
All right fair enough but I do love her.
You'll be apologizing for that next week like I apologize for my I mean I just very
apologizing heavy time in American culture. I don't think Jennifer Jason Lee would be
upset if she heard me say smoking hot. Probably not. Yeah. Yeah. I love JJ. She's been great
in so many things. There's a great movie called Georgia where she plays an alcoholic
and she does like a 10 minute like terror. She thinks she's a great singer and her sister
actually is a really good singer. So then like she does this 10 minute Van Morrison song
It sounds so terrible and she's so wasted and it's one of the hardest things I've ever had to watch check that out Georgia
I'm sure it's not on DVD. It's the VHS. Maybe only I don't know how you're gonna watch
How do people watch movies that aren't on DVD?
Netflix streaming like we are right now. Well, this is on DVD and blue right? Sure. I have a huge VHS collection
But nobody has a VCR anymore. I had a tremendous VHS collection. I had a basement wall covered
The prized possession or the centerpiece of it was the film Fatso starring Dom Delouise.
Sure.
I remember it with Anne Bancroft.
Can't get the fucking thing on DVD.
It's $150 on DVD.
Met Peter, I'm sorry, met, not Peter Delouise, the other Delouise kid.
Michael Delouise.
Yeah.
In a diner recently.
Okay.
Told him how much I love Fatso.
He said, I have an original poster, I'll give it to you.
That's awesome. Never heard from him again. I got to find him. I got to go. We got to
go find Michael Delouise right now. I don't know him. Is he on Twitter? I don't know.
My friend knew him. I got to find him. I had always heard tell that Dom Delouise is a
closet game man. I don't know if that's true. I had heard that too. I don't think
so though. I think he just was a mildly effeminate guy. Yeah. Michael Delouise. Great guy. One
of the nicest, like the gentlest eyes I've ever seen in a man.
Okay.
Seriously.
And was thrilled.
I was apologetically saying to him, I love the movie Fatso, and I'm sure you get this
all the time.
Yeah.
He was so clearly touched.
Well, it's all, now here, this is what I always say when, because we live in here in
Los Angeles.
We see a lot of celebrities of all, of all ranges, A list down to your Z list.
And the good rule of thumb is like if you go up to Tom Cruise, you're like Tommy, I love
Top Gun, but he might humor you, but he doesn't care and he doesn't want to talk to you.
If you go up to like, I saw Richard Reel in a diner the other day.
Who the hell was that?
Richard Reel was in office space, he was the guy who goes, it's a jump to conclusions
man.
I love that guy.
And he was on Cheers and he was also, you're gonna love this connection.
Remember last night I brought up Mysterious Skin about the pedophile?
Yeah.
Yeah. He played a John like a John who picked up a street kid to like have sex with him.
So in the movie he has sex with Joseph Gordon Levitt.
He's like a disgusting hotel pervert. And how old is Levitt in the movie?
18. Is he playing a kid though? Yeah you know he's playing like a teenager.
He's supposed to be like 15. He got molested and now he's like a hustler.
Okay, I got you but so Richard reels sitting there and I was I was saying to the person I was with I was like
Richard reels the kind of guy who you go up to him in a diner and you're like hey man
You're just the best character actor and I always love seeing you and stuff
Sure
So funny in office space and blah blah blah and he would talk to you for an hour and be so flattered and go home and tell
His wife sure some some kid come up to him in a diner and
I didn't do it
But like those are the people who love writing to do it because he left while I was talking about how these people love
being approached he left. This is another great nightmare detail when Nancy's trying to run
up the steps and she's stepping in Marshmallow. The steps are turning into Marshmallow. Great
point. This just is a dream. It's not real. This is just a dream. It's not real. That's
what she keeps saying. And then boom through the mirror Freddie. What a great shot. Good
scare. What a great shot man. Let me I want to tweet out right now that we're watching
this do it and that people should be sending us questions so if you could talk for a moment
well now do I need to say one two three tweet now I'm just gonna I know you're like a countdown
show a lot of smart mouth coming from you tonight why don't you just say by the way
you're you have off tomorrow I do have off tomorrow yes I'm off on script I mean do
we take this party on the town after this podcast yeah let's go get drunk we're sitting
here sipping whiskies. That sounds fantastic. I got a late morning tomorrow. Tomorrow's my
non -workout day. Yeah. You're exactly like me, Joe, and that
if a drop of alcohol touches your lips, you want to go drink until two in the morning.
It's a problem. It's a sad pathetic quality. You're never going to be like, yeah, I'll
have a beer. You have the beer and then you have 17 beers. But I should say this
isn't a drunk podcast and we're not drunk. We're not drunk. But I mean, we've had
I had two wines before this and then I'm sipping this delicious whiskey and I didn't know about
the wine and I'm watching my one of my favorite movies with my one of my best pals I mean thanks
John that's sweet of you I don't keep talking because I got to tweet this okay yeah going
back to VHS I had this huge collection and it's like everybody who bought beanie babies
and thought they're going to be rich or like I have all these baseball cards I thought
I was going to retire at age 21 from my baseball card collection they're all worth nothing
at this point so my VHS I get on Amazon like yeah I can get some money for these
they're they're classics you can't get one penny for a VHS unless it's not
available on DVD or it's gone out of print so I sold a VHS copy of rad the
BMX biking movie I remember you telling me this for nearly $500 and it was in
not I put on there not good condition the box was completely beaten up I'd
I stole it from blockbuster video that I worked at and I got five hundred dollars off of it.
Five hundred.
Would you pay for it?
I stole it.
I worked at blockbuster.
I sold it to myself for like two dollars.
Not I didn't steal it.
Oh my God almighty.
Are we passed the statute of limitations on a hardcore?
Well they fired me for other things.
So I don't really care.
That's a terrible company and they're out of business.
So they can't do anything.
Listen I think maybe you should go down to Barbados until things blow over.
Blockbuster fired me because I was making too much money.
My friend said it eight twenty five an hour at my friend Mike bellow said that to me once back in high school
I was I had a job and and
Or I'm sorry wasn't my job. It was a place where my buddy worked and he gave me free food or something
Yeah, I was panicking
I was panicking that we're gonna get in trouble and the moral people and I was I was just I was going on and on to
Mike about like am I okay?
Do you think I'm gonna go to jail and he said I think you need to go to Barbados until things blow over
over. I mean it was it was such a sharp comment for a seventeen year old kid. The other movie
I had which made me some money was somebody gave me as a Christmas white elephant you
know gag gift thing a VHS copy of a movie called Gator bait and essentially it was like kind
of a deliverance knock off but it had like a playboy playmate on the cover sure and
it was exploitation movie where she gets sexually assaulted in the bayou and then
she goes to kill everybody who wronged her. So I was like how funny gag gift I never opened
it cut to 10 years later. Gator bait is only available on VHS and I have a new sealed copy
of it and I sold it on Amazon for like 250. Jesus Christ. That's what you got to do. You
got to you got to watch the market. Speaking of Gator bait I almost bought
a spit on your grave recently. I was out in the Ridge up in Toronto. I almost bought
the remake. I never I'd never seen the remake. I've seen the original and that remake
was so miserable and I didn't buy it I was like I don't need to see this it's just too
depressing yeah it was too much depressing just I don't it's I it has tapered off considerably
but there was about a three year window in about maybe the mid 2000s where rape was an
element of every horror movie and it bothered me so much there's a lot of these like like
Weird like last house on the left that kind of stuff. Yeah, and which was also a West Craven remake
Now, but there was that one in the woods with like Stallone's son
That that one was like I don't know it's just like where every scare is like watching a woman get raped for 25 minutes
Let me look it up
Well Pat looks that up. We are now at the funeral scene of Rick the guy that killed Tina
Yeah, you know this is a horrible podcast probably 45 dudes just went
I'm usually that guy by the way, but I don't remember those if you're watching along with us
You would have just seen that Rick had the saddest funeral on planet Earth apparently had no parents or family
It's just Nancy and her folks and a couple loose friends and old ladies sure
John Saxon now coming in
Nobody believes you Nancy
see. Nobody believes you that a supernatural burn man is killing your friends. Nobody wants
to hear it. This is one of the things I hate about horror movies is they always have to
have this part where the person is like don't you get it. The clowns are doing it and everybody
is like yeah you why don't you get some sleep sweetheart you know.
Well look if I came over here tonight and you were like Pat don't you see the birds
are gonna kill us all I'd be like Joe the hell's wrong with you you never believe
that person but why does nobody ever say you've been perfectly sane until this
point this is the first I'm gonna go ahead and give you the benefit crazy
thing you've ever said let's spend five minutes exploring this as a real
possibility yeah nobody ever goes nobody ever goes you know Nancy if it
weren't for you painting your name on the wall with your own shit we believe
you. Yeah. Nobody ever says that. It was like, well, you're sound of sound mind. But fuck
it. I don't know what you're nuts now. Yeah. Well, you're my daughter and I love you more
than anyone in the world. But Charles Fleischer, by the way, voice of Roger. Exactly. And
we said who framed Roger Rabbit. By the way, I thought of the perfect name for it for
a documentary about who framed Roger Rabbit. Who framed who framed Roger Rabbit. Beautiful.
That'd be about the shooting of the movie. Yeah exactly. Charles Fleischer was also
amazingly good and creepy in Zodiac which is one of my favorite movies of all time. He's
wonderful in Zodiac. Charles Fleischer is so good in Zodiac and everybody and there's
800 speaking roles in Zodiac and everybody in it is perfect. A bit of a horror movie
veteran Charles Fleischer also one of the one of the cast members of Demon Knight
Which is one of my favorite harm movies of all time never saw it
I only saw Bordello of blood which I
Was watching Bordello of blood outside of the Dennis Miller scenes where he's just being like funny
Yeah, is not good being allegedly fun. He is funny in that. Okay. He is funny that when she wrote his own dialogue
He's funny and Joe dirt. Yeah, when he when she's looking my favorite line in Bordello of blood is when she's looking for
He's a PI. Yeah, she's looking for her brother who's missing played by Corey Feldman
Yeah, and she goes my brother's been missing. I need your help and she shows him the picture of Corey Fulton and he starts laughing
Uh -huh the picture and he goes oh, I got to put this in a locket
All right, yeah, I should check that out
Now again now back to Zodiac the scene where the Zodiac killer kills those two teenagers at the lake
Yeah, and Zodiac's not really a horror movie
But that is by far one of the scariest scenes in movie history.
Dude, that part's scary.
That part's scary when he goes to the guy's house
and he thinks like he might have found the Zodiac
and he's not sure.
Yeah, Zodiac.
I mean, it's probably three hours long.
I could I there was a summer not long ago
where I watched that movie every night for like two weeks.
I was obsessed with it.
Yeah, it was great for like Robert.
That was the first movie where I was like, oh my god,
Robert Downey Jr. is an amazing actor.
Yeah.
And that was just come back.
That was just come back.
Yeah, yeah.
But that was Downey juniors comeback. That was the first movie
I think that he did after he got off the drugs and everything
Yeah, and it was like holy shit. This guy's like no joke me. Oh, he killed it
He was fun. You're like really was really really funny, which you know, he kind of brought that to the part
It wasn't really on the page
This movie that I'm talking about was 2005 called chaos
Right in the heart of like rape horror movies
2005 for sadistic thieves including sage Stallone
Sebastian Stallone son who died recently. Did he die? Did he commit suicide or did he just
die? I think he had an overdose. That's a shame. They brutalized two teenagers looking for drugs
in the woods. So there you go. And it's now his sage. One of the bad guys are good guys.
He's one of the torturers. But you know what? I remember the most and I shut the movie
off at this point, but they cut off the girl's nipple. Oh, come on. Like what are
we doing? I like a horror movie to be a little fun. And I realize a lot of people
like to pray of shit. I don't know what nipples are fun but not when they get cut off. No I
like a nipple attached I always have. Let's get back to call me old fashioned good old
fashioned nipples show. I don't like the nipple being cut off. If you're watching along with
us we're in the hospital scene now where they're trying to monitor Nancy's dreams.
And they just had one of those machines where which I never buy like those machines with
all the pins where the ink lines are going. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean who who was able
to read that. The doctors look at it they go. No. No movement. They might not even use
them in actual. It might only be like a movie only construct.
I don't believe it's a real machine. It's absurd. It's like the lie detector. I don't
believe it exists. I do not believe it exists. I pointed out the blue door. But the final
scare of this I'm not mistaken is Freddie coming out that blue door right. He grabs
or like at the end of care. Yes. Yes. And you can't and Wes Craven did
not like that ending originally. Well Wes it's great and it's OK. It's kind of defeats
what it is which is she defeats Freddie. I'm not scared of you anymore. He disappears.
Yeah. And then he just magically comes back and what
is supposed to be real life. OK. So it's a good harm movie ending. But I remember
Remember Wes Craven saying like you know it was merely just a set up for a sequel and
he didn't think that that was the point of making the movie.
Nice buns Nancy.
Remember when Wes Craven directed like one non horror movie called Music of the Heart
with Meryl Streep and I never did a non horror movie.
I refused to watch it.
I saw it that was during a time where I saw every movie and then gave it a letter grade
in a spiral notebook.
Oh God.
good. That was my life people. Now here's I think I get music of the heart of C plus.
What was it about? Meryl Streep's maybe teaching poor kids or deaf kids or poor deaf kids or
something about the kids never live under stairs or turn evil or anything like that. No, no,
no, no, no. Okay, I don't have no interest. Now I'll tell you a West Cray movie I remember
watching and maybe junior high that is so bad it's called shocker well it's Pat I swear to
God I was just about to bring up shocker bring it up Joe I also think shocker sucks here's
the thing Wes Craven said he thought it was a commentary on the media right well I believe
that is true but he also said that he never got his what he thought was fair royalties
for the franchise of Nightmare on Elm Street.
So he said, I decided I was going to create another franchise and not make the same mistakes
I did contractually like I did with Nightmare on Elm Street and he made shocker.
He thought that was going to be it.
And it was terrible.
Yeah.
I felt bad for him.
I have such respect for the man, but I felt bad for him that that didn't work out.
But then he came back with Scream and I was like, okay, now he got it with Scream.
He nailed it with Scream.
And Scream's great.
But Wes Craven now you do have to ask yourself how do you write and direct this thing and
then he made so many bad movies how does it all happen you know like how he made he made
bad ones and good ones it seems to be the how do people make movies that are so bad
and then so good and music is the same way it's just sure scary you know it really is
scary because you and I are both in the creative field the biggest fear I have in my entire
life beyond death and anything else is losing my ability to be funny or good at what I do.
Well as you know, look, you know, I used to be real hard on guys, you know, I'd be like,
I'd be like, you know, why did John Carpenter make this many good ones and then these other
ones that kind of sucked or whatever.
That was the perfect movie and then so many bad movies.
But you know what it is, I finally realized like, well, everybody doesn't have the advantage
I do of being a stand up where it's like, no, this is what it is.
Put it out or don't.
and nine times out of ten they will and it's fine but you know as a writer I've
staff written you know things get picked apart things get changed around people
get last -minute doubts and everybody has a hand on it and then by the end of it
sometimes the final product isn't what you want it to be especially with a
horror movie that's you're dealing with the story even in carpenter kind of had
I think they pretty much had free reign in the 80s and early 90s but if you
look if you look there's a clear line that gets drawn with this Craven's a great example
in the jump from a young new line cinema which was not a big boy studio it was a very indie
studio was very grass they call it the studio that Freddie built the house the Freddie built
right I mean and who doesn't you know I mean I hear it every day in the coffee shop but
But there's a clear line in quality that gets drawn when it jumps to the major studio stuff.
Now I think they let him dance a little more to his own rhythm with the Scream movies.
Well Scream is written by Kevin Williamson, so that's a different thing too.
It was.
And I also think for some reason they give more slack with slasher movies.
They set this with the - Slasher movies are a little, anything without a supernatural
natural element is a little more legit, I think, because it could really happen.
And they let horrific things go a little more with the, like, it's the opening of Scream.
It's disturbing.
Oh, for sure.
They cut, he cuts Drew Barrymore's throat.
He's gargling on her own blood.
It's very disturbing.
I was terrified by Scream when I saw it.
And now it's more of comedy.
It works as more of a comedy, but it's a really good movie.
They all are.
But you know when they did the nightmare in Elm Street remake
They said one thing we want to do is we want to make them look truly like a burn victim
Right, and then they said well
We had to reel it back because we didn't want people to like turn away from the screen every time they saw them because it was
Disturbing I'm like no make it disturbing. Yeah, I want a monster that sticks in my head and gives me nightmares
That's why the exorcist freaks me out so much. She's so scary looking you rarely get that and
Who played Friday in the new one?
Jackie Earl Haley. Oh yeah. That was a good call. He's great at playing a creep. He's
great at everything. He plays mostly pedophiles now. Again. Little children. It's my girlfriend
when that movie at the time. My girlfriend at the time when that movie came out gave
it to me on DVD and I remember talking to a comedian named Julian McCullough about
it and I said I love Julian McCullough. Yeah. I said my girlfriend just gave me a copy
of little children and he said you should examine your relationship yeah it's a good
movie and a good book the movie is I mean there's literally the most disturbing scene
I've ever seen in a movie is when he's jerking off in front of the school on his date and
the woman starts crying yeah it's terrible it's once again pedophilia rears its head
on me we'll see you in hell podcast yeah we need to stop look at this lady she's got
a very busy she looks like Virginia Madsen is melting the lady from sideways she's just
being so mean to this one what's wrong with her she's so dramatic I love I find her sexy
in a strange way. Yeah I mean it all liquored up by the way it's in the back of Nancy's
sweatshirt. That's my type all liquored up. Nancy's pajamas all day bathroof all liquored
up a nice vodka drunk sure why why is it why is an alcoholic mother always a vodka drunk
well because that's that's that is true to life and now there's so many delicious flavors
of vodka it's a great time to be an alcoholic mother or aunt you got toasted marshmallow vodka
and I'd go my own way I'd be doing Yeager bombs the whole time I get that that's it
just straight Yeager bombs you know what's interesting we talked about her you know her
having a zit and now she has kind of a red nose and etc like the 80s we're talking about
Anthony Michael Hall earlier because of vacation like all the teenagers had zits they were real
this is in the the studio movies the indie movies they the teenagers were real yeah
now you can't find a teenager on screen who doesn't look like she's been airbrush and
it's not real everyone's ugly and awkward and weird when they're teenagers now you're
absolutely right if I may point out the scene we're in now Johnny Depp Johnny Depp is wearing
a he's wearing a belly shirt yeah and which I like but he's also in his bedroom poster
on the wall rush grace under pressure never realized that was the poster never saw that
either love rush one of my favorite bands and the poster predominantly blues and purples
it's the only rush out actually counterparts also has a blue album cover but it wasn't
out yet up to this point that was the bluest of the rush. Yeah I love a phone. Blue phone
Johnny Depp on a tan phone. She probably blew Johnny Depp earlier. Oh you guys I'm just
trying to have fun. And he said don't rush it. Have some grace under pressure. Look at
this folks this is why we write the TV show or I just watched. I never like I just watched
a rush documentary that I loved also on Netflix. Oh it's it's beyond the lighted stage. It's
tremendous. It's great. It's fucking tremendous. I might go see them next week.
Yeah. This week. Where are they playing the forum or the staples.
I think the forum. I can't go. It's my buddy's party. I can't go. I never saw them. They
were never my bag. But whatever. I saw them once. I respect them. I saw them once and
I was so drunk that I weep during Spirit of Radio. You know that's rough where I'm
that in my life at this point. That was three years ago but whatever. Here's the famous
line. Don't fall asleep. She just told you Johnny. Don't fall asleep. She's not fucking
around here. Even you don't believe her. Look nobody believes her that this guy's coming
into their nightmares. Nobody believes her. Here's why there aren't more great horror
movies or great comedies or great whatever. Blue Blanket on Johnny Depp's bed. Sorry
to cut you off but the reason is I think that kind of one line premise if you fall asleep
you're dead is obviously such a perfect you walk into any studio and you go hey I got a
movie where if you fall asleep you die behind you a oversized novelty check right and the
those premises just don't come along that often because if they did somebody would have thought
of it sure and comedy is the same way like the 40 year old Virgin I would imagine somebody
walked in Judd Apatow I guess walked into a studio and said the 40 year old version and
they said here's money right because it's perfect like and those things are they seem so easy
to come up with but they're not right a simple one line premise and that's why whenever
I ask them but somebody's like hey can you read a script of mine I'm like yeah what's
it about and they go okay so there's this guy right and he's like a air traffic control
But he never really and I'm like okay. This movie is not going to happen right you need to for better or worse be able to say
Here's the movie in one sentence right I agree especially for comedy especially for horror
If you want if you want any sort of success if you want somebody to give you some money
You want to do it weird indie? You know you can't explain David Lynch's movies in one
Sure, but you know those aren't the big hits. I well, I would agree with you
I love David Lynch by the way. I love David Lynch. I would agree. My favorite types of
horror movies are horror movies that establish very simply. There's no escape. You have to
face the fear. Yeah. So that's why when people go to these movies they poke holes in them
like I used to only go to the Magic Johnson Theater to see. I think we're going to say
to Magic Johnson movies. I didn't know he made films. I would only go to the Magic
Johnson Theater in Compton here in LA because for horror movies because I loved people shouting
out of the screen and I would have so much fun and laugh and yell out myself at times
and stuff but if people are watching your movie and they can be like don't do that you
idiot what do you do like right that means nobody's buying your shit right what you're
saying is they can't have an out and then that's truly scary they don't have an out
it's truly scary all the best horror movies there's no out nightmare known street you
fall asleep you die yeah Texas chainsaw massacre all the hillbilly inbreds are
running the town you can't get away from them yeah the exorcist your daughter is
possessed by the devil you have to stay here with her yeah look at that mask on
the wall but look at this bod on Nancy taking it off we're only getting it from
the back but it is delish you know when I was a kid because it's all I saw
something about a rear side bottom boob is almost sexier than the whole thing
I love it still to this day but that little small of a back right there you could really
grasp that waste. All right take it easy. I'm getting worked up here. But I was watching
mirrors today and I thought once again brilliant premise for a horror movie. What's everywhere
and you can't get away from them. But isn't that kind of what Poltergeist three was mirrors
water puddles. Yeah but mirrors did it way better I guess.
All right. Do you like me? I don't remember. I enjoyed it very much.
I remember Poltergeist 3 was terrible. Poltergeist 3 is to me unwatchably bad as much as I love
Tom Skerritt. Sure. I saw Poltergeist 2 the day I got braces and then the same with the
kids braces attacking. I mean when I was a kid I loved Poltergeist 2. Now that I'm
older I don't like it as much. No, but it's not a bad movie. That preacher guy is still
a lot of fun. From Phantasm. Am I the same guy? No, not the same guy. Are we sure?
Positive. Angus Scrim? Okay. Not Angus Scrim. All right. Phantasm 5. Eagerly
waiting that it's made it's done so doesn't come out yet theatrical release or you think
it'll go straight now I don't go straight to vid but but I mean you know the guy that
did phantasm did John dies at the end he did Baba Ho Tep right he does a lot of great
stuff Don Cosquerel yes never saw John does the end I like Baba Ho Tep alone but he's
got phantasm five as I believe it's way to get it together for Christ's sake I mean
she's stashing bottles all over the house this lady I don't think and I I've been
a big advocate of drinking for about ten years. I don't think I've ever drank out of a bottle
of liquor. I did once recently my friends and I went
out for a big party night and we were starting at a girl's apartment and I finally did this
I always wanted to do this but one of those little glass pint bottles of whiskey I've
done that just drank the whole thing at her house it was a lot of fun smoking cigarettes
I felt like a real like I was on the case but you never picked up like the ten -pound bottle of Jack to your lips
Yeah, no, I don't stash like Nancy's mom does a
three -liter
Right vodka in the linen closet along with the one in the kitchen that I hide behind my back. Yeah. Yeah
There's Johnny Depp's dad. He's not a good actor. That guy looks like he gave birth to Johnny Depp, right? Yeah. Yeah, I mean viable. I
I had a friend tonight. I had that phone. I had to talk about horror. I had to answer
every phone call until I was 17 until I left the house. I had to answer every phone call.
Hello, Walsh residents. Patrick speaking. Who made you do that? My dad. What was he
a Nazi? Well, no comment. Hello, Walsh residents. Patrick speaking. My friends would be like,
Pat, it's Ryan. What's wrong with you? Who the hell? Yeah. What is that bullshit?
And then even like my dad's friends would be like why do you have to say that can I just
talk to your dad I'm like I'm sorry.
Now if you noticed it we've passed it but they just showed exterior shots of the houses
a moment ago.
Both houses draped in blue light she's wearing a blue members only jacket with a blue phone
and a blue bed.
Patty you really cracked into something here with the blue row baby you really cracked
into something here I'm proud of you man thank you blue towels in the closet blue
towels in the linen closet blue phone is now ringing blue tissues on the on the shelf
blew my mind is what it did blue phone is now released in the back that's the police
right that's the police and her dad's a cop what do you think of that blue painting on
the wall and they really did their work here I this is the part where the tongue comes
out of the phone. Hold on. Here we. I'm your boyfriend now, man. That was always gross.
What do you think Freddie's breath smells like when he licks her face like that? That's
not good, man. No? I went to film school and I took a class where this professor would
talk. He'd make every movie into a game movie. It all had a gay subtext and it was fascinating
How he did it like some like he would talk about Rebecca the old Hitchcock movie where clearly the maid is like has a lesbian interest in her
And you watch and you're like oh shoot you're right. I never saw Rebecca. Is it good?
It's it's a great movie, especially with that bit of information
But then like he'd watch diehard and he'd be like well clearly John McClain is gay and the room would kind of laugh
And then by the end of the class and it wasn't the class wasn't like finding gay subtext in movies
He just did it so like you'd be like maybe John McClain is gay. He was a fascinating man
By the way Johnny Dapp asleep on the bed now blue sweatpants blue number ten on the belly shirt
And now he's dead and there's another blue blanket on the bed
He just got pulled in the bed by Freddy and now a blood fountain shoots out which I enjoy quite a bit
Yeah, it's a good shot
You only get one take of a blood fountain shooting out of the bed. Yeah, this is it
What do you think I guess they must have poured it in or how do they do them?
It looks like it's shot it's going in reverse maybe.
That's an upside down room.
Okay.
Yes.
I can't believe I have to explain that to you.
Look what I do.
I love the magic of cinema Joe.
I like to let it wash over me and confuse me and dazzle me.
Yeah that's clearly an upside down room.
Now I bought the special edition.
Oh braggart of the Nightmare on Elm Street VHS tape my friend Jim and I split split
it we found it one night at a you know Sam Goody or something one of those old record
stores warehouse music. Yeah something like that was a listen on headphones like what we're
doing now. Yeah it was pre DVD and we found the double VHS and we bought it because the
second tape had a bunch of bonus features on it which at that time was pretty unheard
of on anything. Yeah. But the bonus tape had deleted scenes.
games. Okay. And one of the fast forward through to find the next like the ones that you cared
about. Yeah. And but one was Johnny Depp's bloody corpse coming up out of the hole in
the bed and then plopping down before anybody discovered what was happening. So it looked
like he had just been murdered and it was a great shot. I don't really be on the I
have the Blu -ray box. I'm sure it's on there somewhere. I'm sure it is too. I don't
know why though they would have a lot of members only Jack cut it out of the film the dad now
is very upset he's throwing up because his son his son's blood is dripping through the
ceiling that'll that's upsetting I would guess so I'd guess so now do you like the party
the 13th series or do you find it a lesser yeah I like it I don't I don't like it as
much as nightmare on street. But I've only seen for their great. I mean I think the ratio
of good ones to bad ones is equal. I mean for the 13th might actually have a better batting
average. OK, nightmare on street simply because there's more. So they had more chances to
make better ones. But they don't have a classic like the first Friday 13th is not a classic.
It's just kind of OK slasher. I don't like the first one. I think what the remake did
was best which was establishing the events of the first one in the opening credits basically
two is to me we're Friday the 13th really kicks in Tuesday's great three's great four's great
oh okay I gotta watch all those five sucks six and seven are great after that they all
kind of suck takes Manhattan that's a waste of time in my in my opinion Jason takes
Manhattan is eight okay then there's Jason X and space yeah Jason goes to hell is number
nine Jason X is in space is just goes to hell set in hell. No it's just the idea that he
goes to hell at the end of it. OK. And they thought some fucking horseshit thing about
like you know he's it's an ancient demon you know anytime they do that it's like get the
fuck out of here they try to do that with Michael Myers in the curse of Michael Myers
years. Yeah. It's stupid. But front of the 13 part six is my favorite of all of them.
And really I mean it's what's the premise. It's called Jason lives. And the opening
of the movie is fantastic. It's the guy that plays horse shack and welcome back Cotter Ron
Polillo I believe. Yeah and and then the grown up like a different actor but it's the
grown up version of Corey Feldman's character. Okay. From part four. He he wants to make
sure that Jason is actually dead so they go to a cemetery to dig up his corpse. They dig
up his corpse. It's there. Kid pulls out an iron pole from the fence. Starts stabbing
Jason repeatedly out of rage. Right. Lightning strikes the pole reanimates Jason. Okay.
I Jason punches horseshack through the chest hand comes out the other side holding his heart.
It's a great fucking flick man.
All right.
And he talked about Darabont on the last one Darabont directed or he wrote the third nightmare
and I'm sure correct dream warriors.
Did he.
Yeah.
I think you wrote it.
I thought Craven wrote that one.
Let's look it up.
Darabont wrote for them.
By the way Friday the 13th reboot I didn't even realize I knew they were working on
one.
It comes out in like November.
a Friday the 13th reboot. Yeah. Now didn't they already do a Friday the 13th reboot.
They did and I thought it was solid and it didn't for some reason get any traction but
it was one of the scariest kills ever. He he takes a girl and puts her in a sleeping bag
yeah but she's can't and it ties the sleeping on the tree over the fire and it's so scary
man. Hold on. Nightmare on Elm Street 3. Let's see here.
This woman's unattractable and why was I so mean?
I don't know. I mean the strange part is that she's six years younger than we are right
here. People just looked older back then. That's
her. That's true. Let's see. Nightmare on Elm Street
part 3. 74 % of rotten tomatoes deservedly so. Patricia.
She's not back in the bed during this makeup scene.
in. Patricia Arquette's screen debut if you will screenplay West Craven Bruce Wagner Frank
Darabout and Chuck Russell. I want to see what else Darabout wrote in his early career.
He was a he's primarily a screenwriter never known street three love it the blob love
it fly to love it fly to is good. I love what I want. I mean the original. Well it's not
the original so still remake but the fly with Jeff Goldblum to me is could be my second favorite
hard movie ever. Yeah. It's one of the most disturbing things
I've ever seen in my life. Yeah. But I love the fly too. It got a bad rap.
I think it's great. And I'll say it. I don't I never saw a lot of those bad sequels like
I never saw Predator two but I love Predator one.
I never saw Predator two either. You see and Danny Glover and you're right.
Chuck Russell did write the mask he wrote he wrote co -wrote the blog and he wrote a racer
oh that was a rough one he also wrote everyone he shoots that alligator and he goes yo luggage
yes I do that was in the trailer but he also wrote collateral one of my favorite Michael
man movies oh collateral's a fantastic move yeah you adapt it for you Chuck Russell way
to come back baby. Oh was a producer and back to school. Love back to school. Who doesn't.
That's always very inspiring to me when somebody's like got a couple hits in the 80s and then
you're like I guess they tapered off and you see they wrote some big hit in the 90s. I
love it movie or the 2000 co -wrote dreamscape. Love that. I don't know. Dennis Quaid. Yes.
I do know. Did I tell you I saw Dennis Quaid at a party the other night. Who's. When
Yeah.
Quaid was there.
I'm walking out of the house.
It was funnier than Dennis Quaid.
Well, he was doing a reading that Jason Reitman was doing of the Big Lebowski.
What was he playing?
The nihilist?
He was playing Jackie Treyhorn.
I think he was playing the Big Lebowski.
No.
Michael Fassbender was playing.
Fassbender was playing the dude.
The dude, right.
Oh, you're talking about.
I think Quaid played the Big Lebowski.
What?
Oh, well, that seems wrong.
I can't remember.
That was a fat old creed.
It doesn't matter.
But the point is, I got off the elevator in the hotel everybody was staying in.
and there was like 10 people on the elevator
and we're walking to these glass doors to go outside
and you threw the glass doors, there's a set of stairs
and there's this guy on the set of stairs
and I just turned to everybody on the elevator
that was on the elevator and I go,
is that Dennis Quaid?
Yeah.
And we all started laughing because it was Dennis Quaid.
It was like the most random like,
what the fuck is he doing here?
We didn't know that he had done the reading.
Looks amazing.
thing. Of course have two brothers ever looked less similar than Dennis and Randy Quaid. Dennis
Quaid I stand by this should be Indiana Jones next. We could get four or five good movies
out of him as Indiana Jones. He's perfect for it. All right. He's perfect for it.
All right. He looks great. He's got that indignant like come on. You know he's like Dennis Quaid.
I love him. What's your favorite Dennis Quaid movie. I was just on the tip of my tongue.
I was gonna say how much I love interspace. That probably is the best one right. Yeah
I mean it's just a great great movie. Joe Dante. I love a Joe Dante. Yeah. Madden A.
Madden A is a great underrated movie. Yeah. You know I had a Twilight Zone the movie poster
signed by Joe Dante and fucking when I moved it seemed to disappear with all my other
valuable paintings what can you say I'm not accusing anybody no but right yeah we're in
the climax of the film at this point Nancy is Nancy has purposefully gone to sleep she
set up booby traps around the house she's now in the boiler room home alone home alone
Yes.
he horrifically mutilated two men that came into his home. Yeah. I mean that was my fair
movie for years when I was a kid. Like it's a dream. I was I was Macaulay Culkin's age
when that came out. It was like a dream come true. And I love John Hughes and remain a
huge fan. But I watched some I guess it was probably on the DVD like a DVD extra and
Chris Columbus the director was talking about how Joe Pesci like basically came from the
set of good fellas to do home alone right as like an afterthought and he's like we have
days of footage of Joe Pesci like screaming in McCulloch Colkins face I'm gonna fucking
kill you and he's like no Joe Joe he's a ten year old boy and this is a PG rated comedy
like he's an improv guy and he'd get real into it and they'd be like you're not at
good fellas anymore Joe oh that's beautiful you can say like you want to like break
his nose or something fun like that. But you can't say you want to murder him and bury
him in the desert. Is there anything funnier than Daniel Stern
getting the tarantula put on his face. It's the best scream in movie history.
I would say it's you know what another great one is Bruce Willis and death becomes her.
I like a man with a high pitch scream. It's always funny. I never saw death becomes
her. Believe it or not really good. I wasn't rushing to get to the new Goldie Han vehicle.
look fine but it's really good Robert Zemeckis it's it's a very funny Bobby Z very funny
movie great special effects and it has a lot to say about aging and Hollywood and culture
in its great move Nancy just found Glenn's headphones in Freddy's boiler room Glenn
was Johnny Depp right and in case you were mistaken they did have a label on them that
said Glenn you know I thought the other label that said headphones was a bit much
I felt like Wes wasn't really giving us credit there. Why doesn't Nancy currently have blood
all over her fingers. I don't know. What was the yeah. How did she get. Oh because she
picked up Glenn's headphones. What did she land in that she's fine. She's dreaming.
Oh yeah. You're not. Have you lost the premise of the movie already. She landed in some
rose bushes. Freddie's going to jump out. She's going to wake herself up in a minute
it. And this is the whole thing. She figures out halfway through the movie. I can bring
Freddie into real life. Yes, of course. All right. Now she's about
to wake up. There he is. But he doesn't know what she can do. She tackles him. He thinks
easy kill. Boom. Wakes up. And who has now that feeling?
What do you mean? Well, I have this feeling every night where like you're about to be
brutally murdered in your dream. And then you are like wake up. Please wake up and
you jolt yourself away. You know I have that feeling every time I
go into a pitch meeting. I didn't know you had night terrors I'd
love to sleep over one night and hear those things. No you
wouldn't. Oh God I would. I should probably double down on
the therapy as I am like it's like whenever you like talk
about something in public it's like oh wait this isn't normal
that I jolt awake nearly being murdered in my sleep every
night. And you scream. No I usually go like. Now here's
would always bothered me about Freddy Freddy coming into the real world yeah because they
do this in Freddy versus Jason to comes into the real world Freddy versus Jason also we
are yeah horror movies yeah you'd you'd think the first thing he would do is start going
my fucking skin hurts yeah no it's fine burn to a crisp yeah doesn't it doesn't seem to
phase of it all. It always bothered me. Things like that bother me. All right. You know she
just broke through a window with an umbrella. Sure why not. You could break your window with
an umbrella. Here comes Freddy. Look I mean it's home alone.
He gets a sledgehammer. That is home alone. There he goes. The only thing this scene
is missing is paint can to his nuts. Yeah. Or paint cans being thrown in.
Uh, this gets a little paint canny right here. He runs through the, he runs right through
the trip trip wire and sets off the lamp bomb. Yeah, just kind of gives like an ouch. Like
it. Yeah, maybe. I love it. Nancy's screaming out the window for help. That was a weird
choice it takes. There's a cop across the street and he goes
maybe I should go tell the lieutenant. Did you just see on the stairs there appeared.
Yeah that's like a giant bottle of bourbon. Oh she's going to grab. No no this is one
of her booby traps. Okay I was going to say the mob just leave
a bottle out. Which she throws it at him it just shatters
on his chest. She's re -burning him now. But now she's burning them on this side.
There's a man in a Freddie Halloween costume now getting who's on fire. That literally
looks like the Halloween costume of Freddie I bought at right aid when I was a child.
There he goes. He is making sort of Schwarzenegger noises right now to get to the chopper. Come
on you're better than that. That's his big line right. You're better than
that. What is that an old. That's like a Kevin Pollock routine.
All right. Well I'm not saying that's not a diss at Kevin Pollock I'm just saying
he's been saying that for a long time. Well I don't know Kevin Pollock. I don't follow his
career. I do. I liked him in grumpy old men and diner.
Was he wasn't in diner. No I love him in grumpy old men. He's in
a lot of movies that seem like diner. You know pop. That's my Kevin Pollock impression
from your old man. Hey pop. What do you gotta do for dead a pop.
He's got that Queens New York thing to him. The cops are down in the house. They're
smoke coming up from the basement where she set Freddie on fire how by throwing a bottle
of bourbon into his chest. But what's this fiery footprints up the stairs fire. Again this
is what starts to bug me is I love the movie I'm not knocking it but this is now a real
man that has been burnt on top of burnt skin yeah and he's still somehow running around
on the house to kill people we're in the like 12th and 13th degree burns yeah he's on top
of the mother trying to burn her right now and now the mother is look blue again yeah
the mother's corpse burnt to a Chris sinks into a blue abyss look isn't that Saxon's
wife yeah he seems oddly non plus they're divorced oh okay well she was a bitch yeah
Well, there's an extra seven fifty a month. I don't got to spend. That's what he's thinking
right now. You know what? Saxon should have yelled there. Now you deal with her bullshit
Krueger. He should have yelled that as she's sunk into the bed. She's your problem now
Krug's. By the way, watch your credit cards, baby. That's, you know, it's another way
the movie could have gone once again the whole room is blue which makes you question isn't
you ever think about that until I laid that truth bomb on you know it's killing me it's
killing me Shyamalan does it like Unbreakable is an extremely color coded movie if you watch
it purple and you know he's talking about making part two man that'd be great Unbreakable
is such a fucking classic I love it and I'm pissed that he's I'm like why did it take
this long for these guys even talk about making it. Yeah. Such an awesome movie like make the
second one. Everyone talks about it like it's a cult
favorite and it made like 150 million dollars. Yeah. He was still the man. It's like make
the next one break. Unbreakable. Another great effect shot here.
Freddie comes up through the sheet and it again it's like a latexie kind of a condom
kind of a dick going into a condom vibe. So my theory here is now Freddie's back.
He's still alive. He magically comes out of the bed. My theory is is she's actually dreaming here. He doesn't realize she is
However, she still defeats him
because
She realizes I don't I'm not scared of you. Yeah, which is how she felt through the whole booby traps today
Yeah, can I blow your mind again real quick? Yeah
Home alone the big turning point in home alone like the act to when he's like I'm gonna defend everything
he yells I'm not afraid anymore yeah like three times in a row yeah I'm not afraid anymore
so movies the same movie let's let's change the statement I made earlier home alone gets
very nightmare on Elm Street yeah not the other way around yeah got that furnace in
the basement causing trouble that was scary the neighbor how much okay that was kind of
into the corner. Freddie just turned into television snow. She's not scared anymore. She opens
the door. Here's the daylight. Look at those blue. Blue. Red. Blue. Blue eyes. I believe
she had blue eyes in the whole rest of the movie. Did she know and I believe a blue
outfit. They do color contacts on it. Yeah. See I think that whole end is supposed to
be she's still dreaming. The whole thing is she's still dreaming. She thinks she's
awake. She thinks she's defeated him. She hasn't. She's still dreaming. Her mom's wearing
a smock painting with giant buttons on it. Let me tell you something about what the mom
looks like right now. Two words. I likey. Again ladies and gentlemen please don't have
sex with Joe DeRosa. You're just going to hear. I love this access buttons down the
front. Yeah. Yeah purple and blue. Well I guess everything's happy from here on out.
I guess we're gonna hit stop. It looks like never mind this smoke that's everywhere. It
looks like just billowing all around them everywhere. Nobody seems to notice it. They're
dreaming. Wait a minute. I thought this was the end and everything's gonna be fine. She's
still dreaming. The car is Freddie Stripes. The mother doesn't notice. Yeah. That something's
wrong. That the car looks like a Freddie car suddenly. Yeah. And here we go. Mother
in front of the blue door what's going to happen uh -oh there's the little girls from
the beginning right and here's Freddy's arm and he pulls the blow up down through the
window. Yeah that's kind of a weird effect. Well
I mean you know very how else did you make that very like the end of Kerry as well one
final like when the arm jolts out of the grave it's a very final shot Kerry but that's
only in the remake no no no no does that happen in the original what they don't do
it in the remake they do do it in the original and her arm comes out of the grave beautifully
done in the original they keep zooming in on these rocks and it's that beautiful woman whatever
her name is Amy something and she's at the grave and the hand comes out and grass oh
yeah that's right terrifying I forgot about that okay you're right Amy Irving sorry Steven
Spielberg exacts that's it song it the we're at the closing credits what's the song playing
Yeah, did they be like is this song like what they used to do or like there had to be a song about the movie?
Like it's a nightmare on Elm Street and talk about a nightmare
Let me see if I can wear there before we sign on on Elm Street
nightmare on Elm Street like that like the song and who's Harry Crumb by the Temptations and
It's they say who's Harry Crumb they go. It's called big fun parentheses Harry Crumb
fun here a crime. This is the according to YouTube the Everly Brothers. Oh no. This can't
be the Everly Brothers. I mean the Isley Brothers. It says the Everly Brothers all I have to do
is dream. No that's whenever I want you all I have to do. That's in the remake. Oh yeah
you're right. You're absolutely right. Is your backdrop on your phone grease the
movie. Yeah I think that's funny. Okay. It's from the scene. It's from the you're the
one that I want seen. It makes me laugh. All right. I can't find changing the read it.
Hey as we're wrapping up here so you don't have to listen to Joe Google on this podcast.
us send us movie suggestions thoughts ways to improve things you love whatever we're starting
out this is new to us as well um any suggestions you got did you tweet out earlier I did I forgot
to look at it oh my god look there's nothing saying we gotta end if there's any questions
right now I'm gonna look at Twitter we're gonna ask you okay can I read you the one comment
under the video yeah please do on YouTube of the ending song please there's no information
on the guys that did this song. It's actually a really great song. Good drumming. Awesome
synths. Why is there no info on this band? They're called two one three. That was posted
six years ago. Not when the movie came out. Six years ago when YouTube came out that that
was posted. We have any questions. We do. I'm going to read through them. Do you think
Freddie Krueger served in Nam? Do you think he's seen some shit? I think it's a great
question the timeline adds up to me I would not be surprised to be serve the nom but I
bet they would have mentioned it at some point during the series because why not yes and yes
and actually if you're going into pitch and I'm on Elm Street sequel and like the 80s or
whatever you really should have done a nom a nom themed that would have been perfect
great question and our man Ken Hanley our point man over at Fangoria and the Fangoria
podcast network and all that stuff he sent us a bunch of questions I say this is
a good way to end is just answer. Yeah, and questions. He says is Joe checked into a health
care facility after meeting he like Johnny Depp and Tusk. What a beautiful question because
it's one of the worst performances in recent movie history. And you know who else didn't
like it from everything I've heard. Kevin Smith. He was like I hate that I have this
guy and it's such a great get but he's ruining my movie. What are you talking
about? That's what I've heard through the great. Oh I don't believe it. I think that's
in all seriousness though funny Freddy or scary Freddy for me a scary Freddy funny Freddy
is annoying of course is new nightmare the best sequel for me yes but no three is the
best sequel new nightmares the second best sequel okay and then would you recruit in
small towns I don't understand what that means but no yeah just gonna say no thanks
for listening everybody I'm at Joe DeRosa comedy on Twitter I make the Patrick Walsh
on Twitter Vine Instagram. And guys, we'd love your feedback. I hope you're enjoying
the podcast. Yeah. Give us some feedback. It hasn't aired yet.
So, you know, when it does, we'd like to know. We'd love it. All right, guys. Thanks
a lot for listening. Take care and we'll see you in hell next time.