I'll see you in hell.
Folks, we'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast you turn to when you want to talk those hot movies.
He's my name's Joe Derozo.
My name is Walsh, comma, Patrick, what says in my Manila envelope in my file folder,
at the IRS, the IRS.
Joe, how was your tax day this year, did you have a good time?
Did you celebrate like most do or?
Well, Pat, I got to say it was like most tax days, except this time, I got the added joy of being hit with $11 ,000 tax bills.
I'm a me two separate days, yeah, somehow after two years of being unemployed, I don't understand my account goes,
your income somehow went up, I'm like, I don't even know what's going on.
I didn't make a dollar this year or the year before.
Now I'm back kind of making money, but for two years I didn't make any money and I owed a tremendous amount to the IRS.
And I said, what is this, what are you talking about?
Then I said, much as Tyler Perry wants asked, why did I get married?
Wasn't this supposed to bring my tax rate way down?
Wasn't that supposed to help?
No, if anything, my tax rate went up a lot in marriage.
What, so what, what reward is there for anyone in this God forsaken crumbling society?
Even the things we've been told our whole life will benefit you, don't benefit you.
No, nothing.
But just all been lies, it's all been lies.
And then every, you see every day, people talking in government, talking like up on a stand lecturing people,
who are currently on trial for sex trafficking minors.
And our government is like, let's listen to what this guy has to say for an hour.
There's no penalties for anyone except me, set me owing $45 ,000 on zero income.
I do that.
I think sex traffic minor one.
Jesus Christ.
You think you'd get a, I remember it was back in my day, you got a few minors for that money.
I mean, honestly, I don't even need minors, make them of age.
And, you know, let me get the ones who are sort of into being sex traffic, not loving it, but just like,
all right, this is a kind of a brave new world for me.
I'm learning about my sexuality, that kind of a traffic victim.
I got you.
I got you a guy that's going, I don't know, I kind of liked it.
Yeah, I'm looking for one who wants to cuddle afterwards.
You know, I'm not the kind of guy who's going to enter your room in a, in a long floor length robe.
Undo the sash to reveal a giant king, kupa style gut.
And look down at you with disgust while you blow me, that's not the kind of guy I am.
I'm not one of those guys who stole Liam Neeson's daughter.
I'd be, I'd treat you fair.
You'd be more like the guy in boogie nights.
You letting the kid run around, having a good time with his fireworks.
Exactly.
Yeah, I got you.
It's been a while since we've done a good pedophilia bit on the show.
We were known for it at one point.
Remember there was a time where we were.
Well, we were until it became, you know, working at Disney can get you labeled a pedophile.
Now, I'm like, yeah, I guess I'm not joking about it.
But if everyone is a pedophile now, how did that happen?
That's another, it's been six months.
And it seems like the number one word I read day in and day out is pedophile.
What's happening?
I don't know.
I don't know if I don't know.
My theory is this.
My theory is that the world.
And this is, by the way, one of the only theories that'll keep you sane right now.
In my opinion, yeah, my take is the world isn't worse than it was.
It's just that all of it is being light is being shown on all of it now in a way that never was before.
Every single circumstance and instance and situation did not have a magnifying glass over it before.
Now, everything is exposed immediately and you're getting all of it thrown at you at once.
So, so it creates an illusion that, oh, my God, like, the world is crumbling and they're these problems are worse than ever before.
But it's like, well, are they are where they just not really being reported on before?
You know, it's a combo.
Things are worse than before.
Things are worse.
Well, I know that for a fact, but again, this is just what I tell myself.
Yeah, I mean, when you see Rudy Giuliani popping out of a wedding cake, wearing a parrot costume, singing its reigning men on the mass singer,
six months after nearly bringing America and democracy to its knees.
I mean, we're in a different time.
We're in a worse time than before.
I love, I love and look, I take full responsibility for the words that are coming out of my mouth.
None of my views are represented or represent Patrick Walsh.
Yes.
Or Patrick Walsh industries.
I love that Ken John, you know, that's like, he goes, I'm out.
I'm done.
He's done that twice with Rudy Giuliani.
Wait, Giuliani's been bet.
Wait, Giuliani was on a second time.
This was his second time in the show being reported as the first.
That's why I start to feel like I'm going crazy.
And John left the stage that time.
Yeah, I saw, I saw like Jackie Cashian, who's a friend of mine, I like Jackie quite a bit.
But she tweeted out like good, you know, she tweeted a compliment to the Daily Show joke, which was funny.
About like a job.
Yeah, well, it's it.
It was just a tweet.
They brought a comedian in or what they do.
It's just a tweet.
Okay.
It's a Ken John's being replaced by the judge for the Kyle Rittenhouse trial, which is a very
funny.
That's a funny joke.
Yes.
And Jackie was like, that's a perfect joke, Daily Show, but she was like, and good for you Ken.
And it's like, Jackie, no, not good for you.
He has, he has kneeled at the cock of the Fox network for the last three.
Yeah.
It's a despicable network.
Let's not act like he's all of a sudden got integrity because he's now in a room with a guy
where there's photographic evidence of the evil he is.
He's in doubt himself or or bestowed himself.
What's the word I'm looking for?
Not bestowed.
You know what I mean?
It's a coach.
You voluntarily involved himself with.
Yeah.
It's just, it's, it's, it's, it's a come on.
Like, let's say, like, this is the breaking point for, for ethics and dignity and, and, and, uh,
he got raised, he got raised the last time he did it.
So he knew he'd get raised if he did it again, but there's no way in hell he didn't know that
was happening in a second time, by the way.
He a billion percent knew what was happening.
Somebody goes, is that Robert Duval, which is kind of funny.
Julianna does look like Robert Duval.
That is kind of funny.
Equally crazy at this point.
But, um, what's Duval doing?
Duval's a madman.
He always kind of has been, but he stays to himself.
He keeps out of the public eye.
He's not drawing eyebrows on his forehead before.
You know who, Julian, that's me of his uncle Leo at this point.
Yes.
Perfect.
Hello.
Uh,
it's, uh, it's, uh, it's a while.
I mean, just the fact that that's a show that exists and one of our most successful programs is enough
to get America shut down for a while and, and reset.
It is.
I mean, you know, for, for all of Hollywood's complaining about like the White House,
you, you know, under Trump, taking us back to the 50s.
It's like, guys, do you see what you're doing with entertainment?
That's a rollback to the fit.
The mass sink.
This is something you'd see on like the lucky strike hour.
This is, uh, like the, it's so sterile and fucking benign and just, yeah.
You know, like, hey, folks, Julia Roberts is going to come out and sing a tune for us.
Bet you didn't know she could sing. Did you gang?
This is horrible.
Julia Roberts.
So, I mean, geez.
We'd be lucky to get Julia.
Come on, Pat.
Think of it.
Julia Trout was also quite famous.
Julia, uh, my friend Julia Rousey.
Funny comedian.
Julia Rousey.
Well, I said Roberts because now she's in yet another fucking streaming TV show that nobody is going to see.
Yeah.
Get her a leading movie star.
Gaslit.
I started laughing.
Ladies, I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry to say ladies.
I know that's somehow is derogatory now or something, but you don't know what to say.
I walk, I walk into an office at work with two women 50 times a day.
And every time I'm like, hey guys, no, hey ladies derogatory.
Hey women.
Very weird.
Even though that's what I guess I should say.
So I just want to go on.
I say hi all a lot lately.
Hey all.
I do that on emails.
I walk in and I yell, hey ladies, Beastie boys style.
And then I bring the cowbell.
I carry the cowbell with me.
No, but I just started laughing because it's like, it's like gaslit.
The woman that took on Nixon.
It's like guys.
We all know the Nixon story.
I'm sure there was a woman involved somewhere in that takedown.
But it's not making it sound like there was this secret story that nobody knows about.
That like his maid or whatever was really the one to expose it.
Also, gaslit wasn't a phrase that was used back then.
Every part.
And then it's got Julia Roberts looking like Robert Redford.
She's got like this blonde part in hair.
I was like, what is this?
I watched the three hour Nixon where every character actor alive played somebody involved with the Nixon scandal.
Oliver Stone's movie.
There's no key woman involved in the in the bring down.
They wouldn't have been treated with respect at the time.
Which is fine.
There's nothing wrong with there's other things that women have done that are great.
Do a story about one of those like why why every one of these things has to be like, you know,
the thing you saw the man do.
Well, now we have a story of the woman that was involved.
Guess what folks?
There was actually a woman that set foot on the moon first.
No, there wasn't.
There's some coming.
There's a show coming out about the the first woman who in the Pinkerton agency.
So it's like after they've established this one of the most famous detective agencies in the history of whatever it is Britain.
They added a woman to the mix at some point.
Now we're going to watch that story.
It's like, why?
Why is it going to hit all the same beats as every other story?
Well, what would a woman know about sleuthen?
What would a woman know about solving a mystery on these streets lying with London fog?
That's the thing, Gavna.
Woman looks in places you don't think to look as a man.
For instance,
She's going into the ladies room.
It didn't think to look in the cabinets in the kitchen did you now?
Oh, boy.
All right.
Right.
I was just getting my hair perm down at the salon.
And I found a knife covered in blood.
They're all like, oh, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, and then, yeah, and then they'll all be like, yeah, he'll add some bird, cut
a self on a knife down at the salon, couldn't possibly be a murder weapon, it was where
the birds go.
Oh, Jesus Christ, you cut to the hardened, grizzled police chief who's like snooping around
the salon.
Because now he's like, that's where I'm going to get all the, he's maybe perhaps wearing
a wig.
He's wearing the, he's got a wig on.
And, but he still has on the domed, what are those police hats that they wore in England?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's like the huge, great mouth detective hat, yeah, yeah, and they, he's got a magnifying
glass with a pink handle.
Don't mind me, just a, just a lady getting me ahead on Oh, boy, that's very funny.
Oh, wow.
Sean Penn, the gaslight was the show where he said he's not returning to
his set until everybody got vaccinated.
And I'm just like, gaslit, too, yeah, he looks, I don't know, Nixon, oh, I love this
shot pants for trail of Nixon.
That would be something.
I am not a walk.
Just take my daughter's car in there.
Just a weathered Nixon.
Yeah.
Oh, he looks, he looks worse than Nixon.
He looks like there was a catcher's mitt full of ash, cigarette ash.
And he just rubbed his face and at each morning before each take.
But I'm like, Sean, you saying you're not going to return to production?
Yeah, that's going to be annoying for everyone who's paid your salary and, you know, paid
the crew salary and everything.
But if you think anyone cares to see a Sean Penn project in 2022, you're out of your
fucking mind.
Why are they casting?
I mean, it's nothing to anyone.
Well, that's, that's the thing like it makes sense to me that Sean Penn is in a streaming
show.
Why is Julia Roberts doing all these streaming?
She's still a box office draw.
She's still got the way.
She's got the nuts.
Like, why are you doing these damn streaming shows?
I don't understand.
No, flow.
She said the other day, they were like, why didn't you do a romantic comedy for 20 years?
And she was like, I didn't read a single good romantic comedy script for 20 years.
It's like, well, I'm sure they were being written.
And they just weren't getting to her is more, you know, the, the, but yeah, but I can't
remember the last time I saw a good romantic comedy, can you ages, ages, so they're so bad
that when a slightly below average one hits like the Charlie day, Jenny, slate one or the
always be my maybe on Netflix, they wind up, they're like, see, see, see, see plus.
And they wind up getting ray reviews because there are no good ones.
And they, the streamers should be doing them because that's where they belong now.
Romantic comedies should be hitting the streamers, but there's no done that are good.
Yeah.
It's a shame.
It's, I'm also, I'm very surprised.
And I guess they just don't want to fund them for whatever reason, but I'm surprised you're
not seeing more indie romantic comedy.
I mean, that was the go to, when you were an indie filmmaker from like 1970, whatever
on, you did one of two things.
You either tried to be Woody Allen and made a romantic comedy, which is like what Favreau did
with swingers.
And I forget the guy who directed it, who directed go and whatever.
Doug Lama.
He even made his sort of a romantic comedy in its weird way.
And then like, or you tried to be Scorsese and you made like reservoir dogs or, or something
like that.
It was high -smooth, you're a romantic comedy.
I have not seen either of those really interesting indie now was very horror focused.
It's horror.
Or issues.
It's, you know, now the quickest way to a green light is be about an issue, be about something
that they think is affecting all of America, even though most America doesn't care about
them.
Sure.
Where are we at?
Oh, I think I had a news psycho.
Oh, actually, this is a, this is a sort of a news.
Yeah, it's a new psycho.
And it has to do with today's movie that we're reviewing.
We're reviewing Kids in the Hall of Brain candy today.
But my new psycho is simply that the two trailers for the season dropped.
And they look, I haven't seen them yet.
There's a red band and a green band trailer.
They were wonderful.
They, they, they all I kept thinking of going into like an anticipation was, I hope that
they like, they're doing a six season.
I hope that they do a six season that they bring back some of the elements of the earlier
stuff and that it's not like, they're doing a six season, but it's like, uh, there's a new
hook to it or something like that.
And sure enough, trailer opens, it's, it's, I'm getting chills talking about it.
It's McKinney as the boss from brain candy walking with Dave Foley, like as the assistant.
And he's, or the first thing you see in the trailer is they dig up the,
a crane goes to the grave that they got buried in in the finale of season five.
Yes.
And it digs them up.
And they're all screaming like they, like they were alive in there the whole time.
And Bruce McCullough goes, I know we should have gotten cryogenically frozen.
And then it cuts to McKinney and Foley.
And McKinney's like, well, so, uh, the news is the kids are back.
And, uh, and Dave Foley goes, he goes, well, how is that possible?
Don, do you make some deal with the devil?
And, uh, I'm going to go close Amazon, which is a funny joke.
And then it gets rolling and there's tons of new clips from new sketches of them doing
characters I've never seen, but then like, it cuts at once.
You see McCullough as, you know, the kid that's like, in England,
now, everybody only owns one spoon, you know, that's just really annoying.
Yeah, I think you see heck you miss at one point.
Was that kid the basis for Jonathan Lipnicki and Jeremy?
Why are you think?
I never saw Jeremy Guierre believe it or not.
Jesus.
Joe, it's a great film.
So you want to talk about a great romantic comedy?
Yeah.
I don't know why I never, I have no excuse.
I don't know why I've never seen it.
I just never saw it.
Watch it.
Next time we'll do it, we do the show, put it in.
I wanted in the movie corner for you.
I wanted in the movie corner.
All right.
It shows, oh, if they do the parents, when they would do the parents, where it was like,
McCullough was the dad, um, the mom was, uh, Scott Thompson.
And then the son was Dave Foley.
They do that family and Foley is still the candy.
If there was like 58 or whatever, um, and they were just,
they were just, they, they show the office ladies for a moment.
Like they were just, and like, and then the, the voiceover that guides the whole trailer
is McKinney as the boss.
Lorne Michael from Breacan or candy.
Yeah.
Lorne Michael's saying like, they want us to do it safe.
They, they don't want any issues brought up that we were not supposed to make fun of the
genders or whatever.
So like, they're calling attention to like, right.
We're going to do a kids in the whole show.
Even though like, these are kind of like where we're supposed to stay away from.
And this is all the stuff we used to make fun of.
And you know, there are a couple like, like laugh out loud moments in the trailer,
but it's, it's clips.
It's a teaser.
It's not, you're not seeing a lot of, uh, uh, meat, but it was great.
I was so excited.
I was, you know, can't wait.
They do 10, half hours or what?
I don't know what they're doing.
I mean, Christ, if they do it the old way, it's going to be like 24 fucking episodes.
Yeah, 40 minutes, you know, but I doubt that.
But they'll never do that without testing the audience first anymore.
Yeah.
And they don't play the theme in the trailer.
I'm really praying that, I mean, it's got to, right?
That it's still, it has says the opening credits now with them now in the black and white
with the shadowy men song playing, right?
Yeah, they will.
They won't.
So, um, excited to see it for sure.
Very, very excited, very, very excited.
Um, yeah, I can't wait.
Uh, Netflix this week took a huge tank.
Apparently they lost 200 ,000 subscribers.
They're expected to lose two million more in quarter to, uh, they're getting a little
desperate.
And I myself canceled my Netflix subscription.
Yeah, I saw, uh, Russian doll came on right after I canceled and I do want to see that.
So my new plan is just going to be one month a year, get Netflix, watch the 10 things I care
about and save myself a bunch of money.
That's kind of what I'm doing with, um, Disney, um, yeah, you know, luckily with Disney,
you can add it for like four bucks to your Hulu.
Right.
And like, so I added, I take it off, I added, I take it.
But basically, anytime new Star Wars stuff comes out, I add Disney again so I can watch it.
And then I shut it off.
Um, but I'm going to just start doing that with Netflix to do.
I can't, I gotta be honest.
I can't remember the last time I watched something on Netflix.
Me neither.
And, um, I, well, yeah, I watch junk documentaries.
I want when my brain is sort of too overpowered to focus on anything.
I watch something like the goddamn Tinder swindler or bad vegan or whatever.
I feel empty afterwards.
And that's it.
But like in terms of originals, they got nothing.
They also just announced that stranger things is costing 30 million at 30 million dollars on episode,
meaning 300 million a season of stranger things.
And of course, all these shows that people liked on Netflix that got cancelled are like,
are you fucking kidding me?
Like you could have made the babysitters club for one one hundredth of that.
But they're so algorithm focused now that I just think.
Anytime you're letting a computer decide what people want to see,
at some point, you're going to really be lacking actual human input.
You know, because people's tastes aren't that cut and dried.
I'll tell you a sign of the times here.
And we might not be in good shape.
You know, you go to your bank.
It's understaffed.
You go to your supermarket.
You go to most restaurants right now.
They're understaffed.
Anything that is employing somebody.
Yeah.
At an hourly wage essentially or a tip for work kind of gig.
That that is needed by the common person is understaffed.
For the most part, why?
Because of budget cutbacks and people being, you know, spread stretches as they can as far as their dollar can go.
And all these horrible things that are happening to people yet, yet.
Every one of the episodes of Stranger Things was vetted at least by a room of at least eight to nine writers.
I'm sure.
And every one of them making six figures a year.
And forget Stranger Things in the big shows.
Go down to the little shit shows on Netflix or wherever else prime, whatever that nobody cares about.
Every one of those shows is.
So it's a pretty sad state of affairs that.
You know, employment in the entertainment field for whatever reason seems to not have dipped.
Unless you fit a certain.
You know, it's no secret.
They're the hiring practices of shifted right.
You could say that it's dipped in that sense for certain types of people.
But as far as the money there to spread around, that is not really dipped.
What they, the claim it has when they're full of shit.
You know, and also it's too.
Yeah, go ahead.
This use of any.
Any conflict or tragedy.
For them to gal just now on prices for everything.
And the fact that airlines and gas companies are using the Russia Ukraine conflict as an excuse to hike their prices is so despicable and disgusting.
The least of your worries people are whether or not the masks are are used on on board the airlines anymore when it comes to air travel you've got bigger fish to fry.
They're going to make it impossible for you to get on an airplane.
If you are not somebody in the upper middle class echelon at least, they are going to make it impossible for you.
And that's something that you really need to know most of us don't have to fly.
But most of us prefer to because we don't live near our families or we want to go on a vacation or whatever the fuck it is.
And some of us do have to fly for work, but they are going to make it harder and harder and harder.
It's these are to me, these are the real problems and yet I don't see many people complaining about them. I still see all this focus on.
You know, did what did the dumb judge and fucking Florida say or whatever, you know, it's right.
Anyway, sorry, I didn't mean to get on a high horse.
No, I mean, I prefer to ride a high horse. They're more relaxed.
And they usually laugh at my jokes, folks.
Oh, let's get to the movie corn.
Also, the other thing that looks did is cut their entire animation division this week, like fired everybody.
It's like, guys, if you're going to be this one stop destination, you're going to need some animation.
There are families watching. What are you doing?
Well, I just love that now it's, you know, it's panic at the disco now because it's like, guys, when you were putting out a new series and movie every three days, you never thought you might need to save some of that money in the software for a rainy day.
You never thought maybe our staff, maybe we can't continue on at this, at this tick that we're operating at.
Maybe they didn't. They just don't give a shit. Maybe that's just how we're, but they announced now too.
Like we're going to start cracking down on password sharing.
That's like, oh, so now you're going to fuck over the people that were supporting you.
Now I get it. Like somebody using somebody else's password.
I get the argument that they're not supporting you.
But the person that gave them the password is.
And one of the reasons that they gave them that was because they were loyal to you for long enough, as you upped your price continually with them.
They saw one of the benefits of that of paying that price hike and be remaining a loyal member was in the fact that you didn't crack down on the password sharing and you did let them spread the wealth a little bit.
But it also justified you guys being this, this monopolizing, you know, beast in the industry.
It's like, well, at least you're letting people share the passwords and you're spreading the wealth a little bit.
Now you're not even going to spread the wealth and we're all supposed to go boohoo for fucking Netflix.
You know, I mean, they used to say they love that.
They used to say that they love that people share their passwords because they got the word around and everything.
But that is the new thing, be a giant, whether it be Elon Musk, Netflix, Disney, whatever, be a complete monster, not worry about the environment, human beings, anything in your path.
Then when people finally get sick of it, claim you're a victim.
That's the new thing and people fall for it.
Like there are people who if Disney plus was like, hey guys, we got to raise our thing five bucks because of this they'd be like, hey, Disney plus yet we love you.
You know, of course, we'll do it for they start to have alliances to these companies who would would happily see you dead.
Yeah, I mean, it's it's it's just fucking crazy. It's just fucking crazy.
Anyway, anyway, what do you got for us here on the corn? Well, movie corn last night, I saw the unbearable weight of massive talent.
Oh, directed by Tom Gormacken, who I know a bit and written by Tom and Kevin Etten who I know and love me and Kevin were on Hollywood handbook podcasts once together.
But also he was my first writing job I wrote for the Bob and Doug show Bob and Doug McKenzie with Dave Thomas up in Canada.
Anyway, very funny guy. Great right. Great dude.
And thankfully he doesn't listen to this podcast because I got to say the movie was a let down for me.
It just doesn't click this sort of thing works to me as like a five minute MTV awards sketch, you know, and that's what this really is.
It's stretched out kind of past the point of no return much like the bubble, which also was bad and start Pedro Pascal as well.
This goes for like a half hour pretty funny with Nicholas cage parodying himself.
A lot of smart jokes about him and his career and cage is excellent in the move. Don't get me wrong.
But then at some point this the plot kicks in and it's one of these big 80s plots.
They don't have the budget or really the skill to pull off the action sequences, but it becomes an action scene or an action movie where cage is brought to one of these parties by a guy for a million dollars down in Mexico.
And he winds up having to kind of fight his way out.
Not a bad premise, but who plays the bad guy.
Well, the good bad guy, whatever Pedro Pascal is the guy who hires Nicholas cage fan. He's kind of his partner.
And then I don't know the name of the guy who plays the villain, but they're lacking a great villain as well.
It just is kind of a mess, you know, from a script standpoint, and I hate to say it, but.
The laughs, it's one of those things where when something funny happens in the last hour of the movie, you don't laugh just because you're kind of exhausted by all the action and the stuff that doesn't really click.
So.
Not a total loss, you know, there, there, it's a, it's a good start. I think this should not have been a two hour movie. It should have been 90, which I always say about comedies.
But it's a one joke premise, I would say stretched beyond its, it's bending point.
Cage is great, cage is great. And there's lots of little in jokes and references for his fans.
A discussion of guarding tests that made me laugh because I can't believe anyone is still talking about guarding tests at this point.
But yeah, it was a bit of a missed opportunity. I will admit it's not a terrible film. The audience seem to like it a lot.
And I am also in a absolutely horrible mode. So keep that and do a consideration as I review movies.
Alright, fair enough. I did a, I did a John Candy marathon, short marathon because I've been in a horrible mood too. And he, you know, I wanted to put a smile on my face and what better way to do that than what John candy.
Yes, I will start with Uncle Buck, which I think everybody thinks is, you know, I would say is Candy's Sergeant Pepper, right? That's his.
For sure, making plans trans is what? Well, plane strains is a candy move. I'm not counting that. I counted obviously, but I just mean like Uncle Buck is his movie. You know what I mean?
Plane strains is him and Steve Martin. True. And, and weirdly, you don't like even though plans trans is rated R. It's the most PG 13 rated R movie ever made because of one foxing, but it's one scene with a lot of fox. I mean, I feel like even though I love adult shit, comedy, cussing sex, violence, whatever.
Candy is a guy who you like, you prefer to see in a PG setting. Yeah, for some reason, I think that's why Uncle Buck is kind of his masterpiece when he's playing like a purve or a sex creep or something. You don't like it, because it seems like it's not him, you know, anyway, go ahead. Sorry.
Yeah, that's fine. I love Uncle Buck. I've always been a fan. I got to say I never noticed before how amazing the direction is in this movie with John Hughes, you know, John Hughes is always a guy that I sort of thought was that I thought was a good director because of the performances he gets out of people in telling these stories that he writes, which he is very good at.
But John, I never notices Uncle Buck has like art, how cinema sequences in it. There's that thing where like, yeah, the heartbeat is happening as they're all sleeping and it's cutting to all the shots and the alarm goes off. There's the shot of when Culkin tries to was, would anybody be interested in a lunch trade and it cuts the over a shot and everybody likes right flies out across the floor from around him.
There's like a weird shot where the clock turns into the moon, like there's a lot of like these weird artsy shots in it that are really cool that elevate the movie. She's having a baby a couple years before he did a bunch of those like fantasy sequences and stuff too.
I think it comes from his past as an advertiser because all that stuff feels like great commercial bits.
Yeah, you know, what can I say it's, if you haven't seen Uncle Buck, you need to, it's a wonderful movie. It's the, to me, it's the thing that encompasses John candy best next to probably only the lonely as far as like a movie that just showcases like the warmth that you would that you get from this man.
And, you know, it's hilarious. He's great. Culkin really shines in it. He's wonderful. It's great seeing him for the first time in something.
So weird to see a kid like that just be like this kid is going to be a major comedy star, which he was wild.
Yeah, wild. And it's wafting off of him in the movie like he's a legendary character and it's like he's stealing scene.
Well, the whole trailer, I remember the trailer was the extended scene of candy and Culkin, the interrogation scene.
Yeah, much more hair in your nose than my dad, a nice few notice. I'm a kid. That's my job.
The oldest daughter, I forget the actor's name, but she's, she's great. I always forget how fucking awful she is.
Like you watch and you're like, she's the worst human being that's ever lived, which makes the payoff at the end when she finally breaks so wonderful.
But when she breaks emotionally, meaning like learns to appreciate they, you know, and then and then buck learns from her, which is very nice.
Also the, but man, the jokes, I mean, the scene where he's like, you have a plunger just for the mornings.
Being a lot of cheese, been really bound up lately. I don't know what it is. Can't do enough cheese. I'm like a big mouse.
And then he goes, you think that's an allergy. Like an allergy would make you eat a lot of cheese.
It's just such a disgusting discussion to be having.
Yeah. And like, that's funny. Those are the moments in the movie that are my favorite. They're, they're not the most popular. You know, the most popular.
They're, you know, take this quarter, have a rat. I'll do the thing off your face. Getting your mouth.
Yeah, the pancakes, getting your mouths and get out of here. They're all very funny scenes.
But those, those like just the dialogue comedy and it's so funny when he's like, that one, I'm going to five year plan. I'm off cigarettes. I'm on the cigars now.
And I'm going to go to pipes and chewing to back. And then nicotine gum.
So watch Uncle Buck.
Yeah. You, uh, you, you guys like this hat? A lot of people hate this hat. It anger's a lot of people. Just the side of it.
I'll tell you a story about that on the way to school.
Hundreds of great lines. And you don't know where candy's improvs begin and the writing ends. And that's kind of the beauty of their friendship candy and, and, uh,
Hughes, because they loved each other so much that it just kind of, he knew how to write for him in a way that others didn't always know.
Ebert gave it a bad review.
I think I remember him doing like a two and a half. But yeah, that always blew my mind. That always blew my mind. I saw it opening day, Regency AMC played in the arcade afterwards. It was one of the great days of my life.
My mom sobbing at the end when the mom gets home.
Yeah, the hug with the daughter. That's a very plain trains ending.
Oh, yeah, my mom and home alone in my mom leaning over my sister to glare at me during the opening five minutes, where the kids costs a million times when the within the first five minutes for some reason.
Yeah, that's her leaning over like, oh, okay, we do in light. This is Corsese film or what's going on.
Okay, second line of it is you're hurting my arm. God damn it. Your nails are digging into my arm. God damn it.
Oh, let's have a cow.
It's great to hear have a cow again. It's a fantastic movie, of course. I, uh, one of my favorites, for sure. I saw a picture.
Called heavy. We talked about it on this show after our long discussion of Copland. And I said, you know, I haven't seen James Mangold's debut film.
The one that he did before.
Heavy in a very long time. It's on Netflix now. It's one of four movies Netflix has that was made before the year 2000.
Um, and I like to quite a bit. It's a very slow, small indie.
You got that pruit Taylor Vince who has always been a great actor, character actor. He's got the eye that twitches really bad.
Kind of the white forest Whitaker in terms of being a large man with a weird eyes, a great actor.
Um, live Tyler at her most absolutely stunning. She plays a waitress who, you know, I and many of my friends have been subject to this dynamic many times over the course of our life where a very beautiful, very beautiful woman will love the fact that you and your friends are really funny and genuinely funny.
But then and, you know, really nice and like hanging out with you and you mistake that for love, you know, like because you've never really been around it.
You think that this beautiful woman is hanging out with you because she's into you, but she's not. And that's what happens to this man in this case. He's a quasi moto type gentleman.
Who mistakes live Tyler's kindness for affection. So of course it is a sad movie. It's got a lot in common with Marty.
The classic Ernie Borg -9 Best Picture winner from 1955. He had a great brief performance from Shelley Winters, one of her last performances.
And a really good supporting cast. I dug the movie. It feels very 90s ND, but it's worth a watch.
Second on my list.
A sleeper, something a movie I saw as a kid many times went back into it now, just going, I just want to kind of tune out, have a couple laughs maybe, but I don't think I'll be too enthralled by the movie.
And I was pleasantly surprised, armed and dangerous. It was way funnier than I remembered it being. Maybe I just didn't realize when I was a kid, like, how truly funny it was.
There's another tried as horrible reviews, of course, but I don't remember much. It's not a well made movie. Yeah, but it's a very funny move. There's a great scene in the beginning candy plays a cop.
And it opens with a little girl crying under a tree. And he pulls up and he's like, what seems to be the problem. And she's like, my cat.
And he's like, when are you get up there in the tree? And he looks up and she's like, you know, she wants him to go get the cat and he looks up and it's like, way, way up the tree.
And he does this thing. He just looks at her and he goes, I wouldn't worry about it. Cats climb.
Because he's scared to go up the tree. Yeah, there are like tons of moments in it like that that I completely just didn't pick up on as a younger person watching it.
Jonathan Banks in the movie is one of the heavies.
And he's great plays a fucking asshole. I texted him while I was watching it. I was like, John, I hope all is well. I'm watching you in a little picture called armed and dangerous. I grew up on this movie. You just tried to kill Eugene Levy.
I hope all is well. He's great in it. He plays a real asshole. Robert Lozier's in it. He plays like this mob boss teamster leader. He's great.
And of course, Eugene Levy and Meg Ryan, which by the way, you're supposed to believe Meg Ryan is in love with Eugene Levy in this movie, which is a bit of a stretch.
But Eugene Levy's really funny. There's a hilarious scene in this.
And it's classic. It's what you it's the Eugene Levy you want. He's the tight ass. He's a wimp like he you know like he's it's it's it's the Eugene Levy that you like.
And my favorite thing the whole movie is is they you know they they both get fired from their jobs and they become security guards.
And they partner up and they they they they stumble on to some underhanded stuff going on within their security company.
And they're on the case, whatever. And they're trying to correct the case. But because they're sniffing around, they keep getting sent the company for some reason won't just fire them to get rid of them. They keep sending them to bad jobs in the hopes that they'll quit.
Right. So that's like part of the gag.
But my favorite scene is they get sent to work in a toxic waste dump.
And Eugene Levy is like, do you believe this? This is dangerous in John Candy's like stop being a baby. It's a little toxic waste. It's not going to kill you.
And they go to the trailer where they're supposed to report and the two guards that are already stationed there come out.
And they literally look like garbage pill kids. Their skin is green. They have like three teeth. Yeah. They have no hair. The guys like lost about their tooth today.
And Eugene Levy and John Candy do the thing where they cover their faces with their jackets.
Right. And the guys keep getting every time they step towards them. They step backwards. It's very, very funny. It's like a very like Abbott and Castello style.
Like comedy. It's, it's, it's a great scene. It's just a great scene. It's a fun movie. And speaking of what we spoke to last episode.
There's a scene where Candy is spying on Meg Ryan getting changed through the keyhole in her bedroom door.
Not his girlfriend. His best friend's girlfriend.
She's not even his friend's girlfriend. Yeah. They're just, they just, she's the boss's daughter. That's all they know. Right.
And she walks out of the bedroom. It's the classic thing. She opens the door and, and Candy is hunched over her like at the door job.
And, and it's literally played off just like, okay.
Right. You know, like, yeah. There's a line where she talks about how Robert Lojus' hands have been all over her fanny as she puts it.
Okay. And her father goes, that's son of a bitch and she goes, daddy, stop it. I'm a big girl. I can take care of myself.
I'm just like, wow. There's a very, very different climate. We were living in back then.
But it's very funny movie. Very, in my opinion, worth a fun watch. It's not going to change your life.
You're not going to learn anything about the cinema here. But if you want a great outdoor style, just sit down, tune out, laugh. You have a great time.
I own it even in my obsessed with Candy Days as a kid. It was one that I very rarely watched, but I'm doing, I'm doing rewatch. So I'll put it on this weekend.
I watched speaking of Netflix and honestly contributing to my desire to pull the plug on it for a while. I watched brand new cherry flavor.
Oh, yeah. How was it?
Well, I just liked the vibe of it and I had heard it compared to like Cronenberg and David Lynch and et cetera.
And sure, you know, it's influenced by those things, definitely.
It was basically, you know, the story is Rosa Salazar, who's a really good young actress, makes a great short film.
And Hollywood in the early 90s, this one, it's set loves the loves the movie. They're obsessed with it, but they don't really want her to direct because she's inexperienced and she's a woman and et cetera.
So the guy, this big sleazy Hollywood producer, makes her a promise that she can direct and she'll have control over it. And then as always happens in Hollywood takes it away from her, gives it to some hack, et cetera.
So she goes to a witch played by the great Catherine Keener.
And basically says, I would love Keener. I just, could I interject for a second? Of course.
I saw her in living in oblivion.
Oh, that's a great movie.
I didn't like it. I watched about half and I was like, this is even, I'm like, I'm in the mood for one of these 90s, like, yeah.
Cookie cutter indie films that were coming out a mile a minute back then. I got about halfway through. I was like, I can't do this. This is two, this is two 90s. I feel like
fucking screaming trees are going to walk into the living room in a second. Anyway, but she's in that. And I was like, oh my God, she could have been the hottest that ever lived
Keener at one point. I mean, my Lord big fan. I had seen her in a bunch of things. But I feel like the first time she registered for people was being jammed out of it, which I will be rewatching as part of my Charlie coffin to press off that I'm doing now.
But I'm sorry, so she's plays a witch.
She plays a witch. And you know, at the end, at the end of each episode, it's like, oh, we're not, we're not, it's not over yet or something like that. They say the same line at the end of every
episode of some kind of gimmick. But basically, it's truly a tale as old as time. A tale as old as revenge cinema or horror cinema. She wants revenge on this guy for doing this to her.
That revenge winds up taking the form of a lot of like cursed type stuff like he's, you know, he's got weird body horror stuff happening.
Salazar herself starts being affected by it. She keeps throwing up cats live cats, which isn't really explained.
At some point, she gets this big, very, very video drum, like gaping vagina type hole in her side.
She has a man fuck that whole first with his fist and then actually fuck it. That is, that's not an homage to Kronenberg. That's, that's Kronenberg.
That's, he did that in video drum and then crash fucking the wounds at the car crash. That really upsets me. The video drum, it was like right on the line for me.
But man, that really freaks me out for some reason. Well, crash is even more graphic. And this is probably more graphic than that. I mean, it's an episode four if you're watching out for it. But it's gross.
The gross out stuff is fun.
It looked like in order to get the green light from Netflix, they agreed to make this thing for like maybe, maybe a million, an episode because it looks really bad. It looks like it was filmed. Actually, it looks like a 16 millimeter early 90s movie, which maybe was the intent.
But the comedy is not funny enough. The horror is not scary enough. The show would have been great, great, as a two hour movie, even a two and a half like a Mulholland drive, you know, but stretching this to like eight hour long episodes makes no sense to me because the plot is pretty thin.
It's just a collection of gross things happening. But as a horror series, it's kind of fun. You know, I feel like nobody watched this thing. So it's not going to see any more of it. But I think it's a limited series anyway. It was fine. It was fun.
Last on my list, you know, this breaks my heart.
Always been a favorite. Always been a go to. I end the marathon with whose Harry Crumb. I don't know. I don't know if I was just not in the mood. I found it painfully unfunny.
And I always liked it. But there was something about it this go around where I was like, I don't like the character he's playing. Like I don't.
I just don't like the character. Like it's, it's, you know, the great thing about John candy is when he's being like, you know, my favorite part and my favorite thing that candy ever does when he makes a dumb joke and laughs, of course.
He does that in whose Harry Crumb when he's on the bus, cherry and coke. Yeah, cherry coke. Next to me, I got a cherry coke.
Stupid fucking laugh. You know that. And then like awful, like, like, not awful. Excuse me. Awkward John candy. Like when he has egg on his face. Like when he's walking at the beginning of Harry Crumb, he's like, hi, how are you doing? And the person ignores him to go nice people, nice people in this thing.
Like that's when he's the best. Right. But like, he doesn't do a lot of that in this. It's a lot of him doing like this. And it just doesn't play for me like this, this, this character who thinks he's very smart and being like, yes.
And this is my business, sir, you know, like, and he's like playing an investigator type. And it's just not funny. It's not that funny. Yeah, he has funny parts.
You know, it still makes me laugh when like Joe flattery when the coin comes out of the vent goes, lucky day. Come on, baby. You know, then candy barrels out of it. Whatever. The thing on the fan is still very funny.
But this on this go round for me, it played a lot more like delirious where I was just like, it's got funny. You love delirious.
I hate delirious. I do enjoy delirious. But even delirious, he's he's John candy in that he's.
Yeah.
You know, um, but but I was supposed to hear. Have you apologized to Karen Kulgera? No, I did think about calling her and saying, I'm really sorry. Yeah.
But I want to watch it again. I'm like, did I just get a bad viewing or something like, like even like like Jeffrey Jones is sort of wasted in it. He plays a creep and he's great at playing a creep. But like, he doesn't have anything funny to do.
True.
And he's great as the as the as the villainists. Right. But she's so unlikable that she's got no redeeming qualities or any, you know, Tim Thomerson's in it.
You kind of get excited to see him. But then like, he's just kind of here there. Like he doesn't get he's not given much. Yeah.
The movie is definitely serious in moments to what, you know, we're dealing with the kidnapping. You know, you see the girl who's been kidnapped in like a cell, like, like, they're like going to electrocute her and shit like.
Yeah, I remember them. It's weirdly dark.
Um, um, what's her name?
Oh, god damn it. The girl that what's her name? The daughter that helps him through the movie. What's she's, you know, from summer school and, um, uh, Shawnee Smith, Shawnee Smith. Yes.
She's delightful and charming as usual. Like she's playing like sort of the classic Shawnee Smith character.
Yeah, it's just not.
I don't know. I want to watch it again. It's one of the few comedies I still own on Blu -ray. I had a purging of comedies that I own. Uh -huh.
Yeah, a few years back like, because I was like a lot of these was like, I don't need to own anchor man. I love it, but I don't need to own it. Like, you know, and I really narrowed my comedy collection down to like things that like like John Waters and stuff like that where I was like, this is something that you put on because you want to experience.
Um, but who's Harry Krum is one of the ones that made the cut.
And I'm like, maybe I need to, I don't know. I want to give it another shot, but I'm sad to say this right now. No, that's, that makes me sad.
I, um, I, what was it?
Oh, I think, well, it was our own fan will pot of on letterbox who also gave it a pretty lukewarm review. I think people are seeing it on HBO Max where it is now.
I went to stars and stars for some reason at a bunch of candy movies streaming. So I just started going through them. Yeah, you know, one of the ones I would have, I would like to revisit planes trains, but I don't like to waste that outside of the holidays shouldn't.
It's a late night week of Thanksgiving film. Yeah, but, uh, I'll say this is a bonus. I did also watch, I did watch summer school also.
Love it.
Very funny, very much funnier than I thought it was going to be. Chainsaw and Dave are just great. I can't believe that's not Michael Imperial, with Michael Imperial, playing Chainsaw.
The whole time the sopranos were was on. I was like, that's the guy that played Chainsaw and it's not they look so much alike. It's crazy. The one guy reminds me of Trey Parker.
Yes, that's Dave, the guy, his name is Dave. Oh, I know who you mean this guy. Yeah, okay.
That kids got the best line in the, or the funniest thing in the movie when they call time on the exam at the end.
And as like the time is running out, he's like 10 seconds and he's going, he's just trying to fill in the bubbles. He's going, see, see, see.
As the time clicks down, he keeps going faster and then he goes, that's time. And he's going, see, see, see, see.
Yeah, it's a funny movie. I used to rent it a lot and I had never really seen horror.
And I remember being really traumatized by the horror makeup scene that is supposed to be at the big kind of comedic high point. I was terrified by it.
Yeah, I loved that scene as a kid. I used to want to do horror movie makeup because of that scene.
Yeah, that was my, that was what I thought I wanted to do when I grew up.
But they are remaking it far as I know there, or they have been for many years.
I'm sure it'll be great. I bet it'll be a machine gun Kelly has to do.
By the way, talking about a quintessential, where the role Mark Marin was, or sorry, Mark, Mark Harman, I mean, was such a mistake.
I know, but he's so unfunny. He's likable, but it's like for him to be the lead of a Carl Reiner comedy is so nuts to me.
I think he works well in that role. I think it's very likable, but I don't think he's a funny man. I think they're, you know, it's like a part for like an Owen Wilson or somebody who's got the same vibe, but who's funny to me.
I would watch your summer school remake starring Owen. I would even Luke even Luke. I was just going to say that I would love a summer school remake with Luke Wilson at the helm.
I would love that. That's perfect. He's perfect for it. Yeah.
Oh, that's a good. Oh, man, I'm going to think about that all day.
Like a Todd Phillips directed Luke Wilson starring summer school.
Yeah, because we're going to get it in a post -joker world. We would have gotten it 20 years ago, but still yeah, but that's Wilson at his best, like guy back against the wall.
Yeah, being taken advantage of can't stand up for himself is too nice. Like that's comedy gold right there.
Great.
Another movie student falls in love with them. Student played by the wife from according to Jim that was on Smith. Yeah.
And the star of chairman of the board with 15 year old falls in love with him is living with Harmon for three days in the movie.
Does she fuck them in the movie? I forget. No, they don't hook up. But Kirstie Ali who plays the right crush of Harmon.
She sees that she's living there and just says like, look, it's none of my business. I'm just saying. Yeah, you need to think about that you could be damaging because she thinks they're sleeping. Right.
None of my business. She says. Just think that you could damage this girl. Yeah. Yeah.
By the way, we didn't mention it in our screen at M, but I think we might be done with Bill Murray.
I think he's going down over some comedy made in this as these ends are a movie.
What? Because he said the thing about like.
Yeah. No, we don't know what it is yet. They pulled. They pulled production, which if they're doing that, shits bad. They were halfway done shooting the movie written and directed by Z starring Rogan and Murray.
Joe Rogan.
Seth, Seth, Seth, Rogan. We forget Joe Rogan was an actor in a decent one.
Anyway, good.
But yeah, they basically said halfway through production, they pulled the plug on the movie. They don't know if and when they're going to return it.
And they said the reps of a Z's want to make very clear. Everybody knows this was nothing he did, which is actually part of the press release.
Then a day later, they announced that Rogan also wasn't part of it. And then finally it was Bill Murray. So either somebody complained and they decided that the complaint was.
Not only sizable enough to reprimand him, but to shut down production and presumably lose money. So it must have been pretty bad, whatever happened.
Well, he just also got a bunch of shit for something he said in an interview, which was what it was.
I can't remember. It doesn't matter. Wow, that's a bummer. God damn it. That sucks.
You know that there's this really fun new IMDB type game. It's like a word ol' but for movies. I played it a couple days and then forgot about it.
But basically you ask which you get hints to have you guess some some movie. It's actually through box office mojo.
So you're like, there'll be like guess the number four movie at the box office the week of July 10th, 1985.
And you can get hints that lower your point totals. You want the lead? You want the fifth lead? I'm so good with supporting actors down the line down the bench.
I like to take like the fifth lead and go from there.
Because it's not that big a point deduction. But this week I found out about it on Twitter. And I watched this chain of people who I know really well.
Talk at length about how all of them felt that it was unfair because none of them had heard of the film, some are rental.
They're like this, this sucks. Nobody's heard of this movie. And everybody's like, yeah, honestly, not familiar with it at all.
And these are huge movie buffs. How did this thing get lost to the sands of time?
Candy's like first movie. It's not his first movie, but it's first. But you know, one of his first starring roles, you know, Paul Reiner directed.
That's not a fan of that film. That's a movie I want to like so much.
I know.
The stuff at the black family's house is so good.
Yeah.
The dog food spilling everywhere.
But really the back half is a boat race with no jokes.
The 80s were big on ending with a big quote comedic action sequence that has no comedy.
One crazy summer.
Exactly.
All builds to that goddamn boat race.
Yeah.
Stupid.
Gives a shit.
Let's talk about a movie that doesn't build too much of anything, but a very funny movie that was kind of lambasted at the time.
The cast wasn't even too keen on it for a while.
But now I think everyone kind of acknowledges it as a really good feature length.
I think it's okay for the kids in the hall who we started this show talking about kids in the whole brain candy, which is basically a sketch film tied together by a loose plot about anti depressants, you know, which were.
I don't know when they started, but they were certainly starting to become a big part of social consciousness at this time.
And really what's that's it's what's so great about the kids in the hall.
They've always been ahead of their time, but there's not a lot of stuff satirizing the anti -depressant movement and you almost can't say anything negative about anti depressants in this day and age.
But at the time they were like, no, there's something kind of fucked about this and they were right.
It feels more timely than ever.
It's not a perfect film of course is no sketch comedy film could be it's uneven of course.
And you sort of miss fold these presents because he's not really he's in it.
But he's a little bit on the fringes of it.
They were beef and hard as we talked about in a previous episode.
Yeah.
And I recommend highly recommend Paul Myers book about the kids in the hall, which was a great sort of history of them.
And I do want to see that documentary.
But as it is now you watch this thing and you're like, well, it's way funnier than most comedies being released today.
It's got a lot of laughs, a lot of great characters, the closeted gay dad character Scott Thompson plays is amazing, amazing, amazing.
Scott Thompson playing that type of guy is my favorite thing they've ever done in kids in the hall.
Like when he plays like a knuckleheaded straight guy, like the funniest thing in the fucking world to me.
I agree. Kevin MacDonald when they asked him to dance on the talk show and he does that dance was my biggest laugh.
And it was something I rewind a couple of times where he's trying to do like a sexy at walk pants.
Yeah, and it's playing Tom Tom Jones's version of kiss.
Yes.
And then the line that precedes it, the old man, I want to be a scientist, just like you, what a what a absurd joke.
Yeah, yeah.
It's strange.
It's a very funny movie.
Yeah, it's a pretty thin film, but it's very funny, which in my opinion, it should be a thin film.
You want to, you want to, you want to bear tree that you could just hang them to do all their things on, you know what I mean?
You want them to be the ornaments. So like, I, you know, but like I love the, oh, oh, that's what I was going to say, the weird thing is the only characters from the show are the,
yeah, it's, it's, it's McKinney and, and McCullough as the couple, where he's doing baby, don't shoot the messenger baby, you know, that when they do that couple where he like is a cheater and everything.
Yeah, but you got the cops are in there.
Oh, the cops.
Yeah, sorry.
You got cancer boys in there.
Cancer boys not on the show.
Cancer boys, a variation of the kid we were talking about.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Um, but I think that's it.
Here's my point.
What I thought was odd about that was you got the driver, the, the McKinney cab driver.
Yeah.
I was like, but I was, I was kind of like, well, why have any characters from the show like, like, right.
It was such a light sprinkling.
Yeah.
That, and, and, and they didn't pick renowned characters.
It's not like they put in crush your head guy or whatever.
Right.
They picked like very sort of esoteric under the radar characters as far as their show is concerned with the recovery.
You know, they didn't put in cabbage head.
You know what I mean?
So, um,
I thought that was an odd choice.
But the, a lot of the new characters they doing it are variations in ways of the old characters.
And, uh, yeah.
You're going to want to speak into the front of the mic.
You're speaking into the side of it.
Right.
I'm doing it because I was popping.
So I, no, no, it's going to, you're, go ahead.
I'd rather you pop then because the volume's going to be too fucked up.
Isn't this omnidirectional or whatever?
No, it's uni.
Okay.
Yeah.
I, I remember seeing it in high school when I had not seen any of the kids in the hall.
I caught up with them when they were running them on Comedy Central.
Um, but this was, if I'm not mistaken, my first exposure to the kids.
And for me at the time, I had a more mainstream taste.
You know, I was really into the Will Ferrell SNL and all that that was going on.
And, um,
I don't know.
I liked it.
But I remember being kind of let down watching it now.
It really is a fantastic sketch comedy movie.
They, they succeeded where many others haven't.
Mr.
Shows Run, Ronnie Run is bad.
Uh, yeah.
And that, that, that, that movie should have been what they did with this.
It should have been Bob and Dave playing a bunch of characters.
And it's not.
I just listened to Odin Kirk's, uh, audible book.
And he fully acknowledges that.
He's like, we, we made mistake after mistake in the pursuit of making this movie.
We don't like it.
We are embarrassed by it.
Etc.
But yeah, that one.
And then, um,
what's the other one?
Oh, the Tim and Eric movie is awful.
Not really a sketch movie.
But I like the Tim and Eric movie.
I don't think it's great.
All the way.
Yeah.
Look, it suffers from one a lot of comedy suffer from.
It starts real strong.
Yeah.
Then by the end, you kind of don't care about the resolution.
Right.
But I like, I actually do like the Tim and Eric movie.
I think Will Fortay in that movie is hilarious.
Um, but, uh,
you know, this is one of the same thing.
It's like, it's a pretty interesting plot.
I like that it's, it's about a pharmaceutical company that rushes out at anti depression.
Depression drug that Kevin McKinney's character more or less creates.
Right.
Uh,
And, you know, everybody's happy and it sweeps the nation.
And it's a cure for everybody's sadness.
And then all of a sudden things start going wrong.
And there's these terrible side effects.
And it's a, it's an interesting allegory on depression and,
and us trying to, you know, which was a big craze in the 90s get rid of any negative emotions.
Um, yeah.
And weirdly, when they, when they, when it hits its moral, which is like,
it's good to have downtime and bad time.
And you're going to be depressed sometime.
They don't, they don't joke that up.
It was, I was kind of like,
because kids in the hall always have a joke, you know, about something.
It's something they actually kind of cared about the message of this movie.
And you feel it, you know, they were right about anti -depressants.
Um,
the, the greatest scene in my opinion in the home,
that by two favorite scenes when, when Thompson's character.
Dave Foley plays the psychiatrist that's telling him he's gay.
And like, he needs to come out of the closet and he's going, and he's going,
you're gay.
You're gay.
I don't know how to say it.
Dogs know it.
You're gay.
And then, uh, Scott Thompson sits up and he goes, hey, doc,
you, uh, just go to sit here and spew psychiatric mumbo jump.
It'd be all day.
It's so funny.
It's so, it's so direct.
What do you think?
If there's nothing.
Nothing is being miscolored here.
Yeah.
I love that scene.
And I love.
When Scott Thompson's playing the old woman, Mrs. Horticure or whatever.
And it goes back to her happiest memory.
What an amazing scene that is.
Yeah.
And it's Foley as the son coming into Christmas walks in throws the gift
at her.
Yeah.
He goes, oh, I wonder what that is.
And he goes, it's a harmonic.
So funny.
He walks directly to the booze cart.
Poor Zawisky shoots it.
And then he goes, all right, we got to go.
That's the best memory.
And then they somehow top it with her worst memory, being handing a small child.
A collection of helium balloons that make the child fly into the sky.
So dumb.
But so, so funny.
I love them all.
You know, they really, they are one of the few groups.
And I very recently will over the pandemic watched every episode of the show.
They're one of the few groups where there just is not a weak link.
You know, like there are guys that they're, you know, certainly I have favorites.
But there's no one who, when they're in a solo sketch, you're like, God damn it.
They all are different and interesting and funny and great.
I just love.
Yeah.
The other, oh, the other amazing scene too is a.
We had McKinney's like, my father suffered from depression and it shows the flashback of him as the kid and the kids got the currently afro.
Yeah.
And then McKinney plays his dad.
And he walks up.
He's like, can you clean the house today?
Like your old man told you he's like, yeah, he's like, yeah, just clean the car.
He's like, yeah, he goes, what about the good?
You give the gun a good clean.
Yeah, they're all like playing their dads, which is so, so satisfying.
And all their dads are clearly just depressed off the hall, like, which is why they're in comedy and great stuff, great stuff.
My hog is, is up for, for kids in the whole brain candy.
And you can now get it on Blu -ray, which just means they took the DVDs and put them to Blu -ray cases, I believe.
Yeah, they're, they're, if you are able to get like a $2 DVD at the DVD store used, do that.
I bought the new Blu -ray for 15, which isn't a bad price.
But the, the Joe and I were mocking the DVD menu, something hard.
It's a production still of the guys.
And then it's like, click play movie or eject disc.
Those are the two options.
There's no, there's no trailer.
There's no deleted scenes.
There's no anything.
Nothing.
My hog is up.
Great movie if you've never seen it.
And the return of the kids in the hall will be on May 5th, I believe, on Amazon Prime.
I will be there.
And you should be there too.
My name is Patrick Walsh, the Patrick Walsh on Instagram and Twitter.
We'll be back next time.
I'm not sure with what, but we will.
And my solo movie corner will be dropping Saturday morning.
Throwing everything out.
No way.
Jotaro is a comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Again, just pushing this, taping I'm doing shooting my new hour special.
In Houston, Texas May 19th and 20th.
It's a Thursday and Sunday one show each night.
Very intimate shows.
Very limited amount of tickets.
Please come out.
I'm doing this whole thing on the arm.
I'm doing this myself.
off, no network or hiring nothing. So your support is even more appreciated than usual.
Please come out, come and take it fest, which is being held at the secret group in Houston,
Texas. And then on the 20th and 21st, I'll be at the creaking cave in Austin, just running
the same hour and not recording it, though. That said, folks, we'll see you next time and
we'll see you in hell.