How do you do?
Helians, it's your
bonus app
for the month of uh
What month is it August?
It's August. It's a hot August morning.
Pat and I are here at 9 .45 in the morning.
It's already 80 fucking degrees outside.
Just absolutely terrible.
I find myself wearing
long sleeve shirts and jackets
just to kind of trigger it.
I was talking with our buddy Trevor about that the other night
at the bar.
I was like, I noticed we're both wearing jackets.
What's going on?
We had the exact same reason.
Sick of this.
Want to try to maybe
fool old man weather.
But then you just wind up hot.
It always got like a light spritz on my upper back.
Yeah, you know, you go to a party.
A nice young lady comes in for a hug.
You see the face kind of fall
as it presses into a damp.
And you appear to be wearing
woolen pants.
No, these are actually quite light.
They are. They are.
It's going to say that that can't be.
I'm, I made a big part of it is just
today is going to be uncomfortable and bad.
Why don't I just embrace it?
I'll be wearing steel wool like a monk
by the end of the month.
Torture myself.
It is a rare morning edition.
I'm enjoying a cup of
morning Joe with my morning Joe Joe Rosa.
Hello, Pat.
How are you?
I'm good. I went over to the Duncan D's this morning.
Duncan Donuts.
We get Starbucks all the time at work.
And frankly, I'm sick of the taste of it.
I think it's a bad coffee.
Especially to be America's number one choice.
I like Starbucks.
I can make, I can make better at home.
You know, like when they got the diner pot
in the uh...
the uh break room.
I like that better. I don't know.
What type of coffee is going in that diner pot?
Yeah, that's true. Maybe it's really good coffee.
Now Joe wanted hot, I assumed.
Yes.
He said uh...
Get me a black coffee, black like my soul.
I took the similarly one further
and got a black ice coffee
like my soul.
And they gave it to me in a bucket.
Yeah, that's a big uh...
For some reason the ice coffee always comes in a bigger cup.
I guess they're like, oh, because of the ice.
I just feel like it's another way they're ripping you off
with the regular coffees.
It's too much to hold.
And frankly, like this is...
I don't feel good about the environment.
Would you say it's to this giant plastic monstrosity?
Would you say it's uh...
hard to handle?
Like the black rose?
Yeah.
Pretty little thing in my life.
It's not gigantic.
It's a mama ham.
Joe hard to handle now, yes, around.
There's your on with the Joe for two.
And then I'll reverse it.
We don't do those segments on this.
But let's pretend I said all with the Joe at the beginning.
Let me see if I have sip peeled and win.
Couldn't be a grosser three words together.
Sip peel wins.
Disgusting.
The girl wrote good luck on my cup.
I think she probably was into me.
She probably doesn't do that for anybody else.
Yeah.
It says please enjoy any size iced tea for $1 after 11 a .m.
Jackpods?
Any size.
Now do you think there's a bigger size than that?
No, there's just small medium and large.
That's large.
That's a large, yeah.
I set them both on the roof of my car to get my wallet out.
And a light breeze almost took this ten pound iced coffee right onto my head.
It's too big.
I'd like to elaborate on the black like my soul joke.
It's harder and harder these days to come up with black coffee jokes.
Right.
You just can't do the, I like the coffee like I like my women.
It's been done too many times.
And maybe my favorite is an airplane with the little boy.
Yeah.
I know the little girl.
Yes.
She goes black like my man.
Yeah.
She's like nine.
Every grade.
I'm always ready to PG.
And also can tears a giant pair of tits.
One of the rare PG movies with tits.
They show tits an airplane.
Huge jiggling breasts.
When the plane is going through turbulence.
A woman runs a, runs through topless and like just shakes them back and forth and then runs out of frame.
Really?
And a PG nerve.
You don't remember them.
Um, I guess I probably do, but didn't realize the movie was PG.
I think I always thought airplane was rated R.
It feels like a rated R movie.
It would have been 13, but they didn't have it yet.
Okay.
The, uh, speaking of 13.
Actually now though, I don't think you can get boobs in a PG 13.
I think that's an automatic R, which is insane.
Uh, it gets stricter and stricter.
Uh, it used to be that you could get one or two fucks off in a PG 13.
I think you still can.
As long as it's not, I fucked her.
It's gotta be like fuck, whatever.
I have a friend who recently was diagnosed with breast cancer.
Uh, which is terrible.
Very unfortunate.
She's a lovely, lovely person.
And, uh, she posted a picture of herself having like a ceremony.
A ceremony with all her friends there.
And she was topless in the photo, but very tastefully done and fairly, fairly covered to be honest with you.
But it was kind of like a last celebration of her boobs.
Mm hmm.
Um, it was, it was a moving, a special photo, very clearly, very important to her and to her life.
Got flagged, uh, by someone on Instagram.
For an appropriate content.
Jesus, look at that.
Why does anybody care?
It, it boggles the mind.
I mean, even, even if, even if you are for whatever reason, uh, grossly offended by that photo,
why do you care enough to try to get the person kicked off?
Like, who is so offended?
They go, I can't stand seeing it in my feed.
You know, and also follow.
Yeah.
It's.
Oh, it's a hell of a, it's a hell of a week.
I mean, we're back in a trailer hitch up to the apocalypse.
And people are flagging a picture because they saw a nipple.
Nipple, they probably suckled on just 30 years ago.
Different nipple.
They're moms, but you know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's, uh, it's, it's, it's, it's, uh, I don't, I don't understand where the priorities are anymore.
The, uh, it is, I mean, when you're saying a hell of a week, I assume you're following the news.
Yeah.
We don't have to get deep into politics.
The Trump thing where it's like, he praises the one guy that just goes down with the criminal activity.
He doesn't, doesn't roll over on the other guy.
It's like, no, he's fucked up too.
He's like, he's a bum.
He tweeted this morning as if he's, uh, you know, shaky green.
He was like, hey, if you need a good lawyer, might I not recommend Michael Cohen?
Like what?
What?
You're going to jail.
You're all going to jail.
I mean, here's why I don't think anybody's, well, I mean, those guys are going to go to jail.
But the, I mean, people forget this during the, uh, Reagan administration.
Uh, it rattled Reagan.
I believe it was, it was something like 25 people were indicted from his administration on criminal charges.
It was some insane number.
And yet you talked to, you talked to the average Republican about Reagan.
They say it was the greatest president of all time.
They love them.
It seemed to just kind of coast through it.
Yeah.
He did two terms.
He was like, I honestly didn't know the 25 people in his, he got a, yeah, there were a lot of people in his organization that, uh, that were indicted on different criminal charges and whatnot.
Um, and I believe one of the most heavily investigated was the attorney general at that time.
Do you go out and let him?
I don't remember if that's who it was.
I'm the time.
Very bad at history.
I think he was in the 60s, wasn't he?
No, that was what's his face that dressed up in the dresses.
Jay Edgar Hoover.
Yeah.
70s maybe.
I'd look it up, but I don't care.
I got most of my, uh, knowledge of that time from the movie, Dick, starring Kirsten Dunst, and I stars and stripes bikini.
What, what is that movie about?
It's actually a really, really smart, well done movie when they had like a teen movie a week throughout the late 90s, early 2000s.
It was one of the bright spots.
Kirsten Dunst and Michelle Williams.
And they're like two dumb teenage girls who get swept up in watergate.
And they have like all these great comedic character actors playing all the key figures like Dave Foley and a bunch of people.
Oh, that's right.
Didn't Bruce McCullough direct that?
I believe.
No, Andrew Fleming, who did him with two.
But Bruce McCullough is in it as Woodward in Bernstein as one of them.
I would not be surprised if everything Joe and I have said detail wise in the last five minutes has been wrong.
From, from film to politics, I don't think any of it is right.
Just Wikipedia, the movie, Dick.
Uh, this is a, this is a free one.
So we don't have our usual slave.
This is actually the option of the detail.
The free one.
This is actually the one that everybody pays for.
This could be more opposite of the free one.
It feels free to me because we are not tied to any, you know, free in a spiritual sense.
In a spiritual sense, I feel there are no rules here about no rules just right.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can be whatever you want here.
Have you been watching the, uh, well, you don't have shutter, do you?
I don't have shutter.
Uh, I've been watching on shutter the, uh, and this is not a movie corner because we don't do segments on this.
I'm just, just kind of something to talk about.
Like Bonnie Rape.
Uh, I've been watching the Joe Bob Briggs last drive in.
That's what I would get shutter for.
Yeah.
So I have shiver.
I have shake and I have shimmy east.
But I don't have shutter.
This is a man that writes jokes for a living shimmy east.
It wouldn't have been a great joke without that east.
Yeah, I know.
This is why I can walk you through the process.
A pro.
Yeah.
The, uh, I'm serious.
I mean that.
Um, the, uh, it's too early to a moat, but I did mean that.
Anyway, thank you, Joe.
You're welcome.
He went on a, uh, I was watching the sleep away camp one yesterday.
Love sleep away camp.
He goes on this, uh, goes on a tie rate about the governor in North Carolina who wouldn't allow for the unisex bathrooms.
Yeah.
And, uh, breaks the entire thing down into an Andy Griffith episode of how that governor
was Barney Fife instead of being Andy Griffith.
Yeah.
And just, you know, and just being like, well, you know, Walden likes to wear dressing.
Nothing wrong with that Barney.
You know, I get it.
Sounds beautiful.
And he really broke it down like it was a really, really great take on it.
Yeah.
And it was a perfect analogy to, to, to Andy Griffith's show.
Does he show the movies unedited?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And he takes, he pops in every half hour or something.
I bet it's a, every 20 minutes maybe.
All right.
You know, maybe every 15.
It's, you know, it's sort of around commercial break time, but it's not too frequent.
Right.
Uh, yeah.
I mean, I think it's, I mean, is it worth getting all of shutter for that?
I mean, I, I, I, well, you love shutter.
How much is shutter?
I think shutter is worth it period.
Yeah.
Uh, and I think if you were a fan of that show, then, yeah, you'd very much enjoy the
13 episodes of this and wouldn't say, God damn it.
Why did I subscribe?
Um, shutter's to watch him, but then I would get frightened by the movies and turn it on.
I was a kid.
It's a good lineup on this one too.
It's, it's tourist trap.
It's sleep way camp.
It's, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, hell razor.
It's, um,
there's a couple like, like, there's a couple like hell razor in there that are just really good solid,
sort of mainstream horror movies, but still have that drive and quality.
And then some of them are like, you know, like legend of boggy creek.
Some of them are truly right, sort of drive in exploitation type flicks.
Uh, but it's good.
I, I think shutter's great.
I'll get it, I'll get it and watch that for sure.
I think that sounds like a funny evening.
Yeah, well, it would be 13 movies.
It'd be 26 hours of your life.
Did he stay up?
Or they probably just shot.
No, when they first did it, he did it live, live marathon.
Yeah.
Old man too.
He's 65.
Yeah.
Do you know he plays, uh, the guy in casino.
I do.
Yeah.
I told you that probably two weeks ago on this very podcast.
You were like, he's in casino when I said, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He's the guy who, I'll check the tape.
You check the tape.
They'll be missing like Nixon, because I'm a corrupt son of a bitch.
Um, Joe and I saw golden girls live.
Oh, yeah.
With a Z.
I forgot.
For, uh, drag queens and then a midget.
I'm sorry.
Little person who, uh, portrayed, uh, a girl scout.
And also a short man from the episode where Betty White dates a little purse.
Little purse.
Yes.
Um, in, in my opinion, it's the funniest show I've seen in years.
I was scream laughing.
It was very funny.
The B Arthur for God's sake.
They, they actually had like kind of a burly guy.
It was like, come on, Rose.
And what, if you, if you ever see it, and I will see it again,
the real secret of it.
It's all funny, but the secret is to keep your eye on the B Arthur,
which is to me, the secret of the show.
I didn't agree with that.
Love the B Arthur.
B Arthur's my favorite on the actual show.
Yeah.
I thought she was great in this show too.
Yes.
But I did not think she was the show stealer.
I thought Betty White was the show stealer in this show.
That is an acquaintance of mine, Drew Drogie, who is a very, very funny comedian.
I thought he really ran away with it in a, in a, in a special way.
He was sort of parodying an aspect of Betty White that you don't necessarily think about.
But then as soon as he started doing it, you were like, that's perfect.
Yeah.
Where it was just kind of like a, almost, almost hammy.
Which she is a little bit.
Yeah.
No, I, I thought he was, he was my favorite.
It was great.
But I'm not, not can be.
He was great too.
I just, I just didn't think that.
Yes.
That didn't, that didn't define the show for me.
That's all.
I thought Be Arthur, who I, I acknowledge was a man.
I, I'm no, no, I, the room, a, room a clan of hand.
Blanche.
Wait, the person playing Blanche?
The person, or you mean actual room of clan of hand?
The character of the man playing room of clan of hand.
I was, I was attracted to.
Uh, he was a very attractive woman.
Yes.
Uh, and then the Sophia,
Sam Pancake, who has been in like every sitcom of all time.
I thought was funny.
Our friend Jimmy Smagula.
Bridgers who sat next to you.
Oh, oh, oh.
I thought you were saying Sam Pancake's real name was.
No, but Jimmy thought, uh, the, the Sophia could have been a little more accurate.
But I don't need accuracy for these performance.
The, uh, look, I felt like a little exaggerate.
I thought she was great too, but my, uh, the reasons I enjoyed, uh, uh,
Betty and Rue so much were that they played them.
As, as very exaggerated versions of the, um,
they were impressed, they were impressions.
Yes.
It was like if you saw a comedian do an impression of these people,
that's what it would be.
Uh, I thought that B and, um,
they had the B Arthur and Kabuki makeup, which I thought was a wise choice.
I thought B and, um, uh, Sophia were a little,
well, there was a little, a little too much winking to the camera for me.
Like every time Sophia would make one of her great quips,
like she'd like wink to the audience.
Sure.
I got you, you know, like, like it was funny, but I just,
I kind of liked the more the, the over overly dramatic portrayals of the characters.
Right.
But I did like it when they would say like a true clunker,
as every Golden Girls has a few clunkers.
And they would just look out at the audience and be like,
uh, like we didn't write this kind of thing.
I liked that vibe.
I didn't care for that part of it.
I felt like it was an unfair knock.
They showed a period accurate commercials.
Yeah.
They were great for AIDS chocolate.
The chocolate that makes you lose weight.
Unbelievable.
Still unbelievable.
How did that come out in the 80s?
Uh, and I still find myself telling people about that who've never heard about it.
It's really something to see.
This is people who've like, I lost 20 pounds.
I've got AIDS and like clicking their heels.
And they spell it with a Y because they know that there's a horrible disease called AIDS.
Yeah.
I think this was right before it was officially mainstream.
And they put the company under.
I think I would imagine so.
Uh, they also had white diamonds.
Was it with Taylor, which my sister and I used to crack up at how cheesy those were?
Yeah, those session by Calvin Klein.
Uh, Bill Cosby reaching out to a woman from a refrigerator being like, come on.
Give me some of that pudding.
Very disturbing.
It was just a great, a great time.
It was a great show.
I, I really had a lot of fun.
Now wait, who's Sam Pancake?
What's he in?
Sam Pancake has done guest spots on like most sitcoms.
Would I know him?
Can you stand your will and graces?
Your, your, I'm sure a Frazier.
I'm sure.
Can you tell his, his, his real name is Sam Pancake?
Perhaps a stage name, but I mean, that's what he goes by on the shows.
Yeah.
All right, hold on.
I'm going to look him up.
He's a funny guy because he did look familiar.
He was funny.
Uh, the, yeah, it's, it's a show I highly recommend.
It was sold out all weekend, but it's coming back to LA in January if you're here.
Uh, that's, that's who plates of feed.
It's that guy.
Yes, correct.
All right.
I know who that guy is.
Yeah, you've seen him.
And, and he's 50 years old.
Looks great.
Yeah.
Well, uh, gay don't...
gray.
You know, the old expression.
He's been in tons of stuff.
He's very fun.
Curb enthusiasm.
He, remember, he was the guy at the shirt store.
He thought, well, that fact there's a hundred scenes of curb where he's like trying to return a shirt.
But it was one of the early ones where he goes return a shirt and the guy, they get in the big old occasions.
Very funny.
All right.
He was also apparently in space station 76.
No, what's that?
I don't know.
Okay.
Uh, over her dead body.
I'm just reading off some of his...
I remember over her dead body.
Credits here.
Kitchen, confidential, stern, Bradley Cooper.
Okay.
How was that?
It was a short -lived show that was about Anthony Bourdain actually.
It was?
Yeah.
Now did you see burnt with Bradley Cooper as yet another bad boy chef?
That's what I thought it was.
That was a terrible, terrible move.
Was kitchen confidential a comedy?
Yeah.
It was like a single cam fox comedy, probably 2006, right before wedding crashers, Bradley Cooper.
Wow.
All right.
Got good reviews, canceled quickly.
But it was based on the Bourdain memoir.
Okay.
Now this is before he was dead.
This is before he was dead, significantly.
Okay.
Now Joe, why did you tell Asia Argento to do what she did?
That's...
God damn it.
That's what I was trying to get to earlier and I couldn't think of a name.
When I said speaking of 13.
Well, this is a wild one.
I mean, this is truly wild.
Have you seen the picture of her with the boy with a set up?
Yes, I saw it.
And in a statement, in a statement, released by the Harvey Weinstein team, defense team...
So, defense team...
Take it with a grain of salt.
Take it with a thousand milligrams of salt.
I'd go as far as to say this.
Possibly, quite probably, the only statement ever given by the Harvey Weinstein defense team that we might agree with.
Okay.
This displays a stunning level of hypocrisy.
Well, I can't believe they even commented on it.
I know, but...
It's not like he's the only one.
He claimed...
Weinstein claimed is...
I'm not defending Weinstein.
But he claims that he is...
He's steadily claimed that he has not done anything non -consensual.
So, this was their chance to jump on, of course.
But especially with her, because she led the charge, he was very adamantly saying...
None of this was non -consensual.
Pen house...
Who am I right for?
Yeah, as you know.
They...
And pose for them.
I pose for them, yeah.
Well, I stunt dick for them.
They use other guys' faces, but I'm the stand -in for the cock shot.
Is that you on the legs over your head pointing to the B -hole shots?
Yes, yes.
Okay.
It's my butt asshole, and then they put another person's face on it.
All right.
I thought I recognized it, but I won the big fight.
Anyway, they released the article written by...
I forget the woman's name, but she's...
She's actually the woman that got into the text fight with Michael Che, and it was on page six.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She wrote an article called Toxic Femininity, that really went after...
It was very supportive of the Me Too movement, but it really went after AGR Agento.
And Rose McGowan saying, these people are bad for this cause.
These are exploitative sensationalists, and they're playing dirty and whatever.
And she got a lot of shit for it, obviously.
And then two weeks after it drops, this AGR Agento thing comes out.
And I was like, oh, wow.
Well...
And it came from the New York Times, too.
It wasn't like this came from some fucking...
Yeah.
And then her cover of...
Or, you know, we don't know.
It's all a legend, but she was like Anthony Bourdain paid him off.
It was his idea.
Oh, God.
It's like you're gonna throw your boyfriend who killed himself a month ago under the bus.
By the way, people are kind of saying you may have triggered such a thing.
Although you have to, of course, have a level of depression that would bring you to there.
Let's not open that can of worms.
There's a lot of dangerous territory we're circling here.
It's not fine.
Asia, Argento, Rose McGowan.
The issue is, yes, these people don't seem 100 % mentally sound.
Rosanne, another example.
But these are people who were sexually abused.
That makes you not mentally sound.
Allegedly, though.
Allegedly and allegedly and allegedly.
But like...
Here's my thing with it.
If you're gonna say, if Asia Argento is gonna run around saying we got to believe victims.
Yes.
And we need to listen to the victims when they speak up.
And we're gonna say, at all costs, we should believe these people.
Right.
And then her first line of defense is, this kid's lying.
I didn't do that.
I mean, it's insane.
Lena Dunham doing the same shit, although she wasn't involved in it.
What's Lena Dunham saying?
This was a while back.
One of her writers who also wrote for crashing as a matter of fact.
But this guy, writer for girls,
it seemed like allegedly had a thing for younger women.
He had sex with a 17 year old girl got caught.
Lena Dunham immediately takes to Twitter after years of saying, believe the victim.
And says, I know I've said, believe the victim in the past.
But I know this guy so well.
And I know he couldn't have done it because she worked with him.
Yeah.
She had no other proof.
She just said, I know he couldn't have done it.
Well, and look.
And again, it's all legit on every side, on all sides.
Yeah.
On all sides, it's alleged.
Good people are in drugs.
So it's all legit.
I'm not saying I believe or don't believe anybody.
I'm just saying it's a very, very confusing shit storm here.
Doesn't help the fact that Robert Rodriguez,
who was a big supporter of Rosemite Garwin,
she threw him under the fucking bus.
And then he had to come out after publicly supporting her against Weinstein
and saying this guy's a scumbag.
He had to come up publicly and be like, she is not telling the truth about the situation
that she's describing from the Grindhouse movie.
She knew for a year that there was a nude scene in the thing.
She knew for a year that Harvey Weinstein was producing this.
She knew for a year that she was gleefully involved in this.
Right.
And then now 10 years later, she's saying she was side -swiped and all that.
And he goes, look, I'm sorry.
Like it's just not true.
Like I didn't do that to her.
Yeah.
That doesn't help.
You know, it doesn't help.
No.
So it's, you know, it's less.
He's lying people.
We don't know.
Well, this is the thing now.
Now we're going to get into this thing where people, it's going to become,
it's going to become the right versus the left with this, just like with that thing.
This is what they want.
They want nothing to seem real so that every allegation seems fake.
Well, and this is what will happen is people that want to,
people that now have been like chopping at the bit to,
I think it's champion to, to defend a guy like Weinstein,
even though he's gross and most likely a fucking arch criminal,
bare minimum Harvey Weinstein is raped by women.
I mean, it's, I mean, I would think it's got to be with the numbers of accusations that have come out, right?
So it's, it's like Cosby.
It's like, there's too much smoke here for there not to be fun.
Yes, I believe all of Cosby's accused.
Yeah.
I mean, so anyway, the,
the people that are chopping at the bit that just want to Weinstein
to be innocent because they want to get a point for the men.
Now are going to use this as their ammunition to say,
well, see everybody's full of shit.
Right.
And then there's going to be women that double down for Asia Argento
that don't call out the hypocrisy on her side.
And it's going to become like the politics.
It's going to become a far left and a far right contingent
that are screaming and making all the noise about this.
And then there's going to be people like us who are sort of in this middle area
where it's like, guys, we're not saying don't believe anybody.
But we're saying we also can't not say that all the time, too.
Like, it's got to go both ways here.
So when Michelle Obama will do an interview and say, hell,
and then Trump will be like, can you believe this disgusting bitch pig
said, hell, you know, like, and, and his support is like, yeah.
Yeah.
It's, uh, it's the darkest time I'm, I'm familiar with.
Uh, I've never seen anything like it.
No.
I don't know that I'll never ever see anything like it again.
But I will say for the rest of your life,
I will say I've predicted it for years.
Yeah.
I know it was coming.
And all my friends told me to lighten up.
Joe, why are you so down?
The world's not a bad place.
Welcome to the shit you fucks.
Yeah.
It is fun to see all these people like, I just can't seem to find a happy moment.
And I'm like, yeah, where have you been?
I feel like the guys have been open.
I feel like the guy that said the fucking sulfur tablets
and waterproof flashlight in his, in his closet.
Yeah.
All this time that everybody made fun of.
And now everything's going down.
And I have pure water and light.
Well, we're like Michael Gross and Reba McIntyre and Tremors.
They tease us for having a bunker full of elephant guns.
Yes.
But then, grab woods come up from under the ground.
And then, and then, you know, they tease you for having, yeah, loaded weapons all around your house.
And all of a sudden, they say Jamie Kennedy's in this next one.
And then you're glad you have the gun.
I did a show with him the other day for yourself, not for Jamie Kennedy.
I'm sure he's a nice man.
How was he?
He seemed nice enough.
I guess I didn't really talk to him.
Okay.
I got kind of drunk.
Yeah.
Big surprise.
And at one point, I ran into him on the way to the bathroom.
I go, hey man, perhaps on Tremors, man.
Good for you.
Now, weren't you worried he might take that as a slam?
No, I was saying it as a compliment.
The movies aren't my thing, as you know, but I think that's cool.
Anytime somebody gets to be a sort of iconic franchise like that.
Sure.
He's like, thanks, man.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, we're good.
We're going to do another one, man.
So, you know, he was very thankful.
All right.
He's a nice guy.
How much money did Jamie Kennedy have?
I asked him that.
Did you?
Yeah.
And he told me, he gave me a number.
He asked me not to share it.
But I mean, scream.
Jamie would have made 30K for the entire run of a show on MTV, the lowest paying network
of all, where he did everything.
I bet he walked away with a million dollars total.
His ex -factor show wasn't on MTV.
That was on like, that was on like the CW.
And what was the CW before?
Well, saying the PN or whatever.
Yeah, I would say one of those things.
He made a million for three seasons, probably.
And he doesn't say my guy who during the late 90s and 2000s was smart with his money.
So making a bunch of wild speculations and generalizations.
I would say he's got around a half million dollars.
All right.
But he might be one of those guys who surprised you and hasn't mentioned.
Well, I'm forgetting Malibu's most wanted.
I'm forgetting.
He did a lot of big movies that were critical failures.
Son of the mask.
But like, you know, he definitely got paid for those fucking things.
The son of the mask.
He's got two million dollars.
He was also dating Jennifer Love Hewitt, don't forget.
He might have some.
Maybe he got a few bills off of her, you know.
Beautiful.
I haven't seen her in years.
Still looks fantastic.
But Jenny and I, you know, when we were kids, we were just two crazy kids in love.
Running around this town.
Just having a just having a wild day of dreams and wild nights of passion.
And I love to hear.
And we lost track after somewhere along the ghost whisperer.
This is probably the most important time to say allegedly.
Because Jennifer Love Hewitt will sue if she Googles Joe.
And here's the, this happened.
I have no involvement with Jennifer Love Hewitt.
Anthony Bourdain paid me to say this.
So we're going to talk on today's show about a movie.
Now we've seen a while ago.
But now it is already hitting on demand and video.
I think it's out.
VHS.
Beta.
It's a film called Gotti about the life of John Gotti.
As you'd expect.
You want to get there.
Where you want to just mention it and come back to Atlanta.
Come back to it.
All right.
I mean, we're not going to have a ton to say about Gotti.
That's true.
I think trying to squeeze more than a 20 minute review out of this thing is asking for trouble.
Yeah.
It is a troubled film.
I did a tweet about Gotti that triggered a tweet from John Gotti's daughter directly to me,
which was a real thrill.
What did she write again?
Let me find it.
It was something about the, well,
we should save it for when we talk about the movie.
We'll save it.
I'll have it.
Because I remember now it's a reference.
Yeah.
It's a reference to a part in the movie.
The, uh, I was, uh, forgive me, forgive me, my friend.
I hung out, uh, oh, actually, never mind.
Kurt, his name is Kurt Ziegler.
Okay.
Is it the, the, the wrestler?
No, that's Dolph Ziegler.
Dolph Ziegler.
Kurt Ziegler is a fan of ours.
Okay.
Uh, he's a part man.
He's, uh, I was in DC doing shows recently.
Yes.
And, uh, Kurt came up to me after the late show Saturday and he said, hey, man,
I don't know if you remember writing this to me, but I told you I was going to come see your show in Pittsburgh.
And I was going to drive like three hours or something to see it.
Yeah.
And you said don't do that because it's a Sunday night show.
There could only be 10 people there.
I don't want you to drive all that way for it.
And, and it was a small show because there was a huge game going on in Pittsburgh, huge dealers game.
Uh, so he showed up at this show in DC.
So he drove two hours.
Okay.
See the show.
Uh, said he had a great time.
Thank God.
Because that's a little, you know, you're a little worried like, well, Jesus.
Right.
Hope you enjoyed it.
But anyway, I spent a lot of time with him after the show.
We hung out.
We had a drink.
Uh, on him, of course, I wasn't buying it.
No, I bought him a drink.
Uh, actually, I didn't buy him a drink.
A lovely 21 year old woman who was at the show bought me a drink and then bought him a drink.
Okay.
And offered to buy us both drinks.
Uh, so thank you to her, whoever she was.
I didn't return the favor.
She went back inside to watch the third show, which was an 11 o 'clock show that I was not part of.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I didn't have a chance to.
Um, but, uh,
You know, we hung out.
You know, we, we discussed Joe's scary stuff.
One thing leads to another.
We were married.
Yeah.
Um, uh, Vegas is a, it's just a hop skip at a jump on a, on a plane.
We should go again soon.
I have an itch.
Uh, so do I.
And I believe it came from that prostitute.
Anyway, Kurt was good to meet you.
It was nice hanging out.
We had fun.
And, uh, I'm shocked and thrilled and, and, uh, uh,
Delighted.
Delighted is another word I'd add to it.
Be me.
Appreciative.
Yep.
Grateful.
Humboldt.
Okay.
By the fact that we have fans that, uh, get this giddy about this show.
I mean, he was.
I told him a thing I was going to do for scary stuff and literally just like we're talking.
And I was just like, oh, I should do that as a scary stuff.
And I wrote it.
And he was like, oh, this is cool, man.
I can't, like, people who have anybody looks at this show like that.
It's very nice.
The, um, the new network.
I assume the transition has gone well.
Uh, I love reading the comments and the arts.
Sometimes it takes me a while.
I just saw a hog house picture that was very cool by, I believe, Will Potor.
Um, and the Facebook page is always a treat.
I save it.
I don't check it all the time.
I save it for when I'm feeling particularly angry.
And then I go, oh, I had people like me.
And I met a very lovely young woman after the earlier show that night.
Okay.
But it was very brief.
I talked her for a moment.
And they had some pictures of you and some, some fans up on the Instagram.
Oh, cool.
She took off.
I'm, I'm blanking on her name only because we didn't hang out for very long.
Yeah.
We didn't hang out at all.
We just kind of talked for a few minutes and then she left.
Um, but she was lovely too.
And she was, I believe somebody told me they were coming out to LA for the show.
Awesome.
Um, are we sold out?
I have no idea.
Oh, I don't know.
Yeah.
Well, you know, check it.
What do you think I, you think I care about the numbers, Pat?
That's not why I do this.
Now, if I can touch one fan.
I'll tell you, when I meet a fan who, who loves this show dearly, I liken it to the way a father must feel when he says I can't believe a boy looks at me and calls me daddy.
Sure.
Uh, and then also I can't believe I have a son.
Folks.
Yeah.
Um, what's that?
Oh, made in America.
Dancing.
Goldberg.
That's a PG 13 that's got a fuck in it.
Yes.
Yeah.
I remember that not being great.
Really?
The Ted Danson whoopee Goldberg will Smith movie wasn't fantastic.
Is that when they were together or when they like where they met and hit it off?
Uh, I think that's when they met.
I find, I found it disgusting at the time.
The amount of jokes like late night jokes about how could Ted Danson be with whoopee Goldberg.
But they still sort of continue.
Like you'll see on Twitter, like never forget Ted Danson day to whoopee Goldberg.
It's like these.
Yeah, they're, they're age appropriate adults who are both funny.
Um, and charming who found love.
The only reason you're having some issue with this is racism.
These people are all disgusting hypocrites.
Yeah.
They get out there and they say you shouldn't fat shame yet.
Every one of them will make their fucking Kirsty Alley jokes and all that shit.
Of course.
They're all completely full of shit.
Um, and will be Goldberg at a very memorable moment at comic relief.
Uh, she went, she told everybody to shut the fuck up about Ted Danson doing the blackface joke at her roast.
Yes.
And she said, I remember she said on comic relief, she goes,
this wasn't about him doing something important.
This was about, I was fucking somebody I wasn't supposed to be fucking.
Yeah.
I remember that very clearly.
I actually forgot that.
He came out, was it a televised roast?
No, it was a, it was a Friars Club roast.
And he comes out in blackface.
It's her roast.
She's being roasted.
What jokes did he make off of that?
I don't know, but he's dating her.
It's like, this shit drives me nuts.
It's like if, if, if you're the closest person in my life, I eat my girlfriend.
Right.
And I know that you'll think a joke is funny.
And it's your event where we're roasting you.
And I do that joke.
Who the fuck is anybody at that point to say, hey, that's not right.
It's like, no, this isn't about you.
This is me to the person I love right now.
Yeah.
And we're in a goddamn restaurant.
I mean, generally you're not, uh, conveying that love through blackface.
Look, but I do see I come from a strange family.
Papa.
Come here.
I've made up my face.
Um, well, let's get to God.
Let's get God as should have been the poster tagline for this movie.
Get God.
I would have liked it more.
So my tweet was, and I think this moment from God, he really sums up the film.
There is a scene in God.
He wear God.
He's boss.
Stacy Keach tells God.
A truly the cat.
Let's just before you read this.
Sure.
The casting.
It's, it's, it's.
I love Travolta.
It's hard enough to get your head around Travolta playing a mobster.
Yeah.
Even though Travolta is an Italian name, you don't look at John Travolta and think street wise mobster.
No.
They push it even further.
They got Stacy Keach.
The most non -italian man that has ever lived playing his boss, which made no sense to me.
I will say Keach was one of the few who brought a little class of the proceedings.
I like Keach.
Yeah.
He wasn't bad.
Uh, there is a scene in God.
He wear God.
He's boss.
Stacy Keach tells God.
A truly electric John Travolta.
And I mean that.
Here's the quote.
You're going to need the support of all five burrows, Queens, Brooklyn, Staten Island.
He slowly lists the five burrows of New York to John Gotti.
Then at the end, he says and put them together.
He puts all his finger out for each one.
He goes, put them together.
They make a fist.
I forgot about the fist punch line.
Angel Gotti, John Gotti's actual daughter tweeted back to me.
I think they did that for the people who wouldn't know what the five burrows were.
Since the movie will be shown in other states and overseas, shaking my damn head.
So I would have thought she was just like, hey, fun fact.
Right.
But that shake of my damn head makes me think she did not approve of the film.
Yeah.
No, she's being like, oh, God forbid they don't spell it out for people that live in Dick source in South Dakota.
Exactly.
Uh, she says her bio, by the way, is oldest child of John and Victoria Gotti, animal lover, but disrespects rats.
Well, yeah, I mean her dad got Sammy the bull.
There she is.
Sammy the bull rolled over on her father.
It's one of the biggest rat turn coats in mob history.
And what did you think of the film?
Well, first let me say the film was, Travolta was much better than I thought he was going to be.
Yeah.
I actually felt bad for him afterwards.
I said, you know, if this was a well -written film, he probably would have gotten some accolades.
He did a good job with it.
I also felt if it had been like an FX or a TNT or something, it would have, A, they would have taken the necessary time to tell the story.
And B, some of the stuff like him, you know, in the old age makeup and, you know, in the throes of cancer and prison and stuff, he was good in those scenes.
It's the kind of thing where if it wasn't rushed through with Travolta playing John Gotti from age 14 to 80, then, you know, we would have been able to appreciate what he did more because he wasn't bad.
And he was doing what he could with astoundingly bad material.
The movie came up.
Now the reason Pat and I saw this was it got a 0 % when it first came out.
So we said, we got to see this thing.
I also liked the Gotti story.
I was a fan of the already existing movie called Gotti that was made for TV.
I wanted to see it.
I was curious, especially then because it had a 0%.
I was like, oh man, this thing's going to be so bad.
It's good.
Pat said, you know, I don't know if we should review this for the show because it doesn't really fit our wheelhouse.
I said, Pat, some films transcend genre and I believe this is one of them.
I agree.
The movie was bad.
It was bad.
It was very bad.
It wasn't so bad.
It was a riot.
It wasn't Ed Woodbad.
No, we weren't howling throughout.
But there were some special moments.
It was shockingly confusingly bad.
It wreaked to me of a movie that had been overshot and it was probably a mess and they tried to save it in editing with some sort of narrative and it didn't work.
We should add it was the directorial debut of Kevin Connolly who portrayed E on entourage.
And I think debut and also final bow.
And the movie couldn't have felt more like a storyline movie from entourage.
Right.
If Adrian Grenier was playing Goddie himself.
At some point in the development, I'm sure he was just like, we kind of just do this thing like an episode of Teraj.
Did you think they called it Teraj?
I think they called it Teraj.
Teraj, he hints.
He, his visual sense, I mean, he was completely ripping off every mob movie ever made.
Sometimes way too obviously.
So the music he was using were the most obvious mob movie cues of all time.
Then all of a sudden the water is the first one.
It starts with a Goddie two camera.
Travolta two camera being like, this is my story.
This is my town or something like that.
He turns around like Troy McClure style.
He's looking out across the New York skyline.
And he turns to face camera and is like, basically like, hey, I'm John Goddie.
This is my town.
It's like unbelievably on the nose.
Yeah.
And then smoke on the water.
And then a set up line like it all started many years ago.
Yeah.
And then slow motion camera drifting across the Hudson River as bad.
Pretty bad stuff.
In the 80s they start bringing in some more interesting music cues like the pet shop boys, West End Girls.
And I kind of liked that, although these people would never have listened to that music.
No, no choice.
I liked that too, but that was just a Scorsese jack.
Yeah, of course.
That was Scorsese in Casino like using like Whip it.
Right.
And I can't get no satisfaction the Devo version.
It was it was a cool idea.
It's a cool juxtaposition, but it doesn't it doesn't work because it because you're like that's you're doing a Scorsese thing.
I know what you're doing right now.
There are shots that don't match up to each other.
There are plot lines that are introduced and immediately abandoned.
There's that girl that comes up and she's like, how you doing to John Goddie's son.
And you're like, oh, I guess this is starting a romance and that never goes nowhere.
Well, they are married later, but they never explain it.
Why are we treated to like the moment they met?
I don't know. That's what I mean.
I feel like this thing probably had so much other footage.
I it felt like a six hour movie condensed to 90 minutes.
There's absolutely no story.
Absolutely no story.
There's nothing pulled propelling you from saying to saying no.
Big events happen.
Well, they'll be like, John, the feds are after you and you're like, wait, what?
Yeah.
And they'll literally say things like, Johnny, you know, those guys have been on us for years.
We've seen the clues and you're like, wait, no, none of this was mentioned.
What is happening right now?
There's a lot of points where it's like, I guess we'll just assume they know about John Goddie.
And there's other things where they hold your hand so much that you're like, I got it.
The end of the movie does a does an almost Malcolm X style tribute to John Goddie.
They have black and white shots of like murals in his honor.
And people are like, he despite his criminal activity, he put like X millions of dollars into the community.
He was a hero.
I was like, why the fuck didn't you put any of that into the movie?
None of that is mentioned on the movie.
It's like, that's what makes it a cool story.
Right.
It's like this guy does heinous things.
Yeah.
But also he's loved in the community because he actually does take care of people.
Right.
And he is sort of the last bastion of the old school mobsters.
Like he respects the code.
Yeah, they tell you that as an afterthought during a montage featuring a song written for the film Goddie by Pitbull.
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, I forgot about that.
Yep.
It was a, I mean, let's, let's talk the actors.
Kelly Preston.
John Travolta's wife.
Clearly, I mean, it's not hard to see how she got that part.
I always liked Kelly Preston.
I thought she had a good comedic career ahead of her in Jeremy wire.
She's got that amazing intro where she's yelling don't ever stop fucking me.
And she's naked.
And it looks incredible.
And I was like, she's funny in her other scenes with Tom Cruise.
And then never really went anywhere.
Which is fine.
Okay.
But now she's here and you're like, this could have been your comeback.
She's doing like, I mean, what, what would you even call that?
Like on a living color sketch about the mob.
This couldn't be, this couldn't have been her comeback.
The part was not substantial enough for her to be a comeback.
The movie was not good enough.
She's in a lot of it though.
She's like, Johnny, you're always staying out late.
She told me you were going to be home to take care of the kids.
I made a chicken.
I guess I did.
It's getting cold.
They may, I mean, they gave her...
Yeah, it did feel like a sketch because this movie felt like a sketch.
Yeah.
It's like, what else do you do with it?
Which revolta was doing was almost sketchy.
Yeah.
Sketch comedy.
Well, when he's playing...
But he got it at age 25.
When John Travolta is easily 60, those scenes were a little weird too.
They didn't do any of like the X -Men de -aging.
They just kind of gave him a little more hair.
And we're like, now he's 25.
Now I just looked up Kevin Connolly.
E.
Kevin Connolly.
Yeah.
First picture that came up is him with the words kind of a dick printed across his face.
All right.
Gotti still has a 0%.
It's up to 24 % on metacritic.
Which in no fairness I think is fair.
I don't think it deserves a 0.
No.
You know what I'm confused by is when you look up Gotti, it says John Travolta is playing Gotti.
Kelly Preson is playing Victoria Gotti.
And Al Pacino is playing Annie L .O. Delacroche.
Then it goes to Stacey Keach and the rest of the cast.
So was he in it and cut out?
This, I'm telling you, this movie had saved an editing written all over it.
I don't think those Travolta to camera things were originally in the script.
No.
I think they were like, we got a book in this somehow.
John, can you come in for two hours?
Yeah.
And talk to the camera.
The movie ends with him addressing camera going,
if you lived another 5 ,000 years,
you ain't never going to meet another guy like me.
And he walks off camera.
It's one of the worst lines ever.
It was almost like, it was almost like if Adam McKay was on the sideline on drugs,
pitching the lines in like he does with Will Farrell.
You could live to be a thousand.
Yeah.
And you'd never meet a guy like me.
It makes no sense.
And the only thing that could have made it more perfect is if,
as it cut to credits, they should have had dice going.
Oh.
Yeah.
That would have, that would have really put the cherry on top of this thing.
Uh, the, the supporting cast.
It's got fruit Taylor Vince in a pretty key role.
Who's good?
The guy with the weird eye who plays like his right hand man.
I didn't know these people's names.
He, he tries.
You, you know, fruit Taylor Vince.
He's been around.
I'm sure I know by face, but not by name.
Uh, that you see people like in the background of shots,
who have played key figures in like good fellows in casino.
So like, you'll see some guy like walk through the back of a funeral scene and be like,
wait a minute, that guy was in eight episodes of the sopranos.
So clearly a lot of stuff was left in the cutting room floor.
Um, it's just a nuts movie.
And they were using its bad reviews in the ad campaign, which I've never seen.
They were like critics give it a zero percent, but audiences love it.
So check it out.
They were like, let's get ahead of this.
It didn't work, obviously.
But I got to tell you, I wouldn't, I wouldn't dissuade anyone from seeing it.
For what reason?
Because I see so many movies that are boring that make me feel nothing.
And this one had sort of a scrappy spirit to it where it was kind of,
yes, so bad in parts that it kind of carries you through.
You're watching it kind of like a traffic accident.
And there's a fascination to it.
And also, I like trying to piece together where a movie went wrong.
Sure.
I would love to, you know, like, one of my favorite things to read is an oral history of a movie,
where they get like all the key players to talk about their experience.
I'd really love to see one of those on God, for sure.
I remember seeing that I watched one of those about Stan alive,
the sequel to Saturday Night Favour.
Yeah.
And a guy goes, they cut to a producer and he goes,
the first mistake was letting Stallone direct.
Now, where did you see this?
It was like the e -true Hollywood story.
Oh, okay.
Those fucking things.
I usually went up reading them.
Like, there's a great bookie nights one that was in Vanity Fair.
It might have just been the Travolta documentary.
Right.
And they just had that part in it.
Oh, yeah.
About how bad, like, how that movie, like, basically tanked his career for a while.
I haven't seen Stan alive.
I love Saturday Night Favour.
But was he, he was in a Broadway show in that, staying alive?
Staying alive, if I remember correctly.
Wow.
I remember correctly.
He's a, he's now a dance teacher.
Okay.
And maybe he's also on Broadway.
I don't remember.
But it's Travolta in a lot of Leotards.
Yeah.
Him trying to show a young, hungry dancer, the beauty of dance.
And, and you need, you need to want it.
Goddamn it.
Right.
Well, he's right there.
It's one of those things.
Yeah.
It's just everything that made the reason Saturday Night Favour is cool is the absolute value that these neighborhood kids put on the disco.
It's, it's these kids that have, you know, sort of troubled and sorted lives.
Yeah.
And, and, and there's a sense of humor about it.
Like when his parents are making fun of him for his hair and all that, that's, they're kind of letting him off the hook and they're letting the audience kind of make fun of him.
Yeah.
And it's like, it's like, but it's, you know, to me, the takeaway was always like, this is the, this is the Valhalla for these kids.
This is what they have that they can carry worth with or whatever.
And staying alive is nothing.
It's, it's, it's all gone.
Now it's just a movie about a guy that dances.
It's like, who gives a shit?
Right.
You know?
Uh, I think the only time I've ever seen this done, but I saw Saturday Night Favour on VHS.
And it's set on it with a red band around it.
The PG version.
And I watched it, whatever.
And then years later, when I saw the actual R version, it's a much darker movie.
There's like a sexual assault and all kinds of stuff.
Well, there's the famous line, too, where he goes, congratulations, you a cunt.
Yeah.
That's the big line that I remember when I saw the uncut, I was like, whoa.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
But I've never known that to happen any other time where they released two versions on VHS on R and a PG.
Uh, it is an awesome piece of film.
Who directed Saturday Night Favour?
John Badam.
Who did shit?
All kinds of movie.
He did steak out.
Ooh.
You don't like steak out?
I never saw it.
I never cared.
Oh.
Something I'm going to say to this publicly.
Can I say this publicly?
Yeah.
He did war games, too.
A short circuit.
I always liked Emilio Estevez.
Yes.
Richard Dreyf is bothers me.
Always loved Richard Dreyf.
He bothers me.
He's, I think he's really cheesy and a lot of shit.
I think he's really arrogant.
He bothers me.
Yeah.
He just fucking annoys me.
Like when he's, I don't know.
Do you ever watch those shitty mob movies he made?
Like the comedies with like Bert Reynolds that are terrible.
But like, Dreyf is literally being like, that was the thing with the guys.
I'm like, dude, you're this bad.
You don't, you don't understand that you shouldn't fucking talk like that in this shitty movie.
Wait.
What about Bert Reynolds?
No.
Richard Dreyf is.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought you said movies with Bert Reynolds.
Why did I hear Bert Reynolds?
I said because of those, see now you weren't listening to me.
I got a lot of shit.
For one second.
I was looking up John Badam.
He said, what did he direct?
The, uh, don't put it on me.
Don't blame me.
Wow.
The, uh, I'm podcasting with a ghost.
Uh, no, Dreyfist did, did that shitty mobster movie with Bert Reynolds?
Yeah.
The crew or whatever.
And look, the movie's not good, but everybody's doing their best with it.
But then you got Richard Dreyfist doing the voiceover and he's in the lead role.
And he's literally being like, this was Tommy.
Tommy didn't take no crap from nobody.
And it's like, you should be a better actor to know to not do that.
Yeah.
Like, it's ridiculous.
It's fucking ridiculous.
What else would he have done in that film?
Do a normal accent.
That's a guy going, it's funny.
If, if I poke like this, it's funny.
It's like, no, it's not because you're not funny.
I like Richard Dreyfist and Josh.
Huh?
Have you seen what about Bob?
I think he's very funny.
I never really liked what about Bob.
Um, once around with Dreyfist and Holly Hunter and Danny Ayyella.
There's a great movie.
Nobody has seen.
Recommended highly.
Never saw it.
I love Danny Ayyella.
Yeah.
It's a great movie.
Did you ever tell the story when I met him?
No.
He's in my favorite episode of Tells From The Dark Side ever.
Yeah.
It's called The Odds.
Okay.
And me and Pinkstone quoted all the time.
It's about gamblers.
Yeah.
And me and Matt McCarty quoted quite a bit to one another.
Um, so anyway, I met Danny Ayyella at Gotham Comedy Club.
He was downstairs in the lounge because he had just done a show upstairs.
And I was doing the next show.
And I said, hey.
He does stand up.
I don't know if he does.
He does stand up shows.
I don't know if he actually does stand up on them.
But like he'll do shows with standups and I think he sings.
No, he's not dead.
Danny Ayyella.
Continue.
I think he died.
Well, I'm going to wait till you look it up because I want you to hear the story.
All right.
Gotham Comedy.
I say to the manager that night.
Both.
Can you take me down to meet Danny Ayyella?
Yes.
I'm a huge fan.
He goes, yeah, of course.
Takes me downstairs.
You know, when he's like Mr. Ayyella, this is Joe DeRose.
There's a comic and he just won't say hi.
And Danny's like, hey, go ahead and meet your kid.
But you know, and I go, uh, I go.
Danny, I got to tell you.
I love the odds.
Yeah.
I've brought the ups from the dark side.
And, uh, and I just a yellow line out of from it.
And I go, you're a loser, Lacey.
Uh -huh.
Which is a line that he yells at it.
And he goes, oh.
An aficionado.
All right.
Sit out.
He talked to me for five minutes about making that episode.
Nice.
And he's like, I love that character so much.
I got so into it.
That's nice.
This is cool.
Because your average actor that went on to make big pictures
and all this stuff.
Yeah.
You know, they'd be like, oh God.
Good.
You know, when I did the horror TV, you know, he was like, dude,
that was awesome.
I love doing it.
Yeah.
And I got the same thing from, um,
Lance Hendrickson.
I tweeted Lance Hendrickson, uh, because my favorite
episode of television ever is the cutting cards episode
of tells in the crypt.
Okay.
And I tweeted at Lance Hendrickson.
And I said, his first line in the movie is half a grand
howdy, uh, because he plays like this, like sort of like
cowboy gambler.
And I wrote half a grand howdy.
I just wanted to let you know that cutting cards is far
far in a way.
You know, not just the best episode of tells in the crypt,
but the best episode of television ever.
And he wrote back and he's like, thanks, buddy.
We had a lot of fun shooting it, man.
You know, I was like, that's fucking cool, man.
It's nice.
It's just cool when people appreciate the small stuff.
Denny L is alive.
Yeah, I know.
I told you he was.
I was wrong.
Uh, I couldn't admit that.
I haven't seen him in anything in 10 years.
No, he, well, I think he's retired.
Oh, okay.
I think he has a club in Hoboken.
All right, called like Danny's place or something where they did.
It's a comedy club.
And if you want to perform at it, I heard if you didn't know
who you were, you had to go and audition and you had to do your act.
Two Danny I .L .O.
A load in a room.
I would imagine I .L .O.
It was not a guy who likes your, uh, old comedy.
I don't think Danny I .L .O. is enjoying a Kate Berlant.
Well, well, but here's the thing.
Here's the strange, interesting part about I .L .O.
Yes.
You know, I view the guy is, you know, he looks like a traditionalist or whatever.
He put out a, he put out an album where it was, it was rap remakes of
their standards where he sung the synatra parts and then like a rapper
wrapped over the beat.
And I'm like, look, that's pretty out of pocket for a guy like I .L .O.
It's true.
And he was, he was like, he was like, this has never been done before.
You know, like he was, he was excited about it.
Were these actual rappers or like, no, it was one rapper.
He did like a whole album with him.
All right.
Did they ever met?
I don't know, Pat.
I don't know Danny I .L .O. personally.
Well, I'm just talking to you about a thing I saw on the internet.
I just kind of wish I was doing a podcast with Danny I .L .O. sometimes, I guess.
Listen, I wish it was too.
Yeah.
Folks, that's our show.
There's your goddamn gotty episode.
We say goodbye and you say I .L .O.
All right.
We got to get out of here.
There are no plugs, no segments on the special bonus app, but enjoy this.
And we'll see you in September for the next bonus.
Later, guys.