Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff!
The slot that's blowing players away!
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days!
All on our players' favorite game of the summer!
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable Casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured
game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -Terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
howdy folks welcome to we'll see you in hell or your favorite fantasy sci -fi and horror
movie podcast. My name is Joe DeRosa. Sitting across. That's why you're looking at me like that.
Namaste. Yeah. I'm pet walls. Oh, okay. We were looking at me like I was doing it wrong or something.
I know. Did I have a weird inflection? I thought you did a great job. Oh, okay. Thanks. Pat, how are you?
I'm pretty good, you know, going on meetings, having eaten, I'm irritable.
Went to the dentist this morning as you might have heard in the quip ad, that wasn't bullshit.
I don't have a grandpa for rank, I made that up, but the rest is true.
Right.
Do you like a great dental appointment?
Do you feel good when you lick your tongue along the the Ivory's?
There are a few things I hate more than a dental appointment.
I don't have dentist fears or anything like that.
But I hate going.
I hate going.
Yeah.
I don't like a man in my mouth, sure, in every sense of that term, sure.
I just am not a fan.
I don't like going to the doctor and the dentist for some reason.
They poke you.
They prod.
Yeah.
I hate the smell of a doctor's office.
That's sterile.
Yeah, you know, jerk off booth smell like, you know.
Like kind of.
Yeah, it's just, I just don't,
and I talked about on this podcast
when I had something removed from my hand.
I maybe I didn't.
I'll walk it out to the parking lot
and my hand just starts gushing blood,
pouring dumping blood that I was trying to cover
with a parking validation slip.
Uh huh.
And I walked in and I was like,
like, hey guys, you know, blood all down the hallway.
I'm on like the 14th floor, so blood in the elevator.
Everyone looking at me like,
what does this guy have that I'm catching right now?
Right.
Just awful.
And the guy has been a terrible doctor.
And every time I go to the doctor,
I have health insurance through the writer's guilds.
It's supposed to be good insurance.
They do pay well for the insurance.
I'm gonna try some new guy in Burbank.
I think, you know, I'm sitting in the room for 45 minutes.
No one comes and says a word to me.
Then he comes in, there's no checkup of any kind.
He talks to me for like two minutes and he's done.
I can't get a good appointment.
I go to a doctor now who talked to me for three hours
about his life, about the Republican party
and what's become of it.
And it doesn't seem appropriate.
Sir, I have to leave now.
And I know there are other patients out there,
but I can't find a good doctor.
I did find a good dentist, but it's 45 minutes away.
I got a line, you can give that chatty doctor next time.
Go ahead.
You go, hey doc, for a patient, I'm running out of patients here.
Yeah, that's good.
When you look this guy up, every review of him on Yelp
is like, look, this is either for you or it's not,
but he's going to talk to you for a couple of hours about his life.
And it's not, but the problem is he was a good doctor doctor, you can't get anybody who's good at everything.
I got a better line version of that line.
Better than patients, okay.
You wait until he's like 45 minutes and you go, hey, duck.
Apparently, you're not the only one with a lot of patients around here.
You say it like that because you also are exhibiting patients.
Exactly. That's a little better. I like that better. Yeah, that's fine. Now, can I ask you a question?
Because sometimes you'll hit me with a hard -hitting question right off the top. Sure.
Why have you been non -stop complaining about the Bill Cosby verdict?
Well, as Kanye West once screamed with a thousand exclamation points, Bill Cosby innocent.
I don't believe one of these 72 women who have come forward, and I certainly don't believe
there are other women who have not come forward. 72 women only had to do was kill himself with
a bomb. I know. And he would have went to a lot. I got in 72 virgins. That's right. I don't
know what that exact number is. It's a lot. Well, I know the alarm number is 72. All I know is
the man made me smile on TV when I was a kid and for that reason and that reason alone
he couldn't have done this.
Bold stance from Pat Walsh.
No, I hope you're kidding now.
So everybody knows you're kidding.
I hope he dies in prison.
He will die in prison.
Well, they're saying he's not probably not going to see jail time because of like his age
and his condition and all that stuff.
That's too bad.
You know there's a hole.
I'm going to just tap on it and get off.
Tap it, but what's making me real angry these days is people who spend every second of their day -to -day life
doing the most disgusting, depraved
sick things to their fellow man and woman and then
We're supposed to take pity on them
That's Cosby look. He's an old man. Yeah, he
raped upwards of 100 women, probably much, much more than that.
I'm not, this, the White House correspondence dinner.
Hey, how dare you say something mean about these people who wake up, clock in, and then
destroy everyone in America's life until they clock out?
I think the Cosby jail thing, this is not me defending him, not going to jail, because I
do think he should go to jail.
But I think that's, I don't think that's a pity thing.
I think that's, it's about medical expenses and them not being able to afford to put certain type of people
into prison because of the medical cost it might incur. I think that's what it is. Then throw them off a bridge.
You know, you know, what do you want from my mom's calling? Should I answer it on the podcast?
put it on speaker. If you're doing it, listen, we're on the podcast and I'm
recording you. Okay. All right, I'm going to hang up, okay? All right, is
everything all right? Yeah, everything is fine. You want to say anything to the
listeners? No? All right. Bye. Bye.
That's old mom dooks all right I would uh I would have maybe uh had her take us to
her movie corner see what she's up to uh she really didn't sound like she wanted
any part of this all right did you did I said do you want to say anything to listeners
no yeah that's true she really bounced fast um or she could have voice and opinion on
Bill Cosby, who I, you know, throw him in the traffic, we're dumb with it, we're dumb
with you.
Enough.
Um, what, uh, what else is going on in your life?
Well, I, uh, I have, uh, I am approaching the one and a half months mark of no booze.
It's very impressive.
But well, actually, no, it, it now is in the past, uh, at the time of the release of this,
I will have already hit the one -and -a -half month mark, and I will also have been through your
weekend long bachelor party in, we'll see if you have not drank on this bachelor.
Yeah.
In last Vegas.
Now, you were saying, because it's the bachelor party, then two weeks later, is the wedding.
You were saying you're probably going to return to drinking at my wedding, but maybe the
bachelor party.
It wouldn't be outrageous for you to have a couple pops in Vegas.
I might use the bat, if I want to, if in the moment I feel like I don't want to, then I won't,
I'm not going to force myself. But if I do want to drink and I do think at the bachelor party
it would make a significant difference in the time I'm having and celebrating you, I will, and I'll
just use it as a test. If I can come home from that and not indulge for two weeks until you're
wedding, I think you can definitely do that.
And it's not a problem or anything, then great.
Yeah.
If I come home and I start slipping into,
wow, it's Tuesday, I drank Sunday, who cares, you know.
Right.
Then I know that I can't do this, you know.
So, I think regardless, it's gonna be a fun weekend.
I think it's gonna be a great time.
Great, good people.
Yeah, I think it's gonna be good, you know.
Typical bachelor party stuff.
We'll all be having a lot of unprotected sex
with prostitutes the entire time doing cocaine rails off a party where there's a donkey walking around
for some reason you know we'll have our ties tied to our heads yeah exactly somebody wearing a
lampshade right right right somebody's gonna show up with uh with uh oh boy god damn it what was the
The drug I always did used to take, that they don't make anymore, that those pills in
the 70s everybody took, like at Wolf Wall Street?
Yeah, ludes.
Ludes, yeah.
Somebody's going to show up with ludes.
Somebody might show up with ludes.
I think the only thing that you mentioned there that will take place is drugs.
I don't think you're going to see any cocaine.
But we got, we got a lot of married men going on this trip.
We got, you know, men with new babies going on this trip.
I mean, people are going to rain it in, I think.
Keep it tight.
Well, I didn't think that anybody would be having
unprotected sex with prostitutes,
but I did think a donkey might show up.
Sure.
And that's the most innocent of anything we mentioned,
in my opinion.
You could probably get a donkey in Las Vegas if you want to.
I just watched an episode of Cops from Vegas.
Hooker got busted in Vegas on the strip.
That's what the cops said.
He goes, you know, everybody thinks it's legal.
It's not legal. You can't be doing this on the strip. You're banned from the strip. You can't do this
So what can you do you can have them come to your room? No, hooking is not legal in Vegas proper
It's legal in areas around it. Oh, like those ranchers. Yeah, and but but and like you know, it's
It's like the weed laws in Amsterdam
You know weed is you know, technically you're not supposed to smoke weed outside an Amsterdam
And I'm sure people do it and nobody kind of cares.
I think that's how it is with the hooker laws in Vegas.
But yeah, the song episode of Cops.
All right, very fun show to watch if you've never seen it.
I don't, I don't have it in me.
I couldn't, I couldn't make love to a prostitute.
The fear would be too great.
Oh, I thought you meant watching cops.
No, I watched cops.
I always liked the New Orleans cops.
Yeah, there's always a real drunk on there.
I really grew to appreciate the rapport between the cops and the perps
Sure because they'll just be like they just talk like they're having coffee like it's like heat
And the cop will be like would you run for man? You know, we're gonna catch you
I think I was like, I don't know man. I just thought I could get away. He's like, yeah, nah, I hear you
But anyway, listen sit here. All right. You want some water? Yeah
They turn the camera off and let the purpose savagely beaten
Um, yeah, it's, uh, it's a post cop's world.
Now they still make it.
They make new cops.
Yeah, I just watched a ton of them with my dear friend, Big J.
Oakerson.
And they were new cops.
Yeah, I said to him, I go, are these new?
And he's like, oh, yeah, he's like, this, what channel?
Still going strong.
It's like, you know, spike or something like that.
Yeah.
There's no make.
I became the paramount network.
And they do theme ones now. They always did theme ones. I didn't know that. There was one it was like bad girls
It was all like women doing crazy shit
I never saw a theme
I'm looking through our Facebook page trying to find one of the many requests
For a Joe song, and I can't find any now that I need them of course
Thinking what maybe you switch it up from songs. Maybe it's time to move on to a new thing
to what I am
I'm quite tired of having to think of one of these, usually.
Maybe you'd switch it to movie lines now.
I would like that.
No, I don't think that's gonna work.
Why would it not work?
I don't think it's gonna work.
We've gotten so many requests.
I think the movie lines could work.
To what?
A movie line that starts with Joe?
Or a word that sounds like Joe.
I don't wanna do it.
For instance, you'd go and get on with the Joe Ho Ho Merry Christmas like that kind of thing
But not a line from a movie. It's a maybe somebody's it's in a movie somewhere
I'm sure here. I'll do let's get on with the show and on with the Joe ho ho ho and a bottle of rum
There you go
All right, that's the new thing pirate songs only
All right, that should be easy to come up with
Oh boy, what's the one from JAWS?
Joe, any ladies who don't make babies, send them on over to me.
Jo ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
first time we discussed it.
Just go back to the yarn with the, just saying it,
like when you'd say it with a funny voice.
All right, get back to the roots, get back to the basics.
All right, you know, this thing is gotten,
this is like the new Marvel film, it's too big, it's too much.
Well, we are gonna do it, which means I have to see it,
and I mean, it's just nothing could be less appealing to me.
So I see that running time.
Um, oh, baby, and you are, you are so, I'm not, you know what?
I'm not going to say a word.
We will wait till for the review.
I don't want to ruin anything.
I mean, just, we got, we got into this crazy place where every super hero movie is like,
oh, this is the one that changes the game, every single one.
This one, I haven't really even seen any, like passionate, loving reviews of it.
And he kind words and he had everybody seems to love it.
Uh, I have.
I know the ending is bothering a lot of people.
I don't know why.
I've seen plenty of reviews.
Your boy Peter Travers said like, you know, a fuck Peter Travers.
It like redefined the way we think.
That's enough.
Go to take a glass of warm milk and lie down.
Your career is done.
You know what I'm really sick of the hyperbole in this fucking business?
Of course.
I'm sick of seeing people on magazine covers where it's like
They're changing the game is Hollywood ready to ante up
How many times does somebody gonna change the game this year? Right stop it. Jesus Christ
Brendan Fraser is turning Hollywood on its ear. It's like what?
You mean he's accepting the few roles that have been offered to him. I don't know why you're going after him
They're not saying it about I guess I shouldn't go okay was sexually assaulted. I forgot
Folks, let me tell you this if Kevin Spacey grabbed my dick it wouldn't be a traumatic memory
It would be my closer folks. I've always like Brennan Fraser. I shouldn't have gone after him
But I mean, you do you look at every magazine is like well
Andy Brahmavov has really having a hell of a year who the fuck you're like Andy
Who the fuck is Andy Brahma though?
Is that a person that you just said?
I just made him up.
Oh, okay.
But you're like, I guess he's having a hell of a year, I don't know.
The immediate picture it brought to mind was Andy Richter, except with jet black, slick back
hair.
Like if they had him in a sketch where he was playing like a bond type guy, yeah, that's
who I pictured Andy Brahma Voby.
I just made him up.
Maybe I'll write a whole feature about him when I get home.
Speaking of features, can I take you down to Pat's movie corner for a moment?
I'd love it if you took me there.
First picture I saw, I had a meeting over at Happy Madison and I was like I better watch
their new offering the week of starring Adam Sandler, Chris Rock, Rachel Drench, something
about he's a cowboy who used to be a spy, and he's getting married or something.
He's just a man, I mean, look, this is the movie somehow.
And Smigel wrote it, Robert Smigel, who was a genius, and he, I was like, okay, let me see
what this is gonna be.
I'm kind of excited to see it.
The plot is just Chris Rock makes a lot of money.
Adam Sandler is poor, their kids are getting married, right?
Sandler wants to do it his way in Long Island, it's his daughter, and Chris Rock's like let
me pay for a nicer wedding.
The movie is two full hours of this real mild dilemma, and you keep waiting for these moments.
it was written by Smigel and Sandler who are guys who now they can't blame studio notes, network
notes etc. I mean I'm sure Netflix chimes in with a few things but I think one of the main parts
of this deal with Sandler and Netflix was we'll give you some money you make whatever the fuck you want
and this is what they're bringing to the table you know and I saw this thing get some good reviews too
but what's the dilemma I don't even understand with the with the conflict that's it Sandler wants
wants to do it like a wedding, you know, and like a low rent kind of like banquet hall.
Right. And Chris rocks like, won't you just let me help you out? I got the money. And
that dilemma is start to finish the entire movie. Well, let me tell you it. And let me tell
you why I might just, I have not seen the film, but let me tell you why there's no great
gags. That's, that's spade. Sandler movie had better gags in it. Let me tell you why I might
disagree with you about this not being strong enough for a film. This exact storyline
was plenty strong to carry half an episode of Frazier.
Yes, okay.
So the fact that they've now stretched a B subplot
to two hours.
To two hours.
Not 90.
Yeah.
Well, that worries me.
I've met both Chris Rock and Adam Sandler.
They're both very nice men.
Yeah.
I don't know them.
I've enjoyed some of their work.
I don't want to see this film.
Rock seems to still have the urge to, you know, write something of interest.
He'll do a movie every five years that at least has interesting themes and subject
matter, et cetera.
Sailor, I think it's very content to just kind of do this.
He'll act in something great every again, five years.
But it was just kind of depressing.
I mean, even the ridiculous six was like more ambitious and had a really funny set
piece in it.
Yeah, at least it was kind of nothing.
Yeah, at least it was a big swing like why don't we do a comedy Western, right? You know that doesn't get done very often
All right, well
I haven't been watching much
Because I've been
Re -watching the entire Roseanne series
Given the new one that came out. I've been enjoying it and so I went back and started re -watching
Old Roseanne's and much like a Frazier
It's too quality of a show to turn it into some goofy segment on this show, but I've been
enjoying myself and I am more impressed now with the new one as I rewatched the old ones
because the way they recaptured particularly the earlier seasons of that show and the vibe
and the tone and the subject matter is impressive.
That's not an easy thing to just jump back into.
You.
Right.
The only thing that's not quite there is that easy -going Goodman, Rosanne, chemistry in
the new version.
It's not quite as natural.
I mean, for Rosanne to never have acted and be that natural of an actress, people criticize
if they're not being a good actress, but it's the same as Jerry, Seinfeld.
The two of them are both really weirdly natural actors where they're able to keep their persona,
But to me, they never felt like a comedian doing a
She does she does the thing that I've found the most hard as an actor
Which is take whatever you're actually doing in that moment and just fold it into the scene like when she starts laughing
Yeah, she incorporates it in yeah, like that's what supposed to be happening
That's really fucking hard to do and not stop and go oh fuck. I fucked up
Well, can we start again?
Our laughter at Goodman and the early ones always seem supernatural
and they seem like they love each other, et cetera.
I think it's just a matter of Goodman having not done
multi -cam and so long, and Roseanne having not acted
and so long, and I think they'll get back to the groove.
But it's close enough now that I'm still enjoying it.
I always related to the most when I watched Roseanne
it was the constant thread of spousal abuse.
What do you mean?
It's always seemed like, maybe that's in, you know,
your season three's in four,
because I rewatched it 10 years ago or something.
Like Goodman throws a chair across the room
at one point in an argument with Rosanne.
Like it always felt to me like he was about to raise his fist.
And I'm surprised they never went there on that show.
But I never took that from it.
But go, oh, sorry, go ahead.
Well, just that tension of like he's out in the garage drinking or he's angry and the
fight's always seemed real or whatever, it reminded me a lot of the dynamic in my home.
The tension that probably came from work being brought into the home place.
So that's funny, because it reminded me of the tension in my home too, but I never had
a fear of spousal abuse in my house because my dad wouldn't have done it, but there was
it's still that those big explosive arguments.
So when I see it on Rosanna,
I just always thought like,
oh yeah, they're like a family.
Families fight like that sometimes.
Yeah.
People throw shit because they're like,
I'm so angry I have to throw something
and now I'm gonna walk out of the house.
Sure.
But, you know, different strokes for different folks, Pat.
Another great sitcom.
Um, you know, I disagree.
I've only seen the child molestation one.
Over and over.
Yeah, I have a VHS copy that I watch all day.
Criterion should do that.
They should release the dark episodes as, you know,
blue rate.
Um, I'd buy it, absolutely.
What else did you see, my man?
Well, I watched the new Kevin James stand -up special.
I watched two ends of the stand -up spectrum.
Let's say that.
I watched it as well.
I watched the new Kevin James and the new Mulaney.
So you're really talking about two different points of view here.
Yes, Kevin James first stand -up special, but like pre -King of Queens, I believe, is really funny.
And I, despite what I know about the man and his behavior to people, I always found him to be funny.
But lately there's a laziness that he's eclipsed even the sandlers and everyone else
because his career's only been around for, you know, a shorter period of time.
But the laziness is kind of outrageous. I mean, these bits were like,
what the kind of bits you can find in his dog shit sitcom over on CBS.
That last night pulled in a point eight. This is the biggest movie star
in comedy for many, many years. So really, he was pulling in the same numbers
was that my show, which appeared 90 minutes later,
after three other sub part shows was making.
But they're leaving that one on the air for now.
I assume it's about to get canceled.
But these jokes, these observations are,
I mean, they were tired in the 80s.
The shitties talking about in this stand -up special
is like the food allergies.
or these are real real thing.
That's how he kicks off the bit.
I'm like, dude, you have you been to a comedy club,
and of course the answer is he hasn't.
But it's like these jokes have been done
thousands of times, thousands of times.
And he wasn't putting any sort of original spin on them.
They were lazy, and for the first 20 minutes of the special,
the audience really wasn't with them.
They weren't really laughing.
It's not a it's not a great special. I I thought the on core bit was funny, but just because he yelled
Well, when it started I was kind of rolling my eyes. He's like these bands that they go off stage then come back and do the on core
And he's like nobody else does that at their job and I was like, oh, that's dumb
But then when he actually did the accountant being like here are some of your attacks as good night
Like the way he was screaming and the way walked off and face the wall. He's like, I'm not coming back
give me more. I was like, that's funny. But again, it was more funny that he was just yelling.
He could have been doing that voice or act out at any bit. And I would have been laughing
just at him in the yelling. But yeah, I hear you. The special is not.
It's it's very underwhelming. I didn't see Mulaney's. I'd like to. I'm sure it's very funny.
All right. I would guess it's very funny. Right? Yeah. I mean, it's it's the flip of the coin. It's
like an hour so overstuffed with great jokes and great bits that you almost don't want to laugh
to like miss something, it's very tightly written.
He's good, that kid.
He's great.
My only kind of weird thing about him
is that he's gotten this kind of weird,
performance confidence.
I guess from like, oh hello,
which was like just such a funny fucking live show.
But he's kind of like walking the stage
like kind of prowling in a little bit.
He's a radio city and it's a little jarring,
you know, for a guy like that
to have that kind of level of confidence.
But, you know, he's just changing his persona a little bit because he wants to conquer that next level, I guess.
Yeah.
It was super funny, super well written, and I mean, he couldn't have had a better lead in than fucking me watching the Kevin James special the night before.
Fair enough, fair enough. I'll check it out. I buried the lead here. The other thing I saw.
Yep. Maybe I didn't bury the lead. Maybe I'm just closing strong.
sling blade over at Walsh Manor.
Hadn't seen the film, Pat called me the other day,
said, you want to come over watch sling blade.
I showed up with two cakes, two sheet cakes,
a chocolate end of vanilla.
We, it's not sheet cakes,
sheet cakes, they're imagining me, two foot by two foot.
Not the big sheet cake, but they were sheet cakes.
They said sheet cake on them.
Yeah.
They were little sheet cakes.
Right.
And we, we sliced off some, some of each.
and they were delicious, Trader Joe's,
mini sheet cakes, and we watched Sling Blade,
and I gotta tell you, the film exceeded my expectations.
I loved every minute of it.
And the most interesting thing about seeing it now
for me for the first time was,
this is how the world was essentially introduced
to Billy Bob Thornton.
So people were always like,
this guy is a tremendous actor.
I always thought Billy Bob Thornton was a great actor.
But I've only ever seen him play variations
of Billy Bob Thornton. Right. Right. Uh, so to know him so well as the sort of good old boy
and then go back and see this where he's a different human being. Yeah. I was like, my god almighty.
This guy is really, really fucking talented. And then I became obsessed. I look, I watched the short film
on line Molly Ringwald, right? Yeah. JT Walls was also in the short film playing the same guy. Yeah.
Yeah, and then I looked him up on inside the actor studio
because he does the character on stage like instantly.
Yeah.
I thought that was fascinating
because the whole time I was watching it,
I'm like, well, he directed this.
Is he directing in this character?
Like where does he come out of it?
And yeah, it seems like he probably easily comes out of it.
But he said he's just came from like being super depressed,
doing the voice and the face and the mirror.
And then he was like, maybe I'll make it into a movie.
Yeah, and he said um, yeah, he said he was he was his head. Yeah, it was like he was doing a part in something and he yeah started doing that in the mirror
And then he also said that it hurts. He said the posture of the character and the the under bite hurts and the voice hurts
After I guess some time, but I would believe it's uh, I loved it. I saw it twice in the theater one after the other
It's been a favor to mine forever. I wrote a paper on it in college
Wait, you went back, you went back to back?
Did that with Adam Buggie Knights.
Really?
I think of the only two.
Yokem, I think, one of my favorite villains in movie history,
he is the, like a true Missouri alcoholic,
suddenly abusive guy that like he just really rang true
and how I'll say these horrible things back,
I'm just fucking with him.
He's like everyone I went to high school with.
Love him, love Ritter in the movie.
We love Lucas Black, the kid in the movie who still acts like the Fast and the Furious and
stuff.
How old is that kid now?
Probably 30.
I didn't even think the one came up to see like, he's in the Fast and the Furious, it's
one of my favorite movies, Robert Duval making a bizarre appearance at the end, I just love
it.
Big fan.
Yeah, man.
That's crazy.
Duval comes in in a real bit part.
He didn't even have any lines.
He's like two lines.
Yeah, it goes by that
Is that supposed to be that he's like crazy? Yeah, I think it's crazy
I kept his kid in a shed. Yeah, it also seems that he's got jars of piss on his yeah end table there
I love the film surprisingly funny too. I had a way more humor in it than I thought it would have
But I loved it. I thought it was wonderful and that's one that's two -fifteen
Incredibly slow paste and yet you don't feel it. No
You're caught up in it. I love the something that maybe a third or fourth viewing really sunk in for me
Is that everyone says Carl in a kind of a confused way at the end when he was walking off and I think they all know that he's going to kill
Yoke him yeah, and they all just given that Carl like
I'm probably not gonna stop him, but I know what's going on now
Did you see that coming the first time he saw it because as soon as Yoke him came into the fold
I was like, oh, he he's gonna kill him at the end. I think I just saw it when they were doing kind of like the music of him
Sharping the blade and everything, but which when you'd have, but I thought it would go wrong or something would happen that
But they spend a lot of time setting up that he does not want to leave the home. Yeah. Yeah
Anyway, great film if you haven't seen it great film. Well, we're at the 35 -minute mark here. Can I take us?
Just to some deadlines, please do.
Over on screen right now.
They're from their 24 hour news cycle.
I'm just going to do one as I usually do.
John DeLorean, the car, John DeLorean estate sues over back to the future royalties.
Okay.
This came out seven days ago.
Why now?
Now, via Hollywood Reporter, because the fucking thing is all over Ready Player One.
That's true.
But it was also all over back the future.
Well, they're saying, let's see here, according to a complaint in New Jersey Federal Court,
the payment, substantial, DeLorean alleges not receiving a substantial payment from the studio.
The payment apparently went to DeLorean Motor Company.
they're saying they're owed money. They're owed money. That's basically what it comes down to.
Okay. Or they're claiming their owed money. You know, I obviously don't have time to read the whole
story here, but it says no word on who, if anyone, was paid for the delorean in Steven's Bill
was recent film, Ready Player One, which went to pains to license the material, but might
not have imagined this present dispute.
Delorean couldn't be reached for comment, but according to the lawsuit, it's attorney
last week threatened to sue the estate for torches, excuse me, interference unless a request
to universal for payment was retracted.
But like, if I'm not mistaken, you don't have to pay to have a car in a movie.
Yes, you do.
You do?
Yeah.
Every car you see in a movie, they're paying the car.
Yeah, you can't just, that's false app.
You could have a movie that centers on rape and the guy's driving a Nissan around and it's
like, Nissan's like, don't fucking put our car in with the rapist.
You know what I mean?
Like, you can't...
I guess.
It's false adverts.
It's why you can't go on like talk shows.
It's why every time somebody tells a story on a talk show they have to go I can't say the name of it
But we'll call it
Chick -chmonalds, you know what I mean?
Like you especially if you're being disparaging, but yeah, there's all kinds of stuff
So it looks like basically what's happening is the DeLorean estate is suing the DMC motor company for saying that the DMC, Texas
Didn't pay them the money. They should have it. You know, it's just another god damn fucking thing in this fucking business
Where somebody says I should have got some money and they didn't get it and they're probably telling the truth because I will tell you people I can speak from experience when I tell you you got a chase down every fucking dime oh yeah that is oh deal in this god damn fucking business you got a chase down every god damn dime that is oh deal in this fucking business they were a big part of sort of signing the deal on everything to do my show they were like if it syndicates.
which it won't.
You have to, you'll have to sue Warner Brothers.
And telling me this was like basically Warner Brothers.
They were like, you'll have to sue them
to get the money.
That's how it works.
They'll say, well, we did our accounting
and here's what we owe you.
And you'll be like, that doesn't seem right.
There's millions of dollars here.
You have to get a lawyer.
You have to go through the whole process.
And then they're like, oh yeah, okay, here's the money.
If you do a big hit movie,
You'll have to sue to get that money recouped because all they do is make up numbers.
It's like with the Lord of the Rings, they were like, yeah, but you know with marketing
and all that, we only made 17 bucks.
It's ridiculous.
No asshole.
Now are you going to open up the thing?
Because in their mind, they're like, let's at least bluff it because maybe they won't
sue us.
Fucking ridiculous man.
Fucking ridiculous.
us. Well, anyway, that's the world we live in. And I'm sure it's not just a practice in
this business. No. Well, there's your deadlines. We're at the 40 -minute mark. We haven't
even announced our movie yet. But today, we are reviewing, do you have anything for scary
stuff? Yeah, I do, actually. But I can save it to the next. You're a clock watcher on
this podcast. I don't think the people appreciate it.
Well, I'd like to give a static with time to talk for
You're hungry. It pains me to see it. I like my boy to be fed
Joe scary stuff. Yeah, I purchased I think I might have mentioned this before but I didn't get into too much detail
I purchased the last Jedi Blu -ray which came out a few weeks back at this point
People, I am so ripped up about this movie.
I don't know how to feel about it.
I saw it the first time in the theater,
we reviewed it on this podcast.
I liked it okay when we were doing the review
directly after we had seen the film.
Days later, I loathed it, I fucking hated it.
The second time I saw it, I thought it was passable.
And the third time I saw it, I was weeping uncontrollably
and I loved it.
I buy the Blu -ray first time ever in Star Wars history. I have not opened up a
Blu -ray and watched it as soon as I purchased it. No desire. It's still on my
shelf wrapped up as we had farther and farther away from the release, the
initial release of this film. Mark Hamill is like tripling down on the shit he's
saying about not being happy with the film and Ryan Johnson's approached and the
The more I learned about what Ryan Johnson did with this film, the more I'm not liking it.
For instance, the Willem Scream, which is a famous sound effect in Hollywood, this guy
Willem did it in an old western, and movie or tours will put it into the sound bit somewhere
as sort of a wink to one another.
It's that, yeah, Will Helm.
Will Helm Scream.
Yeah, it's been in every Star Wars movie every Indiana Jones movie ever Ryan Johnson doesn't put it in last Jedi
It's like you know, dude. You're doing your own fucking trilogy
Don't put it in that one, but can you just play ball with the with the you're you're in the second to last of the nine
Fucking movies of the Skywalker story. I'm gonna put a quick pause on this. Do you?
seriously give a fuck that they didn't do the Wilhelm scream.
I don't give a fuck that they didn't do the Wilhelm scream.
I think it's just a small representation
of the guy being, it's not just that.
It's also him now Simon Pegg is coming out
and being like he didn't follow the storyline JJ Abrams
was trying to set up with force awakens.
People now as I said last week are now coming out
and say like, you know what, maybe the prequels aren't that bad,
at least they've tried to fucking stay in.
But apparently this guy just came in
and was like, I'm gonna do my own thing.
And for some reason got a big thumbs up from the studio on it.
And, you know, it's not a bad film, but,
you know, there was a lot of dog shit in it.
There was a lot of stuff that didn't need to be in there.
Did you watch the documentary?
No, I've followed it all.
I don't need to watch the documentary.
I've read every fucking news story that's come out about the beef between these two or the you know not beef
But I'm sure there are on speaking terms, but
It's just disappointing to me. It's just disappointing to me
It's it it's got a it's got a hot injection of Disney in it. I don't got any problem with Disney
I don't have a problem when they bought the company. I was excited about that
But you know it rings
You know or it's excuse me it echoes
What a lot of these comic book movies that Disney's doing now, you know, are the same elements. It's
jokes that don't fit
Things tonally that don't really make a whole lot of sense, but overall is it a bad picture? No
Right, so I'm happy JJ's back for the next one. I hope he fixes this
Uh, I pray to God Luke Skywalker is not dead yet
It's because I feel like we didn't get what we were sort of waiting for, which was, they
gave it to us with, Abrams knew what he was doing, gave it to you with Han, he was like,
you want fucking Han Solo, here's Han Solo, and he gave you a nice send -off.
We didn't really get that with Luke, and it's kind of a bummer, especially now that Carrie
Fisher's dead, which nobody was expecting, so I don't know.
No.
This was the best movie for Luke that there's been.
That's absurd.
I mean, I loved Luke's business in this.
I didn't think the movie was excellent.
I did like it, but all of Luke's second half stuff,
brushing off the shoulder bit.
I loved, I loved the sacrifices he made.
I loved it.
I know the parts you loved about Luke in this.
They're five minutes of the movie.
Right. It's five minutes. The rest of the movie is him walking around an island drinking blue milk out of a rubber tit.
Well, no, that happens for 10 seconds. But they cut out. Let me tell you one of the scenes they cut out, one of the deleted.
This is what I mean. Where you're like, what the fuck are you doing, guys?
Thank God you got your fucking
Who's the guy that was married to to Jennifer Aniston, Justin Trudeau, whatever his name is?
or throw, thank God you got his fucking cameo in there that made no sense and was pointless
to the fucking movie.
Because the scene that they cut out that Ryan Johnson said quote, I feel it slowed down
the film too much, is the fucking scene where after Luke finds out Han Solo, his best friend
in the world died, goes behind closed doors and starts to weep, but he's has to hide it
from Ray because he can't show that he's got a motion to her.
They cut that out of the fucking movie.
And even Mark Hamilton was like,
ah, no, yeah, you got time to watch me
drinking blue milk out of an alien's boob.
But you know, don't, don't show me
have a human emotion in the fucking movie.
He's right.
I think people just know too much.
It's not too much.
I'm listening.
You're getting yourself worked up over this.
It's a child's movie.
I don't need this from you.
Be supportive.
I mean, it's just that we're 40 years after Star Wars, like there's gonna be new stories that spring up, and who cares?
I think Ryan Johnson thought he was a real artist here and got real cute with everything.
And I don't think he made the best decisions, that's all.
And for a guy with such discerning taste about what should or shouldn't be in the movie,
He didn't have the fucking insight to cut a goddamn call waiting joke out of the top of the fucking film
Right off the right off the bat. So it's stuff like that that irks me a little bit
It's every star wars a trademark of the star wars movies is I've got a bad feeling about this
Mm -hmm. It's not in the fucking movie. Why because he has the BB -8 robots say it in beeps
He's like yeah, that was just my way of doing it different. It's like don't just do just do it the way you're supposed to fucking do it
like this isn't your thing. It's it's it's it's it's a part it's bigger than you. It's just bothers me. How many movies have to have the same line? It's stupid. It's not stupid to Star Wars fans. It's nine movies. It's a nine -part story. If the first goddamn seven have the line in it, put it in part eight, too.
BBA said it.
Okay, and Beeps, that's the way he looks at it.
Yeah, I mean, it's just, it's just a lot of, it's a lot of precious, you know, look
how, look how quirky I am, I did it my way and I don't like it, I'm sorry.
All right.
But you want a company, man?
Well, you got Ron Howard directing Han Solo's, you'll get that company.
I can't fucking wait to see Han Solo, and I think it's going to be good.
Looks like something I may catch while it's still in theaters, it looks stupid.
Why does it look stupid? I'm not interested in any one or anything in it. Who's it? It's the kid from
Hale Caesar. Yeah, they were like that guy's funny in one scene. Let's give him the most beloved character in
sci -fi history and then who else is in it? Forest Whitaker, probably your boy Woody Harrelson
Tandy Newton. I like Woody Harrelson when he's not in space or apes or other things. He's playing a scumbag in it
I'm excited Donald Glover playing Lando. I'm in. I'm out. I'm on for that. Chewbacca.
You'll hate this too. You'll be screaming about this in a month. Have you ever heard me scream and anger about a Star Wars movie?
And I'm not even saying I hate the last Jedi. I'm just saying it could have been a lot better.
Maybe I'm wrong. Where you wept through it. Does that suddenly have no meaning to you?
I was it was it was well, that's what I'm saying. I'm mixed up. I can't tell how I feel because you're reading too much right now
I'm mad about your kid you go to a movie you're like I don't even know what this is I
Miss those feelings frankly
I have something for scary stuff
What is it you saw a fucking crow outside or something and well, let me ask you do we consider anything
Horror sci -fi fantasy about the movie catty -shack no pat what about the gofer you're doing this to piss me on what about the gofer
Isn't that
Fantasias? No, it's a shitty joke and an otherwise great movie. Then I'll keep it
quick. I ask first, does this meet the guidelines? I say, absolutely. I'm gonna
do it anyway. I listen to the audio book, Caddy Shack, the making of a Hollywood
Cinderella story, which I've had so many books waiting to be listened to that
that have been sitting on there for years. I listen to this eight hour caddy
checkbook in about two days. And I knew everything in it. And
especially coming off the heels of that stupid and futile gesture,
the Will Forte movie, it's, I've heard these stories a thousand
times, there was essentially no new information. If you're,
if you like catty shack and don't know anything about its
production or anything about the national lampoon or the Harvard
lampoon or about Doug Kenny, maybe killing himself for Chevy
chase or what? Then it's for you. I still listen to it in the same way, like if they're doing an
e true Hollywood story of Ghostbusters, I'll sit down and watch it even though I know everything
about that movie. But they could have dug a little deeper as all I'm saying. All I know is there's
a lot of cocaine. I enjoyed hearing about Dangerfield and Ted Knight and Bill Murray and all this.
So not only does your thing not meet the requirements of the segment as a go for, but then
and your thing that didn't meet the requirements,
you're not even doing it about that thing,
you're doing it about a behind the scenes of that thing.
I'm doing it about the book.
We're so far removed at this point.
Scary stuff is if I read a book about the making of it,
that would work, right?
Well, because it fits into the segment.
This has a go for it.
I thought maybe you'd say I saw a caddy shack
and I never realized how life like that go for was.
No, I mean, of course I've seen caddy shack many times,
but all right.
But good enough, let's get to the, I just got an insane, I don't almost call it a lust
for alcohol.
Just wafed it over me.
It's time then.
That's fine.
It's fun.
You don't have to go crazy this weekend.
It'll be a reserved weekend.
Yeah, you know how that goes in Vegas.
You just have a couple drinks.
Keep everything in bounds.
Don't do anything stupid.
Well, Anna and it's free to drink awesome. Yeah, you won't sit at a black jack table cursing the dealer
Bottomless cup of fucking
Yeah, we're talking today about
If anybody asked me what's like your underrated horror movie, if they're a true horror
aficionado, and I know they probably have seen everything, I always recommend Lucky
McKee's May, great picture.
But if I feel like it's kind of a novice, I say, do you ever catch Sturovacos and most
of the time they haven't?
Sturovacos was absolutely buried by the sixth sense.
The previews looked identical, and everybody went to see the sixth sense, nobody saw a stir back up.
Right.
But I got to tell you, I think it's a fantastic movie based on a Richard Matheson story or novel.
Storyable.
No, I think novel.
Excuse me.
You ever read it?
I haven't read that.
When I've only read Matheson's short stories, he's one of my favorite writers.
But I do.
I'm much more a short story guy than a novel guy.
It's done by David Capu wrote, you know, many huge movies, including Jurassic Park.
It's a great, something window.
What's that?
He wrote that Johnny Depp window.
That was a bad move.
What was that called?
Secret window.
That was bad.
Ghost town.
He's a great adapter of stuff, for sure.
Yeah.
He's writing the new latest Indiana Jones.
Yes.
Except for that.
No, he's writing the new one.
You don't know if it's going to be bad.
I have my suspicions.
Sturve Echoes is basically a movie about a man Kevin Bacon who starts seeing disturbing
visions.
He's a summer about the death of a, I don't know, I don't know what I'm spoiling because
I haven't seen it in a while, but you know, he has visions that one of the most disturbing
scenes of yanking a tooth out of his head.
He always wakes up.
He can't get enough orange juice.
He's just going through some shit.
And little by little he starts putting together sort of a murder mystery that took place in the past
Right through using his visions
And that sounds a little hokey, but it's a really intense scary well -done movie that I think does
More than the average movie with character development as well him and his wife Catherine Erby
I love them as a couple it's rooting for them the kid. I just think it's a very well -done movie scary spooky fun
I had not seen the movie until recently and the reason I watched it was because I at one point had a DVD of the film and I had traded it for credit at a store with some other DVDs without having watched it and I was told not only by Pat but some listeners of the show that I made a terrible mistake.
I said, well, you know, what did I miss?
Just one of those, we're in the milk heaven, bacon, horror movies, everybody said, no, no, no, no, no, it's great, it's great, it's great, you made a mistake, and I regretted it ever since.
So I found the movie on HBO go was pleased to see that. I watched it, it was buried by the sixth sense.
The only reason I could tell that that happened was that because the sixth sense was a good movie.
and this was a derivative boring paint by numbers who gives a fuck I figured it out in the
first 12 minutes. Now maybe I needed to see it 20 years ago when it came out and it would have
had a few more surprises but yeah I mean that's when I saw it I was in high school. I rewatched about
a year back with my lady friend. I was just as enamored with it. I thought it was a great picture.
I think it, uh, from the top of this thing, you know Kevin Bacon's a good guy. You know he didn't
kill this girl. You know that the girl almost immediately means no harm to him or to the family.
So immediately you're like, okay, clearly the girl died in the house. She's trying to get a message
to him, six cents style, solve my murder.
Right.
And then at that point, the only question is,
well, who did what to this girl?
Is it as creepy landlord, which it does turn out
that his landlord was involved?
And yeah.
Whatever, that all being said, bad movie?
No, just something I'll never, ever watch ever again.
I just didn't care.
I thought atmosphericly it did a decent job.
Not too many jump scares, because it was made in a time
when jump scares weren't the only way you were allowed to scare somebody. So I
appreciated that. I thought it was well -acted, but it played for me more like a
good you know like a better episode of like a maybe like a sci -fi
anthology TV show or something. It didn't it didn't resonate for me like a great
film that I'd want on my shelf and want to watch. Fair enough. More than once. I
haven't seen any of the sequels or anything like that. I think they're pretty
diminishing returns. But who starts in the sequels? I don't know. I can check. I'll check.
Well, you, you talk what you were going to say. I'll look. Yeah. I just, I think maybe it was helped
by diminished expectations or something as well because no one talked about it. And I was just like,
man, this is really fucking good. And every time I told a friend, they would watch it and say,
you're right. That was really fucking good. So I'm, I'm disappointed who you say that, Joe.
Yeah, frankly, I knew you would be you got you felt the same for tremors.
Maybe you have an issue with Kevin Bacon.
I love Kevin Bacon.
You got Ilyana Douglas in this thing.
You got Catherine Erb.
Oh, Kevin Dunn, who I always like quite a bit.
Yeah.
And I thought I thought all the flashbacks and like the the football town and then
when you find out what did happen to the girl, it's like really kind of weird
and disturbing and it's very disturbing.
I mean, I don't know.
I thought it was very effective and it's a Richard Matheson story who people seem to love and I would imagine
It's a pretty good and faithful adaptation. I love Richard Matheson. Let's see. We did what I am legend. Yes
Rob Lowe
Stars in stir of echoes to the homecoming
It's only connection to the previous work is the inclusion of Jake Whitsky
Who had a key role in the original film? That's the the kid in the original. Okay
but they just have the kid the kid got separated from his parents this movie comes
out six years after the original roughly seven no eight years excuse me after
the original so he's grown up and the kid is played by a completely different
actor who's a full full age adult at this point okay so it was a straight to
DVD or I I'll tell you this I'll tell you this all right I was on a bit of a
and bacon kick. Yeah. And I saved this. I didn't use this in movie corner. So even with your high
cholesterol, you were on a bacon kick. I, uh, after I watched this, I almost immediately watched the
darkness, starring Kevin Bacon, which the darkness, whoo, never even heard of it. Whoa.
What's the dark? Stars him. Stars the lady on the darkness. Stars the lady from Melinda
in Melinda, the Woody Allen movie who plays Melinda, what?
Plays his wife, the kid who plays Bruce Wayne on Gotham plays the sun.
2016.
Same fucking thing.
They're in a house.
The kids see in visions.
Okay.
What's he seeing?
What's going on?
Well, let me tell you something.
Yeah.
That fucking movie.
I mean, that made stir of echoes.
look like the fucking Presidio or something like, you know, I mean, they made the
Presidio with Mark Harmon. That's your gold standard. I never saw the Presidio. I
just remember it got a little. I've never seen it. I don't even know what it is. I
just remember it got a lot of talk when I was a kid and I thought it was like
supposed to be a good movie. Holy shit. What is it? Don't think it was even
well -reviewed. I just remember the box. It was Mark Harmon and Sean Connery. All right.
It makes it made stir of echoes look like an officer in a gentleman is my point to me this thing the darkness holy Christ
Terrible, I see Paul Reiser was involved Paul Reiser is in it. Yeah who plays an asshole through the entire movie like a sort of likable asshole
but like a jerk like a big mouth and whatever and
Kevin Bacon is like mad at his wife and he's like Paul Reiser plays his boss
There's a scene where they all go at the dinner and the wife was like our sons having problems and Kevin Bacon is basically like
Yeah, we got to go well chick, please
And then they're the car and Bacon's like you can't open you can't get through one goddamn dinner without you talking about our kids problems
Now my boss is gonna think that I'm nuts and I can't you know, he's so offended and
She's like your boss is a loudmouth ass. Holy barrels over people. I don't care what he thinks, you know, whatever
and then like the next scene is Paul Reiser being like,
what's going on buddy?
And Kevin Bacon's like, my son keeps seeing a ghost
and Paul Reiser who plays a loud mouth steam roller
through the entire film goes.
You know, I gotta tell you,
we took our kid once to this shaman.
Make fun all you want.
But we followed a steps and the kid was better.
Just get this lady a call.
And that's how they find the like,
Zelda lady, she got a good shaman recommendation.
It is a fucking polarizer anytime say I've never been I've never been a a darkness guy
I like the light the darkness is not not so much
What is that I remember like his catchphrase on mad about you was of course
I like a Danish don't it's not so much
Not it's not funny not so much with his catchphrase not so much
Mad about you coming back to television as well. It is that's right. Shut the fuck up. I won't
That's true.
Helen Hunt and Paul Reiser, they're still mad about each other after all these years.
They're 75 years old.
Yeah.
What is the show going to be about?
The whole point was that they were like a young married couple.
Right.
I guess now it's the ravages of time, what it does to a marriage.
Incontinence.
I'm developing hiccups.
I'm starving.
I need to wrap this up.
Oh, now who's watching the clock?
Remember when I said let's get to the movies so we can I can't even see the clock
I'm just saying we're over an hour. I was saying the audience isn't helped by you going well
We're at 37 minutes trying to help you out because you can't see the damn clock. All right folks. That's our show
Hey, listen watch
By night origins on Amazon Prime a minute and it turned out well
And I'm happy with it proud of it giving a watch would you please give it a nice review if you like also I'll be at the
The end of May, last week at a mall,
I'll be at a Rooster Tea Feathers in Silicon Valley, California,
and Joe DeRose, a comedy on Twitter and Instagram.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Please send your thoughts that Joe has a little drink
this weekend at my bachelor party,
and if you've got gifts you want to send,
blenders, et cetera, just send them to the hog house.
I'll get them there.
there. That's the end of the show, so we'll see you next time, which we don't know what
the next one will be. No, it's anybody's guess. And we'll see you in hell.