Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Well, hello there. Welcome to, we'll see you in hell. It's a podcast. It's now part
of the Fangoria podcast network. And if you want some more information about the Fangoria
podcast network or other programs or this program or whatever, you fucking go to Fangoria .com.
All right? Good. How's it going, Patty? It's going good. I'm going to call up into the
Microquick. It's going good. Uh, this is the seventh and final episode of our second season,
we're going to be focusing on the sin of envy. Uh, I know we have a lot to discuss,
but before we do, I'm driving over here, uh, and I see on the back of a bus an advertisement
for a pill called prep, right? Sorry. I'm like, well, what the hell's prep? Look a little
closer there's like a bunch of like you know dudes running on the on the pill I
figure it's like an energy pill or something sure I get closer to the to the
bus and I see that it is a pill to keep you HIV negative is what the slogan is
so I look it up I guess this is a pill that you take it's a daily pill that if you
were to insert your dick into an AIDS ravaged hole. Right. You wouldn't get AIDS. And how am I
learning about this pill from a bus? It shouldn't this be national news? Is it real? That can't be real.
It's on a bus. It can't be real. You know, e -sigs were on buses and now there's all this shit coming
out about them. What about them? That they're, you know, they're now getting banned from
all the public places because they actually could be harmful and blah, blah, fuck, who
fucking know? My point is, is you saw ads for those things all over the place. Yeah. It's
still in question. Well, I don't think you can legally claim that you can keep someone
from getting HIV and not be able to back up that claim. Well, how much does it cost?
I don't know. I mean, I'm off the market. I'm not even interested in anymore, but when
I was single I sure would have been to know that you're never going to get HIV. I'm
curious. And I'm going to ballpark a cost here. I'm going to say it's a hundred dollars
a month. It's a it's a single pill taken once daily, highly effective against HIV when
and taking every day.
Are you sure it's not to suppress HIV if you already have it?
Yeah.
Yes.
It's to keep you HIV negative is what the slogan said.
Prep pill cost.
Yeah.
Is?
I'm guessing $100 bucks a month.
They don't usually put this shit online.
How much things cost?
Over the counter?
No, I'm sure it's not.
Prescription.
Oh, without insurance prep costs about $1 ,300 a month.
OK, what about with?
I don't know.
Oh, I mean, how deep we want to go into this.
Well, hey, now is that the, that's not the pill
that the fucking little bastard
that bought the Wu -Teng CD?
No, no, no, no.
Well, his pill was like a medication.
Yeah, he's a medication.
Right.
That guy, I hope, has been beaten to death by now.
He, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he,
You know what I don't even feel like talking about him. No, he's been talking about the death. The
I'm in a while I was in a mood when you walked in. I'm very tired and we were discussing a Twitter thing, right?
You know girl made fun of me on Twitter the other night
She made a shitty comment that that I basically had no talent and
You were on at midnight. Yeah, she said she was a rollback
She watched you on that man. I didn't like your material apparently, which is I didn't see it I won
I'd like to make oh that's great make note of that. I also heard this very podcast got a mention
This very podcast was my plug we're probably talking to 10 maybe 12 new listeners tonight
Now was my name mentioned no, no, what do I have a fucking hour to let you know you got to get the plug in fast
Peter Walsh. Look, maybe a second.
Didn't the audience is going who? And then they missed the title of the audience has gone. That Walsh hangs out with this, chowed.
You know, that ain't, you know, yeah, you get effective, buddy. Effective. All right. Just checking.
Now, had it been you on the show, I would suggest mentioning my name.
That's just the way I'm gonna tell you. Yeah. I feel. But anyway, she said she was having a hard time watching the show because she's rolling her eyes the whole time.
I can't resist. I go to a Twitter feed to see, you know, and then around that is all these other tweets about how I'm so sick of fucking mediocre men having platforms to spew their garbage.
This is the first time I ever watched the show shut it off in five minutes, but I hate it.
She's not miserable and women have that. She's never seen the show. She was basing the entire show with a three man panel on the three man panel, which we do a pretty good job of having men.
They do a great job.
your butthole it's not just for rape anymore okay funny bit yeah I mean it
you mentioned prison and it's a comedy show one of the three people make a
rape exactly you know that exactly so she so anyway she writes hard to
watch the show when I'm rolling Joe DeRose is making me roll my eyes I write
back look on the bright side at least it's at least the roles aren't in your
stomach for once uh -huh which I thought given the circumstances of Twitter
character limitation play on the word role right snappy come back right
the body connection rolling the eyes rolls of fat in the stomach I thought
that was a hell of a comeback it is I winced when you told me about it because
that you can see where it's going you know if you think about a woman who's
talking about the patriarchy and etc. and then you're gonna say she's got rolls of
fat well it's not gonna go well she writes back you're not at a at a roast she
He writes back, oh cute, make fun of a woman's body whatever.
And I go, oh cute, pull the woman card down because you can dish it out but you can't
take it.
She writes something else back.
I write, hey, I don't know what to tell you.
You made a joke at my expense.
I made one that you're, I can't even see your body in the, in the picture.
Yeah.
You see your face.
Uh, and, and then she wrote, if you think that's a joke, maybe try a new line of work, I guess.
It's like, now this fucking, this fucking asshole is assessing my entire career, yeah.
And I go, nope.
But a bit of advice for you.
Maybe don't attack people on here for no reason, and your interactions might be more pleasant.
Sure.
Because at the end of the day, and then I went back and I deleted the tweets, because I'm
like, you know what, I shouldn't have engaged this to begin with, run.
It's just shitty to have this fucking dumb joke floating. I just was like whatever
I mean screen and you probably don't engage with any other positive show
I do engage with some of it. I don't engage with it once in a while
I engage with a negative thing because it just I
Yeah, that engagement was more me laughing and being like right. I'm hitting the ball back to you
And then she takes it right to this fucking gender issue. Yeah, it's like hey sister
here. Fuck you. Okay. You're going to attack my fucking talent. And you think somehow
that's less offensive than me making a fat. I don't even know if you're fat. It's a dumb
fucking joke that I made. Yeah. And then she screen caps it and send it to the show. And
like, yeah, because that's what should happen. I should get, she's like, is this the caliber
of comic you want associated with your program? Because in her head, ultimate justice would
be at midnight saying he could never come on again. Let's also like, is she acting like
at midnight would not host someone who would dare to make a fat joke.
It's not the press show, yeah, it's a show about for comedians to make
dick jokes. It's just look, you know, I, I, I, I think her and her
ilk are people to be avoided in life on Twitter. They, they're not
seeking joy or humor. They're seeking a fight in every interaction.
And there's no point to it. But you going back at her, you can't be
surprised it went this way. No, I'm not. I'm mad at myself for giving it to the passion.
Yeah. I gave him to the passion. You're a passionate man. I don't like it and fucking
singled out like that. Don't fucking single me out. I'm not Jenny McCarthy. I'm not Chris
Hardwick. Yeah, there you go. It was on a single doubt bringing it full circle.
I did later write to her and at midnight and say, Hey, can we get this gala mug in a t -shirt?
okay I know what she's gonna do just fill it up with gravy sit and sip at it all
done then wipe her mouth off with the shirt
We're talking about Joe. It's been a while.
Now, what did we want to start with on NV?
Because we brought it up briefly on the previous episode
and we said we couldn't wait to close with NV
because we had so much to say I was just saying that'll be a juicy topic for us I don't think we
had something in particular well I remember you mentioning billboards around town or something yeah I
asked if the bill billboards for comedy specials bug you we discussed that then but you know because you're
a comedian you see how did this fucker get a get a special but you have a special coming up yeah sure
or you don't feel that envy so strongly.
For me, I try not to, I try not, you know,
I will see this, for the most part,
I'm happy for people when they get stuff.
The only time I get annoyed is when,
when there's clearly a hustle going on,
when I'm being sold something,
like that I'm supposed to think this person's
like a brilliant whatever and it's like,
that's when I start to go, oh fuck you.
Either, and that can either be, you know,
Comedy central trying to tell you somebody's the best comedian of their generation or whatever the fuck it is
What gets to me more is when the person is doing it themselves
lying hustling trying to sell themselves and that goes on a lot in this town where you will know that someone is not funny is not talented
Can't write can't act can't can't tell jokes whatever the case may be
They get fired from every job they have and
And yet they keep getting work and it goes on and on and on because they're able to hustle and lie and
Could jewel and that is not an envy because they don't envy that life which must be
Just miserable lying to everyone that you meet knowing that your lies could come back to get you
Etc. It's a haunt you to stay on the horror theme right to haunt you
I don't envy that life, but I do when I see someone undeserving getting success
It drives me a little crazy and sometimes can like lose a week for me
Where this mentally go off the grid? It's a little less about envy a
Little more about winning justice to be served justice my therapist talks to me all the time about
My desire for justice and how maybe I was treated unjustly by
bullies or
Family or whatever the case may be as a child and it puts me on high alert for injustice
us. I have a hard time treating you properly. No, no shit. I know. Speaking of which, if we can
just side note for a second. Side note for a second. This is probably the first episode
of the show that we're doing alcohol free because Pat is on a goddamn fucking cleanse.
And it just irritates the shit out of me when you do these cleanses. I don't know why it
makes me so mad.
Yeah, it's just because I like having a great time with you really, but I also like having
a great time.
There couldn't be anything less helpful to me when I'm doing this than constantly asking
me to drink or to eat a girlfriend's baking up delicious treats never bakes anything baking
it up.
We got a simmering crock pot of pulled pork out last night.
I'm like, what the fuck is this?
You know how to make pulled pork?
Smelling up the damn house like it just drives you crazy
I do it for two weeks a year. I drop 20 pounds every year I gain 20 pounds
I lose 20 pounds roughly is that healthy? No, but it's what I do. I don't know what to tell you
I don't you try to fucking control yourself for the rest of the year
So you don't have to go on this cleanse. No, I do that as well
It's just it makes me feel good my skin looks better my I have more energy it just resets the clock
I get to a point every year where I'm like stress and I have deadlines and shit and I'm just eating too much and drinking too much and
Smoking too much and doing everything too much, and I just need to reset and take a step back. I'll tell you you've been there
You picked a hell of a time to do the cleanse at the tail end of your vacation
I mean really this is the most fun time. We were talking about taking a trip after the desert. We had all this we're going to
When? I just thought I need to quickly do it now because it involves waking up and
Drinking a bunch of saltwater and shitting for for an hour. Right. It doesn't really go well with the work schedule
I get free launch at work. I don't want to pass that up. God for bid
But look I
Listen to hell of a party tonight, buddy. I'll tell you that my friends have an a birthday party. It starts at midnight
Where's that at?
Uh, a friend of ours, a mutual friend of ours has a, like a comedy improv room or whatever command she owns it.
Emeline. No, no, no. This woman we know owns it.
Who? You don't know her. You said a mutual friend of ours? No, of me and the birthday person.
Oh, sorry, I didn't pick that up. When you look me in the eye and say a mutual friend of ours.
Oh, you didn't pick it up because you're dizzy from being on this goddamn water diet that you're doing.
I feel great and you look great, especially in this position you're lying in right now sort of a bird Reynolds and play girl
It's half Reynolds half Cleopatra. Yeah, I don't know which way to go with this
Sure, we have a friend that owns a venue. The friend is
The you know opening the venue at like midnight off hours and we're going in and doing karaoke. Okay, and
hitting it hard, boozing it up for the birthday.
My friend's got an ATM flight out of town.
She, the emails said, let's make this difficult.
Yeah.
I mean, she's ready to burn.
I got a bottle of Jamison uncracked over there
that I'll be bringing to the party.
I mean, I could possibly go.
I don't, there you go.
You know, I'm going to see the who this evening,
which I was very much made fun of yesterday.
Do you still have a spare ticket?
No.
Who's going with you?
I sold it.
Oh, okay.
I might not see it. I looked on stubble. I was like, oh shit, that's going for a ton of money. I'll just fucking sell it and go to the show. My night got freed up.
It's fine. I'll take a nap. So you didn't say you were busy. You mocked me for wanting to see
one of history's greatest rock bands before they die. We mock each other. That's what we do. You were mocking me. We mock each other. We do.
You got to admit seeing the who right now isn't going to be the best way of seeing the who. I'm sorry.
Have you seen them on like they they pop up every so often an American Idol or some shit like that?
Yeah, it's never that great. It looks like Roger Daltry's chest has had a facelift. Right. It probably is enough. It looks odd like Pete Townsend is still pretty cool
Except for the perhaps kiddie porn dungeon. I you know what? I believed his story on that he never
Offended again. It was a one -time thing and I believed him
He was like I was trying to see like what was going on because I wanted to make a documentary about it
But now I thought he was doing like a rock opera about it, but no he was he was molested as a kid
He was molested, right? And he said he wanted to do a documentary exposing what's going on out there
Yeah, I was like I was trying to find like sites to see like that. I could expose I believe that all right
It's just
And plus you know when you're that old you don't think the internet is gonna keep a record of everything you do
No, he didn't even know he was looking. He thought he was looking at a light bright
He didn't know what the Hollywood was looking at life's bright, especially when you're
that famous by the way, he could say, you know, yeah, bring me the fresh butthole of
a child.
Right.
That's his thing, and he's got people that could make it happen, probably.
Elijah Wood just gave some interview where he talked about, it was careful to say that
he was not molested, but that the biggest problem in Hollywood, he thinks bigger than anything
else is pedophiles.
I've heard this and Corey Feldman has gone on and on about that about how
These vipers as he calls them including of course his dear friend Michael Jackson, which we all know about now
We're it is strange. He was a big proponent of Mike. Yeah, I don't think any more
But he was at the funeral and
See, I mean, you know Michael Jackson McCulley Culkin had their period as well. You know you look at McCulley now
Now you got to think maybe something happened there.
Elijah was like my mom looks somehow looks like Mark Hamill at the end of the new
star wars.
He does.
And there's a 30 year gap there easily.
I don't know what the fuck McColle's doing man.
It's a shame because as a 10 year old boy he had better comedic timing than most people
who are 40 years old still doing it.
Yeah I know.
He was incredible.
I was a little disappointed in that funnier dive video they did.
I wanted that to be funnier when he was the grown -up Kevin Macaulister.
I didn't see it. Yeah. Yeah, that doesn't matter.
Sorry. Go ahead. Sorry.
But yeah, to say something is the biggest problem in Hollywood, which is easily the most
fucked up industry there is, is kind of insane. That means that Elijah Wood knows of and saw
a lot of pedophilia going on. Yeah. Well, the Brian Singer thing was very quickly buried,
But I sort of know from which I would not dare of even mentioning the way I know this person
But some kid who was like
17 years old or something and he said Brian Singer was like had him at a
paid his rent out here in L .A. for three years and he just come in and fuck him and leave. I completely a hundred percent believe the Brian Singer stuff is true
Yeah
from
A lot of hearsay, but you know we both have some hearsay on the problem the problem is with anything else
when anybody does anything rot in this town.
To prove it, or to go to the lengths of trying to prove any of it, would be virtually impossible.
It would cost you an amount of money you would probably never see in a lifetime.
And it would destroy your life.
So it's a very, very hard fight to fight, and you're going up against people with a thousand
times your money.
You're not going to win.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's disgusting bureaucratic system of pigs, and all you can do is hope that you
do the right thing.
And if you encounter something bad, you can talk about your own situation, but who of
us is going to launch a campaign against Brian Singer?
What's a town?
I also think there's a, I'm not saying Brian Singer would have you killed, but I mean it's
not another realm of possibility in this town that somebody could have you murdered for
something like that.
Yeah, I feel like that happened much more in the 50s, but I'm sure it still happens.
I was gambling this weekend.
I won another large sum of money, and they had a giant poster up, I was at Planet Hollywood
at a giant frame poster of Frank Sinatra in a shirt and pants with a giant gun on a holster
like looking out with a big smile on his face.
And I was like that, maybe that was a better time.
Uh, big picture wise, I don't think it was socially
on the small picture I think it was.
Yeah, you know, big picture wise, you had a lot,
you know, women's rights were, women were worse off
than any minority group was worse off.
We're sure, you know, but in a social setting,
you take a guy where I could say,
Hey, I'm not subscribing to the ideals of the South where the general sexist whatever
Right, you know, and you had the right to individually go against those things. I think it was a better time
I'd rather be in a fucking bar
And somebody starts talking shit and you go let's go fight. Yeah, I agree. Can't do it anymore. You can't I and you know
I look you look around I'm at a really nice casino the cause of Paul and you look around and there's like, you know, there's
girls gambling and bikinis, which is great, A, but also it's kind of like, put a fucking dress on.
Like no one, no one's there in a suit is what I'm saying and Vegas used to be like, you dress up, you go out.
You go to any restaurant in L .A., people in flip flops and shorts, and you know, I don't go that extreme, but I dress down, go into these places too, because I'm like, well, I'm not gonna be the chump standing out.
No, I mean, you look at a picture in the 50s, every hamburger stand, every guy's got a shirt and tie on, it's kind of sad.
We live in a time of pigs it's a real shit diarrhea show out there and there's
really no hope in it getting better it'll continue to get worse yeah as it
always has and of course all you can do is have a good time that's where I don't
get this cleanse just have some fun well I will have a better time in my social
interactions and etc if I if I drop a little excess weight that I put on
throughout the year I'm just I was just making a joke and sometimes you know
You're off drinking or whatever else it did it happened. I got to tell you it's very rarely these days
It's much rarer these days than it used to be like a one week on one week off kind of guy
Yeah, there was a time. I just I don't care anymore. Yeah, I like having drinks. I don't do it every day
Yeah, all right. I don't think I do at least
But right now also too like I'm not you know if I'm on I'm not I'm in between I'm not on a writing job now
I'm not on the road, so when I have these stretches at home without anything, any commitments
besides doing my sets and writing here in the apartment, it feels kind of like a vacation
to me.
It is.
You know, then I go back on the road and it's like, I gotta get a little more focused.
Yeah, I mean, you and I both have lives that even when working sort of can feel like vacations,
That's that's why I don't feel a
Struggle with envy I
Don't nice way to bring it back unless I think we were ever going back
I gotta be honest we were so far away from it at this point
No, we weren't we were you know
We're talking about people were disgusted with which to me if you want to call it a bastardized version of envy then fine because
None of these people I don't envy the pedophile who gets away with it for a hundred years
I don't envy what that soul must look like
I don't envy Bill Cosby, you know, like did he live his life?
How he wanted to for seven years, he sure did, is he going to enjoy the winding down of
his life?
I sure hope not.
And it seems like a big no, like these people have to live with what they've done.
So I don't envy it.
It's really a rough scene reading those transcripts from the depositions, yeah, just like, did
She masturbate you with lotion. Yeah, yeah, like yes, like it's just it's creepy and then now it's all underage girls is coming out
Boy, it's just gonna keep spiraling and he's not gonna have to pay for any of it. I don't think
Well, I don't know the trial in Montgomery County where I grew up the courthouse my hometown courthouse is where the trials happening
All right, and it is happening
it is happening. It works there. How could he get off? There'll be another riot.
What do you mean, how could he get off? How could he get off with the amount of
evidence we have here? Well, we don't have, I don't, I don't know what evidence
there is pertaining to that trial, but I mean that is going to trial. Yeah. So that
could be the one sort of, you know, now it is a sexual assault -related trial, but
I feel like that could be the sort of Al Capone thing where it might not be the heaviest allegation. Yeah, or maybe it is
I don't know, but if it's not it could be the thing that puts him away and I
Mean I hope you just fucking kills himself before it gets there. What a fucking loser. Uh, I mean
No, I don't want him to kill himself. He should have to go to jail and pay for something
But he will though like that's just the perfect cowards out for him as to kill himself
Yeah, but then he doesn't have any pun it. There's no punishment
You know way, then it's like that's like then it's not on his
It's supposed to go to hell. There's no hell
We'll see you and hell we sure will there is no I mean, you know
You know what I'm saying. It's like come on. He's got to suffer a little bit man. No, I agree
I
Can't believe the poise the fucking guy has to roll this. Oh, he's deceased. He's discussed it with us for daring
to rain on his parade that's the attitude he has it's shocking to me it is how
dare you I guess you all want your hot gossip huh it's like no you you
raped minimum a hundred women what do you you don't get to talk down to us
anymore yeah no it's you've been doing it for 30 years but that's enough
I had earth shattering you know I always said when Zeppelin got what all the stuff
came out about how they stole the songs I was like the only thing I mean like
They pulled from blues songs that way or something.
Oh, there's, I mean, you go on YouTube.
There's countless, right, countless examples of them,
just stealing music.
They're finally going to trial for stuff like,
really?
Yeah, there's something, uh, I didn't know about that.
Something's finally coming up legally where it's like,
they might get in trouble now for,
it's for stairway to heaven, particularly.
Yeah.
But my point is, is when I was ever a big Zeppelin fan,
so when that came out, I was like, man,
the only way I could relate to this, I think,
is if I found out that Richard Pryor stole all his
material right and thankfully that is not what happened but something almost as
devastating to me well it's I understand that rape is much worse than stealing
yeah I just wasn't as I wasn't as big a fan of Cosby as I was of Richard
Prior right my point is is pretty devastating to me to see this this whole thing
collapse with this guy because you're just like that sucks he was a demon the
whole time I looked up to this guy yeah I think that if we truly knew
what went on with a lot of people some of them are heroes we would be pretty
fucking disgusted and probably not like them as much I agree with that they
recently did some big thing trying to expose Bill Murray about how he had
beaten an ex -wife and all of her allegations and I had heard from a pretty
reliable source that Bill Murray was punching a woman who was down on the
ground on the streets of New York with like people trying to pull them off of her at one point.
And the Bill Murray thing just kind of fly off, you know, you don't want to believe it, you can't
believe it. I don't know if either of those things are true, but his wife was alleging these things
during a messy divorce, so who knows. But like something like that, what do you do? What do you
all and it's starting to seem like people are getting more and more vocal about that?
Well, what do you do? I still, I still stand with the opinion that I don't think
Woody Allen did it.
I really don't.
Yeah.
Rowan Farrow's latest piece against Woody Allen came out conveniently during the premiere
of Woody Allen's latest movie at the Cannes Festival.
Right.
Now, I know that's how that stuff works and you got to put it out there at the right time
whatever.
But, you know, according, you could use Rowan, is it Rowan or Rowan, whatever, Rowan.
them. You could use his argument against his argument. His whole thing is, well, I guess
the celebrities never have to pay. And fame is the opinion that we will, you know, we'll
dictate the opinion. We'll let's do it. It's like, well, dude, you have a brother that
has said the polar opposite of what you're saying. And it's contradicted everything you and
your mother are saying. And saying is, in fact, that she is brainwashed you and many of
other children in that house and this is all lie. Right. But nobody knows about that because
that guy's like a lawyer and you're Ronin, Ronin Farrow. You know what I mean? Farrow.
So it's all, you know, I got to just tell you Pat, everything just disgusts me. Sure.
I just, you know, I just hate everything. And I'm envious. What do you envy? I envy people.
Honestly, I envy people that are too aloof to not care about this. Well, no, it's not true. I don't envy people that are too aloof to not care about the state of thing. I sometimes envy the stupidity of a person who was able to just go through their day and not be affected by every little thing and not be like, ah, you fucking kid me with this traffic, you kid me with this asshole.
Well, there's a difference this asshole is getting this job. Are you kidding me? He's you know
Oh, here's the thing there are stupid people and aloof people that that sort of stuff doesn't affect
But then the person I truly envy is the person that understands what's happening can process it and
Knows how to compartmentalize it and not let it fuck their day up
That's who I envy because I'll tell you man
It doesn't take much for me to just want to not even leave the house. Yeah, you know one weird interaction at a taco stand or
or, you know, at the coffee shop or whatever,
somebody shoves in line in front of me,
somebody, you know, doesn't say thank you.
I mean, I'll just be like, did the world's fucked?
I just can't stand it.
Yeah.
You know, and that's a major fault of mine.
So that's who I envy.
I envy the person that can go through.
And just, and I also envy the people
that don't beat themselves up,
because as much as I like to go out
and have some fun as a bachelor or whatever,
there's always the self -deprecation
in the judgment that I inflict on myself with, you know, why aren't you married yet
or should you be settled down or you're too old for this shit, blah, blah, blah.
You know, and then every, without fail, every time I say that to one of my married friends
they go, stop beating yourself up, you know, having a great time, it'll happen when it happens
and enjoy yourself, trust me, just have fun.
Well, then you'll get married and have kids and be like, why didn't I enjoy myself more?
Well, that's what I'm saying.
I don't have a way to live. Yeah, I don't want to do that. So those are my top two. But you will like that's the that's the types of
personalities we have and it's it's awful, but that's the truth. All right. Well, so there's no hope as I said before. There's no happiness. You
forget that you are unhappy when you, you know, diarrhea shit show, as I said, I went back to New York and I was like, you know, I went
there very recently and I was like, boy, when I was here 10 years ago, that's when I was truly happy and on top of the
world and everything. And I'm like, no, you were miserable and broken. What are you talking about?
Right. You just romanticize different times in your life. Stupid. You're in your
NVS of yourself. And you shouldn't be. You try to enjoy what you have. I think the point of all
these things is enjoy what you have and don't do anything to access is the point of these seven
deadly sins. But I completely disagree with the excess part. Except I see where being NVS to
access is bad for you but like as we discuss with gluttony if you're not being
gluttonous once in a while I don't think you're living life no you gotta yeah
it's when you do it constantly yeah that it hurts you sorry I just stand up
here and look because there's a spider behind you I need to make sure it wasn't
like a tick is it gonna leap into my hair hey hope so a rack of
love you spice to this day yeah I mean it's I agree Pat I think the point of
these seven podcasts has been, have fun.
Do what you gotta do.
Yeah.
Do what you wanna do.
Don't hurt other people and don't hurt yourself.
Yeah.
And excess can lead to that.
Well, but what type of person are you most jealous of?
Well, I was trying to think on the way over here,
like I love my house, my job, my friends, my girlfriend,
friend, etc. I'm not envious of people in that way. I don't think, oh, I wish I had
a bigger house. I don't think, oh, I wish I had, you know, I used to think to myself
some friend to show up and be dating like a model or something. It still happens in a
lay at happens all the time. You're like, how did this loser get this girl? What's going
on? And I would be jealous. I guess until you spend 10 minutes with them, you're like, oh,
they are completely miserable. This girl is awful. She's controlling of him. He
hates his life right now. You just got to dig a little deeper into these situations and
the envy goes away. Instagram now, Facebook creates these things where people will brag
about their fucking lives or show some picture of me and my boo out on the boat. And when
you get to know these couples, as I do in some cases, well, you're like, oh no, wait a minute,
I've spent time with you guys. You're putting these pictures out to create some
image of yourself to make everyone jealous of you which is a part of it
whether they would admit it or not makes people envious of you and also act like
you've got your shit together and you have this great life. But if you spend
five minutes with these people they have huge problems. The more a couple posts
about their love and how crazy they are about each other, the more things are
really going to shit and rotting inside in my opinion. My friend my friend
Rachel Feinstein, who's a very funny comic.
Yes, I like her special.
Yes, watch her special, only whores wear purple.
It's out now.
Comedy Central, I think it's on Amazon.
You can watch it, too.
But she's great.
But she said once about, we knew a guy who was married and had
kids and was always just telling you about his family
and whatever.
And one day, she said, I've never met anybody that
tries so hard to make you think he's happy.
And it's like, yeah, that's exactly what that is.
like I know several people like that and it when you when you can pick at it that's when you
realize that what's going on is just a façade you don't feel that envy and then you're like oh no
this is actually way sadder than what I'm dealing with go yeah um oh yeah
But it's the dumb people you know that I worry about it's when it's when you see you
know the Kardashians are an easy target or whoever else who still claim publicly in interviews
that they've had no plastic surgery they didn't have any ass implants or anything like that.
And they put these pictures up so girls are doing 8 billion squats a day trying to get their asses to act like that
When they won't and can't these Instagram models some girl finally went off and explained that each of her pictures requires like three hours of prep and
Filters and doctoring she looked insanely hot in the pictures, right, but then you see her and she's like kind of normal looking
But then as these little because it's not all guys following hot girls Instagram. It's girls like for hashtag body goals
who follow these beautiful girls and they're trying to get their bodies to look like these girls,
and they can't because through the work of Photoshop, filters, and plastic surgery,
they look like completely unattainable people.
Yeah, no, it's absurd.
It's absurd.
It's a lady, stop doing it to yourself.
It creates much more envy.
And, you know, like, look, I know that at times, men are at fault of making women feel
they have to live up to that standard.
Now it's an open playing field.
Women are just as guilty of making themselves feel like that.
As men have been previously, it's like stop doing it to yourself, like just be you.
Yeah.
Yeah, the, you know, every girl's obsessed now with an ass, getting a bigger ass.
Years ago it was tits, you know, it's just whatever anyone says is now suddenly cool, everyone's
focused on.
It's kind of crazy.
Rap kind of dictates it in an odd way.
Whatever they're talking about in rap becomes like the thing.
Well, who knew that Sir Mixellot was a prophet?
A foreseer.
Who's a prophet?
to come. You know why either. We learned it. I think we learned a nice lesson here today.
I really do. I think we learned that both of us are far less envious than maybe we feared we were
initially. And it makes me feel pretty goddamn good. Yes, my envy is anger at the undeserving
getting things that they don't deserve. And really all that does after all that anger and frustration
at the world, at some horrifically unfunny person,
getting some job, getting some deal, whatever.
All it really does is make me go,
but you know you're so much funnier and more talented,
so just do the work and then you'll be better off.
And it makes you work.
And my envy is at the people that don't let,
you know, the guy that,
oh God, can you give me an example here?
You know my envy is the guy that can go to the growth of the guy that can go to the grocery store and
Get an attitude when he's trying to return the fish that they sold him that was rotten when they sold it to right
Not letting that destroy his day. Yeah. No, I have to that as well
Well, I was trying to my own because you had your own, but you can take mine too, Pat
I'm just merely agreeing and I would think you'd agree with mine as well. I do. I didn't quite fully grab a tuned out half
It's part of the way through but I sounded like I got it
Yeah, it's just you know when I you know, I have some success when I
Reach the next level whatever that may be I will know I got there off of talent and not off of lying
That makes me feel good that makes me
Comfortable with the envy that I feel because it drives me on. I'm gonna say this person is not happy. They know they got there through
false pretenses. I hear you. This person, that person, and it's and it's acting
and everything else. Actors in this town are like, how did that guy get in
other parties? A terrible actor? I can almost can't be friends with actors.
Yeah, it's that's a tough game. The amount of envy in that job. You know, the
writing world is sort of bad enough, but the acting world is perhaps worse.
Comedians are like everybody's like that unfortunately, and I'm just very
happy that I don't partake in it to anywhere near the extent that I used to.
And then I guess at an office, people are like, how the fuck did he get promoted?
He's an asshole, he's a kiss ass.
I mean, it goes on everywhere, I would assume.
Well, I would say this also this, you know, in summary of all seven of these sins, Prozek is
the answer.
Prozek is what made me start doing these things with proper limitations and enjoying
them instead of doing them to complete excess with terrible guilt and self -loathing and
whatever else.
I tell you, I still haven't done it, but I always think about it.
Change my life for the better with 100 % you see go off of it. I go why do you go off of it? Yeah, it's just
Stay on it forever. Who cares? What do you pay a year for pros? I?
$4 a month or something
$10 a month. Yeah, you get the generic kind. It's it's nothing even if you don't have insurance. It's like 10 dollars
Yeah, you know, I'm like yeah, I mean, I can't imagine you without it at this entire time. You've been on
Let's just be in God damn nightmare. You don't even know, buddy. Yeah. You don't even know. I
I tear the whole hang out down if I wasn't if I wasn't in the mood. I was sure. I wasn't.
I still had friends and I was well liked, but I had a dark side that I wasn't very proud of.
Emotional dark side, I should say. Listen. Pat is enjoyable as it's been talking about all these
sins for these last seven episodes. I greatly and eagerly look forward to our return to movies.
Yeah, just movies. Starting next month. If only I knew who came up with the idea for this
seven deadly sins format change, we could really write him an angry letter. Yeah, it was me and
and we're exhibiting pride right now,
which makes me want to exhibit wrath.
Yeah.
So we're gonna go back to the new format
that's gonna be of Not Mistaken.
You and I both watch a movie
before Sepulair together
and then we discuss it, correct?
It'll be, yes.
It'll be, I sent you the new description
and essentially the new description
is it's like Cisco and Ebert
except Meanor and Grumpier and with more cursing.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, it's Pat and I very much agree on movies a lot of the time and very much
disagree on movies a lot of the time.
So the new format will be us discussing movies, some of them contemporary, some of them
classics, but you know, now we can kind of cover, will they be horror?
They will all be within the realm of horror, sci -fi or fantasy because all that relates to
the Fangoria, but you know, it kind of opens up the doors for us to kind of talk about
any movie we want that falls within those categories, and maybe even some of the episodes
we do a few movies, you know, the way the way SNE used to, if you will.
But I think for sure our first episode will probably be Blade Runner because you and I both
seemed to despise the film.
Hate it.
And I feel like we just got a lot to talk about on that.
And we got it aside and we'll let's decide right now.
I own four versions of it on the same Blu -ray.
Which one am I supposed to fucking watch?
Directors, which we watched the original,
to be honest with you.
There's no fucking way I'm watching it again.
I watched the goddamn thing.
It's been too long for me.
I won't be able to talk comfortably about it
so I got to re -watch it.
I own what supposedly is the best version of it.
I can't get through the fucking thing. All right, so what should we tell them we're watching the theatrical release or the director's cut doesn't matter
What's it matter?
They there's massive changes between them. We're gonna talk all things blade runner
All right fun. Yeah, well one of the things I want to talk about is how everybody goes
Oh, you got to see this version. Yeah, once somebody starts saying that about a movie. It's not a good movie
Yeah, did it have the narration was the unicorn in it like you know what they're all they're all really bad
I've seen at least two versions of it. It's boring as shit. So we'll probably do Blade Runner
as the first one. And I have a feeling the fans have spoken. The consensus seems to be that
everybody's favorite thing is when we talk about movies and especially when we disagree about movies.
Yeah. And we've got a lot to disagree about. I mean, I want to do a Batman Superman episode.
I'm not going to watch that again, but you don't have to watch it again.
We had a long argument about on the air Batman. I'd like to devote a whole episode to it
I want to do the Star Wars prequels as an episode
You know, yes, that sounds great. You don't have to rewatch all these you've seen them
I think it would be good for us to go in as experts if we're gonna talk for an hour about a movie
Well, I didn't see the Star Wars prequels seven times in theaters as you nobody said experts first of all and let's not commit to any
Time frame right now. Let's just enjoy it. Let's just do it as we do it all right
We'll start with this negative shit before we even go down the road
I mean, you know, I want to recommend a couple movies real quick the nice guys with Russell Crowe and Ryan Gosling is not a
Masterpiece as some would lead you to believe, but it's really fun and really funny. I had a great time with it
Sing Street isn't probably my favorite movie of the year
Terrible title, but it's about you know a group of like 16 -year -old kids in the 80s who decide they want to be a band like the cure
or it was so funny, amazing music in it.
They played the song that inspired each song
that they kind of rip off, leading into their song.
It was an amazing gimmick in the whole movie.
I thought it was perfect.
He has a relationship with his brother
that had me almost in tears.
I loved the movie.
And then Joe and I both,
although we still haven't talked about it,
that's three times what you thought.
Saw a grain room.
I loved it.
You didn't see it.
No, I didn't go that night.
I was gonna go and but I didn't eat too much pie the diner and I felt tired and I went home
So I still haven't seen it. Greenroom is excellent. Especially, you know talking about the horror genre
It's it's a real thrill rod. I want to see it the type of horror movie it is
I'm not a big thriller guy. So, you know, I'll watch it
But it wasn't when I felt like I had to get to the theater to see whereas the conjuring two which comes out in two weeks
I will be there opening weekend
I'll be there for that tube a green room almost seems like it was made for you
It's really it's about the hardcore punk world. It's about like there's no way you wouldn't like it
Let's see it. I know I like it. I'll go see it two minutes away get off my back. It's not there anymore
We took it out. Well, you only had six weeks
A week let's not exaggerate we thought you sure saw Captain America though didn't you well?
I was gonna go see green room three times
I was going to see green room and by the way fuck Captain America. I didn't like it. Yeah, I haven't seen it yet
Well, don't waste your time
Folks, this has been
We'll see you in hell the season two finale and what a finale it was season three starts in June
With that return to a movie related format. We look forward to it
We will be back kicking things off with Blade Runner and maybe another movie who knows
If you want to follow me on Twitter, it's Joe DeRosa Comedy, my website, JoeDeRosaComedy .com
and I will be coming to your town in June, a lot of touring coming up, Denver, Colorado,
Comedy Works, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, the punchline, opening weekend, first weekend
ever at that club, I am headlining it.
The saint in Asbury Park, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore, Alturbore,
Check my website for details
That's you got anything
Sounds good to me Joe. I I'm on Twitter Vine Instagram at the Patrick Walsh
I don't really have anything else to plug coming up. All right
Well, you've been listening to we'll see you in hell it's a presentation of the fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFaio
Executive produced by Ken Haley a fangoria entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiries and information about we'll see you in hell contact
Back to Ken, is email us at www .canditfangeria .com.
Thank you.
Thanks again.