I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, welcome to We'll See You in Hell. Back for the month of March. Two different men today discussing a motion picture called A Different Man.
A movie that I have called 50 different titles in the six months since it's been released. A Serious Man, A Single Man, A Different Day. I just, there's too many titles and too many sound exactly the same.
This movie shouldn't even be called...
Called A Different Man. That's not a right title for this movie.
I think it's, couldn't be more on the nose.
I hate it. It's just, it's too generic for what it is. Like, yeah, it's too bland, it's too boring. And we have had movies, A Single Man with Colin Firth, A Serious Man, which is one of the Coen brothers' most underrated movies.
Every Jason Statham movie is a something man. There's that Vin Diesel, A Man Apart, whatever it is.
Enough.
What's the Woody Allen one? Rational Man or something?
Irrational Man.
That's the one where Parker Posey invites him up to smoke some grass in 2024 or whatever year that came out.
What's the Vin Diesel A Something Man?
I'm gonna look that up.
I don't know. I don't know.
A gorgeous man. A very hot man.
Vin Diesel, does he only do the fasts now?
I guess, and he's the voyeur.
He's the voice of Groot.
Yeah, I think he's just enjoying life at this point. I mean, those fasts must, I feel like the whole cast of those fasts, that's all they do. I feel like it must take the life out of you for, you probably work out like eight hours a day for 12 months and then you shoot it and you're catching on fire every other day and crawling out of wrecks.
Yeah, your whole day's work is gone like, stop!
And they're like, that's a wrap on Vin Diesel.
Vin Diesel, like no talent required of any kind. I stopped seeing them. They were fun for a minute, but I was never into them. I really got annoyed when all the nerds that mocked those movies suddenly were telling me that they were badass and tons of fun and I needed to go see them. I was like, oh, fuck off.
Yeah, it used to coincide with like the Onion AV Club. Whatever they said became what all these fucking loosers.
Loosers decided was their new gospel. Now I don't know what the cool website is that everybody parrots, but everybody just has the exact same opinion on everything. So when the tide shifted around Fast 10, I had the exact same experience. All my cool friends were suddenly like, no, man, these are like tongue in cheek. They know how it's funny. They get it.
Shut up.
I'm like, no, you just decided that. You just decided to go along with everyone else in America and have fun with them.
And after making fun of them for a decade, I don't have to suddenly like this horse shit because public perception changed.
Yeah.
A Man Apart was the Vin Diesel movie. I fell asleep when watching it and I don't know how it ended, but it was very bad.
Well, speaking of man movies.
Yeah.
They just announced that I got the link here. Let me let me go to the link.
But they just announced that they're re not remaking, but they're doing a new version of the Elephant Man.
Theatrically movie wise.
Yeah. Another movie. Just when you thought it was just when you thought they were out of reboots.
Now, let me ask you this. Are they going to cast the actor from the movie we're discussing today or are they going to put Bradley Cooper in makeup again?
That I don't know. Bradley Cooper did not wear makeup on Broadway.
It's typically the play is.
It's typically performed without makeup with pictures of the actual guy, Joseph Merrick, being projected behind them.
Oh, this I don't know. I have no idea how they'll do it.
But Jack Houston, who is an actor from Boardwalk Empire at American Hustle, is helming the remake of David Lynch's bio.
They're calling it. I hate when they do this, when they say it's a it's not a remake.
It's another movie about a guy that existed.
Yeah.
Remake. It's just another.
Yeah. My guess is you're not going to try to make the artistic statement that David Lynch did because you will fail.
So it'll probably just be a straightforward biopic.
So anyway, Jack Houston, the right show is for MovieWeb.
I don't know. He's excited to make this thing.
But here's the thing.
I'm glad he's excited.
It's called. This is the part that made me laugh.
It's called Joseph Merrick.
It's the name of the movie, which sounds like it's going to be a John Wick style, which I'd watch.
You said we're doing Elephant Man, John Wick.
Joe, I got to tell you more than more than I want to see any remake of anything.
I want to see an Elephant Man where he kicks ass.
I mean, that sounds like a 30 rock bit, but I would love to see that.
He gets made fun of until the third act when he snaps.
I don't think we're far from it.
It's like a package.
It's like my trunk, mate.
He's putting all these weapons into his suitcase.
Yeah.
Love it.
So anyway.
Speaking of Brad Cooper, do you watch the Righteous Gemstones?
No.
It's a funny show.
I mean, to me, Eastbound and Down is Danny McBride's masterpiece and will never be equaled.
I kind of liked Vice Principals.
It had some great moments.
And I enjoy Righteous Gemstones week to week.
It's one of the few shows going for laughs.
Mm -hmm.
You know, still being a.
Comedy and a hard R comedy at that.
So it's the final season.
I tune into the premiere this week being like, man, I could really use a fucking laugh tonight.
Thank God the Gemstones are back.
Some big, stupid comedy.
And it's Danny McBride directed it and was one of the three writers.
It is a half hour Civil War drama.
Starring Bradley Cooper, who is not in the cast.
And when I looked him up.
He had never seen the show before.
He's playing an early Gemstone.
So it's like Gemstone's origins or whatever.
Yeah.
I've seen the announcements of that.
And they didn't make it funny, though.
I was like, that sounds funny.
It's not funny.
No.
So I'm like, I hate when shows do this, especially for a premiere.
You're all excited to see everybody again.
And they give you some thing that nobody wants.
But I'm like, OK, they got Bradley Cooper.
It must be pretty good.
But there was not a joke attempt in the entire half hour.
And maybe somebody could argue with me and say this was funny or that was.
But no, there was no attempt at comedy.
So clearly, to me, it was just Danny McBride saying, I want to become the next David Gordon Green and start directing dramatic features.
I better use this episode of my show as like a sample.
But we all have to watch this shit.
It was so boring.
And I like Bradley Cooper.
Forget not being funny.
If it was actually like moving.
Or had an interesting story or theme or anything.
But I hated it.
I don't know why shows can't just tell the fucking story they're telling anymore.
Sopranos didn't start going into like arthouse territory until the very end.
And it was only to make the show deeper and more resonant.
Like the older I get, the more fascinated I am by the late in the series choices that show made.
But Gemstones, I don't get it.
I don't get anything.
I don't get anything anymore.
I'm trying with Severance.
And as cool as it looks, every time I get home from work, I'm like, boy, I'd rather die than watch another episode of Severance.
It's too dense.
It's very well done.
But it's like watching every episode.
It's like watching a David Mamet procedural.
You're like, it's too heavy, man.
I'm like, you know.
Yeah.
I was showing.
We need to laugh.
M -A -ha -ha -A.
M -A -H -A -H -A -H -A -A.
My ex -girlfriend, she was saying she had never really seen it.
She'd seen some of It's Always Sunny, but she hadn't seen a lot of it.
Yeah.
So I was showing her episodes, and we were laughing our asses off.
And we were just scrolling through the Hulu, you know, the seasons.
And she saw the Mac Finds His Pride title.
And she goes, oh, Mac turns out to be gay?
And I was like, yeah, they tease it for a long time.
He finally comes out.
And she goes, is that episode?
Is it funny?
And I go, not really.
And I hate it.
Because they were, it's clearly the penance episode,
where they had made fun of the idea of him being gay for so long.
They're like, we better do one where we show that he's very proud of it.
Yeah.
But it's like, guys, but that's not what the show is.
It's not the tone of it.
I don't, it's just, can't you just do it in a funny way?
Can't you show him be prideful in a funny way?
Like, it's too much.
I got to see his head doesn't accept him.
What's that?
They had that all built into that character.
Raised Catholic, you know, still very religious, Catholic shame, whatever else.
So, yeah, it did sort of seem like more a Hollywood tip of the hat
than an actual grounded route for that character to take.
Yeah, have him go to church.
Yeah.
And yell at, have it, look, look at the way Ellen did it.
You know, not so Ellen.
She did it on her sitcom.
It was really funny.
Where she's like, it's all this big secret.
Yeah.
And when she finally says I'm gay, she, she's accidentally says it into the microphone in
the department store or whatever.
And everybody hears it like, do it funny.
Yeah.
You know, and then, and then have him go, have Matt go to a church and yell at the priest
in the middle of a mass for what he did to him.
And then still look like an ass somehow.
And it's funny.
It's like, that's who that character is.
Have him yell at God.
You know, like if, look, now it's, now it's getting into a Paul Schrader movie or something.
But if he's like, you know, why did you put these?
These urges in me?
If you hate homosexuality, like, I think that'd be an interesting route to go and easy to
make funny, funny episode.
Yeah.
Mac, I'm not speaking to God anymore.
Dennis is like, you know, he's not real, right?
Yeah.
It's like the whole thing is just very funny.
Um, I pitched them when I worked there, a Lent episode where they each gave up something
for Lent and it drove each of them completely insane.
And I still think they should do it.
It's a, it's just such a great, uh, engine for characters.
One of my favorite EPS is.
The gang gets quarantined and I was very perplexed and disappointed that they didn't do a sequel
episode for COVID.
They did it during a flu season.
Yeah.
And I was like, oh, they do sequels all the time.
They're clearly going to do another quarantined and it's going to be about, and they're like,
no, instead we're going to go to Ireland.
Well, I, I kind of liked that arc just cause I am Irish and kind of enjoyed it.
But, and I think, look.
It's hard to be critical of a show that's been genuinely funny for 20 years.
I agree.
I hope this new season is funny.
It's not hard to be critical of gemstones after they did that.
And severance, I I'm about to finish the first season, but it's a rewatch.
And I realized that like, it's just not getting into my bones.
You know what I mean?
Like I'm watching it the second time before this, I start the second season and I'm like,
not only do I not remember any of this, it's just not sticking to me.
Like.
I don't care.
I don't care because it's so science fictiony or something, you know, like, I don't know
how to explain it, but I guess like you're saying, it's just too heady.
It's like a, an endless twilight zone episode when really you just want it to end after
a couple hours.
It would have made an amazing movie.
And there's really no cooler sci -fi premise for today's world.
I see why the show sold.
Certainly.
Then you get to shut your brain off at work.
And then when you leave work, it opens up.
It opens up another part.
I love that you're, you're different people at work and home.
I love that.
And they, they often bring it to the screen in genius ways.
It's just like nine hours of it starts to become like a hostage situation.
I don't want to sit.
I don't want to sit in the office space world for 10 hours.
You know what I mean?
For 20 hours.
I'm going to throw a sort of heady commentary at you.
Maybe it's, maybe it's accurate.
Maybe it's not.
I think possibly part of the reason.
It's becoming harder and harder to sit down with these TV shows as,
especially as people that work in this horrific industry.
Once you know how the sausage is made, you know,
I'm at a point where I'm like, Hey, Apple TV,
I'm not giving you 28 hours of my fucking life.
As you show me a thing where a quarter of an episode could have paid off my
entire family's mortgages.
Like fuck off.
Hey, you know, not only that, Joe, you want to get a little madder.
I don't know how much you do know about how that, that shows particular brand of
sausages made, but they shot an entire nine episodes.
Second season, Ben Stiller said, I don't like it.
And they threw it away.
And this is one of the most expensive shows on television.
They go, yeah, we'll start a whole new writing room, a whole new reshoot of it.
So that's annoying.
But then also imagine you're John Turturro.
And, and you're, you're killing it in the show,
but you got to sit around for two years,
like not taking any work because they decided, ah,
we messed up the creative.
It bothers me.
Well,
is that something he'd be contractually obligated to do?
Or at that point,
are you able to say a thousand percent if you sign on for it?
Now they can let you out of a contract.
Nobody's fucking doing that anymore.
Forget that.
They might also pay you a holding deal,
meaning you get paid to not work,
which is always nice,
but,
who knows?
Yeah.
Also too,
if they do let you out of that contract,
you're not skating clean.
They're going to go right to the press and go,
look how he fucked this all up.
Yeah.
Um,
no,
it's a,
it's a wild world as cat Stevens.
Well,
here's good TV news in the new psycho.
Yeah.
Uh,
just announced Alan Partridge.
How are you?
Uh,
a new series.
Oh,
thank God.
New series.
Here's the premise.
Here's the log line.
Uh,
Alan Partridge,
uh,
returns to London life after spending 12 months working in Saudi Arabia.
Oh yeah.
I mean,
just write what you want.
Exactly what you want.
I was just listening to the third season of his podcast from the host house.
Uh,
somehow I had missed the latest season and I'm dying on my way to work every
day.
And,
uh,
our boy,
Matt McCarthy,
who will be discussing next,
uh,
week in our review of companion,
which Matt has a small pivotal role in.
Uh,
but he sent me this last night.
It's coming to theaters.
Steve Coogan in Stanley Kubrick's Dr.
Strange love.
Yeah.
I've seen the trailer for it.
He plays all four roles in the premier stage adaptation,
and I guess they're going to show it in theaters.
So,
uh,
look,
look for that.
If you're a,
a,
a Coogan fan as I am,
but I'm such a fan.
I don't really care to see this.
Like,
I don't really have an interest.
I watched the trailer and it,
it,
it kind of just looks like,
it's kind of like when I saw back to the future of the musical.
And I'm like,
you're just doing back to the future on a stage.
Like it's not,
is he straight up mimicking,
um,
sellers characters are very similar from what I saw.
So I was just like,
it just seems like you're just recreating the thing or like for the state.
I don't know,
but maybe they'll do something.
but it's,
it's weird,
you know,
because that movie has always been described as being,
so,
uh,
prescient and ahead of its time and all that.
But like the,
the wheelchair bound,
uh,
Peter Sellers character who can't,
can't control himself from doing the Heil Hitler.
Yeah.
Like I'm surprised I did not see that more in connection with Elon because it's
like,
yeah,
this movie is like 70 years old and it's pretty much predicting our reality.
Yes.
Weird times.
Well,
let's get to that movie corn.
Um,
I'd like to start speaking of how comedy is in the gutter,
if you will,
by recommending a movie that's pretty darn funny called the gutter.
Um,
it was directed by Yasser Lester and Isaiah Lester.
Yasser is a comedian who I've known casually for years.
I don't know his brother.
Um,
and to be honest,
it really took me by surprise.
It's brand new to Hulu.
It was definitely 1000 % pitched as the black Kingpin.
And I got to tell you,
I didn't know how much I wanted the black Kingpin.
It's not perfect.
Um,
we're not talking about like an a,
even maybe a B plus type of movie here.
It's there's a,
there's a certain junkie low budge quality to it,
but that's where comedy can really take risks and chances and thrive.
And the cast is funny as hell.
It's Shamik Moore who voiced,
uh,
Miles Morales in the new Spider -Man's the Spider -Verse movies,
but I hadn't really seen him act in anything.
He's very funny and charming in this.
And I'm surprised he's not popping off more as an actor.
Uh,
Darcy Carden,
Paul.
Okay.
Paul Reiser basically steals the movie.
He is playing the Fred Willard,
uh,
racist,
clueless sports commentator.
Okay.
And so he's,
you know,
he's commenting on the world of,
of black bowling and he's,
he's super,
super funny.
And,
uh,
then they add another level of pathos to his character where he's just this
pathetic and lonely divorced man who wants to hang out with them.
He's not just reporting on them,
but he wants them to like bring him to dinner and stuff.
And a lot of good laughs with him.
Jack,
Hey,
Harry,
who I have worked with before on,
on broke girls.
And then again on cool kids,
how Jack K is not,
is not nailing tiny parts in movies all the time.
I don't know.
There's few people funnier than Jack K.
And she's been funny since I was a little kid.
She is so funny in this movie in kind of the,
the role,
not as gross,
but kind of the same role as the old lady who does the pussy licking gesture and Kingpin.
Um,
she just plays this incredibly cheap woman who runs the bowling alley.
Really funny.
And there's cameos from all kinds of people.
Uh,
you know,
comedians,
Adam Brody,
Paul Shearer,
uh,
people from the past,
Kim Fields,
Susan Sarandon,
has a pretty big role in it.
George Basil,
who was really funny on,
uh,
crashing.
It's a great cast.
Earthquake,
Adam Pally,
rel battle,
Tony Baker.
Um,
I laughed a lot.
Friends with rel and I'm friends with Langston and they're both Kirby Langston's in it.
Yeah.
That's cool.
It's really solid.
Uh,
check it out.
If you're looking for a return to that,
like late nineties,
early two thousands kind of gross,
uh,
you know,
racially charged,
politically incorrect comedy.
I really do recommend the gutter.
It's not perfect.
Don't go,
Pat,
you told me this was some sort of masterpiece.
It isn't,
but it sure is funny,
at least for the first hour or so.
And it's a tight 90.
Check it out.
The gutter,
Joe.
Uh,
Hmm.
Well,
I guess I'll go with comedy.
Um,
I watched,
um,
uh,
last night I was in bed having an anxiety attack.
As,
as you do.
Oh,
okay.
And,
uh,
I turned on a wrongfully accused the Leslie Nielsen movie.
And I thought,
you know,
I had such fun watching two of the three,
uh,
pull,
um,
naked guns were,
you know,
returning to that franchise.
Yeah.
I remember this movie having a few laughs in it.
And certainly it's not something that's going to trigger you in any way.
Uh,
let me watch it.
my God,
is it terrible?
Yeah.
Jesus.
Feeling.
It was,
it's really bad.
I mean,
there are a couple of jokes that are funny.
There's a,
there's a boner joke in it.
That's pretty funny.
Uh,
excuse me towards the beginning.
Um,
some of his reaction shots are funny when something very awkward is happening or
whatever.
Uh,
but overall the gags just don't hit for that reason.
They're gags,
uh,
and not well constructed ones.
Um,
I will say this though.
Many of them don't work just because they're executed in the wrong way.
The concept in and of itself is funny,
but they just execute the gag poorly and too simply.
And you're like,
you missed if you just did this instead of that,
like there's a scene where,
uh,
a woman,
after she murders somebody at the beginning of the movie,
um,
she goes to throw the gun away.
And the house that she's at,
I think her name's Melinda McGraw.
I think that's the actor's name.
Um,
anyway,
she,
uh,
she goes to,
dispose of the gun and she's at the house where she just killed the guy.
And the guy's house is on these cliffs next to the ocean.
So she walks to the edge of the cliff and she tosses the gun,
which is tiny over the cliff and it falls way down and hits the water.
And then it shows her.
And she gets like hit with this,
like massive splash of water.
It's a terrible joke.
Like,
you know,
the joke is,
could you imagine a splash this big coming from that small of a,
it's,
it's a terrible joke.
Um,
but her reaction to it is she remained stoic and tries to remain looking
dignified.
Like it didn't happen.
And then she takes a beat and spits all this water out of her mouth.
And I'm like,
if you had just done that same gag,
but she was standing next to water.
Yeah.
In a moment where she needed to be taken seriously.
And she got hit like that with water and had the same reaction.
That would be really funny.
So write it in that way.
Like it's,
it's,
it's very confusing.
There's a lot of jokes in it like that,
where you're like,
guys,
you almost got this.
You almost got this.
And you just,
the execution's off.
It's a shame,
but it is still kind of fun to watch Leslie.
Bounce around and be Leslie Nielsen.
It's before the complete deterioration of his,
was it pre that?
I think spy hard was maybe the first one after 33 and a third.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Spy hard.
And I think then this,
yeah.
Um,
Comedy,
you know,
it just goes to show you,
they think anybody can do it.
They think,
Oh,
a big,
broad,
stupid comedy.
We can just hire any old Jack off to direct it.
But there's a reason that the only good ones were Zucker,
Abraham,
Zucker.
They know how to do it.
Then I'll give it,
I'll hand it to the Wayans brothers,
particularly scary movie.
The first,
and then parts of the second are an excellent black version of that formula.
They do it really,
really well.
But when the franchise changed hands,
because the Weinstein brothers refused to pay the Wayans brothers,
even though they saved their company,
um,
it,
it fell to shit.
Those later scary movies are embarrassing.
Well,
funny and funny enough.
And that's when Leslie,
Leslie Nielsen comes into them.
He comes in.
Yeah,
exactly.
Uh,
yeah.
Bold choice by Weinstein's.
We don't need the Wayans brothers,
but we do need Anna Ferris.
Yeah.
Uh,
I'm kind of pumped about the new scary movie just to see this.
Cause they've had so many decades now to make fun of horror movies.
And if they,
if they target a 24,
um,
that could be new and fresh because nobody's really made fun of that shit yet.
And,
and it's,
it's got it coming for sure.
There's another joke.
There's a joke opportunity in this that really Kelly LeBrock's in it looking as hot as ever.
Uh,
there's a part where she,
she becomes obsessed with Leslie Nielsen and she leaves him this note and says,
if I can't see you tonight,
I'm going to kill myself.
And then it's,
so you need to come to my house immediately.
And then the,
the last sentence of the note says,
also,
I'm out of two,
I'm out of milk.
Can you pick up a gallon of 2 %?
That's a funny joke,
right?
Yeah,
it is.
He walks into the house holding groceries.
Yeah.
And he goes,
whatever her name is,
Elaine,
whatever.
I'm here to talk to you.
We're through.
There's nothing between us anymore.
And you're waiting for the joke and they don't do it.
It's like,
and,
and then say,
also,
they were out of 2%.
Just like,
it's so clearly like also is skim.
All right.
Yeah.
Anything there.
And they just don't do it.
They're like,
no,
he's holding groceries.
That's the guy.
It's like,
I guess.
Anyway,
I'd skip wrongfully accused,
but if you do want to watch it,
you can watch it for free on YouTube.
There you go.
Also on Hulu,
I watched a movie recommended by my father.
Always a dicey proposition.
It was called ghost light.
It came out last year and it stars as kind of an interesting gimmick,
an actual family.
It stars a man who's an actor.
His name is,
is Keith Kupfer,
who I recognized as being a character actor.
And he like auditioned with his wife and they were like,
let's cast your wife as your wife.
And then they were like,
who's going to play your daughter.
And he's like,
why don't we audition my daughter?
So that's kind of cool,
I guess.
And the movie has a charm.
Don't get me wrong.
It's kind of this full Monty thing where it's a construction worker who gets in a fight at work.
He's constantly embroiled in,
in a lawsuit.
And we're not quite sure what the lawsuit is until about halfway through the picture.
Um,
but to kind of deal with his anger,
he joins a local theater production of Romeo and Juliet.
So I was like,
all right,
kind of a hackneyed premise,
but I love the full Monty.
I love blue collar guys tapping into their artistic side.
You know,
it makes me smile and I'm like,
this is going to be funny.
And it's going to be sad and I'm going to love it.
And that's what my dad told me it was.
But here's what I couldn't get past with it.
He's in this production of Romeo and Juliet.
And about halfway through the film,
we find out that the reason he's suing is he's suing his son's girlfriend because his son and his son's girlfriend both tried to commit suicide at the same time.
But only the daughter lived.
Okay.
So he's suing her.
And then,
you know,
of course it's like you realize like,
Hey,
they both fucked up and it's not her fault.
You're just mad at the world or whatever else.
But he coincidentally joins a local theaters production of Romeo and Juliet about two teenagers who are so in love that they commit suicide.
I was just like,
this is some of,
this is the worst clumsiest storytelling I've ever seen.
It's so coincidental.
And so on the nose that I just threw my hands up.
I was like,
and then he gets all pissed when he finds out that that's how the play ends.
I don't care if you're a construction worker,
everyone on earth knows how Romeo and Juliet ends.
You read it in high school.
So he's like,
wait,
what?
They kill themselves.
And it brings up all this anger in him.
And you're just like,
come on.
I've never seen a movie where it was like,
I'm sure I have.
I just off the top of my head where the premise just destroys it.
It's like got all this goodwill going for it.
The actors are great.
You're rooting for him.
You're curious about this lawsuit and what's going on.
But when you get the reveal,
it's just this like the two stories don't have to perfectly dovetail like this to where they coincidentally everybody's committing suicide in his world.
So it lost me in a very big way at the halfway point.
And I found it pretty charming up till then.
It's not a waste of time.
It's just kind of like,
come on,
man.
Maybe how they convince people was like,
you know,
Shakespeare had a lot of big,
crazy coincidences in his work too,
or something like that.
But,
and that's true.
He has big,
stupid coincidences in his boring ass plays.
But,
um,
this did not work for me at all.
Ghost light,
Joe.
Um,
another rewatch of a comedy.
Uh,
but a very good one.
I rewatched matchstick man for the first time.
And so I love that movie.
I only saw it once.
I love it too.
I've seen it a few times now.
It gets better every time I watch it.
It is Nicholas cage.
In my opinion,
might be Nicholas cages,
best performance.
I mean,
he's amazing in it as this con man.
That's got severe OCD.
Yeah.
Uh,
that manifests in all kinds of ticks and panic attacks.
And,
um,
you know,
there's a great scene.
Sam Rockwell plays his partner.
Uh,
there's a great scene where they're running their hustle and they go to these
people's house to scam them out of money.
And,
uh,
the,
the wife opens the sliding glass door and leaves it open.
And like,
he can't handle it.
And he starts having like this panic attack and sweating and almost blows the
hustle.
And,
uh,
they go outside and Sam Rockwell's like,
what the hell was that,
man?
Did you not take your pills today?
And,
and,
uh,
Nicolas Cage is going,
woo,
woo.
She left the door open.
It was bitching.
He,
he does the perfect amount of like wild Nicolas Cage in this.
Yeah.
But like,
it's somehow very grounded.
It's weird with Nicolas Cage.
I think we're all going to kind of go back and look at his past performances
and go,
they weren't over the top.
They made a lot of sense.
They were just,
he just did offbeat really well.
Like I,
I like that.
We're all taking him seriously now.
Yeah.
or,
or again,
I should say.
Um,
but anyway,
uh,
Alison Lohman rounds out the cast.
Uh,
she plays Nicolas Cage's daughter that he did not know he had,
who comes back into his life as he and Sam Rockwell are trying to pull
off their one last big con.
Um,
it's an awesome movie.
It's terribly funny.
Rockwell,
as always,
just,
just charming and so funny.
Um,
is he playing like a,
his partner or his brother or both or what?
His partner.
Okay.
Um,
it's just a great movie directed by Ridley Scott.
Uh,
I won't give away too many of the details in case you haven't seen it.
Cause it is a bit of a caper.
Uh,
but watch it and very endearing,
very endearing,
a very beautiful movie at its core.
And,
uh,
one that I think I might repurchase.
I had the DVD at one point and then said,
I don't need to own matchstick men.
Uh,
but I do.
I,
I was foolish in my,
uh,
ridding myself of it.
So,
uh,
check it out.
I highly recommend it.
Uh,
yeah,
I'd love to watch it again.
Cause it's been 20,
25 years.
Uh,
I just rewatched a movie.
I also hadn't seen in 20,
25 years called trees lounge written and directed by Steve Buscemi.
And it is currently on Amazon prime.
This is one that's pretty hard to find.
It's only on DVD to my knowledge.
It never came out on Blu -ray and certainly not 4k either.
It's very low budget.
Uh,
it's excellent.
David Chase sites,
good fellows as probably the number one influence of course,
on the Sopranos.
But he says right up there is this little movie trees lounge,
and it feels like a Sopranos episode,
including it as the entire same cast as that show.
So it's got Michael Imperioli,
John Ventimiglia,
um,
Buscemi of course,
famously directed a lot of the best episodes of the Sopranos.
The look is very similar.
Uh,
Carmela's mom plays a bar fly in this movie.
So half the time I was going,
oh shit,
you know,
Carmela's mom's playing this alcoholic nightmare,
you know?
So that was really cool.
Um,
in addition,
the movie is just so great.
It understand they rarely make movies about alcoholics unless it's like leaving Las Vegas with cage or something.
Where it's really got a big theme about the dangers of alcoholism or something.
This movie is not trying to force any agenda down your head.
It's just a slice of life about a fuck up who drinks way too much and spends his life in bars.
Um,
he's got his ex wife or ex girlfriend who is now with Anthony La Paglia,
who was the original first choice for Tony Soprano.
Uh,
it's very clear that David Chase was like,
I just want to take this vibe and make it a TV show.
Um,
Michael Buscemi,
who's Steve Buscemi's brother,
plays his brother in the movie and does an excellent job.
He,
Buscemi is an alcoholic ice cream man who falls for Chloe Savigny,
who is 16 years old.
She's playing a 16 year old.
Uh,
it is left kind of up to your imagination whether or not they fuck,
even though I think it's strongly indicated that they do.
It's not trying to make this guy lovable,
but you can't help but love Buscemi.
And,
and I,
this is just a great movie.
I like it a lot.
Carol Kane in a small role as a bartender,
Samuel L.
Jackson coming in for a great cameo with his son,
Debbie Mazur and Kevin Corrigan,
of course,
from Goodfellas,
Mimi Rogers,
Daniel Baldwin,
uh,
Michael Imperioli,
like I said,
Seymour Cassell.
It's a great cast,
a great little slice of life movie,
and a way better Sopranos companion piece than the actual Sopranos movie,
Many Saints of Newark.
Uh,
check it out.
It's it's,
it comes from that period of independent cinema of like Fargo with Buscemi,
of course.
And,
uh,
just where every movie that came out,
Sling Blade was all just really,
really exciting.
And this one kind of gets forgotten and that's not fair because it's great.
Joe,
that's Kismet Pat.
My last movie also features Michael Buscemi,
and it was also in theme,
uh,
with what I'm talking about,
a comedy,
uh,
that it was an also a rewatch.
I rewatched about black Klansman,
uh,
which I know is more than just a comedy,
but what a fucking,
I truly think that this movie is Spike Lee's best movie since Malcolm X.
And I would rank it among his best movies,
period.
I think,
you know,
uh,
I,
for me personally,
it's probably this Malcolm X and,
uh,
do the right thing.
Um,
it's,
it's just an excellent,
excellent movie.
If you don't know the premise,
it's about,
it's based on a true story of a black police officer in the 1970s who infiltrates the Ku Klux Klan by posing as a white racist on the phone with them and then sending in a white officer to be his proxy when they actually need to meet up with the person,
the,
the clan,
uh,
that person in the movie is played by,
um,
well,
the,
the main characters is Denzel Washington's,
uh,
son.
But what's his first Isaiah?
Is it,
I,
what is his first name?
It's a three name.
I,
let me make sure.
John David.
Yeah.
John David Washington.
Um,
and then,
uh,
what's his face?
Kylo Ren,
uh,
Adam driver,
Adam driver.
Yeah.
And Paul Walter Hauser,
right?
Yeah.
He,
that guy's in it.
That's the chunky guy,
right?
Yeah.
He's in it playing one of the Klansmen.
Um,
you got the guy from thinner.
As the police chief,
uh,
you got Michael Buscemi is one of the cops.
Um,
it's a great movie.
It's,
it's an insane story and it's mostly true.
Um,
I guess you do kind of scratch your head at one point and go,
why wouldn't he just start telling the white cop what to say on the phone?
Uh,
instead of having to worry about,
are they going to recognize my voice or consistency or whatever?
But in real life,
that's not what happens.
So that's the story.
Um,
you know,
uh,
the,
the amidst all this,
one of the assignments given to the main character is to sort of infiltrate the black Panther party in the city they're in and see if they are planning to,
to commit any sort of terrorist acts.
Uh,
so he's infiltrated the clan and the black Panthers at the same time.
And he is trying to,
to,
he falls in love with a woman in the,
the black Panthers.
He's trying to assure her that not every cop is a piece of garbage.
And some of them are there trying to do the right thing.
And of course he's trying to take down the Ku Klux Klan and prevent them from doing anything terrible.
So he's,
he's,
he's sort of riding a strange fence in this.
Uh,
there's a really interesting turn of character with Adam driver.
Who's it plays a Jewish cop who doesn't have any investment in the racial hatred of the clan.
And as it goes along,
he starts to become more aware of his Jewish heritage.
And that's interesting.
The whole thing,
the mood is very interesting,
but to,
to keep it within the theme of my movie corner,
it is extraordinarily funny.
Like in the,
the funniest joke in the whole thing is when,
uh,
David,
God damn it.
What is his name?
John David Washington.
You're absolutely right though.
It just,
it never sticks.
For some reason,
when he's talking to,
uh,
his chief of police and he goes,
sir,
I have a meeting with the Ku Klux Klan and the chief of police goes,
uh,
I would not go to that meeting.
That's very fun.
Yeah.
Uh,
it's a great movie.
It's awesome.
It's an awesome,
awesome movie.
It's got all the hallmarks of a Spike Lee film.
Uh,
it's Spike Lee.
The,
the thing that makes me laugh the hardest though,
is that,
and I don't know,
if he's doing this to be funny or not,
but Spike Lee,
who often casts the Totoro brothers.
Yeah.
He's got Nick Totoro in this,
who on his palest day with a pound of pancake powder on his face would still
look borderline Hispanic.
He's got him as a Klansman.
I'm like,
they would see this guy and send him,
like in the other direction.
That's a weird choice for sure.
Full New York accent.
Still full New York accent.
It's,
it's an,
it's so odd.
It's such odd casting.
And I think,
I really think Spike Lee was just like,
I think it'll be funny to make Nick Totoro play a Klansman in this.
Yeah.
Or maybe to make the Klan look even dumber for not recognizing that he's not pure white.
Something.
Yeah.
I saw that movie in theaters and fucking loved it.
I own it in 4k and you have convinced me to do a rewatch.
The second I get back to LA,
I think the only Spike Lee that could really give it a run for its money would be inside man,
which I did rewatch recently and just thought was incredible.
But inside man lacks that sort of racial punch that you love with a,
with a Spike Lee joint for sure.
I'm excited to see his remake of high and low,
which is a great Kurosawa movie with Denzel.
He's back reunited with Denzel.
Jeffrey Wright again,
ASAP Rocky,
who I don't know how he is as an actor,
but he,
he looks exactly like Denzel.
So I hope they're playing father and son.
I'm sure they are.
Um,
and I'm excited.
It is called,
which again,
sounds like a 30 rock joke,
highest to lowest with the number two.
All right.
But,
uh,
I'm curious to see it.
All right,
folks.
I want to,
before we get to the movie at hand,
uh,
do a little news psycho for you.
Warner brothers is replacing rotten DVDs.
So even,
even as all the big studios are,
are pulling their funding from blue rays and saying we might not even release
new movies in,
in the format anymore in physical media,
this is a bit of good news.
Uh,
I have sold a couple of old criterions.
I mean,
I've sold a ton of old criterions,
but I had complaints from the Amazon buyer where they said,
Hey man,
this disc doesn't work anymore.
And I'm like,
what are you talking about?
I never even opened it.
It was sealed.
So that's not my fault.
And they're like,
yeah,
but you sold me a movie that doesn't work and I have to give a refund.
And it's because,
and this is scary.
Um,
DVDs can go bad.
And I used to think that it was all DVDs and blue rays are going to go bad
over time,
but it turns out it's just certain years and,
uh,
certain ways of manufacturing them.
So,
uh,
it says where possible,
the defective discs are going to be replaced by the same title.
However,
as some of the affected titles are no longer in,
in print or the rights have expired,
consumers have been offered an exchange for a title of like value.
Uh,
so these are movies released between 2006 and 2008,
or at least the DVDs were released between that time.
So make sure you check them out.
If you got a WB movie from those couple of years,
um,
there's a big list online that you can find and look through your titles,
make sure they still work.
But it says here,
disc rot is caused by corrosion between the discs,
protective lacquer and reflective,
protective layer DVDs should be more resistant because unlike CDs,
the lacquer on the back of discs is made of plastic instead of aluminum.
Those,
some precautions can prevent this deterioration.
Some reports confirm that this issue has hit discs that are even fresh out of
the package.
So this is a way to really replenish your collection,
get better versions of things.
Um,
look it up online.
If you're a big DVD collector like myself,
I'm definitely going to be swallowing.
Popping out some titles when I get back to town.
I just bought,
I went to half price books here in Austin and I bought,
they had an out of print dirty Harry box set.
Uh,
yeah.
And I looked it up.
It was 20 bucks.
I looked it up online.
It sells for like 50,
whatever.
I'm not going to resell it,
but I was like,
I really want this.
It's just,
it's not 4k.
It's just DVDs.
But I really want,
this is very cool looking.
The packaging is great.
I bought it.
I watched,
uh,
the first movie and I really enjoyed it.
There was something really fun about,
I hadn't done it in a while,
but there was something really fun about putting a DVD back in and seeing the grain and the grit.
It,
it was a different experience.
And I forgot that I used to enjoy those different mediums a lot more.
I've gotten a little swept up in this 4k thing,
but it was nice to know,
like,
no,
there's a great value.
Like DVD is kind of becoming the VHS now where it's,
there's such a drastic difference.
It's kind of,
it's kind of fun and bringing you back into a,
a moodier viewing.
So,
um,
so I like that.
And that's great news.
At the Vista Tarantino's theater.
He's got the main theater where you see the new movies or,
or old revivals of stuff.
And he's been true to his word.
He,
he shows a perfect mix.
Like he's showing the five hour cut of Bertolucci's 1900 all week.
Like he's really not going strictly for the money.
Although in LA you can make just as much money.
Doing repertory movies.
Um,
but I love that theater.
It's right by my house.
And he has a small,
tiny theater off to the side where he shows VHS movies that are like impossible
to find it from his collection.
And I've not been to a movie there.
I think it's only like a 20 seat house,
but pretty cool.
Where,
where the hell is that in the Vista?
Or did he get the,
I've never seen it even.
I've never bought a ticket to one,
but he has like the VHS club there and I need to go to one.
But,
but I haven't yet.
Well,
let's move on to the movie of the hour.
A different man.
Yeah.
Different man.
Uh,
put out by a 24 starring Sebastian Stan.
this is for its first act,
a character study of a man with a very severe facial deformity.
He is played by,
uh,
Adam Pearson,
who definitely should have been nominated for best supporting actor.
Kind of nuts that he wasn't,
especially since we're so inclusive nowadays.
Wait,
he,
not the,
the first act Adam comes in later.
The first act is Sebastian.
No.
Yes.
No,
the Sebastian Stan doesn't enter this movie until halfway through.
It's Sebastian Stan and makeup and his face falls off,
which they literally show happening in the movie.
Yeah.
And then Adam Pearson comes in later as a completely different human being.
That's the plot of the entire movie.
You don't think that Adam Pearson,
played the guy for the entire first part a hundred percent.
Didn't there's factually that's the whole thing.
I don't even know why Sebastian Stan would agree to do this.
I thought he was coming in because he didn't have to wear all this makeup and
prosthetics and play this part.
No,
no.
The that's why it's such a brilliant film.
He in fact,
even carries a mask with him of what he used to look.
No,
I know what the story is,
but I,
are you,
are you a hundred percent sure that Sebastian Stan was playing him in
prosthetics for the first act of this movie?
Not only am I a hundred percent sure I am floored that you're,
that you're surprised by this at the moment.
I say that with as little judgment as possible,
but yeah,
that was the whole point of the movie is that not the whole point,
but you know what I mean?
And also Adam Pearson looks nothing like Sebastian Stan in the makeup.
They have a completely different facial configuration of this condition.
Well,
that is true,
but I thought,
I honestly thought that was another actor.
To be honest,
I thought that the guy,
the guy meaning Adam Pearson was playing that part.
And then when he takes the mask off,
he just becomes Sebastian Stan.
I knew,
I know what the plot is.
The plot's very clear to me,
but the casting element was not like I thought,
well,
Sebastian Stan makes these $500 million movies.
He thought,
Oh great.
Yeah.
I can just come in and play this comedic.
Second act.
No,
he's,
uh,
he plays,
he's in heavy prosthetics for the first act of the film.
Um,
he is a struggling actor.
He is in love with his neighbor,
but he is too self -conscious to make a move on her.
She's an aspiring playwright by Renata Reinsville.
I don't know how to quite pronounce that,
but she is the star of one of my favorite movies of the last five years,
the worst person in the world.
And it was great to see her again,
because I think she's an,
she's an excellent actress.
Joe.
Um,
she,
um,
he's very uncomfortable in his own skin.
Uh,
and he's an awkward guy and he's kind of,
you know,
having an awkward sort of lonely life.
And,
um,
he,
uh,
is approached by,
well,
his doctor,
he goes to a doctor and his doctor is explaining,
you know,
your condition is,
is,
is stabilized for the moment,
but it's only a matter of time before it worsens again.
And you're going to,
you're going to lose vision in your one eye and all this stuff.
And he said,
but an alternative treatment has presented itself.
And the alternative treatment is,
is that he's going to go through this weird,
like facial laser process where he takes,
I guess a pill or something.
I don't remember exactly how they do it.
And it could reverse the effects of this condition.
And sure enough,
and quite horrifically that happens.
Here's where we're going to start to get into spoilers.
You can kind of pick all this up in the trailer,
but if you haven't seen it,
this is where the spoilers will begin.
Um,
quite horrifically that happens and his face starts to literally fall off,
uh,
to slowly reveal the face underneath.
Um,
it's pretty grotesque.
and then all of a sudden he's his true face,
if you will,
is revealed and it's Sebastian Stan and this guy that's had a tough time throughout life.
Um,
uh,
because of this condition is suddenly now feeling okay about himself and feeling quite confident.
Uh,
you then skip forward to a year or two years later,
whatever it is.
He's living a new life.
He's in a nice new apartment.
He's got a real estate job where he's killing it.
They have him on billboards around town.
Uh,
his face is being celebrated.
he gets a role in an off,
off,
off Broadway play.
That is,
written by the woman that he used to live next door to.
She does not know that he is the guy she lived next door to because he chooses to of instead telling people that he went through this change that his old self had died.
He has abandoned who he was 100 % and become a new person,
a different man,
if you will.
Um,
he then,
uh,
ends up landing the role in the play,
the lead,
uh,
which she wrote about him.
About who he used to be.
And she's awestruck by how much he understands the character and she doesn't get how he could understand the character because he had never experienced what this character had been through as far as she knows.
quite the opposite.
He's a very handsome man and,
and you know,
right,
right.
Yeah.
Never had that experience and all is going well.
He starts dating this woman.
All is good.
He's wearing a mask of what he used to look like on stage.
And then,
uh,
he's like,
things really heat up when Adam Pearson shows up as a man who still has the condition and says,
Oh,
I thought there were auditions were still open for this role.
Yeah.
No,
we're cheers.
And he is the most comfortable in his own skin,
a person who's ever existed.
He loves life.
He approaches people.
People love him.
Women flirt with him.
He's confident.
And it's truly,
and it makes Sebastian,
uh,
Sebastian Stan now start to regret that he did this and he becomes jealous of the guy he didn't want to be anymore.
And it all,
it all unfolds from there.
Um,
it is surprisingly a very funny movie.
It sounds heavy.
It's not really that heavy.
The part where his face starts falling off is kind of upsetting,
but,
but it's a very,
very funny movie.
And,
uh,
yeah,
this is the guy from,
uh,
from under the sky.
Skin,
uh,
the excellent Scarlett Johansson kind of sci -fi movie that Jonathan Glazer did.
And he,
to show you how far we've come,
he played that role in that movie 10 years ago,
2013.
And his role was literally credited as the deformed man.
Right.
So,
you know,
this movie is,
it's apologetic to how we have treated our,
our disfigured,
if that's the appropriate way to say it.
I don't know,
but,
um,
it,
it's critical of that,
but not in a shameful finger pointing way.
Like Joe said,
it's like,
there is an element of comedy to it.
It's like,
you don't need to pity these people.
Like it.
So many of them are very happy.
It reminded me a lot of the current controversy was snow white about how now all these little people are like,
so now we're just not going to get parts in the movies.
They're going to animate them.
You know,
it's like you can do so much to try to accommodate people who look different than you.
That you,
you wind up pissing them off.
Um,
so I,
and I gotta say,
I'm more impressed by the movie.
Now I saw it twice.
I watched it a second time because I had to admit that I was in and out of sleep the first time I saw it.
Right.
And I was like,
I'm not gonna be able to talk about this,
uh,
appropriately.
So watching it twice now for me to still not put together that that was Sebastian Stan,
the first act of the movie,
I'm going to choose not to be ashamed and embarrassed and instead just credit the movie for being,
for being exceptionally well done.
Um,
because it really fucking works.
yeah,
I didn't,
I probably didn't love it as much as Joe.
I certainly wasn't laughing out loud.
There's a very funny,
pure comedy scene where it's,
um,
they're doing a,
you know,
one of those educational like office videos on how to deal with people who are physically deformed.
And that's really laugh out loud.
Funny.
The rest of it falls into this kind of discomfort comedy,
especially in the first act.
And then the second,
the third act of,
um,
you know,
like Boa's afraid or a lot of these indie movies where it's just like following a guy on the fringes of society.
It reminded me of the best of independent film because it tells a story you just would never tell anywhere else,
but on a very low budget,
I got to credit Sebastian Stan for taking the part.
And now I credit him even more knowing that that was him in the fucking prosthetics because I completely thought he was like,
yeah,
I'll do it.
I just get to be the handsome guy for the last half of the movie.
And I was mistaken.
Um,
the script is really clever and really good.
It plays almost like a screwball comedy at times with,
with a lot of misunderstandings and twists and turns.
But,
um,
interesting movie,
this scene where what's his name?
Sean,
what's it?
What is it?
Adam Pearson or Adam Pierce?
Sorry.
This,
this scene where Adam Pearson gets up and sings karaoke and everybody's,
he's cheering and they're showing Sebastian sand sitting there with this look on his face.
Like how the fuck is this guy doing this right now?
I mean,
I was literally laughing out loud on my couch.
I was like,
this is so funny how perplexed he is that this man could be this comfortable.
Um,
that really,
really made me laugh a couple of weird nods to Woody Allen where they say in the beginning of the movie was one of Adam Pearson.
I mean,
sorry,
one of Sebastian stands,
neighbor says,
that guy reminds me of that Woody Allen guy.
And yeah,
by the end of the movie,
uh,
Sebastian Stan has become so reclusive and damaged that he becomes this nebbishy,
like hunched over little guy and they show him walking at the end of the movie and he's dressed like Woody Allen with the fishermen hat on and everything.
And then the play that his ex girlfriend is doing now is a major.
Broadway hit and it's called the heart wants what the heart wants,
which is what Woody Allen said about his,
uh,
his relationship with,
soon.
Ye that's right.
Um,
there's,
uh,
and there's some weird,
funny gags,
like the whole thing.
When,
when,
uh,
when Sebastian Stan gets so mad that he literally attacks Adam Pearson mid performance.
Yeah.
And you think it's going to be super serious and then the set wall falls on,
Sebastian Stan and then the lights fall on him and it's like a,
it's a gag.
It's funny.
And then it cuts to him in the full body cast and Adam Pearson is still taking care of him even though he did this to him and he just keeps being forgiving and nurturing and being like,
I know you didn't mean to hurt me,
my friend.
I know that you truly are just hurt and lost right now.
Like it's,
it's a fascinating film.
I really enjoyed it.
And,
um,
I thought it was a really,
really great approach to taking,
you know,
a subject matter that has been treated as,
I guess for lack of a better way of putting it.
Well,
we talked earlier about elephant man,
you know,
in that sort of taboo taboo sense of the pain and the struggle of the person and kind of flipped it on its head.
And like,
as Pat said already and said,
no,
it's,
it's about how,
you know,
they have beautiful lives and,
and people can have a challenge like this and still be happy and still be wonderful.
And it's about loving yourself no matter what skin you're in.
And I think that that's a really beautiful idea.
And,
uh,
and I,
I really enjoyed the movie.
My hog is up.
Yeah.
It,
it heaps this like meet the parents level of shit upon the Sebastian Stan character.
Like he just,
like,
as Joe said,
the set falls on him and ever,
everything bad keeps happening and happening and happening.
And what's great about it is that in meet the parents stiller did not deserve any of that.
He was trying to do the right thing at all times.
This is a man who decided I'm not happy with how I look and I'm going to change it.
You know,
there's a very clear moral and message there about plastic surgery about ozempic about trying to change the way you look and how much more people like and respond to you if you just own it and are confident.
And live your life.
You know,
he,
he doesn't start feeling the way to the world until he throws away his face until he's like,
no,
I hate the way I look.
I hate who I am.
And then the world starts going.
All right,
well,
we're going to fuck you up now.
It is really interesting.
There's a lot of themes at play and I it's one of those movies where I have a feeling everybody would get something different out of it and we need more movies like this.
I dug it.
My hog is also up.
And if you want to see,
Sebastian Stan's dick while he's wearing a mask,
this is another opportunity for you to do.
So do they show his dick in it?
Pretty long shot of his dick.
Yeah,
that's in under the skin,
isn't it?
Joe,
it's in this movie.
He comes out.
They show you dick in that movie too.
He comes out of the bathroom with the mask on.
Now,
maybe it was somebody else under the mask.
Oh,
when,
when they're,
when they're having sex or whatever,
having sex.
Oh,
I see.
Okay.
I missed his dick.
Surprisingly,
I always look.
Looking at dicks.
Yeah.
Well,
notice folks.
How Pat picked up on that detail.
Yeah,
but yeah.
All right,
folks,
we'll be back with companion.
I'm Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram.
If you want to check me out on the road,
please do.
I'm in Chicago this coming weekend at Zany's,
Rosemont,
their Rosemont location next at the end of the month.
I'm supposed to be in Phoenix at the Desert Ridge Improv.
Yeah,
that's that's last weekend of March.
First weekend.
Well,
I'll be a Q West first weekend of May in Key West,
Florida for the for Brian Quinn's Festival,
but that's sold out.
And then I have other dates coming up all of them available at Joe DeRosa .com.
And of course,
if you're in New York,
come by Joey roses for a sandwich and or a drink.
Joey roses .com.
I am the Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
Thank you to everybody for your spirited and ongoing discussions.
About political extremism and how it is affecting our friendships and our relationships with people,
our fellow man,
our family,
Etc from the solo movie corner.
It's been really fun reading everybody's responses and a big thank you in particular for just being respectful and everybody voicing how they feel,
but it not devolving into name -calling and finger pointing.
I was very impressed by our fans after reading the comments on that post.
Thank you everybody.
We'll see you next time with a discussion of companion and we will see you in hell.