I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's a podcast.
You know that.
That's why you're here.
We're talking about movies as usual, my name is Joe DeRosa, and my name is Patrick Walsh.
And hello everybody, welcome to a new Patreon.
We'll see you in hell.
We're this week.
We're discussing both coming to America, the original, and coming to number two America,
the sequel that was just released on Amazon Prime.
Joe, welcome.
It's good to see you.
How have you been over the last five minutes between episodes?
I'm good.
I've had some coffee, so who knows where this is going to go, you know.
I'm one of those bitches where don't talk to me until I've had my coffee.
I know.
I hear you, bitch.
I've had quite a bit of coffee already today.
In fact, I'm going to need to pump the brakes a bit.
The best part of waking up is fulges in your cup.
The, I don't know that I've ever had folders in my life.
It's about as average a coffee as you can get.
It's probably what you're drinking at a diner.
I, I don't know that I've ever had folders.
I've never had Maxwell house.
Yeah.
Sanca.
Never had classics.
How about folders, crystals?
That was the one that was supposed to be like, like great, right?
Great.
Wasn't that the one that was like their premium one, right?
I thought folders, crystals, all you might be right, but there's also like frozen coffee.
Is that what that was?
That's what I thought it was, but what do I know?
That's grandpa shit, you know?
The, yeah, maybe it was, folders, I want to look it up, but I'm afraid I'm going to slow
down the internet connection and then we'll have audio problems and we've got a real
top operation here.
Top option.
Yeah.
What else is in your world, Joe?
What's happening in New York City?
New York City.
Last coast to coast with Pat and Joe, I'm not against it.
Okay.
What's going on in my world?
The movie theaters are open again.
New York.
Or as a rumored to be opening next week, which came out of nowhere, yeah, our movie theaters
are open again.
You're going to go?
Yeah.
I'll absolutely go.
I also get vaccinated tomorrow.
How?
What'd you do?
I'm a restaurant worker because of my sandwich shop and that's deemed an essential worker
here in New York City.
Okay.
So I get, and fair enough, I mean, I am facing the public several days a week.
Sure.
I get my first dose tomorrow out in Brooklyn and, yeah, I'll go to the movies.
You know, they're going to keep it safe.
It's like, you know, it's not going to be a free for all.
So what's, what's the capacity?
They allow 2550 something like that, you know, and everybody's got to sit apart and all
that stuff.
So, yeah, I look forward to that.
You know, bars and restaurants are open again, 25%.
You know, it's starting to feel a little normal again here.
And they're, I mean, I don't, I can't speak for California, but they are, they are rolling
out the vaccine here, dude.
It is like, there's sites everywhere.
So.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're, it seems to me like nobody's getting vaccinated, but then I think it's just
people scared to talk because of Twitter.
I did get sent like a dude, you know, you can use this link.
It's not quite on the up and up kind of thing.
And I opted not to just because it's like, I'll get it when it's my turn, you know, I don't
really care.
I'm not dying to travel or something.
So, but yeah, once I get vaccinated, I'd go sit in a movie with a mask on.
What the hell?
I would go to a movie before I was vaccinated if they're following the rules because I do this
crazy thing called reading and learning and understanding how viruses are transmitted.
So it's, it's just a wild, wild thing, you know, I feel bad for the people of Los Angeles
because you got a group of people out there that, I mean, the vaccination, they're
could be a vaccination stand at the foot of their driveway and they'll be afraid to leave
the house because they'll think somebody that had COVID walked by two months ago and left
it in the air.
Well, there's also this thing of vaccine shaming.
So people will go, got my first vaccine today.
I'm so excited.
And then 35 comments underneath it like what, excuse me, what, what is your pre -existing
condition?
I'm sorry.
What is it?
I wish I'm all the fuck a wood.
Yeah, it's like a, not your business and b, why don't you just be happy that people
are getting the fucking vaccine done?
But things are clearly turning around.
My, my grandma, mom, and dad all got their first shots within like a day of each other.
Like I think just shit's starting to get where it needs to be and things are happening.
My folks have, they, I think they expanded it here in New York to media people too.
Okay.
Yeah.
Which again, fair enough, people have to travel, you know, and some people, that's the only
way they make their living.
I know some of you Hollywood folks think everybody should just stay home.
But you know, some people are starving to death.
So there's that.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's just a miserable lot of people out there that I see them on Twitter saying it's just,
it's just fucking, and I can't imagine the level of privilege you're coming from to shame
somebody who's forced into position to having to work.
They act like everybody out there is just doing it because they, they feel like being out
of the house.
You know, no, it's complete madness.
And when the first reports were getting out, are that they're throwing away large amounts
of the vaccine.
It's like, yeah, if you have an opportunity to take it, it would be my POV.
And I think there are people that are just going to be angry at anybody who gets vaccinated
before them.
I'm just going to stay inside until I get the email from my doctor that says, come on
in and I'm doing it that way, I'm in the clear.
But I do find almost everyone on all sides of the issue to be just disgusting.
Like there's no precedent for this.
If you're Chrissy Teigen and you're spending $10 ,000 to get the shot before a guy who works
at a taco card here in Los Angeles, I find that gross.
I also can't.
Let's say that I don't understand why Chrissy Teigen would do that.
I don't know why I'm talking about Chrissy Teigen.
I don't disagree with any of that.
What annoys me is is that the people acting as if, but would you say something about it?
You know what I mean?
It's this grandstanding on social media of, I mean, these fucking losers, man, Jesus, get
a fucking life.
Do something.
Write a book.
Read a book.
It was always the case.
And I think now with this much time being inside that it's just, it's, it's turning into
bad shit for people.
My buddy was telling me he went to the dog park with a little dog the other day.
And this guy, he said, he was wearing like a wizard's cloak and just started coming at
his dog and picked up the dog and said, I'm going to eat you.
Was holding his dog over his head with his mouth wide open.
And my friend was like, now I knew that he was not going to be able to fit my dog into
his mouth.
But he's like, I was so horrified.
And he goes over to get his dog back from the guy and he's like, I can't touch him or get
close to him because if anybody's got COVID, it's the guy dressed like a wizard at the park.
And it's that kind of vibe.
I mean, the few times I go out of my house, go to get groceries or something.
The people I see out and about has me very worried about the reopening.
Yeah.
I'd love it to just be this great everybody's fucking and everybody's happy and everybody's
hugging.
But I do think there's a contingent of American life right now that is just people who are
unable to communicate with their fellow man.
They're not going to be able to assimilate back into society for a bit.
And that'll be interesting to watch.
Well, I mean, you're unfortunately in the eye of that storm.
I mean, it's it's going to happen everywhere.
But you know, you're in the like, the people, the people were getting the meds just
enough to be able to take a walk around the perimeter of the courtyard once a day before
they went back to the padded cell.
And then this happened and the meds went away and they're about to open those doors again.
For sure.
Woohoo.
Honestly, there and this is sad, very sad, but there are probably people who went off their
meds, you know, or he was just speaking metaphorically.
I wasn't.
But I'm saying, you know, like as people lose money, insurance, people forget, you
know, I don't know.
I'm curious to see what happens, but this has been, this is our first experience, at least
my first experience of just feeling like we are alone.
You know, I always, I always at least believed in the past that somebody had my back.
So it's kind of good to know now that we are alone and to sort of act accordingly.
I said that at the beginning of this whole thing to my parents.
I said, if there was ever a situation to let you know how on your own, you are, this
is it.
God is not here to help your government will not take care of you.
Your job means nothing and can disappear at the drop of a hat and you could be homeless
overnight.
Correct.
You are on your own period, which is why I get so mad when people search, look, I get it.
There are people out there that are running around to being stupid and doing and being
careful.
I get all that, but there are also people that are like, dude, I'm in a bad fucking spot
here, man.
I got two kids and a wife or a husband and for the last 10 years, the only way I've had
any income was touring.
Right.
You know, it's not as easy as just so that's it.
So just you just don't do it until they say, okay, you know, it's it's some people who have
to make some really hard decisions right now.
It's suck.
Yeah.
I was fortunate enough to not have to.
So, you know, anyway, that's just because you don't consider turning tricks a hard decision.
Well, I'm also too because I'm lazy.
Yeah.
They come to you and they come.
I mean, I am the type of person.
If you gave me the option of work the full day or eat one less meal tomorrow, I'd be like,
I can get by on the one less meal.
Sure.
I don't think I need to.
All of them.
I hear.
I'm.
Anyway, let's get back to the fun, Pat.
Yeah.
You know, let's get back to the fun.
What's going on in the world of entertainment?
Is there any news happening?
I mean, lately, it's all just we're pulling the plug on this, they're putting warnings in
front of this.
I don't consider that actual news.
The whole, that whole thing is being just used as a political spike.
I saw that the Snyder cut of Justice League was, yeah, putting heavy quotes around this mistakenly
streamed for an hour.
I'm like, who believes this?
Who believes that this is how this happened and that they didn't just let people watch an
hour of it and say, just say it was mistakenly streak, but why would they do it?
Like why would A, why would they put it in place of Tom and Jerry, where they're going to
get in trouble?
Because it's an R rated movie instead of a G rated movie.
But why, what do they gain from releasing it online and our early, doesn't it hurt their
bottom line?
They didn't do this.
It didn't happen is what I'm saying, they got a bunch of people together and said, we're
going to give you a link to watch an hour of Justice League.
We want you to say good things.
And then the story is is that it mistakenly streamed on HBO Max because that gives it more
mistake.
That's what they did.
Oh, okay.
I mean, give me a fucking break with this.
Oh, we mistakenly sent it out over, I mean, what the fuck are they talking?
It's not a pocket text, it can't happen.
It can.
I mean, I don't know what happened here, but I will tell you on, on this last sitcom I did,
the first three episodes, the, the dialogue was not matching the mouths like in an old karate
movie, like in half the country, it was, it was a five -second delay on their mouth and
their boy.
And I went in and I said, guys, this is the fox network, are you, are you fucking kidding?
I was furious.
And it did it for three additional weeks.
Sometimes these servers get jumbled or something, I mean, look, I just said these servers get
jumbled.
I'm not, I'm not a big computer head, but something goes on where these places can have fuck
ups, but I, I don't know, I don't know how exciting it is that it accidentally dropped
in the place of Tom and Jerry.
I'm not sure I agree with you then.
Um, I, I don't think there's any way that happened.
I just applied it all, but, but, you know, that's, that's just me.
Another movie news, there's rumors swirling that Rob Zombie is going to direct, oh, for Christ's
an adaptation of the monsters.
That's been in the works for a while, with Sherry Moon Zombie playing Lily.
I love these people who the only time they work is because somebody in their family puts
them in something.
Yeah.
Well, you know, I mean, I don't mean to pick on her, but like Kevin Smith's, like when
I was reading the line up for the new He -Man show and it's like Kevin Smith's, it's like,
guys, you know, anyway, Jill, uh, Jill Ireland, uh,
was Charles Bronson's wife is in a lot of these Bronson pictures.
And it's like, oh, boy.
And, yeah, Eastwood did it with Sandra Locke.
Well, and it was like that thing where last two weeks ago when, um, what's her face, uh,
that was married, Olivia Wilde came out, you know, praising, who's that hot stud?
She's fucking Mary Styles.
Hi, I was Harry style.
Oh, he's so this and it's like, you're fucking this guy.
And that's why he's in the movie.
Yeah, it's so nice to have a gentleman on set.
Like she's going after LeBouf who did some terrible things, but he's like trying to do
the work and get better and she takes a pot shot at him and praises how it's nice to finally
have somebody of quality on set, somebody who treats people with respect.
And yeah, you can't, we can't trust you when you're fucking him and you're in the honeymoon
phase of fucking the hottest guy in the world.
Like you might be a little infatuated with him.
Yeah, that's your movie news.
I was just fucking great.
I don't fucking know, but God, it's just like, you know too much when you start working
in this business and you can't enjoy things in the same way.
And for me, that's been a real tough pill to swallow that I sit down and watch a movie
and I'll just, I know too much.
I just don't know who's an asshole.
I know who's a phony.
I just don't understand why everybody can't shut the fuck up.
Why is everything a fucking ethics pose?
Why just shut the fuck up?
You know, yeah, it's, you know, like the Meghan Markle thing.
It's like, it's like, I think the royal family's gross.
I'm not surprised to hear that they're probably racists.
Yeah, but, but why do you have to go on Oprah and do this whole like I couldn't believe it?
Could you not believe it?
You got into bed with these people.
Are you surprised that it's a backwards family over there like, you know,
I watched that, that interview too and I couldn't have cared less about it.
But it was sort of interesting as a, you know, little sociology type deal.
Sure.
My, my thing is in, let's say at least 25 % of marriages,
there is an older relative who would definitely say something racist about an
interracial couple, right?
Yeah.
And I would say in 75 % of marriages are interracial relationships.
There is an old relative who's going to think something and not say it.
Because of how they grew up, there are tons and tons of racists in the world.
We all know that.
So like, okay, the queen who is 90 says, well, what color will the boy skin be?
You know, and I don't doubt that that happened.
But generally that would not be a, we go on Oprah kind of discussion.
You know, yeah, the, the woman's in her 90s.
She seems bad shit to me.
It's like, if I, if I had brought home one of the girl that did it who was black,
my, I have relatives who would say something to my face.
And it wouldn't be, you know, something out of Mississippi burning,
but it would be some sort of weird half -assed, you know, I'm going to ask this
without, you know, being offensive, but it is offensive.
It'd be a question of what would your baby look like?
Sometimes it's that, right?
The passive aggressive.
Yeah.
And sometimes it's somebody who's so racially uneducated, they ask a question
that they don't even realize is offensive.
Correct.
Yes.
So I don't look.
If I had to stick it up for any of these folks, I know, if I had to put my
Elizabeth is a monster, don't get me wrong.
If I had to put my money on it, I'd say Queen Elizabeth is probably genuinely racist.
Of course, it's just like that to me, that discussion would be on the way home,
Harry and Megan being like, Jesus Christ, could you believe she asks us that and kind
of chuckle about it.
And or also the looker in the eye and say, that's a racist thing to say.
How dare you ask me that if you really want to stand up to her, but to then report it
months later on Oprah is sort of a bizarre choice to me.
I just, I don't get the people that are always at every turn like I couldn't believe.
It's like, you know, I was comparing it to the, I've been watching a lot of mob documentaries.
And it's always about a guy testifying against the family and all this.
And there's always a part where the guy goes, I lived the life I followed the code.
And then I realized that my life was threatened.
And I decided that because they had turned on me, I had to, it's like, they didn't turn on you.
You knew what this was when you got into it.
Agreed. Agreed.
Like the, can somebody one time ever just go, you know, I don't know what I was expecting.
But this is fucked up, you know, like just that much, that much.
I don't know what I was expecting, but, you know, like, right.
It's, you know, it, it, it really does seem like the sort of thing that they should have.
Maybe they did, but like, just looked at the queen and been like, I think this is fucked up in racist.
And let's talk about it.
And maybe that would work.
Maybe it wouldn't, but like, this whole thing of people delighting in others being exposed
or private things coming out of whatever, it's, it becomes gross because it can always turn right back around.
You know, like, I don't know, it's a, it's an ugly time.
It's not speaking of exposed.
You have your penis out right now.
Why?
Is that a problem?
Is that a problem for you, Joe?
It's just like, I, I, I like, I talk a lot of shit.
Joe and I talk a lot of shit about a lot of, a lot of things, a lot of people.
And I never feel good about it, you know, and when I watch all these people, like,
uh, you know, bring them down, fuck them all, bring them down.
I'm like, I know shit about you.
Okay.
Oh, well, I'm not going to name it on about.
I'm not going to name names.
Yeah.
Well, let me name it off.
We'll talk, continue to talk shit.
I just know a lot of, I know a few people out in the big press right now.
Okay.
Really flying their ethics flag that have a lot of nice, juicy rumors floating around about them.
And yeah, and when I tell you folks, it's not what you're thinking, meaning, no,
it's not some lug head guy that you think it's just like, dude, what are you doing,
man?
You're playing Rachel Maddo, isn't it?
She's, she's, she's handsy.
Handsy, handsy, Maddo.
Yeah.
Anyway, yeah, well, basically, what I'm saying is we got a, no,
we got to stop us.
We got to stop it.
I mean, it's just, it's out of control.
And, and I'm sitting there watching it.
I'm always a part of it, you know, I'm watching it.
I'm enjoying it, but there's just, there's a grossness about it.
It's a, it used to be, you know, a tabloid thing.
It would be on a current affair or something like that.
And now it like is culture.
And it's, well, there was a thing that we shit on.
It was a thing that we shouldn't look at these rags that, that, that,
that only promote celebrity gossip in these, right, just, you know,
Kitty Kelly was like sort of like a, you know, you know, she would write these
exposé biographies and the celebrities always railed against her.
And like, you know, and there was, there was kind of like a skepticism about it.
Like, oh, that, you know, and, and when somebody in turn, like a celebrity,
we'd go out and write a tell all book.
Yeah.
It was kind of gross and like, what are you doing?
And now it's applauded.
Now it's like people are applauded.
I remember tweeting about this about a year ago.
The, the tattletail, like the Europe praise now for being a tattletail.
Yeah.
Like, and not saying that that's always bad.
Sometimes, sometimes you have to, yeah, we're not talking about sexual assault.
We're not talking about whatever we get serious, horrible things that go up.
Of course, but yeah, it's, so nobody's saying that there just, there just is no
line anymore with, with, you know, like the cost.
My friend was pointing out to me the other night.
My friend Dante was pointing out to Cauchy six nine.
It's like, there's a documentary about him now.
And he's spun his snitchery.
This is a, he's a perfect example of what we're talking about.
He spun his whole snitch thing into like, he, like, brags about it now.
Yeah.
Like, oh, I switched it up on those motherfuckers and this and that.
And it's like, dude, you're a rat.
You're a rat piece of shit.
Well, what did he do?
I'm sorry.
He fucking went and court and testified against all these people when he got in trouble.
He got arrested and then he turned states and testified and sent all these
people off to jail to save his own ass and and and now he's bragging about that.
And people are applauding him like good for you.
And it's like, this guy wasn't Donnie Brasco.
Right.
He wasn't sent in by the feds to, to, to infiltrate.
He fucking and Donnie Brasco's great, a great example.
It's like, here's a guy that did it legally and was supposed to do it as his job
and had to go into hiding because it was like, you know, like snitches get stitches.
You know, whatever that was called back then.
Now it's a cause he's excited.
He's being like applauded for it.
Like people are like, this is great.
What the fuck is going on?
I don't know what I, what I realized was, was really making my anxiety worse.
Was every time I go on Twitter and seeing how much of Twitter now is somebody
screen grabbing or retweeting somebody's tweet and then saying like, look at this
fucking idiot here.
Yeah.
And it first, you know, when it's somebody calling out Donald Trump, okay,
yeah, you're, you're punching up there at the president.
And, and of course he gave us lots of stuff to laugh about.
But what I'm seeing now is like a guy I know calling out another guy I
knows tweet and saying like, look at this complete fucking idiot.
And I'm like, wow, do I hate this?
Why do I hate that like when I have, when somebody quote, tweet something of mine
and you don't see one of the people who did it, like you know, that probably means
it's somebody talking shit about something you said and it starts to make you crazy.
And none of it's real even.
But bull shit, everybody's bored and they want to feel better about themselves.
And at some point, the way you feel better about yourselves is bringing down
others. And it's, you know, I've been guilty of it myself.
Talking shit is fun.
There's a, there's a scratching an itch feeling about it that does make you feel
better about yourself.
But at the end of the day, man, it's just bad, comically.
And they won't.
And like, you're going to see it a party in three months and you're like,
look at this fucking idiot with this fucking stupid opinion.
It's like guys, they won't even do that jokes.
They won't even do that at the party.
They'll walk up and be friendly and act like, and act like they shouldn't have done
it. And then go back online later that night and do it again.
And, and that's the thing, because thanks to Hollywood and all of its disgusting
fucking glory, there is, you can't apply punching up to it anymore.
Because everybody figures out a way to manipulate what the definition of
punching up is to say that anything they do is punching up.
It's all bullshit.
Everybody in that industry is full of shit.
They're all fucking hypocrites.
And they've been hypocrites from day one when they said fat shaming was wrong.
But then all fucking clamored around Conan O 'Brien every night and laughed at
when he made fun of Kirstie Alley.
They're all fucking lying scum.
I mean, to use a much more current example,
the fat shaming stuff, God, they went after Trump for his wait for the Republicans,
all these goons and Ted Cruz.
Look at this, look at how bad he fucking looks.
Look at his fucking beard, look at his fucking jeans, look at his foot.
I despised Ted Cruz.
I despised Donald Trump.
They're evil people who are trying to make society worse.
When you go after their clothes, hair, weight, whatever else, it's just kind of
like, guys, there are people reading this who are on your side,
who are much fatter than Donald Trump, who know now that you hate them and think
they are worth less.
You know, you went to the wait thing.
You didn't have to.
You had every other thing at your disposal.
But all these, I saw so many times on Twitter, people would say like, Hey, guys,
let's not shame them for such and such.
But then turn around and be like, look at the juicy ass on Donald Trump.
I'm just saying you can't do both.
If you want to make your fat jokes, please make them go right ahead.
I don't care.
But don't then act like certain kinds of jokes are wrong.
And if they're about certain people, you can say they're fat because if you say Donald
Trump's fat, you're also saying a guy who was the same size as Donald Trump is fat.
He gets that a guy, a lady who's fatter than Donald Trump now has to want to kill
herself because millions of people are like, look at this fat piece of shit.
I hate Hollywood so much.
It's not even just Hollywood.
It's just it's ever mostly Hollywood.
Hollywood is an awful place.
Don't get me wrong.
No, it's not an awful place.
It's awful people.
There's two, those are two different things.
The people make the place and the place make the people.
But you know, I don't want to shit on the whole town.
It's not the town's fault.
You know, Joe, you can check out any time you like, but the thing is you can never leave.
All right.
We got to get moving here.
Let's do.
Why don't we just do a quick movie corner, two and two and then get to our movies.
You know, usually on these ones where we cover more than three, let's do two and two.
Because usually on these ones where we cover more than one film, we don't even do a movie corner.
All right.
Well, that's when we're doing 12 films, Joe.
Well, all right, don't, don't, don't, everything doesn't have to be an argument.
Southland tales.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Why would you?
So look, everyone has these movies where like you watch it, you hate it.
Five years pass and you're like, I've got to be wrong.
You know, that's the reason why I've watched Blade Runner in all its many forums where I'm like, I'm just missing something.
And then at the end of the day, I go, Pat, it's okay that you don't like Blade Runner.
Southland tales I saw theatrically when it came out.
I absolutely loved and continued to love Donnie Darko.
I think it is an amazing first film.
I think it is, you know, we'll do an episode about it sometime.
But I do really think it's something special.
Southland tales was hated on its release.
I saw it.
I hated it.
And everyone now says, well, it was the sophomore slump.
Everybody thought it was going to be another Donnie Darko.
Actually, Donnie Darko is bad.
A lot of people say on that lately because it became something that like dudes liked.
But Southland tales is this lost masterpiece.
I keep reading this more and more.
It's not no movie captured.
The poster rock or post 9 11 sensibility like Southland.
You read this all the time and everybody got on it just because it wasn't Donnie Darko,
but it's actually better.
It's his masterpiece, blah, blah.
I've been here in this talk, get louder and louder over the last 10 years.
But I never thought I was going to rewatch the thing just because I hated it so much.
Then out on arrow films comes a big overstuffed tons of extras.
It's got the three hour con cut.
When it premiered a con, it was considered one of the biggest debacles in the history of the festival.
They cut like 20 minutes from it, re -restructured the entire movie.
And it still didn't work.
But the cons cut is supposed to be like this big disaster.
And it's like heaven's gate.
Like everybody always wondered what if this was the lost masterpiece.
So I watched it.
I watched the full three hour cut.
I remembered all the feelings I had about.
I actually remembered a lot more of it than I expected to.
The movie makes almost no sense.
Very little of it works.
All of the actors, he's clearly trying to do a Tarantino thing where he reinvents people,
but he winds up just with a lot of miscast actors.
It's wall is Sean as like some sort of wizard.
It's Sherry O 'Terry.
It's John Lovitz as a hardcore police officer.
You know, it's Sean William Scott and Justin Timberlake as Iraq that's Justin Timberlake
sings that killer song, all the things that I've done.
And like a musical sequence with dancing girls like out of the big lapowski.
It's it.
If you want to say something positive about it, it feels like
America now.
It felt like it was sort of ahead of its time in in the same way that
what's the mic judge movie?
Idiocracy.
And the same way that like while we thought that this was supposed to be like look how crazy things might get
and it actually feels like how society turned out.
That's sort of an interesting aspect about watching it now, but the movie is impossible to decipher.
It doesn't make sense.
It's not fun.
It's not good.
It doesn't work.
The con cut doesn't work.
When you watch him discuss it, he seems like a guy who's just kind of troubled and has a lot of anxiety.
And can't seem to get his thoughts on paper the way he wants.
He now wants to make this into like a five part thing, incorporating film and graphic novels and etc.
And I just think it seems to be like a guy who had all the heat in the world.
He blew it.
And now he can't just let it go and admit that this thing didn't work.
Because more Southland tales, I assure you, is not the answer to fix the problem of Southland.
Original soundtrack by Moby on this film.
I mean, Moby.
Right there.
It would turn me away.
Have you seen Southland tales?
I tried to watch it when it came.
That was terrible.
It's really bad.
I mean, anyway, people sometimes want to just award ambition.
You know, like an ambition is a great thing.
And at a time when many movies are very unambitious kudos.
But you still have to have a movie that makes sense.
Ambition alone doesn't make a good movie.
I, because we're doing Eddie Murphy, I'm going to do two Eddie Murphy films.
I watched start to finish last night, Mr. Church on 2B.
Now it was on IMDB TV.
I think it was on whatever.
I've seen I think every Eddie Murphy except Mr. Church.
I mean, it is, it's a terrible movie.
It's terrible.
It's, it's, it's, it's so amateurly written.
It's written by somebody.
By the way, as we, as we sit and talk about everything wrong with television,
it's written by a producer and writer of many of your favorite sitcoms these days.
You know, no offense to her, but you know, she's way up the ladder at mom.
Who wrote it?
I don't remember her name.
Okay.
But she wrote on sitcoms and then she wrote this story about her childhood.
And this man named Mr. Church who came to stay with her, her and her mother,
as her mother was dying of cancer to cook for them.
And Eddie Murphy's great in it.
You know, he is, he assumes the role and he is, he is this person.
He's great.
It's interesting watching it because you forget sometimes there were a few moments where I was like,
oh, wait, this is the Eddie Murphy that was in like trading places.
That's weird.
You know, like, he's great.
All the actors actually are pretty great in it.
But the script is so poorly written.
It's so cliched.
I mean, you know, it's, it's also suffered great criticism for the, you know,
what, what Spike Lee, I believe, coined as the magical Negro approach in cinema.
But that, all of that aside, it's just a bad, bad movie.
But Eddie Murphy was so good.
And there was enough mystery around his character that I wanted to keep watching
because I really wanted to see what this character was all about.
So I hung in there till the end.
And, you know, it didn't make me cry as it, as much as it tried to.
It didn't make me feel much as much as it tried to.
But I enjoyed watching Eddie Murphy in his performance in it.
And I thought he was very good.
Is it just his name or is there a religious aspect to it?
Like my, my thinking with how you're describing it is that he turns out to be Jesus or something.
No, no, it's nothing supernatural.
Again, this is based on a true story, Pat.
And, you know, it's, it's, it's, he's a very sweet man.
But then you realize there's, there's potentially a dark side there or something,
like something's going on.
Like he's got, he's got some demons.
And you, you want to find out what they are?
So he's Satan.
He's Satan.
He's the devil.
Yeah.
And they call him Mr. Church to throw you off.
Yeah, yeah.
There you go.
That's the big twist.
So Eddie Murphy with a stellar performance, but terrible, terrible, terrible script.
Also directed poorly by the man who did driving this daisy and Bruce Barisford.
Yeah.
So.
I saw, I care a lot, which is new to Netflix.
And just one Rosamond Pike, the best actress, Golden Globe, even though the Golden Globes,
have recently been added as a complete sham, even though everyone knew this for decades.
I care a lot is a really nasty piece of work.
It is a woman, Rosamond Pike, who played the Gone Girl.
And she's in kind of a similar mode here, a very like ice queen type.
But she, you know, uses conservator conservator ship, which is what Britney Spears has been in the news about lately.
Her dad has a conservator, man, it's hard to say.
Conservative ship on her.
That's not the right word.
What do you call it?
I don't know.
I know what you're talking about, but I don't know how to say the word properly either.
But yeah, she basically takes old people out of their homes and puts them into this home and takes their money.
So you can kind of take control of a human being.
Apparently this actually happens in the real world a lot, where it's like we've deemed you unable to live on your own.
You need to be put into housing by a judge, and then they clean them out.
So it's like an actual practice that people use to sort of like what John Mahoney's character was doing and say anything on a more modern level.
But so obviously she's a terrible person.
And at one point she decides to do this to DN Weast, the great DN Weast, who I'm very happy to see in movies more lately.
Yeah.
They take her out of this big nice house.
They learn that she's got like diamonds and kind of a lot of money to her name.
And they're like, oh, sweet.
We found a real, a real great target here.
And come to find out that her son is in the Russian mob, which is a really great premise for a movie.
He's going to want revenge on her.
However, the Russian mobster is played by Peter Dinklage.
That's fine, by the way.
He is very funny in the movie.
But tonally, I mean he is doing a big broad comedy with his henchmen.
It's like the villains and like the mask with Jim Carey kind of stuff when they go to their scenes.
Like being over the top villain stuff.
He's always requesting a smoothie.
And then it's like not the right mix of his smoothie and stuff.
It's like big jokes.
Then they try to play like the dark realism of the other story.
And for me, really it just kind of needed an iron to go through the thing and just iron out the tone and decide what kind of movie they wanted to make.
That said, it keeps the twists coming.
It's entertaining.
It's not a great movie, but it certainly passes the time and it works.
It holds your interest.
It's just one of those where everybody in the movie is such a piece of shit.
Everybody in the movie.
That you're just, you're left feeling kind of bad and gross as opposed to rooting for anybody.
And there's a moment in this speaking of Jay Ferguson again.
I was talking with him about this movie and he was like, yeah, you're just like, oh fuck.
There's a moment in this movie where you're like, Dan Weist is going to kick ass.
And like, what a great movie that would be an old lady getting her revenge.
And it's not that.
It just, it keeps going in ways that make you feel worse as opposed to feeling some form of release.
It's a lot of shitty people behaving shittily.
And at the end, you just feel kind of shitty.
But it's not a bad movie.
I liked it to some degree.
All right.
I watched the Eddie Murphy Owen Wilson vehicle I spy.
That I always thought was funny.
I remember when I was in college, it was on cable a lot.
And I would catch it and enjoy parts of it.
And I wanted to sit down and rewatch the whole thing.
It got completely eviscerated at the time that it was released.
But which I don't understand because Owen Wilson is really funny in it.
It's, it's, it's, it's the, you know, it's classic.
It's like your favorite form of Owen Wilson.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Where he's like kind of a nerd.
And he's trying to, you know, he, but he's a spy and he's trying to be cool.
But he's not cool.
And whatever.
And it's, it's your favorite Eddie Murphy Murphy, like big, arrogant, loud, hilarious Eddie Murphy.
And, you know, it's a buddy movie.
They have to work together to go on this spy mission.
Eddie Murphy plays a boxer that, that is brought in as a civilian for cover.
To help Owen Wilson be able to pull off this mission.
Owen Wilson hates Eddie Murphy's character.
You know, he doesn't like him because he finds him to be obnoxious.
Eddie Murphy is condescending and thinks Owen Wilson is a nerd.
And then, you know, slowly, they have to learn how to work together.
It's classic buddy movie shit.
But it's really fucking funny.
It's really funny.
You know, there was a, there was a scene I sent you last night, Pat, that didn't come through.
Because it was, you know, the quality was bad because I recorded on my phone.
But where they're, they're like trapped in a sewer.
And they're a little worried about what might happen with the outcome might be.
And Owen Wilson goes, where are you from, man?
Because he's like trying to be human for the first time with, with Eddie Murphy.
And Eddie Murphy goes, look, man, don't take it personally.
I'm not one of those dudes is going to open up and, and, and really bond with another dude.
So just I'm sorry, man, nothing, no offense, but find the next man.
And then it immediately cuts to Eddie Murphy sitting on a pipe going, my grandma raised me.
She's the one to put all the work in.
It's funny.
It's, it's got some really classic funny Eddie Murphy stuff.
Classic funny own Wilson stuff.
Fomka Janssen's in it.
She's great.
It's a fun movie, man.
I mean, that's it.
It's just a fun.
You're not there for the action.
Obviously, and they know that.
You're not there for the espionage and they know that you're there to watch two funny guys.
Sort of work their way through a spy mission.
And I thought it was funny.
Saw it theatrically.
I remember nothing about it.
That was a real lost period for Eddie.
Didn't he do one with De Niro called like showtime or something?
Yeah, which I think sucked.
Look, that was like when it was like nutty professor.
And then like, it'd be a bad one, then a decent one.
Yeah.
Then like he would do like doctor do little and that would hit.
And then he would do like a thousand leaves or whatever the fuck that thing was.
Right.
You know, like one.
Well, there was one where he only gets a thousand words.
That's what I would say.
I didn't see that one either.
But I will say this.
I and I texted you this last night.
I said there should be a box set where it's life.
Norbit.
And I spy and that's the overlooked Eddie Murphy comedies.
There is funny as the golden child or any one of, you know, those types of Eddie Murphy movies.
I mean, it's not everything can't be trading places is my point.
Trading places is an utter masterpiece in the comedy genre.
And this is not that.
But it's definitely funny or in my opinion, then like the golden child.
It's definitely better than the clumps to.
Yeah.
I think it's funny or overall than nutty professor.
I like the nutty professor a lot.
But like, I think this has more consistently funny scenes in it.
Fair enough.
I mean, for me, if I'm talking all time, great Eddie Murphy, I'm talking about nutty professor.
And I'm also talking about today's film, the original coming to America.
Which is, I guess, where we'll start.
I mean, I rewatched coming to America this week in anticipation of the sequel.
It is very, very, very funny.
There is really hilarious stuff in it.
The highlights, of course, are the fringe characters with Arsenio and Eddie playing, you know, all the guys in the barbershop.
Playing the guy in sexual chocolate, playing the preacher, et cetera.
Yeah.
They all return for the sequel.
From the episode that's my mama.
Yeah, yeah.
That boy good.
The barbershop scenes still to this day.
I mean, I used to rewind them as a kid and I rewind them now.
When they're doing the bit where they're going back and forth, no, you didn't.
When that little guy goes, no, you did not scrams it at him.
That is one of the biggest laughs I've ever had in a movie.
I love his delivery of that line.
Yeah.
It's those scenes are great.
Eddie Murphy playing all those.
Can I remember at the end of the movie when it revealed that he was the Jewish guy?
My mom and dad and I were like, what?
We couldn't even believe it.
But Heather didn't know.
She hadn't seen the movie and had no idea that that was him.
But you know, the whole exchange about Muhammad Ali and the juxtaposition of the black
guys being like, I was mama named Clay.
I'm called Clay and the white Jewish guy being the guy being like, God damn it.
He has a right to be called Muhammad Ali.
It's such a crazy exchange between these guys.
The Joe Frazier Rocky Marciano, that whole boxing thing is insanity.
Like, it's great.
It's really, really great.
And Eddie Murphy's character, Prince Akeem, is one of his best characters.
I mean, Eddie's usually just Eddie.
This is definitely a character.
You get the innocence of this guy really comes through.
When he does really specific character work like in Bowfinger, like in Knight of Professor,
you know, some of the smaller parts.
It's just the most impressive character work you could ever find.
And the fact that he's never been awarded for it is honestly kind of criminal.
He won an Oscar.
When?
I got nominated for Dreamgirls.
And he won?
No, he didn't win.
He did get nominated.
But he didn't win.
Yeah.
But look, it made me sit through Mr. Church.
That's what I'm saying.
You know, but yeah, you're right.
The innocence like him standing on the fire scape.
Yes.
Fuck you too.
Yeah.
Just not getting like what any of it really means.
He's just so excited to be in this in this other world that he's not used to.
And you know, it's it's it's prints in the proper kind of stuff, you know.
Yeah.
And to watch it now, you know, Eddie Murphy, you have to remember was like 25 in coming to
America.
I mean, like a kid.
And he's just a man in complete control of his gifts.
He is amazing.
The movie is hilarious.
And John Landis, despite his numerous flaws, which let's not discuss his personal life for
wants on this podcast and just say he is one of the all time great directors of comedy.
When he was in his zone, he did comedy that it's weird because it's pace so slowly sort of.
He just sort of puts the camera in wide so you can sort of see everything.
And just lets it play out.
And it feel it almost felt like watching a silent film compared to the editing of today's
comedies in both the sequel to coming to America, which will be discussing and Tom and Jerry.
It's like a million edits.
The most simple scene is is chopped up to the point where you can barely follow what's going on.
And there was something really appealing in coming to America about just Landis knows where the camera
should be to get the biggest laugh at every time.
He gives you the reaction shots you want when you want them.
He knows how to add little tweaks to make scenes funnier.
And coming to America is some of his best stuff, especially the first half.
The stuff in Zamunda is hilarious in coming to America.
And when he first arrives here, stuff in the back half, like it's good.
The farce where John Amos is running around, which John Amos trips on the stairs is.
Which I still don't know if that was on purpose or not.
I would say much like the Bill Murray fall in Scrooge.
It had to have been real.
Had to have been real.
But that whole farce thing at the end, they kind of don't know how to end the movie
to some extent.
The romance stuff doesn't hit as hard as the comedy stuff.
I don't find Eddie Murphy's girlfriend to be particularly interesting as a character.
But coming to America is a classic comedy and it's one of Eddie's best for sure.
And one of the great cameo roles of all time.
Frankie Faison as the landlord is just.
I mean, he's talking about a show stealer.
I mean, that guy comes in the way like Bernie Mac used to come in in a comedy in one scene.
And you'd be like, holy shit man.
You know, but yeah, his opening line when he opens the door and just goes,
what the fuck do you want?
Like there, it's just like the line after.
I've always said my favorite line of the whole movie is when he goes,
here's the apartment I was telling you about.
It's real fucked up.
I mean, he just hit in the notes, man.
The guy just knows how to, oh, he knows the music.
Samuel Jackson coming in as the.
Not a funny scene, but Samuel Jackson.
So convincing as the crazed like gunpoint robber like.
Landis knows that that scene works off of that guy being scary.
It's young.
It's young terrifying like jagged Samuel Jackson.
Like it's a scary and tense scene.
Now that movie would be.
It would be a cameo from Tracy Morgan would come in as the killer.
And he'd have his own comedy and there'd be no stakes to the scene at all.
Like watching them back to back, it's just kind of like.
It really kind of encapsulated how far film an American comedy has fallen.
Yeah.
And I'm not saying there weren't bad movies made in the fucking eighties.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just saying like.
As we head into coming to America.
I listened to two, three hours of our Cineo Hall on Howard Stern this week.
I was driving around and I parked in my garage and listened to him.
Because I don't know much about our Cineo Hall.
I wasn't allowed to watch a show as a kid, which is weird, but I just couldn't watch it.
Or in living color, which shows you that maybe there was some racism in my parents.
I don't know.
But our Cineo was talking about how.
Eddie's, you know, people have been begging Eddie to make come to America too for 30 years.
And he kept saying no.
He was holding out for the script to be perfect.
He had the original guys do a draft.
He had Kenya Barris do a draft.
He had all these different people do drafts and nothing was right.
And then finally our Cineo gets the call and Eddie's like, we got it.
We got it.
And I bought it and I usually am so skeptical and I'm like, you're fucking lying.
And they're talking and Robin on Stern is like, oh, I love it and I was laughing.
And then it gets to Howard and Howard is the most prepared interviewer in the world.
He always knows questions where they're like, how did you know that about me?
That's crazy.
I was 12 other people in another room sending him the questions.
Of course.
But I love Stern.
I love his interviews.
I love what he gets out of people.
And Stern says when our Cineo asks him, have you seen it?
There's this weird pause.
And he goes, you know, they sent me the link on Friday.
And he launches into this thing that sounded exactly like something that I would say.
If somebody asked me if I had seen the move.
And the link didn't work, then I finally got it going.
And the audio didn't work.
Then I just got it going.
And the video worked.
But the audio didn't.
And he keeps going through it.
You're lying.
I'm just like Howard.
Because Howard has been talking now for weeks about how coming to America is one of his favorite movies
of all time and how he can't wait for this.
And it was so clear to me that he was just like, I'm not going to be able to lie about this
convincingly.
And that's how I feel about it, too.
It's not like Tom and Jerry where it's a piece of shit and you kick it out the door and you never think about it again.
It's like, it's just, it's like the Bill and Ted thing.
It puts a stain on something you loved.
And that always is going to hurt more.
It really hurt more.
I was concerned about the sequel after the first trailer.
Because I was like, man, they're, they're rehashing a lot in this trailer.
And this is not going to be the movie.
So they've constructed a trailer here that's showing me everything I want to see to make me want to watch it.
Right.
But this movie is clearly going to be much more than this because it's going to be about him and his son.
And which concerned me because I was thinking to myself, well, I don't know if that's the movie I want to see.
Yeah.
Very happy for Jermaine.
Jermaine and I've been friends since he started in comedy.
I love Jermaine.
So I was happy for him to be in something this high profile.
Then the second trailer came out.
And the second trailer again hit all the nostalgia notes.
And I was like, this is not good, man, something's up here.
Yeah.
The title was also bothering me because you got a trailer that's saying with a song and it's going, I was coming to America.
Now it's coming to me.
And it was very obvious that most of this film was going to take place in Africa.
Yeah.
And I remember I even texted you and I said, why is this not called coming to Africa?
That's a perfect sequel title.
Like why wouldn't they just call it that?
And I was like, something, something's not right here, man.
It also worried me that it was the entire crew.
This always concerns me when it's like the entire crew from Dolomite came back.
And it's like, they Dolomite worked.
It was well received.
It was highly praised.
Everybody said, it's so good to see Eddie back in a comedy.
That's actually funny.
That's also dirty.
Like how Lulia Eddie Murphy said, fuck again.
Right.
And then immediately it was like, let's put the entire crew back together.
Wesley's going to be in this now.
And it's like, you've written apart for him.
Yeah.
There was no character for him.
You've written it.
You start to smell those rats.
And then also then they came out and said, it's going to be PG 13.
You're like, all right.
I don't know, man.
Like the original, the fucks are pretty funny in the original, but I get it.
If you take those out, it's a pretty clean movie.
So I wasn't too worried about that.
Then by the way, you know, the whole and Eddie Cosby used to say this too, you know, like it's cheap to, it's cheap to swear and so forth.
Coming to America is a movie that thrives on its vulgarity on its fucking and people, because it's New York.
He's in Queens.
Yeah.
You know, it really, it really makes it sing.
And sometimes there are movies where the profanity is a part of the reason that the comedy sings.
It's like, it can be used as any other tool in a writer's arsenal, but coming to America is a, is a cussing movie.
Yeah.
And then the second thing I read where you go, okay, now my antenna is really up, was the director saying we didn't need it to be rated R.
We made a really funny PG 13 movie that pushes the boundaries of PG 13 in certain places.
And then when he said that, I was like, Jesus, there's not even going to be, because I was like, they could get away with a couple of fucks and PG 13 these days.
I was like, there's not going to be any curses.
And then he said, and we needed to make a movie that was conscious of gender and race issues right now, because some of the stuff in that first movie just wouldn't flaw.
And I was like, here we go. This is going to be a fucking disaster. As soon as you started talking about all that, I was like, this is going to be a fucking disaster because everything in that first movie, the gender issues were addressing the gender issues.
Absolutely.
It was about sexism. It was about a man going flying his flying in the face of authority and saying, I'm not doing this, like I'm going to do this my way because I'm a decent man.
And once the director was saying, we needed to make sure that we didn't, I was like, we're in a lot of trouble now, because now it's not even going to tackle these issues in an edgy way, like they did in the first movie.
Yeah.
I think it's a, it's a choice in the first movie to have, you know, the woman's like, I will do whatever you say, I will do whatever you want.
And he has her bark like a dog and hop on one foot. There's an, there's an ugliness to that that I think is intentional because it's, it's saying this life that I could have.
I'm sure a lot of people watching that 1988 were like, oh man, imagine you could have a girl do whatever you want and she looks hot and you can do whatever you want to or whatever.
But Eddie Murphy goes, no, I don't want that. I want something more pure. I want something better. That is dealing with gender issues in a way that is edgy and is funny.
Also, Eddie Murphy in 1988, making a movie where every single person with the exception of Louis Anderson, that you see on screen is black.
That is revolutionary. That was revolutionary. That is dealing with, you know, and in this one, he's got the same thing.
He's got a black director, a black crew, which he didn't have back then, a black writer.
And for some reason, that's not enough. We also have to explicitly in dialogue have the characters talking about these issues.
And that's the problem with movies now is that you don't, after the fact go interesting, that had something to say about, like even weird science.
You know, that's a premise that's like kind of gross by today's standards. They create a woman.
But the message that comes away, you come away from that movie with is that they realize that they want a woman with heart and a woman with intelligence.
But they don't have them sit on a chair and talk about it saying explicitly what the theme of the movie is because that's shitty writing.
And if you do say it, you say it with different words, like they say it in that film when she yells at them and goes, you had to be big shots.
You had to, you know, it's like that says it all. Why is she so angry because of these other issues. This is the point.
Right.
And you're right. I mean, but, but he also too, the director said in the interview, can't have a woman hopping on one foot and barking like a dog by today's standards.
That would be crazy and offensive. And then the character is in this sequel.
Hopping on one foot, they do it.
If ever there was a character who you did not need to have back again, it's like they, you know, Joe pointed out to me.
He watched it before I did that like the women that dropped the roses before the Prince and the king are back and they're the same actresses.
That's the extent. And there's something kind of sweet about that that everyone is back.
But it's like you don't even know or care. And they do so much bending over backwards to bring back these these actors to bring back every single bit that was successful and coming to America and do it again and do it two and three times.
And it's just they they forgot to they did come up with a new story.
They just forgot to make the movie funny and interesting, you know, like it's there's a story there.
But yeah, what this didn't need was a new story, though, all this had to be was, hey, he has a son.
His son wants to get married. He takes his son to America the way he did.
That's it. That's the story. Now they're in a new America.
They throw these opportunities away in this movie. It's unreal. They get to Queens and Arsenio looks around and goes, Queens has changed.
And they don't show you any of it. Right.
They don't at least be a montage of them walking around and seeing how things have changed. Yeah, they don't show you any of it.
It's like this could have been they come to Queens. Queens has been gentrified now.
Social media has led to an obsession with wealth and fame and money that didn't exist in the 80s when he was here.
Women literally referring to themselves as queen all the time. Right.
This, he can't find a woman who's not about the money because of modern time.
There was a million fucking ways to just kind of retread this journey again. Yeah.
And give it all the heart and all everything and make it now way more the first one was a commentary on the backwardness and the old fashioned
backwards traditions of a country that was in America. This could have been about how backwards the newfangled behaviors in America are.
You just flip it. That's it. This is such fucking simple shit and they over complicated. Now let's create a storyline where he had sex, but he was unconscious and he doesn't remember and he's got a son over there.
And then the worst decision of all and he's got to go get his son because his son is his rightful air.
And now the character that you love in the first movie for being a sweetheart is an asshole who's insisting that a man take over the throne after him.
And they make any Murphy's character completely unlikable through the entire movie.
Eddie Murphy's character is completely unlikable and what I noticed at there's a scene where Eddie tries to have sex with his wife who's the same actress from the original.
And she turns him down and his reaction to it made me laugh. He has this very funny reaction to her shutting him down for sex.
And I realized that this was about an hour into the movie and it was kind of the first time I was making noise with my mouth.
And it was like they haven't given Eddie Murphy a single moment, a single comedic moment, a single joke.
He plays this like scowling angry character that you don't like.
Every joke in the movie was clearly in my opinion was clearly ad libbed because every joke falls in exactly the same place.
Right before the edit out if every scene somebody slips a line in right and the line is the most go to first thing you would think of line whatever the scene you're talking about Eddie Murphy rolls over and he's and he's supposed to be going to sleep and then he goes this is bullshit.
And it's like that was an improper how it's just an improv Tracy Morgan at one point I mean you want to talk about wasted talent through this entire fucking thing.
When I saw everybody that was in this movie in the trailer, I was like all right, there'll be some laughs.
Yeah, because there are all these great comedians and there's not you have Tracy Morgan at that one time with a one scene where he's complaining and he's like he's like how are y 'all kings you even got no lunchables.
It's like yeah guys, this is like that was not written down you're just letting the camera roll and you're letting people rip they show one of the only funny lines of the movie is when Leslie Jones says.
Is somebody going to tell me why these match potatoes are black and then the wife says that's caviar and then they show you the outtakes at the end and you realize that that's probably a line Leslie Jones just ripped because everybody laughs when she says it like uncontrollably right.
It feels like the type of movie where everyone is laughing really hard and the director gets on his megaphone and goes all right, everybody stop laughing.
We're about to shoot this comedy scene then they shoot the scene as scripted nobody laughs then everybody resumes laughing again once it's over it seems like the original captured all the joy and the love and the happiness.
And this one it's all off screen it's just there's no fun on screen when when you're watching at the end and there's there's three scenes at least that go on for five minutes and it's
German Fowler and his love interest they have zero chemistry they have not been written a single joke there's a long scene where they riff on barbershop one and two which were written by Kenya Barris who also wrote this so it's like this weird shout out to himself.
But those dialogue scenes between Fowler and that girl that he's dating are in my opinion some of the worst romantic scenes since attack of the clones when Natalie Portman and Hayden Christensen are talking about like the sands of time or whatever and it's the most boring shit.
I could not believe that we're in like act late act two of this movie and it's German Fowler trying to fuck this girl in the most generic boring scenes I've ever seen.
Eddie Murphy disappears much in the same way Tom and Jerry disappear you don't see Eddie for a while.
Arsenios not good in it you know.
Arsenios terrible in it because he hasn't done a movie in 30 years yeah he also plays one of the most horrifying characters I've ever seen in a film he plays like this crypt keeper style like medicine man it makes no sense who like is like literally like rolling bones and saying you can see the future it's like what the fuck is this supernatural so here's another little fun story from the Arsenio on stern they they talk about kind of assembling the cast and getting everybody together.
Another and they talk to Dave Chappelle and Chappelle goes now you know that I have to be in this come to America sequel he's like I I'll do whatever it takes and Arsenio was like we were so excited and you know me and Eddie were arguing all the time because we never wanted to be in the makeup he's like these funny characters that you guys love we got to be a makeup for four hours or whatever and the shaman character was going to be six hours in the makeup chair.
So Eddie wanted to play it and then he said no I'm not doing six hours so I was going to play it and then once Chappelle came on board Eddie goes give Chappelle that part he'd be amazing in it which I don't know why Chappelle would be amazing in it but fun.
So then they they're talking to Dave he's like we sent him the script he's like the day day or two before we're getting ready to shoot the call comes in from Chappelle and he can't make it.
So I had to step into the and I'm like you know what happened is Chappelle read the script.
Chappelle is a man who knows where the funny is and he looked at the script and said oh god they've ruined it i'm dropping out yeah it's it's it's a bad bad movie I mean you know you're in trouble when one of the first jokes in the movie is Wesley snipes his country is called next door.
I mean just horrible a joke so bad that I thought I misheard it and then realized I didn't when I read some reviews later yeah everybody keeps talking about funny Wesley snipes is in this thing no it's not it's not funny at all he does a funny walk and that's it yeah he's not funny at all and he was he was a revelation in dolomite it was like okay this guy is going to have a whole new career and they somehow waste him in this because it was actually in dolomite it was a funny character in this it's like yeah.
Yeah the gag of the walk it's like do that's like stand up 101 shit man that's like that's like taking your pants off on stage for the laugh it's like come on man like this is all you guys have right now is a funny walk yeah.
The the the what's it called to one of the only laughs and this is a terrible joke even too was like they do the the McDowell thing and like
Louis Anderson comes back and they're trying the veggie burger and Louis Anderson just gags on it and again this is that's rough stuff that I mean the gag made me laugh but again it's like that's clearly not in the script they're going to react like you're eating a disgusting veggie burger right now.
The McDowell stuff there's like four retreads in this fucking thing of the McDowell's joke of like we had the Mick for what the fuck was it they have the McFlurry we had the McFurbie or whatever the fuck it is they stretch the McDowell's joke to its limit and the original I mean they didn't need to bring it back.
They not only do they bring it back the big scene in the climactic scene the movie where where Eddie is finding his his true self again and becoming trying to find his decent side again is McDowell saying to him like when McDonald's tried to take this is serious this is played serious not for humor when McDonald's tried to take me down I thought and it's like the whole joke of this is that you're a scam artist yeah that's the joke.
And by the way John Amos gets some big laughs out of playing a part that's very unlike him at the like he's a weasel in the first one and it's so funny yeah and and this one they just don't I don't know it's also go go ahead man.
There's also four musical numbers in this so pepper show up singing what a king what a mighty good can I mean this is an invoke yeah it's something else.
Then they do the thing where what's the the the queen from next door you that are the princess from next story that they want to marry Jermaine Fowler so they can rule the two countries together comes in singing get off by prints and then Leslie Jones who plays Jermaine's mom says you better get in there I know you know this song and Jermaine grabs a microphone and starts wrapping I was like what the fuck is going on in the.
I keep saying what the fuck is going on in these last two episodes a lot but that's what the reaction to have that's the reaction to have.
We in watching the original when all the dancers come in and do the big like tribal dance.
It goes on way too long you know but it's it's it is also kind of like we're celebrating this culture we've got these beautiful costumes you know we're we're going to really show you an extravagant.
You know introduction of this world the musical numbers in this are really they seem like padding you know like yeah it's like when you watch when you watch the old marks brothers movies and there'd be it the movie was like 80 minutes and three of it were like zepo singing to an old lady or something like all right I'll just fast forward this shit but why are we doing that in 2021 when you're we've got one of the most beloved properties in America it's a hundred percent padding.
In the first film it at least provides spectacle to to elaborate look how look how lavish they the the royalty lives here look at this presentation they're giving just to show him who is bright is going to be.
All that stuff in this like you said it's just padding it makes no fucking sense that invogue and salt and pepper in it other than somebody thought what a king.
Instead of what a man as a song parody was funny where I wouldn't do it I mean it's again this is stand -up comedy hack 101 it's like what the fuck man yeah and there was a point in this where I was like man Eddie Murphy I don't think he's funny anymore and then I remember no wait a minute yes he is dolomite just came out he's still funny like why I don't.
It's interesting to is that in all of my he seemed alive like again there was a light in his eyes again a joy of performing again and he was incredibly funny throughout while staying true to his character.
In this one which he's a producer of and apparently was this labor of love and etc he's checked out more often than not he's turning over the action to Germain Fowler you know like in the back half and he's not really even a key player.
The barbershop scenes are a highlight but they're about one one hundred this funny as they were the first time around so something wrong because they can't say fuck you're probably right.
So and Craig Greg Brewer did you know he's he did hustling flow he did black snake moan he did dolomite is my name he's a really good director.
This movie is shot in a way that it's it's complete there's a scene that I was talking about with Joe with Colin Jost and Germain Fowler Jost is in both movies we're talking about this week.
And the two of them are just sitting across from each other at a table and it is shot and edited in a way that you're like what in God's name is going on.
It's it seems like a first time outing and it's a it's Eddie Murphy and Craig Brewer these aren't first timers so I don't know what happened here.
But I mean anyone who's saying coming to America to is like some equal or even in the same ballpark or even a decent attempt is just lying to themselves.
I haven't talked to anybody who even liked it.
It's all nostalgia no substance when you see the first barbershop scene you laugh.
But but it's bittersweet because you're like this is the first time I've laughed in the entire movie and it's right just a straight nostalgia trip by the end of the movie you're you're praying that they bring in something else nostalgic and funny.
And then when they finally do it's wasted they bring Arsenio's preacher character back and cut away to a sincere exchange between Germain Fowler and his love interest.
Well all the funny shit that Arsenio may or may not be doing is in the background of the scene and you can't even hear it sexual chocolate comes out at the end of the movie doesn't say a word just sings a song.
Who gives a shit then he brings out the two wrapping twins from the first it's this thing is a fucking.
When he brought out the fucking wrapping twins it's like okay so you're I mean that's a very funny joke in the original but so what.
Look and I know we're not supposed to be looking at logic and something like this but what it did Eddie's character stay in touch with these two twins.
It makes most like why are they there it's like this sense you've already called back everything else let this one go we don't need the wrapping twins back.
I think and I pray that this is the case I pray that this is the case of COVID hitting at the wrong time and they had to piece this thing together as best they could.
And that's it like I pray to God that that's just what went wrong with this because I'm scratching my head it doesn't make any sense Arsenio said they wrapped the Thanksgiving before COVID well then then we're in trouble.
The only thing they might have done and no studio is going to give them money for this in this day and age is said hey we should go back and shoot some more stuff like but you know that that might have fixed it but it wouldn't have fixed problems this deep it might have added some laughs maybe.
So it's so misguided you got John legend singing queen to be at the John legends in both movies yeah really if it's if it's legend and just don't buy a ticket but a legend at the end of this and that's no offense to just.
Or legend but yeah just bad movies well she's your queen to be in the original is one of the biggest laughs of the 80s she's your queen to be is absolutely hilarious.
And you know I didn't mind John legend singing in the credit that's fine I did I did not because it's John legend singing it but because what are we doing here what are we how much nostalgia we doing why is this contemporary singer singing this just so we can have it be a part of the movie.
And it's on zoom he was doing it on zoom that's what I'm saying it's you know and then and then that character when he sings again in this movie it's clearly lip sync.
Oh yeah yeah it's it's it's a terrible terrible movie it really I want to want to redeeming quality I want to point out one last thing it's that about an hour into this movie they do a full recap of coming to America one with clips from coming to America one yeah.
Now this is one of the most beloved comedies made in my life so you got to assume everybody's seen it most people who show up for coming to America have seen coming to America almost all I would say.
But if you do feel like you need to do a recap a previously on coming to America why are you doing it an hour into the film anyone who's lost is going to be lost for an hour do it up top or don't do it.
Did you just and they're showing clips as though it's like a sitcom episode where they're reminiscing on some favorite.
You're already you're already digging up every funny moment from one and doing it again don't then show me actual clips from one.
I mean Jesus Christ how lazy can you get this feels to me and I and I I have experienced this on some of the TV shows I've I've worked on.
This to me is Eddie Murphy being in total control and nobody being there to say dude stop we're doing this it's I've I've experienced on TV shows where you do 35 rewrites of a fucking script and by the end of it and then on rewrite 36 they're like you know what let's blow it apart and just start over and it's like.
Yeah guys I don't even know what the fuck we're looking at anymore yeah you know in music they call a demo ears you've heard the song too many times from the very beginning you you have to get away from it you and he was just way too close to this nobody was saying dude no stop and and you ended up with this muddled mess of a film yeah so I unfortunately hog way down on coming to America.
Hog way down I mean we usually don't review to that we just hated but that's the case here I do think coming to America has has an edge over Tom and Jerry but the we're talking about bad bad movies and hopefully things improve yeah alright folks that's our show we'll see you next time and we'll see you and how.