I'll see you with the show you turn to when you want to hear
about movies, forget about your troubles, that sort of thing.
My name is Joe DeRosa and I will say that is the end, the extent of the fake enthusiasm
I will be putting into this day's episode.
Here with Pat, my trusty co -hosts, we were talking earlier, and the world as Pat put it has
taken an even darker turn, and it's hard to just even smile through it anymore.
It is, and there's not, I can't really put a finger on what it is.
Nothing really new happened.
They announced the master coming off on planes and everyone cheered.
Yeah, well, I love that, but I mean, you can't even take any peace of mind with it because as they tell you that,
they're telling you from the other end that it's that everything is spiking again.
They're telling you between that and Coachella,
one concert in the fucking desert are going to bring us to our knees in the coming weeks,
the plane thing and Coachella, and it's like, maybe, you know, you don't know, I don't know.
Yeah, it's just not good.
Everyone is suffering and I would say new ways, I went to a wedding this weekend and every conversation was strange.
And forced and weird.
Good wedding. Don't get me wrong, great wedding.
But yeah, I just feel like people aren't doing well, you know, as a whole.
No, my mom hosted Easter, big dinner.
Yeah, ham, ham and some turkey.
And you know, pretty large amount of people for our family, our family is shrunk significantly over the years due to death.
But, but you know, for us, it was a pretty large gathering about 14 people and it was there too, man.
I was just talking to my cousin in the kitchen, my cousin Kevin at one point and he was just like,
I just hope to God, there's just some normalcy this year and like the desperation and his voice, it's just everybody is exhausted, man.
We're exhausted.
You know, it's, I'm sorry, I don't mean to harp on it here.
You guys probably turn to this for a breath of fresh air.
Maybe our pain will ease yours.
Misery loves company as they say, but title or film I'm trying to get set up.
There you go.
And I'm sure that's a delightful experience.
It's been, it's been real fun.
Yeah.
Waiting six months for someone to read a script who you don't even want to play the lead part.
Only to have them say they're not going to get around to reading.
You know, it's some version of that experience over and over is the process of casting them.
Yeah, that's about it.
We're all keeping our fingers crossed for this person who sucks.
And then yeah, it turns out they didn't read it.
They're in a show and they're set for money.
So they're not going to read.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, it'll be like, and it'll be like, remember, Daphne from Frazier and you're like, of course, and they go, not her, but the second or third choice down from her.
Who obviously didn't play the role, but anyway, they thought about this person.
Do you know from that from being considered for the part of Daphne?
You're like, what?
Well, it's funny that you'd be excited to cast the actual Daphne from Frazier and your film.
That might mean that things aren't going so well.
She's a big get.
I'd be thrilled.
Sure.
What's her name again?
Jane Leaves.
I saw her in.
I believe it was to live in Diana L .A. playing a prostitute.
And she was naked.
And I was shocked because it's Daphne after all.
Oh, I got to go check that out now.
Come on, Joe.
Well, I.
I'd always.
I was always talking about nudity on this show.
I was always curious what Daphne looked like naked.
I know.
Oh, well, I will.
It's in to live in Diana L .A.
Which is a great movie with Willem Dafoe and Billy Peterson.
And she's credited as Jane Leaves, L .E .A .V .E .S.
So she changed it probably to get away from that nude scene.
Great two -pock song to live in Diana L .A.
That's right.
Yeah.
With a guest verse by Jane Leaves.
A lot of people don't realize that.
They're not.
Oh, the Maka Valley record.
That's why nobody knows it cuz nobody listens to that record.
No, that's in the hip hop community.
That's considered a classic.
Alright.
It's okay.
I love Mac.
It's a dark record.
That's the one that came out of treat.
I did.
Then he was.
The whole record was him saying he was coming.
Get his revenge on everybody.
It's the one thing you experienced.
that album. I'm fairly well I'm very well versed in hip -hop and hip -hop history. I feel like I've
heard at least the crucial albums from every major artist, but Tupac, even though I own his albums
on vinyl, I never listen to, never ever. I'll always throw on a biggie over a Tupac and outcast
over at Tupac. I almost cube over at anybody over at Tupac. I am a big big big Tupac guy. I am a
Tupac over biggie guy. That's a big debate you have in New York and L .A. Sure. Everybody in L .A.
says Tupac usually everybody in New York says Brooklyn or Biggie. Now here we are reversed. I live
in New York, I'm saying, Park, you live in L .A. You say Biggie. Who says there can't be unity?
I say Biggie. I mean, there's no fun to Tupac for me. He's not having fun. Although now at this
stage of my life, I used to listen to hip -hop for driving around zoom in the girls. Right. Now with my
current state of depression, maybe I would love Tupac. It's pretty good when you're not feeling great
because like I said, it's a lot of, I'll kill you and get my revenge. You know, I'll have my day,
you know, it's a lot of that kind of stuff. And this life is next. Yeah. I'll end you. What are some
more of those posthumous albums? Well, life after death, Biggie Smalls. A great one. Again, terribly
haunting. Easy, straight off the streets of Motherfuckin Compton. Yeah. But nothing on that record,
that was just a record that came out after he died. There was nothing on it like the other two where he
was like watching you right now from my grave. And you're like, wait, what? Yeah. I mean, Prince has
had a new album every three months since he passed. Same with Tom Petty. I find that stuff a little
gross even while I buy and listen to the outtakes and everything. Well, I'll tell you which one piss me
off was these these fucking twats. I mean, I mean, Austin at the Waterloo record, they're not the twats.
I like Waterloo records quite a bit. But I'm at Waterloo records. And there's a CD, a double -seat
triple CD, Bowie on the wall. And the manufacturer of the CD said, look, a new Bowie album,
you know, Exclamation Points or whatever. And I was like, oh, that's cool. There's like a triple
posthumous release Bowie record that never, you know, he never got it out of here. And then the thing
hits, I wasn't going to buy it blindly. There's only on CD and whatever. Thing hits streaming.
And I look at it. It's like, it's in a, it's in a record. It's like, it's like all versions of songs.
And then by the way, you know, Blackstar, which was his, I think, last record, is a Blackstar.
Masterpiece. It's so inventive and cool. Even if it's not your thing, just the scope of it is amazing.
And then this is like the worst version of Bowie. This is like when he was doing like, this song is
called Thaz Days Child. You know, it's like soft rock. Like, you know what I mean?
What are you talking like early, early, early days, like singer, songwriter days?
No, I'm talking about post 10 machine and prisoner phase. Yeah, that's a bad time.
Where, you know, I'm afraid of Americans. Yeah, it's after that. Like he did like,
you know, and then like towards the, then he put up that record that was like the take on,
it was like the variation of the changes cover. And then that was like he was good again, you know,
right? I still throw on his albums all the time. I really do. I got, I think I have every one of his albums,
except that really bleak period from like 1990 to 2000, 2005. Who knows, but that was.
I was watching old Bowie clips and there's a clip of him on Soul Train,
doing fame. And he kills it. He kills it. And like everybody's dancing. He's probably one of the
few white artists to play on Soul Train, I would think. And it's like so funky and like, it's awesome.
You got this like weird sort of white British guy, not sort of white, the whitest British
guys ever lived made of like all at that time. Yeah. And all the, all these, the black people in the
audience are dancing and like grooving. And you're like, wow, what a meeting of cultures here. And
like it's so cool. And then he jumped to like the late 90 or early 90s. And it's Howard Stern's
like birthday bash. And they have Bowie come on. And he does fame. And these clips will come up
like together, right? But it's his like nine inch nails version of fame. And it's just shit. And
like he's he's so into it like because it's like his new version. The sucks dude. The sucks.
Yeah. Was Luther Vandros his backup singer in that Soul Train clip? Luther Campbell of two live
crew. Well, Vandros actually sings back up on fame. That's not a joke. Oh, I didn't know that.
That's very cool. Tina Turner sings back up on some early, not early, but some early 70s
for example recording. There's some stuff. There's a song called Dirty Love on the album
Overnight Sensation. And it's a pretty funky song. And Tina Turner is one of the backup singers on it.
You know, Carly Simons, you're so vain. You're so vain. Yes. Yeah, probably I think this song is
a bio to you. You know, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Back up on that. Mr. Mick Jagger.
Oh, next time you listen to it, you won't be able to unhear it. It's like you've heard the song
a billion times. But then when it was pointed out to me, I was like, oh, shit, it's very obviously
Mick Jagger singing back up. But that's more of like a favor, right? Oh, sure. I just I always love
that one. Some big star singing. Sure. That's just a little that's a little like I'm more I'm more
mesmerized or infatuated by the idea of before they were there, like like how Stevie Ray Vaughn played
guitar. Yeah. That's dance. And no, right. We was. Yeah. That stuff's kind of cool. Or like how Adam
Duritz of Counting Crows sang back up on Sixth Avenue Heartache by the Wall Flops.
Well, you'll be proud of me as somebody who comes from the field of comedy and somebody who has
probably been subjected to this as I have. Yeah. At a family gathering. I stood up for the team
at Easter dinner this year. Okay. I did what we all want to do. And all of us feel far too awkward
and guilty to do it most of the time. I mean, I know it's taken me 22 years instead of to get to
this point. Yeah. We're sitting at the dinner table. My cousin Danielle, who I love dearly,
handed me her phone. She goes, you have to see this. You're going to be hysterical.
It is the funniest thing in the world. Oh my God. I would have loved it.
Dad would have loved this, meaning her uncle John, who was a second father, my uncle John,
who was her dad, and a second father to me and a man I miss every day that he's been gone.
All right. So a lot is riding on this right now. Yeah. Way too much pressure that you have to laugh
at. Yeah. She hands like your phone. We're pleasing ghosts with your laughter. Yeah. She hands
me the phone. I hit play. It's an acapella group doing a cover medley of Billy Joel songs
where they have changed all the lyrics to be about Passover. Oh, that's the gag. Oh, no.
I get my passing over that clip. Yeah. I get two sentences into the first song which is a
Passover version of piano in. Yeah. And I hand her back the phone. I go, this isn't for me.
And the relief. Yeah. I was like, I could have been doing this for 22 years.
Getting cornered. Oh, I got a great joke for you. You're a comedian. Listen to that.
Just finally, this isn't for me. And you got to call that a classic Passover going forward.
A Passover. Yeah. Well, she offended. Couldn't tell marginally cared. She thought she wasn't thrilled.
But no, she wasn't like, fuck you. Was her father a Jewish man?
No, that's why I was confused. Well, her husband even know enough about Passover. I wanted to do
the little riffing Billy Joel Passover songs. And I was like, I don't know any facts about Passover.
Her husband is Jewish. So I think that's why she found humor in it. Okay.
I got why she thought my uncle would think it was funny. He'd pee my like he had a really good
sense of humor. But once in a while, I think something real stupid like that was funny.
Like all parents do. All parents. I keep waiting for the day I get there.
You know, not to being a parent, but to that, to finding stupid shit funny.
Hopefully, I'll always keep my, my wit. I feel like for me, it's already there with like, how funny
I still think shit jokes are, you know, like stuff like that. You can't find a good shit joke anymore.
Shit jokes come jokes, piss jokes. They're all out the way.
Yeah.
Grabbing jokes. Yeah. So buying on girls, showering jokes. That's all gone.
It is crazy what a running theme in 80s team comedies. Just borderline sexual assault for laughs was.
Oh, yeah. It's really crazy. And it's stuff that when I was a kid, it really didn't register as being
weird. Yeah, it's wild stuff, man.
Yeah, I mean, spy the most innocent thing you get away with is
20 men spying on women, fully naked showering. Women who are 17 years old.
It was the reason you didn't think it was weird was because people didn't think it was weird.
I'm not saying women didn't. But, but like that message was not getting a crop. Like you could know
openly talk about it. And people would be like, yeah, and there was no moral, no message to it.
It was just like no one ever got punished for it. You would just watch women bathed.
When I was in college, we had a party on our I lived in a building of apartments my last few years.
There was going to be exhibit A in your trial. Is this story or about that? I hope not.
But there were six. I like beer your honor. I like beer. There were four or six units or
something in the building. And it was it was a party building. It was a very the most fun time of
my life ever was in that. One of the farewell parties we had, it was called the Panny party, I believe.
Oh, boy. And the all the hallways between the units were that was like they were outdoor balconies.
There were no interior halls. And the outdoor balcony where we had the party was draped in
panties that my friends had stolen on panty raids from a house of women that we were friends with.
And all those women came and it was like a big goof. Everybody thought it was funny, including the
women. Like everybody was laughing. And the girls were being like, look, there's money. Oh my god,
there's mine. And you didn't think there was nothing about it. And I guess it's not that terrible.
But I mean by today's standards it is, but even by those standards back then, it's it's not awful.
But it certainly wouldn't be a violation. I never took in any of that probably because I commuted to
an art school. But don't I mean, surely women have like a pair of underwear. They would rather die
than 50 people look at and hold in the air. I got to say all these were really pristine.
They were making every girl look great. Well, they were they were they were young.
You know, they were your thongs and your purples and your lace. Okay. Strabbs and all that stuff.
I didn't give any to panties. I want to be clear about that. No.
You paid and bought them. Well, yeah, I said, I paid the guys to let me borrow them.
We had a joke this week on Miss Pat. I cannot take credit for writing the joke. It was so
believe it was Pat herself, but it was so filthy that I was just shook to my core by it.
It was Miss Pat talking to her daughter who's a lesbian. And she's like, look,
I have no problem with lesbianism. She's like, I could just never do it because I know what my panties
look like at the end of the day. The audience screamed in horror, but it's funny. You know,
and you'd think at some point of one of these panty reads, somebody would be like, check it out
and there would be like a disgusting skid mark down the middle of it. No, no, nobody. There was no
shit. I mean, look, maybe we were the lucky ones. Yeah. But yeah, no, no shit, incident,
incident, or anything like that. But I mean, my point is is that now keep in mind,
we were still progressive enough that if anybody at any point had heard of a woman, I remember
one time a guy I knew, panced a girl we knew in front of everybody. Yeah. And we were like all the
other guys were like, are you insane? Like, why did you just do that? And we thought he was going to
like, he kicked out of school. Like, we were like, if dude, if she's like, she has every right to
get you like thrown out of school for that. Yeah. And panced to bush or to pants to underwear.
But it was still completely, it was bad. Yeah. But like, that's bad. And like we, you know,
we talked to her about it. And she was upset. Yeah. We talked to him about it. We were not easy on him.
And then she just, she forgave them and they got past it and whatever. And he was like, I'm sorry,
this was just a joke where I thought, you know, we're friends and I ended up being fine ultimately.
Yeah. But like, my point is, as we were still living in a progressive enough of a time that a
pancing of a woman, even if our friends was like, that's not a cool. Yeah. But we lived in a time
where, where exposed dick humor was still fine. But I guess in a jackass kind of way was usually
amongst the guys, you know, I don't think you know, I never saw Dix and I never saw Dix
in movies or anything either. Now Dix are always used in comedy. But it used to be a massive scandal
of Harvey Kitell flipped his dick out or you and McGregor, you know, now it's pretty commonplace,
especially in comedies. But and good. So be it. But I will say none of my friends were big on
showing me there. I don't think I've seen any of my friends Dix. I had one guy who'd do the thing
like, here, I got some bubble gum and like, show you his watered up holes. Oh, I love that bit.
I love that bit. I really do. Well, we were also, I think the first generation not to have to take
Jim showers, which bring me flowers. We walked into the locker room. Like, we hold it not to have to
or they were like, this isn't okay anymore. Didn't have to take them. We got in. I remember being
nervous and sick to my stomach about it. I remember a collective of fat kids being like, we can tell
them we have scoliosis. We just need to find out about a doctor who will give you a scoliosis
recommendation. Looking back now, I was rail thin and clearly I had and continue to have about it
just more. But I was like, I know I really didn't want to get naked. I was terrified about it.
We got into the locker room and there was the shower portion of the locker room had 500
desks piled high. It was being used as storage. And then there was this kid who was, I probably told
the story on the show, this kid was so tiny, so skinny, tiniest dick I've ever seen to this day,
including babies. And he goes tiptoeing practically across the floor completely nude over to the
showers, sees that shower room is being filled up by all these desks and we're not going to be
asked to shower as the previous year was and was left standing there in a room full of clothes men
who laughed and pointed at him and mocked the size of the genitals. Jesus Christ. You know that kid
grows up to be somebody who needs his girlfriend to drag him around town on a leash with a sign
pointing to him that says tiny penis or something like that. Like that's his fetish. You mean
that's his fetish. There's that right next to boardeners, there's that golf club. And I saw a woman
there once with a man in a leash with a sign with an arrow pointing to his dick that's his small
penis. Oh my god. Like some guys get off on that and that has to be tied to childhood I would think.
Oh yeah, I forgot. There was that like at boardeners isn't there like there's like a sort of like
dungeon -y sexy, no club over there, right? Yeah, it's right next door. I think it's the one that
took down or didn't take down. He still has a television show, the Thomas Middle Ditch.
Because he was there. He put his hands up some woman's shirt and filtered boobs and she came forward and
was like this scumbag did this to me at sex night at our sex club. So he didn't get his show pulled
because everybody was like it was sex night at a sex club and you're mad about and yet it was
unauthorized and you still need clearance at these places. So yeah, just a weird vibe that club.
That's never been my scene, the golf world. And when I was in high school, I didn't get to nine -inch
nails and all that. I like them more now than I did then actually. But I just don't I like
cure kind of golf where there's a love about it. But I don't like the golf where it's like
hell -raiser. You know what I mean? Yeah, I don't know. I don't like it with my fucking is what I'm
trying to say. Sucking and fucking fucking. I like that separate from from my Edward Scissorhands
Cosplay. I was never oh, that's what I was going to say. I was never a golf guy. I've tried over and
I have an immense respect for Trent Rezner. But I just don't like the music. I just don't I've
trailly put them on. I love his film scores now to write to my right to his. Those are a lot.
But yeah, he was never my bag. I do want to get to a very important scream and end, which is that
Pete Davidson. And I know he's a friend Joe has been cast as Marma Duke. Wait, that's the dog.
The dog. I texted you this the other day. But I know he was playing the dog. He's voicing the dog.
Okay. So Marma Duke is the I would say a worse comic strip than family circus, which is generally
considered the worst. I would put Marma Duke with a haggar, the horrible, with a wizard of id,
with a dunesbury. It's just a really bad comic. And the whole premise of it is that there is a
dog that is big. There's no twist. Although, look, that was the plot of Beethoven, too. But in
Beethoven, you have Charles Rodin to react. You have a brilliant straight man. Marma Duke just had
the most generic family ever and a dog who was big. The punchline would often be like, Marma Duke,
you're too big to sit in that chair end of end of comic strip. Okay. How the fuck is this going to
be a move? So I guarantee they saw Clifford and they were like Clifford did pretty good money. We need
another movie about a big dog. But Marma Duke isn't giant like Clifford. That's their spin on it.
Clifford the size of a city fucking block. Marma Duke is just slightly bigger than your average dog.
Why has this character lived on for a hundred years?
I don't know. I don't know. It's troubling. It's troubling. As is, and this is also screaming and we
discussed this other day, the growing, the perpetually growing cast of the Barbie movie. When I saw
Serben Kingsley got added to the Barbie movie, I said to sit down. This thing is going like like
COVID variants. It's just a new fucking strain every day. Everybody in Hollywood is in this goddamn movie.
Who is it? Is it Robert Altman's Barbie? I sense the other day to nobody in my empty home.
Yeah, it's, I feel like this is going to be our, it's a mad, mad, mad, mad world. That this is going to
be our, which nobody asked for that. Yeah. You know, we're our Cannonball Run. You know, like God bless
Bert and Dom. I love him to the day I die, but those are not good films, man. No, we're going to,
there was talk five years ago because I pitched on it 10 years ago to bring back Cannonball Run
with like the stars of the day, or actually, they kind of did it with rat race, which was really funny.
I thought rat race was very funny. I don't know if it holds up. Speed zone. No, speed zone is not fun.
That was the John Candy low point. Now, I wasn't done talking about fucking Marma Duke.
Oh, I'm sorry. Pete Davidson, I got no problem with the man, and I'm jealous of him for, for putting
it into Kim Kardashian every day probably many times a day. But listen, Marma Duke is not Pete
Davidson. If anything, Pete Davidson should be voicing Heathcliff when they bring back that piece of
shit comedy. He would be a good Keith Cliff, like a scrappy cat. He scrappy. Yeah.
All that he's always eating fish out of a dumpster. That's a metaphor.
Pete Davidson is not Marma Duke. Marma Duke is like Brad Garrett.
Like that's the voice of Marma Duke. Pete Davidson can't be everything.
Well, it can't be Brad Garrett. He passed the age of 51.
No, you're absolutely right. Brad Garrett would be a good Garfield to it. Now, I'll tell you this.
Great Garfield. When I would sit and read Garfield books as a kid, and I'm talking 10, 11, 12, older
even. So I'm looking at porn at the same age I'm reading Garfield, and I would throw my head back and
laugh at Garfield, laugh and laugh and laugh. Really, I think as big an influence on me as many of my
favorite comedians, certainly as Alph who I consider a key influence as well. But I love Garfield so much.
He had a great world view. He hates everybody. He's funny as hell. He's clearly depressed and
dealing with it and in my lashing out at John and Odie and and Nirmal to some extent.
Heathcliff, even if Heathcliff preceded Garfield, which I think it did, what a pathetic knockoff
that was. The theme song was Heathcliff, Heathcliff, no one should terrorize the neighborhood.
Heathcliff didn't terrorize the neighborhood. He calmly walked around and ate. He would
graze, but it was food you were throwing at anyway. Fish skeletons. Did you want that? I'm sorry,
did you need that for a recipe? This fish skeleton you had in your trash can? How is he bothering anybody?
Why is that? That's comic. By the way, I just got to notice that the meeting is going to end in
nine minutes. I don't understand why. Yeah, we're logged in. We're doing what we always do.
The meeting never ends, and now it's going to end in nine minutes. So that'll happen.
I don't have to send you a third link today to get this episode done.
Folks, it'll be like when you used to rent Meet Joe Black at Blockbuster and they'd give you the
two VHS tapes Velcroed together. That'll be this episode. Two parts. And the second part, like
Empire Strikes Back, Joe and I are going to make much more dark and with big chilling reveals about
our relationship. Let's stop here and come back. I'll start the recording again and we'll be
right back with a movie corner. And we're back. That's the magic of recording in the modern age.
If there was a commercial, what it went right there, but there wasn't. We just had to stop
recording and start recording again. And we believe you should get this show works and all.
You should hear what's happening as we do it. Well, we believe.
Anyway, Marvin is sorry, Pete. I love you. Marmadouk is going to start.
I mean, I was just reading panels of this strip. It's just like, holy shit.
Like the dog is going up to the kid and he's like barking and the kid's like, no, here's the
punch line. No, no, no, I'm not going to carry you. That's it. That's the entire comic strip.
This is when I was five years old, I would be like, what the fuck is this shit?
Here's one where dad is shaving and the sun goes, hey, dad, if you cut yourself, can Marmadouk
kiss it and make it all better. That's the whole thing. These are some of the best of's.
What's the, I don't understand what the point of that is. I don't either.
Here. Christ. Here's Marmadouk leaning on the dad while the dad reads the newspaper.
And the dad saying to Marmadouk, don't ask me for help. Try and landers.
That's at least sort of a joke. I guess, Joe, you would send the dog to and landers
when she was really popular. Uh -huh. That's like kind of a joke. It's not a good joke.
I'll give you that. Joe, let me take you down because I'm going to. I don't think I can get
anymore down, but yes, nor do I. Well, I do actually because I watched some very depressing films.
Um, I watched Blue Valentine, the story of a disintegration of a young couple's marriage. I watched it
in theaters whenever it came out 10 years ago or so, and I absolutely loved it. And I loved it again.
It's Rai Gosling, who's always great. He's doing like a
uh, uh, seating hairline glasses, beer gut kind of thing that works really well on him.
The great Michelle Williams as his wife. And basically it goes back and forth between a couple
at the end of their marriage and when they first meet extremely depressing film. It's one you always
see referenced like when they say depressing films. It's one that comes up.
Um, Michelle Williams has carved out a strange niche for herself.
This is like the only thing she does is hardly tragic, you know.
Well, she said a horribly tragic life. And then she mixes that with like venom.
She's in the venom franchise. Yeah. And even as far as superheroes goes, that's one of the more
depressing ones. So oh, really bad. She was also really funny surprisingly because she's the last
person I would ever consider funny. She was really funny in that Amy Schumer.
Just like, what's what was that called? Surprise. I'm fat or whatever that movie was.
I got hit in the head and I think I'm hot now. That one. Yeah, that was always something.
From the minute that trailer dropped. I think that was when that pushed America further into the
Me Too movement, that trailer. I think everybody was like, she's what? Like what's going on?
Can you believe this woman without the perfect quote, perfect Hollywood body
thinks that she's hot? Like what a rough premise. But the movie was actually okay.
And Michelle Williams was very funny in it. That's what was it called?
I feel pretty. I just thought I'd feel pretty.
You ever say that to yourself, Joe, when you wake up, especially when you wake up, just I feel pretty.
I, similar, I will, I will stare at myself deadlocked in the eyes at night and I will repeatedly say,
I am pretty god damn it. I am pretty god damn it. I'll repeat it much like gold blooms saying,
I want my cake and eat it too in deep cover. I like to say that while slapping my limp dick into my
palm trying to get it hard. Yeah. When you, when you climax, you go there's the icing on top.
Joe, you're assuming I am able to climax anymore. Folks, what movie was I even talked about? Blue
Valentine. Blue Valentine. Blue Valentine. It's got all the trappings of one of these films. There's
that goes wrong. You know, they're fighting. They're yelling at each other. It's all the theatrics.
But I will say it feels much more real and authentic than say a marriage story. I think the
performances are what make it amazing. And I love the director Derek Sian France, who also did
place beyond the pines with Ryan Gosling, which is an awesome underrated film. Joe, take it away.
I'm going to stick with three that I watched to lighten my mood. Okay. I should do that probably
at some point. Yeah. I'm going to start with a little TV show that I've fallen in love with called
Julia about. Oh no. I was given Joe shit about this the other day. Julia Child. It's a wonderful show.
It features a lot of Frazier alumni. Can you imagine wanting to know more about Julia Child?
It's a great in the year of our Lord 2022. It's a great story. It's a really great story.
She didn't pop till she was 51. She had a lot of pushback on all fronts because she wasn't in
quotes pretty, you know, that whole thing. When Dan Acroid plays you in a sketch, the odds are
you're not to easy on the eyes as a woman. So it's just an interesting story. And the focal
point is her and her husband's relationship or husband's played by David Hyde Pierce. The woman
playing Julia Child is a award -winning English actress who I had not been had never heard of until
I blow your mind, Joe. Yeah. That was Daniel DeLewis. That's how good he is. Let me look up.
Her name is Sarah Lancashire, I believe. Yorkshire. Sorry. Sarah Lancashire. Sarah Lancashire.
Anyway, she's tremendous in it in the starring role. Bebe Newworth, another Frazier alum is in it,
playing her best friend and doing what Bebe Newworth does best, like a boozy, brassy lady. She's great.
Fran Kranz is playing her Julia Child's producer and the guy at the public TV network that picks up
her show that is very much against her and it's weird because he's playing a fucking prick.
Who's also very funny. It's a very interesting role for him. And then there's Robert Joy. I'm looking
at IMGB. I'm not remembering all these names. Robert Joy shows up as the head of the public television
network. He's great. Judith Light plays the head of the publishing company that put out Julia Child's first
cookbook called Mastering French cuisine. And again, it's Judith Light at her best. She plays like
this lady that's like chain smoking and drinking whiskey in every meeting. You know, being like Christ,
the god damn cookbook Jesus, go see William up die for Christ. You know, this sounds awful.
I just don't get why you're so adverse to it. Like I get why you wouldn't be interested, but
you watch far worse than this. Absolutely. Absolutely. I have. I'm just saying what I feel.
Which used to be allowed on this podcast. And in this friendship, what it still is.
No, I just don't care about Julia Child. I saw Julia and Julia theatrically. I thought it was okay,
but that was more than enough. I'm like, I got them from from from 20 to 80. I know all about the life
of Julia Child and to think that I need more is insulting. Well, I got to push back there. All right,
Julia and Julia does not cover any of that. It covers a very, very specific period of her life.
And she is far, far secondary to the Amy Adams character. I felt I walked away from that movie
only knowing one thing. She had to devote it husband. That was it. Like I didn't really learn much
else about her life. I guess we didn't learn anything about her Julia Childhood. Oh, boy.
But you know, here's the thing. I didn't think I was interested either. I put it on because I was just
like, let me check it out. Everybody's saying it's good. And it just it just took me out of the
shit. All right. I know with each viewing, it just made me happy. It was nice. It was also nice not
being hit over the head with things. It was just, oh, one other actor in it who's just great. She plays
one of the producers of the network, Brittany Bradford. And she's got an interesting story like she plays
a black woman in the 60s who's moving up in the ranks. And you know, but like even with that story
in line, they don't like pound it over your head like the racial overtones and undertones of it.
They touch on it. And they they they let it be said through the writing and the interactions. And
that's it. And I haven't seen a show like that in a long time, especially one that's addressing
in some way feminism and these other things where they're not beating you. You know, it's not like a
Blumhouse movie where, you know, right. You know, but, but anyway, I like the show and how long
till you're watching Minks? What is Minks about porn? I think it's about the early days of Play Girl magazine.
They're doing shows about everything that has ever happened now.
Well, they got to put a show out every six minutes. Yeah. There's too much too much streaming. What
happens if the streaming space is vacant for a minute? What happens? There's some sort of time space
portal open up. I don't know. They're all trying to stay competitive. But there's so much shit that I
don't think anyone ever sees on these places on these platforms. Anyway, go ahead. So Joe watched
something to improve his mood. I rewatched Charlie Kaufman's I'm thinking of ending thing
on Netflix. I watched it when it was released. I believe mid pandemic as as the case with a lot of
movies I watched over the pandemic that kind of went in one ear and out the other. I was just sort of
not present at all. So I remember liking it, but also being very frustrated by it. Watch it again
just absolutely fucking loved it. Love the acting in it. Love what it was saying. Jesse Plemons and
who's the girl? It's weird. I always, if I can't remember a black actress's name, I feel so terrible.
And if I can't remember a white actress's name, I go, whatever the fuck the city's name is.
Okay. I don't know. I don't know when that started for me, but that's where I am. Jesse Buckley,
who is a great actress. I think we've talked about her here, her on here before.
Yeah, she is awesome. He is awesome. I love the scenes where they go to visit his parents. David
and I really the first time I kept trying to figure out every minute of this movie and then this time
I just sort of relaxed and everything was incredibly clear to me. I didn't get it on a first viewing
to be honest, but it's pretty deep, but really at its core, it's a very funny movie about how humiliating
our families are, especially to a romantic partner. And as with all Charlie Coffin movies about how
impossible it is to be in a relationship with someone. So I loved it on a second viewing. I think it's
sort of a modern classic. Have you watched that one, Joe? No, no, the title maybe I should
say. I mean, it's super dark. It's fucked. There's a moment at the ending where it's kind of like
getting at just a different level. And he really, he gets a deepness that you normally find,
like when I used to go to plays New York all the time, I don't do that anymore. I don't live there.
But he just works with some very, very deep themes and mixes them with just laugh out loud,
funny moments. And nobody else really does that. I think he's awesome.
I, I, I, I, I, I speak in a place. I'm going to go see that I have to go alone because nobody I know what
wants to go to a play. You do it. Let me get some American Buffalo. I'm going to see American. Well,
that one I might see my buddy chip. But yeah, definitely see American Buffalo. And I got to tell you,
I'm going to go see Mr. Saturday night. I want to see the Billy Crystal. Sure. I want to see it.
Is somebody else playing him as a kid now? I'm curious if it's just the story now of him old.
Yeah. My guess would be because I've seen cast interviews and there's no like young man in there.
Right. So I think that what they're going to do is some theater trick. If I had to guess where like
when he talks about the past, like a section of the stage lights up with a silhouette and you see
like a younger, the silhouette of a younger comic doing, you know what I mean? Like,
but they make it look like a memory kind of a thing. I don't know. But I want to see it. David
Paymer's in it too. Of course, everybody from the original movies and it except the woman that
played his wife because I guess she's too old. Of course. A year old Billy Crystal and Paymer is fine.
But yeah, I mean, I have a soft spot in my heart for Mr. Saturday night. It's not a great film,
but I like it. No, you know, just like how I think Multicam was ruined by HD, those movies kind of
got fucked too. Like any movie where old age makeup is required, you know, like just looks so bad.
If you're not watching on VHS, if you look at it, like the end of a beautiful mind on Blu -ray. And
I'm thinking of ending things, takes a bizarre out of nowhere cheap shot at Roberts and Meckas.
They show this really embarrassing scene with people in old age makeup and then in giant letters,
it says directed by Roberts and Meckas. It's like an out of nowhere dish. That's very funny. But
that's very funny. The over effects of things and the over clarity of picture has really made
classic special effects look so much cooler and better. And CGI of any generation look like shit for
the most part. No, it looks terrible. I watched the trailer for the new David, sorry, David Cronenberg movie.
Yeah. You know, scenes from yesterday's future or whatever the fuck it's called.
But there's CGI in it and the CGI looks terrible. It looks like sci -fi channels circa 92. I'm like,
what the fuck? I didn't see the trailer, but yeah, it looks cool. It was more perfect when he,
you know, made heads explode out of like a can of soup. Yeah, it's a botchie go back to Dave.
It's a body horror movie. So that's the cool. Yeah. I haven't seen the trailer.
I watched, oh, we called it, by the way, because I did see footage of the opening like opening night
of Mr. Saturday night. Yeah, like him talking to the crowd after the show. Uh -huh.
You know, when they come out, thanks for coming all that shit. Right. And he came out and he just
goes, we got through a show with no slapping. And I was like, there it is. Oh, Billy. We knew Billy was
anyway. Of course, Billy. Um, I rewatched and folks, if you want to put a smile on your face,
I swear to God, I might put it on again today. It made me so happy. Multiplicity.
Great. I'm our man, Michael Katen. Harold Raider.
Correcting. Yeah. And our gal, Annie McDowell, and our boy Eugene Levy.
It's, if you don't know the movie, Michael Katen clones himself. It's, it's, it's, it's classic
early 90s comedy in the vein of Ivan right men twins and all that sort of thing.
Um, I will say I think it was 96 and I saw it the after. Oh, well, yeah. All right.
Well, it's just great. He's awesome in the different roles. He's really funny. The special
effects hold up enough that they're not distracting. That's it to see the movie. It's great. Richard
Mouser plays his boss, uh, but it's classic. It's everything you want in Keaton. It is classic.
Keaton. The first cloning, and you get a lot of varieties of Keaton. Yeah. So it's like,
I'm one of four to spend the finance. Yeah. Well, you get Mr. mom, Keaton in the main role,
right? Then you get funny scumbag Keaton in the first clone. Then you get an unseen before
Keaton of him playing like a very like prissy version of himself, which is very funny. Yeah.
And then they do a clone of a clone. And basically the gag is that the man is mentally handicapped.
Yeah. I mean, again, a joke you could never do now feature length joke. Yeah. By the way,
they all fuck his wife at some point, including mentally handicapped one,
because she doesn't know that they're not him. It's a great, it's a fucking great movie. I love it.
I love it. I do. And then third for me, another darker fare. I will rewatch Charlie Kaufman's
animal Lisa. Oh, Jesus Christ. Have you seen that one, John? That thing to me, the trailer for that
might as well have been a guy loading a gun. I was just like, I'm not going anywhere near this
fucking movie puppets crying and shit. I was like, I can't. I just can't. It's too depressing.
Animal Lisa, I mean, you would, you would relate. I don't know whether you'd love it, but it most
for the most part takes place in a on the road hotel room of a touring book or author
played by a puppet played by a puppet. I forgot about the puppet gimmick pretty early, but I mean,
I saw this one theatrically and thought it was fine. And then now, again, maybe I've depressed my
way into it. I absolutely loved it. It's sort of central gimmick is Twilight Zone worthy. I think
it's got an awesome little kind of emotional twist to it. It's best to go in knowing nothing,
even though that's what I found frustrating the first time. It's best to kind of try to figure it
out as you go. But yeah, it's beyond depressing. There's a long puppet sex scene that is probably
the most realistic sex scene in movie history. It's not doing the team America thing where it's all
the crazy positions. It's like trying to portray the real awkwardness of a first time sexual encounter
between two kind of out of shape, sad human beings. That's very depressing and hard to watch.
The whole movie is. I mean, it's, but I really did love it. I think it's kind of brilliant in a way.
I dug it. It's Jennifer Jason Lee. And again, Dave Thulis as the central couple. And then Tom Noonan.
But, um, Christ and you're throwing Noonan into the bed. I mean, my God. A lot of Noonan. A lot of
Noonan. It is really depressing. It's also got very funny moments. And I think it's great.
I'm going to do a rewatch of all of his stuff. I always love Malkovich and adaptation and other
things he's done less and less. But I really think it's due for me to rewatch them all again.
I mean, I get that I get indignant, overly indignant about things and sometimes to spite myself. But,
you know, when I saw the trailer that said the most human movie of the year, I was like, oh,
fuck you. Well, even though they're puppets. Yeah, exactly. Last for me is,
and then we'll move to our major review here. We haven't said it yet, but we're reviewing X today.
X gone give it to you. I'm wearing a DMX shirt. I saw. I like that. I watched this is a horror movie,
but it I did throw it on to be again, as an escape thing. It's a thing I've always wanted to see.
I've never seen it. I've never heard anything good about it, but as a John Carpenter fan,
I always wanted to see his version of Village of the Damned. I'm a fan of the original.
Watched it pretty recently myself. Yeah, I bought a set. There's a set on Amazon. If you,
if you're in need of these four films where you can get some of my wall there. Let me see if I can
spot it. It's Village of the Damned. They live print. Prince of darkness. Not very good.
And the fourth one is a good one. It's like, you know, it's like the thing or something like that,
but it's not as good as the thing. It's something good though. It might be in the mouth of madness,
but anyway, I had wanted to give Prince of darkness another chance and I would always want to see
Village of the Damned and I didn't own they live. So this was kind of a no brainer. It was like 10 bucks
for the four DVDs. Village of the Damned is terrible. It starts pretty interesting. It starts cool.
He does a good job with it opening up and the opening. As it progresses, it just gets bad. It just
gets corny and it's a shame. It's like, I think it's the last movie Christopher Reeve was in before
his accident, which is a bummer. It's one of the last things, Kirsty Ali. You know, it was in before she
started becoming like a fucking punch line, a shitty punch line for Conan O 'Brien every week.
So that makes me sad for her because she's solid enough and it's always Christopher Reeve.
Mark Hamill's in it as a priest. You know, it does a good job. It's got a cast of people that I do
enjoy. I don't know, it just doesn't good. I can't even put my finger on why it isn't good. It's not
that the special effects suck. It's not that the script sucks and it also seems to me like Carpenter
was phoning that in beyond belief. Everything is just the laziest choice in that movie.
See, that's interesting to say that. With the opening, I remember thinking like, oh, here's Carpenter
when he's still trying a little bit and then I feel like halfway through that movie, he dies inside
and it becomes whatever movie he was doing at that time became. Like Ghost of Mars is by far the worst.
Yeah. This is running in second place probably for me. Vampires. You just kind of see him
wilt in the middle of this movie and that's it. That's kind of the end of it.
I think he was too rebellious a man to exist in the studio system like he did.
As long as he kept his independence, things were great and then as he had to get on the company
dime, things just got bad and worse. So I mean, look, I have a category of horror movies that I talk
about with Pinkstone all the time, basically called like Sunday afternoon nap horror.
You know, it's a rainy Sunday. You want to put on a horror movie like they used to air on public
television on a Sunday afternoon. That was the thing when I was growing up and you kind of fall
asleep to it given the weather outside and the fact the movie isn't terribly intriguing. Village of the
damned is one of those along with poltergeist three. There's I have a handful of deck that I keep
around for that reason. So this will become movies where you can, you can dose off after the first half
hour and be better off for it because you'll think, oh, I bet that was going somewhere good and you'll
just guess what you didn't say and you're probably right. Yeah, for sure. By the way, the original
village of the damned is very cool. I love that movie. The old black light. Yeah, I like the original.
I have that and children of the damned on blue on DVD. I'd like to get actually a blue ray. Yeah,
version of it. I bet it would look really cool on blue ray, especially the kids with the white hair.
But you know, Carpenter doesn't do enough to modernize it.
But then he does enough to take it away from the original. It just sits in this weird limbo space.
It's like I would have rather it had been a full -on tribute to the original or just a new retelling
that we hadn't seen. Yeah, this is sort of neither. And that's kind of that.
Anyway, that's that's my take. Pat, as we give us a synopsis of x, please.
Well, sure. I mean, it's essentially an update of Texas Chainsaw Masker. It's essentially
Texas Chainsaw Masker meets bookie knights. Let's say so takes place in 1979.
There is a group of porn actors and filmmakers who drive out into Texas
to make a porno while there they meet an elderly couple who is kind of in charge of the barn. He's
allowing them to stay at his place, sort of like an old Airbnb, but he doesn't realize what they're
up to making this pornographic film. And then the roles basically switch when you learn that this old
couple is not all that they appear and they have ulterior motives of their own. And then the porn
people who were supposed to be the depraved people wind up being the victims as, you know, this old
couple, Teresma part, slasher movie style. And I don't know, we always kind of go back and forth
on spoilers. There's not there's a central twist that could easily be spoiled. But I think for the
most part, it's a pretty straightforward slasher, an update of the Texas Chainsaw formula. And as such,
I think we're talking about one of the best modern slasher that I have seen. And I realize
when I say that, we're not talking about a long list of classics. Slasher genre is essentially dead.
But I thought it was four times as good an update of Texas Chainsaw as that Texas Chainsaw Netflix
piece of shit was. I think that it was scary and the kills which were practical effects were all
pretty damn cool. Nothing groundbreaking per se, but they were all pretty damn cool. The A -24thness
of it was not super present. I thought it was shot in a really cool way. There were, of course,
some dicks and some disturbing imagery and stuff, but it didn't feel overly A -24ized.
And I like T .I. West. I think that he is a great tie.
Don't tie West. Sorry. It's really, really did think it was T .I. I really, really love House of the
Devil. That's a movie I wound up revisiting like once a year. His other ones are hit and missed,
but I do think that he is a guy who clearly has a great love of horror. And I think he's carved out
a neat little niche for himself. And I think this is the best movie. I really
respect what T .I. West has contributed as far as his efforts go in horror. And I especially
tip my hat to him because he was the guy with House of the Devil that brought back the cool,
that made it cool to do throwbacks to late 70s early 80s horror. He was the guy that did that.
Like, that was not a mainstream thing that was being done at the time. And when House of the Devil
came out, that was a kind of a big deal. So I respect the how out of him for that. That said,
I think he's made two good movies in his career. And it's House of the Devil and X. I think his
other movies have been anywhere from boring and bland to flat out bad. So I think that he's got a
great spirit. I think he's puts in tremendous effort. And I think sometimes he gets,
I hate to say gets lucky. Maybe it's not luck. Maybe it's just sometimes he comes down to Earth
and just attacks something the way it needs to be attacked and tells the story that needs to be
told. And maybe at other times he's too ambitious. And it just, you know, or he's dealing with a genre
like a western or something that he's just not very well equipped for. But he did a great job with
those two movies. This is, in my opinion, his second best movie. I still like House of the Devil
better. A lot because of Tom Noonan. Sure. But this is a very solid film. My only criticism of it,
and I don't even know if it's valid, is that your plot thickens when this old couple realizes what
these kids are up to in the barn. And because the wife at their, her husband has a heart problem.
And because the wife is so neglected by him sexually, she then starts to try to seduce the young people
and the husband evokes his wrath on them. Because it's sin and it's dirty and it's this and that.
So my one gripe was, well, that's awfully convenient, guys. You've got a real problem with outsiders
and like modern sand and all this, but you've rented your barn to a bunch of young people
who just happened to be shooting a porno in it. So, you know, but I was like, you know what?
I think that's sort of the drive and exploitation of at all of just like, wouldn't it be wild if they
ended up in this predicament? What are the chances? blah blah blah. I thought that
and it's public knowledge at this point with the movie. I mean, you know, and they never call any
real, well, I think they kind of clumsily call attention to it in the movie. But the main,
the lead actress, what's her name again? Mia Goth. Yeah. Is playing the old woman as well? It's very
obvious. Immediately, I think. I will say I missed it. I knew that somebody was playing them,
but I didn't know that she was playing them. I didn't know that actors that were in the movie
were playing them older. I just thought they had young people playing older people. I didn't know
that that was going to happen either. And then I saw the old man and I was like, why do they keep
shadowing him? And I was like, that looks like a guy in makeup. That's kind of weird. And then
when Mia Goth met the old woman, I was like, one of the first lines is like, you're just like,
I used to be, you know, something that really tips the hats or nods to it. And I was like,
wait, they have the same exact nose. Wait a minute. Right. That's Mia Goth in makeup, I think.
Yeah. Look, she does a great job. She's very good in both roles. But it doesn't take
take away from the fact that I could not stop thinking about that for the whole movie. I thought
that was pointless. I also thought with a movie like this that you're trying to shoot on some sort
of budget. I mean, this was, this was an acquisition by 824, 824 as far as I know did not fund this film.
You know, this is an indie in a true sense. Why would you, in a million years, bring that into your
budget? I mean, that's just so much extra money for no reason. I mean, you know, you get, you get a
double here and there. And then, you know, it's like you and you shoot around it or whatever. But like,
I thought that was a crazy, crazy decision to make, not just financially, but aesthetically in the
film, it was distracting. You could tell it was an old, it was old people makeup. So what was the
other movie that we did on this show that did that too, Joe? Pretty recently. Was that the
damn fuck we were just, we feel like we'd just talked about this where it was a movie. Oh, I
know what it was. It was the Netflix series that Flanagan did. Oh, yeah. Well, at least in that,
the point, at least in that, the point was that the people were healing and de -aging.
Yes. So like there was a lot of people walking around for like three hours of that, where you're like,
why is this woman wearing an old, it's, it's a weird, new thing that they're doing. Yeah. Yeah. So in
this, I thought in this, there might be a moment of that. Yeah. Where it would make, you know, I,
but there wasn't. Look, this all said, cast was great. Everybody did a spectacular job with their
roles, especially I thought was shocked that Kid Cuddy. I didn't realize it was Kid Cuddy the whole time.
I think Kid Cuddy is as boring a rapper turned actor as common who I consider the least talented of
the rapper turned actors. But I like Kid Cuddy in this too. I love Britney Snow. I love me a
goth in it. I think I'd only seen her in Lars von Trier's Nymphomaniac, another fun one. But she's
the one that dated Shyla Buff and it got crazy, I believe. Yes, correct. I have to say, I'm a champion
of sex in the movies. Joe's always like, you got porn. What do you need sex in the movies for? I
got to tell you, I still love it. I still love being in a theater and seeing some nudity. I really
thought, even though this was about porn, it was going to be one of those movies where they pan up,
you never see anything, the pan away. So, you know, the girls covering herself with a blanket, whatever.
There's some graphic sex in this, including Britney Snow, who I did not think was that kind of gal.
But she from, she's been in all kinds of teen movies and stuff. She's great. She's in pitch perfect
and all that. That's right. That's right. But I got to give it up for the sexuality in this picture.
I thought it was very hot. I got to say. And then they use that against you. Yeah, well, they turn
that against you. You know, you're getting off on it and then they make you pay for that. But
I really did what it was doing. I thought everybody in it was great. Like I said, they're doing a
prequel for it now about, so that's why they had a dress up, Joe. They're going to have to play her
as a problem. I will definitely check that prequel out. I'm, I'm a big fan. I like this movie a
lot. My hog is way up. I liked it very much. My hog is 75 % up. As I said to Pinkstone about this movie,
I said, Hey, man, it is solid as hell. But to compare to what they're putting out today, it's a
fucking masterpiece. Yeah. So I have not seen a horror movie. This solid in theaters, particularly,
particularly in a while, you know, the last few I saw in theaters that I really liked were big
studio pieces. You know, it was, it was Spyro and it was screen five. These indies, especially
from 824, I have loathed. You know, so it was nice to see this one hit a hit a home run.
I've loved a few of them. I think they very potentially call that elevated horror stuff like
hereditary and midsummer. I love those, but a lot of 824s I have issues with. This doesn't feel
like that. It feels like a great update of old horror. And I don't know. I'm excited to see what
the gentleman does next. I was, I was very pleased with the film. All right. All right. Not a bad,
you know, positive review. You got to weigh up hog. I got a 75 % up hog. The hogs are up as the
point. The hogs are on. Folks, that's our show. We'll be back next time with Brain Candy. We're
going to review the kids in the hall. Epic film in celebration of the fact that they are about to
have their six season of their TV show, dropping a couple of weeks on Amazon. In the meantime,
I'm Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Huge plug, huge plug, huge plug. I am shooting my
new hour of stand -up comedy, special. I'm doing it myself, folks. Grass roots. I'm shooting it
in Houston, Texas at the come and take it festival. We're doing two shows. May 19th. That's a Thursday
and then again on May 22nd. That's a Sunday. Come on out. Very intimate shows. About 60 seats per show.
Get your tickets now. It's going to sell out and we're going to have a very intimate recording of
my new hour taping, full on taping. Please, please come out for that. In between those two shows on the
20th and 21st of May, I will be in Austin, Texas at the creek in the cave, not recording, just doing
shows. So come out to those if you're in the Austin area and also visit Joey Roses, Joey Roses,
NYC .com for details. Thank you. I am the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram. We will be back
shortly with a review of Kids in the Hall of Brain Candy. As Joe said, we will see you next time
and we will see you in hell.