It's We'll See You in Hell.
We talk movies.
We review movies.
Today we're reviewing a movie so good they had to name it twice.
Beetlejuice.
That's it.
We'll get to it.
Now, do you think the third movie, they're going to do a third movie it seems, will be
called Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice?
I mean it's without question, right?
I actually don't think they'll do a third movie.
No?
No.
They had no story in this one, nothing to really keep going or continue, nothing anybody
would want to come back and see.
I think it is doing well financially.
I just don't see it.
I mean Keaton's 70, there was 30 years between one and two.
Well, we'll get to it.
What else is going on, Pat?
We just watched the Wolfman teaser.
Yeah, Joe sent me a picture last night of the first glimpse of the Wolfman and it looks
like Warwick Davis in full makeup.
It's like almost a leprechaun vibe, an angry old man.
It looks sort of like my college mascot, the Gorlock, which is half angry old man, half
groundhog sort of thing, but definitely not scary in any way.
And then this morning the teaser dropped.
It's Lee Whannell who did the Elizabeth Moss Invisible Man, which I love, Joe didn't.
And I think it looks pretty cool.
It's Chris Abbott who I like a lot and Julia Garner who I like a lot.
Two great young actors.
They don't show you the Wolfman.
I don't believe the Warwick Davis creature is going to be the Wolfman.
I just don't buy it.
Well, when you said there's no way this is real, I thought, all right, maybe he's right.
But then I dug a little bit and the reveal was done at Universal Studios Halloween Horror
Nights, which is official, you know, they do a lot of official IP stuff there.
Universal is the Wolfman, and I think it would make perfect sense that they were going to
do some sort of reveal at Halloween Horror Nights for this movie.
But I will say this.
I think it's probably some sort of other monster, like there's like many Wolfman or Wolf Minions
or something.
I don't know.
Like, I don't think it's the Wolfman himself.
I mean, as I was telling Joe, I think a much more interesting version at this point would
have been go the invisible man route and make Wolf Woman, but then you got to compete
with Night Bitch and you can't compete with Night Bitch.
So I'm shocked at this point.
It's not just called Wolfman starring Elizabeth Moss as the Wolfman.
Yeah, that's true.
Wolf they I'm I'm very actually a trans werewolf movie is are we revealing a genius idea
here on the air?
I mean, the themes are built in.
You'd think it's well, I just read an article about the way I don't mean when you become
trans, you turn into a hideous monster.
I mean that you your body and everything goes through a bunch of changes.
It would thematically be well, I just read a I just read a review or not a review, but
a commentary editorial on past werewolf movies.
And one of the things the guy talked about in the I think it was a guy that wrote it.
It was was that the original Wolfman, the Lon Chaney one, Jr. one was a metaphor for
trans stuff and the more astute the more astute viewer has has realized it's not a metaphor
for puberty, which everybody thought is a metaphor for trans.
Now here's the thing.
Maybe it is, maybe it is.
I don't know.
But I think the danger you face because the article was about the the the monsterization
of queerness in horror, meaning like in the 80s, these are a lot of fun horror movies.
But there was this repeated repetitive thing where like it's like was a gay guy who was
crazy, you know, and they reference sleepaway camp.
They reference a lot.
I've seen that trope.
I've seen that trope be discussed and I get it.
They also talk about like De Palma's movies like Body Double where the killer is trans
or whatever or psycho.
But, you know, we're really talking about 10 movies over the course of 60, 70 years
of cinema.
I don't know that I agree that it was a it was jammed down our throats.
But I will say that, yeah, I don't know where I quite stand on that.
Silence of the Lambs was also criticized as being transphobic.
And it's like, no, the killer is trans.
And we've never I mean, that's not great trans representation.
Don't get me wrong.
But that was the first time I saw a trans character with Silence of the Lambs.
I think that was the point that it was sort of brought in always, even if it was seldomly
brought in, it was always brought in as negative.
And now we're trying to get to a place where it's not always negative.
But the point I'm getting at is I do think Wolfman is a great metaphor for it.
However, you're going to face the problem of, well, now we're saying the main monster
is a trans person or whatever.
So I think if you did it, yeah.
If you did it where you didn't address the trans aspect, if you got like
Chastity Bono, Chas Bono.
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
I wasn't being a smartass and dead naming.
I forgot.
But if you got Chas Bono and then and then he was just the Wolfman and you were like,
oh, well, there there's an interesting, quiet commentary there.
It's a box office smash in the waiting room.
I'd watch Chas Bono is Chas Bono, who I think is very funny.
I think I'd watch Chas Bono.
Well, well, better better.
The real version of it would be Elliot Page, right?
Yes.
But I'd watch a comedy Wolfman starring Chas Bono.
I bet that'd be really funny.
I mean, Page should do it.
It should be a trans writer, director, star, obviously.
I don't know. I'm sort of intrigued by it.
But I thought the new Wolfman looked kind of cool.
I like that it's like a young, hot couple and that immediately makes it a different
vibe than like Anthony Hopkins and Benicio del Toro, which I never even saw.
Did you see the Tom Cruise Mummy?
No, but to me, that is one of the strangest movies.
Yeah, the Mummy Tom Cruise, because nobody has seen it.
And everybody sees every movie Tom Cruise comes out with.
He comes out with one huge movie a year and everybody sees it.
You and I are movie buffs who do a movie podcast about horror films.
I don't recall us ever discussing seeing the Mummy.
And it came out during the time we were doing this show.
I'll tell you when you know a movie's a bomb.
When I see, and I remember this came out on the Nintendo Switch,
this game dropped called The Mummy Demastered and I was like...
And it was at the time the movie came out and the movie was so forgettable.
I remember thinking, this can't possibly be linked to the actual movie.
This just has to be a game called The Mummy.
And then I looked it up, I was like, no, no, no, it's based on the movie.
And I couldn't wrap my head around that they had actually gotten a video game made
of this movie that nobody saw.
That was in the Dark Stretcher Cruise where he actually had a couple bombs
and nobody could believe it.
And then the movies he was doing at the time that were good, like Air...
Was it American Made?
Made in America?
Whatever the fuck that airplane was.
That one and Edge of Tomorrow both kind of didn't hit like they should have.
And they were good, but yeah, exactly.
They were under the radar and everybody kind of thought, is he done?
And then he came out Mission Impossible 5 and 6 and they was like, oh baby, he is not done.
They have him at the Olympics jumping off a building.
I mean, he's in a strange new mental place.
The man needs a woman, clearly, in his life.
Or a man.
He just needs somebody.
He needs somebody there.
I got a great pitch for you.
By the way, Benicio, you said he didn't see it.
It was terrible.
It sucked.
Because like, I want to like that.
Del Toro and Hopkins, I'm like, fuck yeah, and it's good casting.
It is the epitome of CGI, blacked, bloodless, no pun intended horror.
It is so boring.
Del Toro is, I mean, you want to talk about a guy sleepwalking through a movie.
I have never seen a man on screen less committed to something in my life.
I don't know what was going on, but it's a terrible, terrible movie.
I got your trans wolf man pitch and it's positive and this is the horror.
Wolf trans.
Yeah.
It's a trans woman and then it's called the wolf man.
Because the terror is the, the curse is she reverts back into a man in the body.
She doesn't want to be in and that heart and that, and then the, the body is also like a
monster or whatever.
Oh yeah.
I'll take this even further.
It's like she becomes a misogynist when she, when she reverts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's very good.
We're not the men to write this movie, Joe, but this is a good area for somebody.
By the way, this would be the pitch that you hear.
These stories always make me laugh where like there'll be a pitch that it'll be like,
you know, original director of the Salem's Lot remake reveals why he was taken off the
project and then like you'll read the guy's vision and he'll be like,
I thought instead of vampires, it was far more interesting
to study a boy challenged by sexuality.
And they're like, wait, what?
Yeah.
Remember the, remember the original it this, this, you know, this one that just came out
reading the original ideas and they were like, there was no clown, but there was a scene
where a boy goes into the synagogue and a woman tries to seduce him.
And it's terrifying to him.
You're like, what, what are you talking about?
Yeah, I got the, the original Carrie Fukunawa 180 page script for it when I was working
at Warner Brothers and I was really pumped to read it.
And I just didn't much like how I got the naked gun script.
And I was like, all right, these, these gags aren't hitting on paper.
I'm going to give it a fair shake when it comes out.
But the it script had the full child orgy in it originally.
Well, it was, they were going to shoot it.
I mean, it was a, it was a NC 17.
No question.
It's I, I think, I mean, you could never shoot it ever for obvious reasons,
but I think that child orgy scene is important to the story.
I think there's a dark commentary to it.
Yeah.
And I also think that it's a shame they lost the scenes of the bullies doing
homosexual stuff with each other because I thought that's, that's so revealing to like
the time period, these what's happening in the town to the marginalized people in the town.
The fact that these bullies seem to be outside of it, but they have their own secret that they
can't deal with.
And then that's causing them to act horrifically to the other kids.
That was the thing I really thought it was a shame they didn't explore that in some way.
Yeah.
I mean, it, it too, I remember starting with the gay hate crime and it's just like the,
it's like a lot of these adaptations and it felt like a Cliff's Notes version.
You know, you're getting sort of like bullet points as opposed to ever feeling any of the
moments in the story.
But the audio book of it is 48 hours long, so it's an adaptation job that I would not envy.
You know, it sounds like a miserable job.
That's probably one of the hardest adaptations ever is something like that.
It's just 60 hours that you got to get down to three without pissing off the fans.
It's a pretty much impossible task.
Years later, when I look back at it, it's not with hatred.
It's with, all right, you know, better than Pet Sematary.
They didn't completely bobble it, but I also wish it had been better.
You mean better than the Pet Sematary, the new one, you know?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
If I was tasked with adapting it and they handed me that book, my first question would be,
do I have to read the whole thing?
I mean, you got to imagine it's probably got like 15 highlighter colors going through it
and, you know, notes in every margin.
You look like fucking John Doe and Seven's little notebook and stuff.
It's got to make you crazy.
Did you see Joe?
And I just bought it because it was seven.
For some reason, it was 701 on Amazon.
New.
Seven dollars and one cent.
The 4K of Van Helsing.
Speaking of these types of movies, I've never seen it.
I know it's supposed to be bad.
I tried watching it with, that was from that, it was from a different CGI period.
Yeah.
Where it was, that was like League of Extraordinary Gentlemen.
That was like when all the action movies.
Oh, that was a bad movie.
Yeah.
I loved League when it, when I first saw it.
And then upon revisits, I was like, oh, this isn't good, but for whatever reason.
I didn't see League.
I only saw the, I'm thinking of the Avengers.
With Sean Connery.
Ralph Fiennes.
No, wait, that was 10 years earlier.
I'm in the wrong, but I know Connery was in both.
And then there was the other Avengers with Anne Heish and Steve Carell, right?
Heish and Carell?
Oh no, that was Get Smart.
I'm sorry.
That was Get Smart.
Get Smart, yeah, yeah.
Jesus Christ.
So I, my mom bought Van Helsing where my dad bought it on DVD at one point.
Remember they used to have those three packs of DVDs at like, at Walmart or whatever.
And they would, they put them side by side.
So it was like really long.
He got that and it was like League of Extraordinary Gentlemen, Van Helsing and something else.
I tried watching Van Helsing.
I was like, this sucks.
Like it just looks so fake.
That 4K ain't going to do it any favors.
No, it's definitely not.
Yeah, sometimes the Charlie's Angels did not look great in 4K.
It's like that time period does not translate well, like 2000 and that 10 year block.
It's so weird.
We talk about this all the time on here, but it's so weird how
the more expensive these effects get, it's like the less convincing they are.
And that by the time they master it, we're beyond it.
By the time they finally get it right, James Cameron's doing Avatar and you're like,
oh, now this looks like it was made in the 20s.
It's gotta be frustrating if you're into that sort of world, the special effects world.
I got a read here if you want.
Oh yeah, of course.
Reads Reads.
The title of this.
I haven't read this yet.
I just bookmarked it.
A new mean old bitch.
The title of this made me laugh so hard and I couldn't agree more just with the title alone.
Of a movie I've never seen.
The Fabulous Four.
You know this movie?
It's like the latest.
Oh, is it the four old ladies going on a trip movie?
Sarandon Midler, Cheryl Lee Ralph and Megan Mullally.
Wait, now you've already read a read review of one of these four old broad movies.
Is this a different one?
I believe that was book club chapter two.
Yeah, okay, you're right.
But he's on a mission here.
Headline.
The Fabulous Four is the latest humiliation of seniors seeking employment.
Followed by the sentence, the movie is an unsavageable mess.
Salvageable mess, but the most appalling problem is its premise
that women will do anything to be admired.
Dear God.
Wow.
He is going in heavy now.
This is it.
This is full bitch.
At a time when mature women are making giant strides toward honor, respect and dignity in
every walk of life.
Progress to gain equal footing is evident everywhere except the movies.
Even for accomplished award winners.
If you're a woman over 60, you're toast.
This has led to an alarming trend for aging stars still ready, willing and able to take
their chances, pull their talents and band together on the same marquee to prove their
safety in numbers.
The results have so far been a sorry group of star -studded artistic and commercial flops
that have failed to raise box office expectations.
Projects such as book club, 80 for Brady, blah, blah, blah.
Their eulogies were more interesting than the films themselves.
We gave it one out of four stars.
The latest example of the humiliations, lovely seniors desperately seeking employment or
forced to endure in order to call themselves working actors is a dismal comedy without
a shred of wit, imagination or originality called The Fabulous Four.
A piddling plot so thin you could write it on a matchbook cover.
Centers on four aging gal pals, friends and roommates through college who vowed to stay
loyal and supportive through life.
So I agree with what he's saying.
He's saying these women deserve better and these projects are horrific.
But at the same time, ladies, you're accomplished.
Just don't do it.
Just say no to this, please.
That's what I'm picking up he's saying, right?
That's what he's saying.
But at the same time, I get you're 75 years old and you still want to feel relevant and
go to work every day.
I get why they take the jobs, too.
I mean, certainly the older I get, the more I understand it.
I used to be like, why is De Niro doing Rocky and Bullwinkle?
What is he, a fucking idiot?
And then you get older and you're like, oh, no, he's got six alimony's and, you know.
Well, that was always the, you know, apology made.
And I don't mean because of gender or anything like that.
But De Niro and Pacino were the two people I heard get apologized for.
Yeah.
Because they said Pacino went through a horrific divorce and he was in the hole.
Now, in the hole for a guy like that could mean I'm down to 20 million.
You know what I mean? I don't know what it even means.
Yeah.
De Niro, the reasoning was I'm on two houses.
De Niro in America.
She believed this shit.
South America.
De Niro's excuse or rationale was that he had sunk every dime he could or had into the Tribeca
Film Festival after 9 -11 in an attempt to bring New York back to its rightfully place.
Yeah, that's true.
So look, if there's a reason for that, fine.
But I think those guys are well past that phase at this point.
I think these stars, as far as I know, are not suffering or at least destitute.
It is odd to me. I get that you want to keep working.
I get that you want to be active. I get that you want to be relevant.
I just don't, at a certain point, I'm just like, guys, for Christ sakes, like, open us,
you know, I'm watching these.
And by the way, I worked with the guy. He was really cool.
I'm not shitting on him.
Or I'm not intentionally shitting on him.
I did a thing with Zach Braff once on Amy Schumer's show.
He was awesome. We had a blast.
We couldn't get through the scene.
We did 87 takes.
We were laughing so hard.
He was fucking great.
He's a great guy.
But I'm watching these T -Mobile commercials.
This latest one where they're doing -
Joe, for some reason, I didn't realize you were going there, but these commercials
make me, and I'm not kidding, I turn off my television.
I don't like leave the room or go, I don't want to watch this.
It makes me go, I'm done with television for tonight when I see one of those commercials.
And I like Scrubs.
Yeah.
Scrubs is not a huge enough show to have its leads selling you things 20 years later.
Well, and here's the thing.
It's like, okay, you're doing a commercial campaign.
That's fine.
My podcast with Sal was riddled with live reads.
It was also a free podcast.
But my point is, I get it.
Commercials are necessary.
And that could include an actor doing a commercial campaign
because he needs money for the year or whatever it is.
But, guys, when it gets to the thing where they're saying,
we're going to have you do a parody of the vacation song of Holiday Road.
Oh, that's the worst one, Joe.
That's the worst one, Joe.
Guys, say no.
Why is Jason Momoa in one of these?
Jason Momoa doesn't need to be in a T -Mobile commercial.
I think in the Super Bowl one, John Travolta was in it with them.
He might need a little cash, but what's the connection between Donald Faison,
Zach Braff, John Travolta, Jason Momoa?
They're singing a vacation spoof song.
What is the concept, guys?
Did you ever watch Mad Men?
You come in with a clear, concise concept.
This has been one of my go -to lines since I was in high school.
I used to say, I firmly believe, and I still do, and I may have to.
That I could rise to the top of the advertising world in six months, max.
I'm always coming up with little slogans and shit.
And also when I see what is being produced, I'm like,
we're not, they're not sending their best.
These commercials are a lost art.
It used to be hilarious when we were kids.
Here's why you wouldn't.
Because it's just like the movie and TV industry.
You're right.
And they'd say, yeah.
And they'd say, no, we're going with the Holiday Road parody.
But why?
And they'd go, don't worry about why.
And whatever.
But my point is, is like, you know, when Mark Wahlberg was pimping AT &T,
it's like, dude, you don't need to be doing this.
So it gets to a point where it's like, don't you want to just go?
I don't know.
At the end, I don't know.
I just feel like I'd get to a point in life where it's like, I've got money.
I've done a ton of stuff.
I don't need to do bad projects.
I'll go open a boutique.
Yeah.
I'll go, I don't know, just something.
Like, my God, man.
You would think you'd walk away.
You would.
But then again, I get not wanting to leave the spotlight as well, I suppose.
Joe, this might be, I'm putting this out in the universe.
I've always been very hesitant to work with you because I can't lose our precious friendship.
I need it in my life.
Yeah.
Not that working with you would mean we'd lose our friendship.
But it usually, for most people, it does.
All right.
You said it, not me.
We've stood the test of time.
But now more than ever is the time to sell this old guys
with coffee breath and the retirement home movie.
Listen, four old legends.
Let's go.
They're all dead.
Who's the old legends now?
I'll tell you who we could be.
I'll tell you this.
I have Craig T. Nelson's phone number.
I got Craig T. Nelson's phone number.
We could get Spacey.
Right now.
Did you ever think we'd live in a world where you and I said we could get Spacey?
Well, we could get Spacey.
We're going to be shooting it in international waters, but we could get Spacey.
Craig T. Nelson.
They're shooting it on a barge, like in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean.
My pitch is Nelson.
Dabney's gone.
Sadly, Dabney was our heart.
By the way, we used to talk about Mole before I worked with him, and now he's dead.
Dabney's gone.
Mole's gone.
But we could get Nelson.
We could get...
Here's what you're not thinking about.
The guys who are not working but are not thought of yet as old guys.
Guys, you know, like a little older than Vince Vaughn, who are becoming like 65.
Like who though?
I don't know.
I'm just saying like there's a pretty big net we can cast.
You know who we could get?
Chris Lloyd.
Who's the...
We could get Charles Dance.
We could get one of those English guys in there.
He creeps me out.
I never liked seeing Charles Dance.
Bill Nighy.
He'd be good.
Love Nighy.
I watched some like, as always on my nightly Reels run, I watched him talking about acting
for like three minutes on there and now my feed this morning was like too much Nighy,
quite frankly.
I was like I didn't need to hear his every thought but I do love that guy.
I'll tell you I think you could get because the guy will come out of left field sometimes
and stuff.
I think maybe get Oldman.
I think maybe get Gary Oldman.
Maybe Oldman.
By the way, have you seen Slow Horses?
I hear it's great.
I want to watch it.
And I want to watch it even more now that I hear it's six episodes a season.
And by the way, with Oldman, guy's a chameleon.
We could have him play a Hispanic guy, an Englishman, an Italian.
Like he could do, you plug him in wherever you need him.
True.
And I say you go the distance, you cast Ben Stiller as the same character from Billy Madison
and he's -
Oh, I love it.
Yeah.
You know, he's running the place.
I'm halfway through Heavyweights.
Somehow I missed Heavyweights as a kid.
It's really funny and he's funny in it.
He's amazing.
Because he's doing Appetow.
Yeah.
And he does the, if I'm not mistaken, he's doing the old Jewish tracksuit guy, right?
That and the guy at the old folks' home, they're all of a similar base, you know?
He's not the most chameleonic character actor, but -
What was the -
What was -
The dodgeball guy.
We're missing the two we've already said that are probably gettable.
De Niro and Magino.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you know, I have this thing coming out and like his, or not, you know, hopefully
a script being sent out to the town and the names that come up, you're like,
oh, well, obviously we're not going to go after Robert De Niro or something.
And then you forget.
It's like, even though he's been, he's probably been doing shitty
movies longer than he was doing great movies.
But it's like, you hear the name and you're like, we're not going to get him.
And then you remember he's probably filming Dirty Grandpa 3 right now somewhere.
Um, what was the plot of the movie?
It was, it was that, that they were four retired mobsters
and they were in this retirement home.
Crew.
Yeah, they were a crew and they were in this retirement home.
It was called The Crew.
No, The Crew is already a movie.
That's that movie with Peter Falk and Burt Reynolds or whatever.
I thought, isn't that what you're doing, describing a movie
and you want the title or what's happening?
No, no, no.
I'm saying the old man coffee breath plot.
All the plot, yeah.
We'll see.
The other issue is now there's a Ted Danson sitcom coming out
where Ted Danson is going undercover at a retirement home.
So we'd have to kind of think on it.
Well, that's not, I don't think that's what this was.
This was that these, this, this retired crew from the mob
that had all these mob secrets was going, they'd aged into a home at this point.
And the fear was that as their grasp on reality went, they were going to start leaking.
Yes.
Inside information.
And then they send a hit man in or whatever,
and the hilarity ensues as they have to defend the nursing home.
Yeah.
That's a goddamn elevator, perfect elevator pitch.
That's it.
No, it is.
And we, well, as Steven Spielberg says, if you can tell me your,
your movie in two sentences, you probably got something great on your hands.
And then you get, you need a sassy old broad in the mix, a middler,
an ex -wife who's on the outside, you know, but we need, we need women in this thing.
Of course you bring in middler, you bring in whoopee.
Yeah.
You know, who's the perfect example of the guy who's a little older than Vaughn,
but just said, fuck it.
Yeah. I'll do these old people movies.
I don't care. Mr. Andy Garcia.
He's like, oh, you're going to give me 2 million a picture.
Yeah. I'll play the guy who fucks Candice Bergen on a yacht.
You know, sure.
Don Johnson.
Perfect.
Oh yeah. Exact same thing.
Yeah.
Um, the, uh, that part, by the way, in fall guy, when, uh, when he takes off on the speedboat
and the Miami vice music kicked in, I got like real excited. That was awesome.
I just bought, it was clearly some sort of misprint on Amazon, but I bought,
I've never seen, I've only seen the movie, Miami vice, not the show.
I bought the entire series on Blu ray for 1199.
Okay.
Never seen the show. I don't even know if I will watch it, but, or if it holds up,
it always looks pretty cool. They drive around pretty dope suits.
Phil Collins on the soundtrack.
There's an episode with Frank Zappa.
Yeah.
Where he plays a cocaine dealer and he's, he's good in it.
Um, speaking of Zappa, the appeal is all the great actors you see like coming up.
I've seen a kind of a compilation. They had like Turturro and all these people
who got their first jobs on Miami vice.
Um, speaking of Zappa, that's my first movie corner. It's not really a movie, but it's
moon Zappa.
Uh, it's the audio book. Sometimes I count these audio books as part of the movie
corner because they do take time and they're entertaining. Um, but moon Zappa wrote a book
called earth to moon. It's a memoir about her entire life. Uh, I listened to the audio book.
She reads it. It's a wonderful, wonderful, wonderful book.
It's the stories are wild. Some of them, some of them are just heartwarming.
Some of them are heartbreaking, but she just goes through her entire life
from young child up through now and, uh, the ups, the downs, all of it.
Uh, what I loved most about it was it's a book that has a tangential connection to Frank Zappa,
but it's not a book about Frank Zappa. Most of the time when anybody that was in the Zappa
circle writes a book, it's about my experience with Frank. And that's not what this is. This
is her experience of just, this is who, this is my life. And there are some people you've heard of
that played a part in it and they're going to be in the book for that reason,
but it's really her book and it's beautiful. I wrote to her, I DMed her on Instagram to
compliment her and she actually wrote back. We should see if she wants to come on the podcast.
It'd be fun to talk to fucking Moon Zappa. She's been in horror movies and she's been in other
movies and I don't know, that'd be kind of wild, right? But anyway, um, it's a wonderful book,
man. It's, it's funny. It's vulnerable. It's, it's tragic. It's, it's, it's,
it's really everything that you want in a memoir. And again, the stories are just so riveting and
interesting. And, um, whether you're, whether you are very familiar with Moon Zappa or any of the
Zappas or not, I think you still find the book equally as, as interesting. So, uh, it's a really,
really good book. I recommend it. All right. Uh, I purchased the Mexico trilogy. Uh, well,
I'm holding up to the camera like an idiot for some reason. Um, this is
listed on Amazon as being in 4k. Then you buy it and one of the three movies is in 4k.
The others El Mariachi and Once Upon a Time in Mexico are Blu -rays. This is infuriating to me.
And then you go online and of course, millions of nerds are just as upset as I am about this
because this was not a cheap item. Uh, they lowered the price quite a bit on Amazon. I,
and that's why I bought it like on sale. Please tell me what you paid for the Mexico trilogy.
Now I know El Mariachi is a classic. I know Desperado is, is a solid flick. The third I've
always heard was forgettable. Well, I hadn't seen them. I hadn't seen any of them in at least 20
years. So I was buying it to sell it. That's kind of what I do now. I want to watch it in the best
way possible 4k, sell it usually at roughly the same price. I buy it for sale. It's almost like
the stock market, except way less cool and makes way less money. But, um, I paid, I think 50 bucks
and I've just sold it for 60 bucks. So it worked out well, but the only one I watched so far is
Desperado because it's the only one in 4k, but you can't do that gang. You can't say, hey,
here's the new 4k box set and have one of the three movies be remastered for 4k. It's insane.
And you know, you're going to piss people off. You, these people who run these boutique agencies
know how anal people are about their physical media. Okay. And, uh, this was disappointing to
me to say the least. Um, but Desperado and 4k looked pretty good. The movie, and I could say
this about every single one of Robert Rodriguez's movies other than sin city, which I haven't
revisited in ages. The guy makes junk. Oh yeah. Oh, the guy just makes junk. His kids movies are
junk. His adult movies are junk. His action movies are junk. His sci -fi movies are junk.
Um, he's been attached to so many things that have fallen apart. I guess that could be said
about many directors, but like, I, I don't know if the guy's a pothead or what, but it's like,
you're giving Kevin Smith the reins to like these shoot them up slam bang Sergio Leone action movies
that he, I don't know. I guess El Mariachi was, is, was, I remember it being discussed all the time
because it was made for seven grand. Great. Okay. That's, that's how everybody breaks in
nowadays. It's not quite as novel a story. He made a low budget indie. It took off.
Um, desperado is kind of a remake sort of the evil dead two to the evil dead of Mariachi, but
the story is just not there. Buscemi comes in, has a great five minute monologue. Um, Tarantino has a
kind of weird cameo in it where he gets his head blown off, but most of the time, other than like
some cameos, a great sex scene with Salma Hayek. That was something. Um, and Antonio Banderas is
but it's just kind of there, you know, it's like this, the story is so generic and I don't really
remember Mexico or Mariachi being that much better. So yeah, it was just a quick sale for me.
They get the guy always lets me down. Planet terror, I guess, was sort of fun as an homage
to carpenter. It was almost like an homage to bad carpenter. Well, I, I never, I never saw
Planet Terror as a, as a carpenter homage. I don't know if that's what he meant to do.
I, you know, look, Rodriguez, I think is a passionate filmmaker that, um,
you know, I feel like he's the guy, he's like the guy that's good at guitar because he practiced
more than everybody else, but he never quite got the music. Yeah. Yeah. You know, and like he's,
very competent and he's very schooled and he's a cinema file and all that stuff.
But you see something like Planet Terror, which is a good example. And when you watch death proof,
you know, one of the things that bothered me tremendously about death proof,
which was Tarantino's movie in that thing, um, was the use of cell phones. Cause I'm like,
Quentin, like you've gone, you've made a pitch perfect looking thing that looks like it was
excavated out of 1971. Like, why do you have them using cell phones? Just have it take place then.
It's taking me out of it, but at least it, it hit all the marks. Otherwise there with,
with Rodriguez's, I was like, here's a guy that just made a goofy zombie movie,
which I did enjoy Rodriguez's movie more, but I was like, it's a goofy zombie movie that they put
a filter over to make it look old. But clearly what I'm seeing effects wise and whatever else
is not old. It's clearly new. Whereas you watch the Tarantino one, you're like that woman,
Zoe Bell is on the hood of the fucking car right now. And the car is going 80 miles.
This is really happening. This is insane. And I think that's kind of the difference. I think
it's understanding the notes versus just knowing how to play them or whatever. And
that's how Rodriguez has always struck. It's like a Brad track or track. It's like a Brad,
Brett Ratner is like that. It's like, yeah, he gets out of
Mick G is kind of like that. You know, you just sort of,
yes, not, I don't know, not a real personal stamp on anything.
Um, his issue to me just seems to be scripting. I mean, these, just as I was watching Desperado,
I was like, Oh, right. I never liked any of these because you don't give a shit. Like they're like
revenge stories, but he doesn't even get that right. Like you don't even really see what
happened. So you don't care. Sure. Um, I don't know. It's, um, not great. All right. Pouring
coffee. Uh, I rewatched, and this is a movie we've reviewed on here in the mouth of madness.
Yes. Um, God, God, boy, do I love in the mouth of man. I love in the mouth of madness in the way
that I've been going to sleep to it on multiple nights. It lulls me. It's comforting in some weird
way. I know that's probably a sign of something deeper and more problematic, but it doesn't
matter. It's where I'm at. I love in the mouth of madness, but the, the reason I thought the
rewatch was noteworthy, uh, was I gotta say, this was the first time I had watched it and noticed
that it was a flawed movie and really understood. Like I get now why some people don't like this
movie. I like it. I like it a lot, but it doesn't really make a lot of sense. Uh, it's Sam Neil,
the writing, the technical aspect of the writing on how this works with an insurance
investigator and all that stuff is pretty loosey goosey. It doesn't seem like Carpenter did a lot
of research into like how that would work. And the dialogue is kind of dumb, you know, like,
like the idea that Sam Neil, who's an insurance investigator and he's the best of the best,
and he catches anybody who's fraudulent and he's attuned to all of it and he's got his eyes on
everything. Whatever. The fact that he doesn't know who the horror writer is, who's bigger than
Stephen King is like, guys, come on, write this in a believable way. Like he knows him, but he hates
it or whatever. So there's all that. And then once again, I like the guy. I don't want to go after
but Sam Neil, I don't think he's a good actor. It's just, I've always, always said that going
back to Jurassic park, I was like, how did this man get this part? But you do always kind of like
him. I'm always happy to see him, but then he delivers a line and I'm like, wait, what? Yeah.
No, I hear you. And he's been in some great stuff. Uh, possession event arise in Jurassic park.
Anyway, I, I, I that this all said, I love the movie. It's one of the few movies that I will
probably repeatedly buy in every iteration that it, you know, that it ever comes out in when we're
up to 17 K or whatever, I'll be like, I gotta get the, in the mouth of madness, you know what, you
can finally admit that. Uh, I watched two of the like most notorious Indy Tweed, uh, non Wes
Anderson Fox searchlight movies of my lifetime. I just wanted to revisit them. I liked them both
at the time, but I was like, man, I bet these age like milk and they kind of did kind of didn't,
but they are Juno and little miss sunshine. Now I'll start with little miss sunshine.
There's shit in that movie. You couldn't do now in little miss sunshine. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um,
but it was, it was still really good. You know, I didn't love it. I remember tearing up watching
that movie the first time and I didn't get there. I think I noticed a little bit more the
checking off the Indy movie beats kind of vibe of it. And that was very much the vibe of the time,
but in an age where these movies don't really get made in an age where you barely get competence
every time you go to the cinema, little miss sunshine is great. The characters are great.
The story's fun. It's in and out. Uh, it's shot well. I really enjoyed it. It's not, it's not a
masterpiece, but I really enjoyed it. It's Greg Kinnear as kind of, I forgot what a dick he is
in it. He's very controlling. He's always watching his daughter's weight. The daughter, Abigail
Breslin is one of the great movie kids ever. She's very, very cute and funny in this. That's her
breakout, right? Yeah. Yeah. I think she got nominated for it. Uh, Steve Carell plays the
suicidal brother who's just getting out of a mental hospital. Um, and you can see what I mean
by kind of checking off the quirky characters. Like at some point I'm kind of like these, and
these people all get into a van on the same day, but that's just me being older and more cynical.
You know, don't forget the grandfather that says inappropriate things. I'm not you. You got Alan
Arkin who won the Oscar. Um, and he's great in this because he's the grandpa. That's what they
don't understand. That's what a lot of these Candice Berg and old lady movies don't get is
like just some old lady being like, well, my husband's got the little blue pill, so I'll be
fine. You know, I, on cool kids, I was like, we can never make a Viagra joke. Like it's just,
it's low hanging the lowest hanging fruit. And what I love about the old, the old grandpa
dialogue and little miss sunshine, a Alan Arkin is incredible, but he's like, you should fuck a lot
women. Fuck as many women as, as humanly possible young ones too, cause you're young. So it's not
creepy. You know, you, you give it specifics. That's, that's, they think that simply saying
a dirty thing from an old person's mouth is enough. And the sad part is they're rewarded
by audiences laughing at this shit for hundreds of years, but give them something, give them a
specific point of view. I love that Alan Arkin is on heroin in this movie, you know? Um,
he eventually dies of a heroin overdose, which I forgot as well. And then you have Tony Collette
as the mom, um, who's actually not given much more other than she's divorced.
All these wacky characters, I mean, it's a sitcom. They, they get into a van,
they bicker with each other and you got Paul Dano as a, the depressed teen.
Can I say something about Paul Dano on this? Of course it was interesting when I saw it in the
theater, cause I'd only ever seen Paul Dano in the Girl Next Door, which he's very funny in as
Klitz. Like that movie? Yeah. And I remember seeing this and being like, oh, that's Klitz.
Oh, this guy like is, is actually like an actor, you know? And Emile Hirsch eventually too, and
everybody in the Girl Next Door. But it was weird cause Girl Next Door is like a sex teen romp. And
it was, I remember when I saw Paul Dano on this, I was like, oh, this guy I think is going to be
an actor actor. Yeah. He's, he's one of the oddest, like I guess A, maybe high B list actors we have
because it's like, he's not opening a movie, but everybody likes him. He's always good.
So yeah, it's a star -studded cast. The movie got all sorts of attention and acclaim and box office
and et cetera when it came out. And you see why it all builds to this pageant. That's why you're
there. The daughter gets up. I think there was a Netflix show that they wound up getting like
picketed and got pulled off the air that had a similar vibe, tarted up little girls at a pageant.
And yeah, I mean, it's, it's a dark joke. The girl gets up there and she's dancing to Super
Freak that was picked out by Alan Arkin and kind of grinding and doing like stripper moves. And
family gets up and supports her and you, it's just, it's, it's sweet. It's sappy. It's corny.
I really can't imagine a human being not having a big smile on their face at the end of the movie.
And what more can he ask for? I enjoy the film. My final one, speaking of Alan Arkin is I rewatched
the jerky boys movie. Never seen it. Never seen it again. I was trying to go to sleep. I was like,
let me just put something on that's going to comfort me right now. It's a, it's a, I'm a huge
jerky boys fan. I am as big a jerky boys fan as you can get. I met Johnny Brennan one time.
I, he indulged every fucking question I had about the jerky boys. He told me about like
where the calls happened, how they happened, what they were doing. It was awesome. I love,
love the jerky boys. I saw this movie on opening night. I remember Pinkstone was like,
Hey man, I love the jerky boys too. That movie's going to suck. I was like, no, it's going to be
great. Yeah. I remember Pinkstone saying to, he goes, let me guess the plot without knowing it.
They're going to have to use their prank call skills to get out of a jam. And sure enough,
that's what it is. They get, they get in bed with the mob and have to keep doing their prank call
voices to get out of hairy situations is basically it. I remember the trailer,
which made it seem like it was an Alan Arkin vehicle. Well, Alan Arkin plays the mob boss.
Right. And the movie does have a few laughs on the jerky boys part and Alan Arkin's part,
but there's a part in it. And then I'll shut up cause I can't in good mind recommend this movie
to anybody. But there's a part where they prank call Alan Arkin's main henchmen. And
Johnny Brennan is doing the Frank Rizzo character and he goes, you tell that fruity ass boss of
yours that Frank Rizzo is in town. The boss is the henchman is played by big pussy. Okay. Yeah.
And that guy goes to Alan Arkin. It's the first time you see Alan Arkin in the movie.
And, uh, he goes, do you know who Frank Rizzo is? And he's like, no, who is that? And he goes, um,
I don't know boss, but, uh, he, uh, he said some things and Alan Arkin goes, what did he say?
And he goes, he said some things about you, boss. I don't want to repeat them.
And Alan Arkin goes, you don't tell me what I want to hear. I tell you what I want to hear.
Tell me what he said. And big pussy goes, he called you a fruity ass and there's this pause
and Alan Arkin goes, what the hell is a fruity ass? And it is a perfect delivery.
It's, it's an immaculate moment in a terrible movie. It's the most Alan Arkin moment ever.
It's almost worth watching just for that. And then that's it. Bad movie. Tom Jones is in it too.
So is Ozzy. Tom Jones plays Tom Jones. Ozzy plays -
The band helmet is in it in a cameo. They're playing at a club and Ozzy plays their manager.
Okay. Um, they're, uh, it's, it's, it's an insane movie. It's not very good. Great soundtrack though.
The soundtrack's got the best House of Pain song ever on it. Uh, anyway, jerky boys free on YouTube.
If you're curious, you can just go watch it for free and probably on Tubi. Let's be real.
I will close with Juno still waiting for that sequel, Tuno. Um, it stars Elliot Page.
It stars Jan Garner, Jason Bateman. I had forgotten this movie entirely. I
remembered it being deeply annoying at first to the point where I was like, I'm not going to make
it because of the way everybody was talking the affected way. The most famous, the most famous
example is, um, honest to blog. One of her friends says just like apropos of nothing, like honest to
blog. It's like, no, that's not how teenagers talk. That's not how anybody talks. That's, that's just
really weird and overwritten. And this is annoying. So it's, she goes in, you know, Juno's pregnant.
Her boyfriend's Michael, Sarah. She goes in, she has this conversation with Rainn Wilson.
He's working at the convenience store that sells her the pregnancy test. That conversation is so
annoying. Um, I mean, it just set my teeth on edge and it's tough. It's a tough movie to watch for
about 20 minutes. It's too much of everything. Um, it's doing the Wes Anderson thing, but not
fully committing to it. So everything looks like it's on a bad set. Um, I don't know, just nothing
really clicks. And then all of a sudden the story kicks in and it starts to kind of work. You have
Jason Bateman as the cool older guy who's into sonic youth and everything, but little by little,
he reveals his more sinister side that he is trying to fuck Juno and cheat on his wife. And
he's going to be a terrible father and a terrible husband. That plot works like gangbusters. I mean,
I, I was really, really interested in all that stuff. I thought that was great. The stuff with
Juno and Michael Sarah's is hit and miss. And then you got JK Simmons and Alison Janney as her parents
who are great. So it's, it's an average movie ultimately, but it has moments of greatness.
I get why people love it. It also has moments that are just plain awkward,
like painful to watch. Um, and it's kind of a tonal mess, but, uh, I like it. I think Diablo
Cody got a lot better. I much prefer Jennifer's body, young adult especially. And I liked, uh,
Tully quite a bit as well. Joe? And it's Reitman directed it, right? Reitman. Yeah. I think it was
both of their first, Cody and Reitman. Um, well that's it. No, his was thank you for smoke. Sorry.
Let's get to, uh, the movie at hand. Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice. Um, there is still a charge when you
say it twice that it might manifest. Yeah. It's like, it's like saying Bloody Mary in the mirror.
Do you used to do that? Yeah. Um, yeah, I did. I don't think I ever got through it. Maybe I'll
have still not seen at one second of Wednesday, but my fee, my guess of what Wednesday is like
was this movie. Um, so maybe that's accurate. Maybe it's not, I don't know, but Burton's back.
Keaton's back. O 'Hara's back. Everybody's back. The one character who doesn't fully survive or
the one main character is Jeffrey Jones. And the way they handled that to me is the weirdest aspect
of an already weird project. We see a flashback of him in claymation. One of the only sequences
in the movie that is claymation. Um, we learned that he got his head blown off. Then we see it
off by a shark and then we see him at the end, uh, with no upper half. He's been bitten in half
and Catherine O 'Hara sees him and hugs him and they're reunited and he's talking, but it's not
Jeffrey Jones's voice. And it's like, guys, you killed him off. Just be done with it.
We don't need to. They also say like, it's the, oh, that's the worst thing he ever did. Like as a
little wink to the allegations I felt like guys, you don't need to, to wallow in this, just kill
him and move on. It's hard to kill a character off in a movie about nobody dies and there's an
afterlife there. That's fair. So I actually liked, so the plot of this is we're 30 years later,
Winona Ryder is now a widow with her own daughter played, um, by, uh, Jenny Ortega,
uh, or Jenna Ortega. Her father dies. She then has to, um,
you know, go home for the funeral. So it's back to the house. They haven't lived in forever
and she's having sightings of Beetlejuice. She's a medium who can see dead people
her and her daughter have a strained relationship because her daughter thinks she's a fraud. Her
daughter blames the father's death on Winona Ryder. Um, and it kind of goes from there,
picks up where these people are at. At this point, uh, Lydia Dietz is a renowned artist.
Uh, as I said, Delia, Delia? Yeah. Yeah. Is, is now a medium Lydia or Lydia is now
and kind of famous with a TV show and it goes from there. They have to go home for the funeral
and the whole can of worms from the first movie reopens. Um, Beetlejuice is hell bent on getting
back to the real world because he is convinced that, uh, Lydia Dietz is his long lost love and
he still wants to marry her like he was supposed to at the end of the first movie and that is hers,
his plot line. Um, when they get home, uh, Jenna Ortega meets a boy who seems like a great guy
and then it turns out he's actually a ghost and a sinister ghost and because of his intentions
with Jenna Ortega to steal her soul, uh, Lydia and Delia have to resurrect Beetlejuice to save
the daughter. Now that in and of itself is enough plot. Yeah, that's more than enough plot,
way more than the first movie had, but they unfortunately throw two or three other plot
lines into this. One of them being that Beetlejuice's ex -wife, who's a soul sucker,
who can actually kill dead people and that means they're permanently dead forever. There is no
afterlife for them. Monica Bellucci, who I guess is Tim Burton's new wife, right? I don't know.
Probably had to write her in the way he used to write Helena Bonham Carter into every one of his
movies. So, um, yeah, that subplot was death. She's pursuing, she's pursuing, um, um, uh,
Beetlejuice, sorry, uh, for revenge. Um, then you've got the Jeffrey Jones plot line,
which I was actually happy that they got him in the character in here in some way,
shape or form and it wasn't just, they didn't Roseanne him where it's like he's gone. That's it.
Right. Um, they used his likeness in the claymation sequence and they show pictures of him and it just
kind of gave a spiritual connection to the, to the original film that I, that I didn't mind. Um,
but, but they give him a full plot line where he's like stumbling around the afterlife with
half a body trying to figure out what's going on and where he should go. And it just wasn't needed.
No. Um, neither was this ex -wife thing with Beetlejuice. It just wasn't needed.
And if it was going to be the ex -wife is pursuing Beetlejuice, then that should have just been the
whole plot that now Beetle, now, you know, then put the whole movie in the afterlife and Beetlejuice
has to escape. And the only way he can escape is by getting to the real world to marry Lydia,
go one way or the other, but they put so many plot lines into this. Um,
and what you're saying is, I don't know if it's the problem, but it's one of the bigger problems
with the movie is the original Beetlejuice is essentially plotless. Couple dies, annoying
couple who's their polar opposite moves in, they scare them out and then they use Beetlejuice's
help. But the movie is sort of like almost like a fever dream. It's insane. It's, it's almost David
Lynchian in spots. It doesn't really make a great deal of sense. It's a young guy showing off his
amazing visual style and chops. You got to remember seeing Beetlejuice for the first time
and there was no Tim Burton world. Like all he had done was peewees, big adventure, which is one of
my favorite movies, but that's not really the Tim Burton style. Beetlejuice was, was mind blowing,
never been anything like it, but it's really comedy at its heart. Very, very funny comedy.
And most of Michael Keaton's dialogue was improvised in Beetlejuice. Now
he's not going to be as quick an improviser at age 70. So I don't think there was any,
all the dialogue to me felt badly written quips that to me, the quips on the Beetlejuice animated
show were sharper than these quips. He would be like, uh, you know, sorry, I'm late, but you know,
I was in, I was in traffic, you know, like these just like lame vaudeville type jokes
that aren't even really what he does. Um, there's no comedy in this. It's bogged down with plot from
all sides. And as the original proves, you don't need it. That was a surreal comedy,
just weird shit, weird, funny shit. And this is a densely plotted slog with to me, zero laughs.
I didn't smile. I liked hearing Danny Elfman score, which is one of my favorite scores.
Well, the three and a half minutes of Danny Elfman score that you get, you get the opening theme.
It starts with the opening theme from the original. And I, I got excited when I sat down,
I was like, Oh man, Beetlejuice, here we go. This is awesome. They're playing the music.
And I did think, I did, I disagree with you. I did think it was funny. I thought Catherine O 'Hara
was very funny. I thought Justin Theroux was very funny. Um, I thought Keaton -
Maybe I wasn't in the mood. I, I, I, I see O 'Hara as being funny. I, Theroux, I don't even know
what he's doing in this movie. Keaton, surprisingly, he was great, but he was the,
he wasn't the funniest part of the movie. The biggest problem with this is like all sequels,
they went, well, they're here for Beetlejuice. Let's give them way more Beetlejuice. And that's
like doing a sequel to Glengarry Glen Ross and going, let's give way more screen time to the
Baldwin character. And it's like, no, the reason it works is because he's used sparingly and
that's what they did with the first Beetlejuice. In this one, you get so much of him that you're
like, it loses its luster. And then because you get so much of him, they start doing all of these
weird wild gags with him where like he's telling the story of his wife and when he got married
her when he was still alive and it turns into a film reel of like a 1945 like German film or
something. And he's narrating the story, but he suddenly is speaking in this other person's
German voice or whatever. They do that gag quite a few times. They do a gag a few times where he's
lip syncing to modern music, which I just didn't understand. I got that the whole -
And he does, I guess as a nod to Deo, well, they do Deo with a kid's choir. Then they have him do
MacArthur Park, which is a song from the seventies that no one in the audience is going to know.
I only know it because Weird Al did Jurassic Park as a parody, but it was a song by Richard Harris,
an actor who plays English Bob in Unforgiven. But they perform it in this movie in full as
a musical number. And I just sat there like there was no laughter in the audience. I don't know if
the goal was comedy. I just don't know what it was. Well, the thing with the MacArthur Park
sequence is the climactic scene in the film. Yeah. When he's supposed to be finally marrying
Lydia and she's trying to figure out how to get out of it. And he takes over everybody and they're
all singing the song against their will and dancing and whatever. And halfway through it,
after being sort of confused, I was like, oh wait, they're doing the Deo gag from the first movie.
And because that was everybody's favorite scene in the first movie, they're now doing it as the
climax. So this is their alien chest burst in the sequel. How are they going to work it in? It's the
memorable scene or whatever. And it's just too long. It's just too big. I did laugh.
There's also another plot line. By the way, it's 104 minutes.
No, it feels too long, but it's 104 minutes. Yeah, which is odd, right? So there's another plot line
where Willem Dafoe. Oh Christ, I forgot he was in it. He's an other world, whatever you call it,
detective who is trying - Brutal stuff. Brutal.
He's trying to find Beetlejuice because his ex -wife is murdering people and
Beetlejuice is going to help the guy solve the crime. So even that in and of itself is too much
of another plot line, but then they make it even more convoluted because Willem Dafoe isn't a cop.
He was a guy that played a cop in movies and now he's dead and he's somehow an underworld cop,
but then they keep saying throughout the movie, you're not a real cop.
It's very confusing. It's a hat on a hat. Yeah, it's a bit that doesn't work a hat on a hat.
These guys, you know, Wednesday does not appear to be a laugh riot. I don't think they're real
comedy writers. If you go back and watch Beetlejuice, it's like laugh out loud, funny throughout.
I can't say I was destroyed by Beetlejuice because I had lowered my expectations so low,
but to me, this was as big a drop off as like an analyze that or a meet the Fokkers.
You know, it's a huge drop off in quality. I thought the plot of course was convoluted.
I think Ryder were almost putting her out there against her will at this point. I don't know that
she's mentally there. I'm not, maybe that's just something I'm putting on her. No, I don't think
that's true. I think she's there. I mean, Stranger Things, you know, she's had it. I feel that way
in that. I just feel like she's barely in control. I don't, I didn't feel she remembered the character
here at all. She didn't seem to be playing that character grown up to me. Jenna Ortega,
I guess I've liked her in things. I don't know what she was doing here really. I did like O 'Hara,
Thoreau I didn't get. Defoe was his whole plot should have been excised. It was terrible.
Keaton didn't have a laugh, which to me is the tragedy. They, like you said, Joe, they're like
gags upon him instead of just letting him riff. And maybe he can't riff like he used to.
No, I think it was just the, the sequel syndrome of bigger means better and it doesn't.
I had a few laughs with Keaton. You know, I laughed really hard out loud when he goes,
and they blew this gag in the trailer. It was still funny in the movie though. But when he goes,
I swear on my mother's soul, and then his chest sets on fire, I was like, that's funny. Like that's
Beetlejuice. Like that's what we want to see. But I'll tell you the biggest tragedy of the movie.
And I didn't not enjoy it. I just was kind of like, this just sort of feels like if they made a
Beetlejuice TV show, like sequel TV show. I'd be like, yeah, that's exactly what it felt like.
Yeah. So I didn't not enjoy it. I didn't hate it. I just thought it was sort of troubled. But the
biggest tragedy of it to me was as I was sitting there watching it, I was like, oh yeah, the original
movie makes no sense. None of this makes any sense. Why are the sand worms there? What is
that part of this other place? Why when they say home, home, home, do they go away? Why is it that
if you say his name, he can appear, and that's terrible, but then he disappears and isn't a
threat after that? None of it makes any goddamn sense. And you're supposed to be able to say
Beetlejuice three times and have them go away. It's no, it's all over the place. It really makes
no sense. But I'm saying it holds together as this surreal comedy. But then again, maybe it's
because I saw it when I was a kid. Why can he, you know, at the end when she says his name finally
three times and he disappears, it's like, but he's not powerless. He would just stop her again.
He just made everybody in the chapel get sucked into their phones. He's got immense power in the
real world. He would just make the sewing thread go on her lips again where she can't talk or
whatever. Like, yeah, he can throw a giant metal zipper on her mouth like he did Gina Davis, like
he's in a Warner Brothers cartoon. So it was odd. They talked about how the Dietz's from the
original movie, cause they're not in this, how they moved on to the next plane. They could have
just said that about Jeffrey Jones, you know, and not done this weird subplot with him.
But I want to discuss, and I left you a voice thing about this last night, and I don't know if
it's me being sensitive. They do this gag where they talk about how the sole, yeah, the sole train
is the train that takes you to the next stop after you die. And I was like, soul train,
I get it. It's your soul or whatever, you know, whatever. That's kind of dumb, but funny enough.
But then they go to the soul train, as Pat said many times, and every time it's soul train,
it's the show and it's tons of dead black people, disco dancing. The only black people in the movie,
and I'm just going, this is not, this feels not right. This doesn't feel okay. This is weird.
Well, they added, you know, four or five characters to the Beetlejuice universe,
all of them white. And then you're absolutely right. It's them dancing around. They give the
conductor of the soul train. Was he a cameo? I didn't know who that was.
I think it was supposed, it was clearly supposed to be Don Cornelius and it wasn't,
but yeah, they're, they're dancing to, to disco songs. There's a lot of disco music in this movie,
a lot. And that's not a part of the Beetlejuice world at all. It's like, you got Danny Elfman
guys, like, like you could have had his last great score before he spends the rest of his career in
jail. It seems like he's about to do. I think that's why they probably didn't get much of a
score. Oh, you're right. You might be right. But also this disco backdrop to the movie doesn't
work. You're like this, it didn't really feel like Beetlejuice. The practical effects did.
I liked the kind of, you know, cheapish looking sets and, and, uh, character design and stuff
was kind of fun. I'll give it that. But I'll tell you this when the, yeah. So just real quick on
the Soul Train thing. Oh, I'm sorry. So, no, so it is weird that the only black characters they
have in the movie, it's the Soul Train gag. And then everybody in that gag is acting like it's
still the seventies. And it starts to feel like an excuse to have black characters talking in this
stereotypical way. It just felt problematic. And we, you know, I don't think a petition needs to
be started, but it just didn't feel right. But on top of that, the practical effect stuff was fun
and was goofy and, and whatever. But then when they do CGI, which they do a little bit of,
it looks terrible. Yeah. Like terrible. When Monica Bellucci is putting herself back together
and they're showing like a leg with the inside, you can see the inside of the severed leg or what
it looks so fake. I was like, guys, Jesus Christ, this looks like final destination three
CGI. Like this is not good. So Sandworms looked better in 88. I still don't even get
the Sandworms. And then by the way, you want to talk about shine the flashlight on an issue
with the original movie. I'm like, nobody said Sandworms are dune. We're not, we're just gonna,
you're just gonna just jack that out of Frank Herbert and just, that's it. Like nobody's,
there's no explanation. Like it's very weird. Bill just came out four years after Lynch is dune too.
So I didn't hate the film. I didn't love it. I'll probably never watch it again. I absolutely
enjoyed it enough that I could, I'll take my mom to see it and she'll enjoy it and I'll have a
time watching her enjoy it. And that's kind of where it stands for me. My hog is,
is tipping downward, but I'm not disgusted. I'm just like, yeah, it's just like any other
legacy sequel. I'm just like, yeah, yeah, they did another one and it wasn't that great. And it
could have been, but you know, the studio interference, I guarantee you they could,
Elfman had problems. They said, we got to back off of Elfman. Burton said, there's no way he's
being a part of this. They said, okay, he can be a part of it a little bit. Elfman probably said,
I don't have the bandwidth right now. And Burton probably said, well, I'll tell you how we're going
to fix it. We're going to put pop music into the soundtrack and that's how we're going to cover the
bases. And it's like, yeah, but that doesn't work now because the, it feels not like the original
when you do that. And you're not even putting pop music in that a younger audience could grasp.
You're just putting in these songs that like, it's like, dude, that like, like you said,
nobody knows these goddamn songs. Like it's weird. Yeah, this, this felt to me like an old
person's movie and Beetlejuice feels like a young, insane person's movie. This felt like an old guy
taking a stab and just not, not hitting. I don't know what's, what's there for a young audience
going to see this movie? Um, because it felt, you know, old and stodgy to me other than Jenna
Ortega. But, um, I did hate the movie to put it in perspective. Beetlejuice is like my ghostbusters.
I prefer it to ghostbusters. It had a much bigger impact on my life. Um, I got amnesia when I was a
kid and the thing I was the most devastated about was that the doctor said I couldn't go see Beetlejuice
on opening night because it would be too exciting for me. Um, I just have a long history with it.
I love the film and this probably hit lower, hit, hit harder below the belt because of my love for
the original. I'll give it that. But I also didn't laugh, didn't smile, didn't have a good time,
hated the story, thought it completely lacked the spirit of Beetlejuice. And it, it bothers me so
much when they go out on the publicity trail and you hear, I've heard Michael Keaton on podcasts
and stuff saying it's better than the original. It's deeper. It's more emotional. It's funnier.
Uh, you know, you won't believe how funny so and so is in the movie. And it just starts to hurt
after a while. The amount of times these people lie to our faces, maybe he believes it. I don't
know. I hated the movie. Um, disappointing to say the least. Joe, uh, I am at the Patrick Walsh on
Instagram. We are at see you and help out on Instagram and coming up, we were doing immaculate
and, uh, what's that movie called? Probably blink twice. Blink twice. Um, Joe DeRosa comedy
on Instagram. Uh, I think it's Joe DeRosa comedian on Tik TOK. I believe I'm not sure. Um, anyway,
uh, I'll see you in, um, uh, December, uh, crystal ballroom, Somerville, Massachusetts. Please come
on out. Tickets at Joe DeRosa .com and tickets for all the shows, uh, for the new tour starting in
January also available there. New shows will be announced soon. Uh, and I will be, uh, you know,
come by Joey roses. If you're in New York, joeyroses .com folks, we'll see you next time
and we'll see you and how