I'll see you in the next video.
I hope you got some stuff to say.
Folks, we've started in Pat's talking.
What did you say?
I was just clarifying what movie we're doing.
Sometimes that's up for debate, even as we start recording.
But hey, I'll take the reins.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
It's about time we had somebody with some authority
in his voice open up the show.
It's probably not stumbling over every third word.
Today we will be discussing and disgusting the New
Barry Levinson mob movie.
I guess you can call it that.
I feel like Jane Austen's mafia was a superior mob movie.
But yeah, it's Robert De Niro in a dual role and it's called the alto nights and it's
on HBO Max and we'll get into it.
Joe, how are you?
I know the answer is bad, but tell me why?
The answer's not bad.
It's terrible.
Why?
Well, as you can hear from my voice, me saying you're doing bad was actually me kind
of being a noingly positive.
My voice, my personal life is bringing me nothing but stress in the way of break up once
again.
This time it's for real.
How many how many off it on's just three?
I think it was three total and a lot of let's look.
She's great.
I have no bad thing.
You know, no bad thoughts or feelings about her only terrible thoughts and feelings or
the relationship for that matter.
I appreciated every minute of it even when we were struggling here or there, but you know,
the break up will hit you hard, man.
It's, you know, you're, you're, I'm realizing this because I'm also trying not to drink.
Yeah, well, at least not drink as much because these last few months, stuff with my family
and there's stuff going on.
I've been, I've been turning to old, old Jack, my friend old Jack, old Jack's an odd
duck for some long nights.
And you know, when you're, when you're suffering from, I shouldn't say suffering, but you know,
you're dealing with anxiety and, and other things.
And you're suffering.
I think if ever the word was applicable, you're suffering from anxiety, of course.
I just made me think of the Brian Regan bit where he's like, I suffer from anxiety.
He goes, you see the guy in the street that got like hit by the car.
Yeah.
Are you suffering?
I get it.
I have anxiety.
Yeah.
Very funny.
Take.
I'm suffering from anxiety.
And I would argue it's more painful because you're sitting with it all day every day.
You get hit by a car.
It's over and a half hour.
Yeah.
So yeah.
All right.
Fair enough.
The fuck you Brian Regan.
So here's the thing.
I, you know, in, in, in, in, in order, in order to try to deal with, see, now there might
be people saying, well, Joe, why wouldn't you just get some professional help?
Well, because the fact that I am jumping between Pennsylvania and Austin all the time, I,
it's very hard to lock down, you know, therapy or something like that because the lot of them,
you know, they can't do telemed meetings out with, you're out of state physically and
all this crap.
So that's been a little bit of a struggle.
So I have been self-medicating a little too much.
And, you know, I always, booze was always a great part of my life.
It was always something that brought me fun.
And even if it made me depressed the times, I enjoyed it.
But what started happening was it was now piling on to the anxiety.
And now that was, it was, it was enhancing the anxiety.
So, you know, trying to, what I'm getting at is this, trying to not have a drink is the
same thing as trying to not text your ex-girlfriend when you're sad.
Like, there's the thing.
There's the thing.
You're trying to do both at the same time.
It's very difficult.
Yeah.
It's like, it's the thing.
It's like, you can't do that.
You got to give each other the space you need.
Yeah.
As soon as you do that, you're going to start the whole thing over again.
And you got to give each other space.
So I'm respecting that.
And I'm, it's very hard.
A lot of crying mid-meal.
Yeah.
You know, you lose a, you lose a whole another year of your life when you send that I miss
you text.
You're like, you know, what's it going to hurt?
I tell her I miss her.
I do miss her.
Maybe she's missing me too.
It'll be a nice thought.
And then you're up and talking again.
It wasn't right the first three times.
It's not going to be right the fourth.
We all do it.
Yeah.
So I'm on, I'm on, I'm on no sleep.
I'm on no sleep.
And the, so wait, so, so, so, so I'm, this is the last part.
So I'm wrestling with all my buddies.
I'm in Pennsylvania right now.
All my boys I grew up with or getting together tomorrow.
Yeah.
I'm like, do I go and just say you were wrestling with them.
No, I'm wrestling with this.
Oh, okay.
With this.
There's no way you go to that and you don't drink.
I'm sure.
You go and say, fuck it and have a night.
Or is that sending the I miss you text and starting everything all over again.
I don't know.
But it's, it's, it's tough.
So, so what I've been doing all week is sitting in my home and working and doing being productive.
But then I smoke cigarettes at night.
Not a ton.
But now even that I three cigarettes throughout the day yesterday.
And I've lost my voice.
But everything I love is being taken.
Yeah.
No, I hear you.
Including Robert De Niro in the man that made this movie.
Yeah.
That's true.
Sorry.
And you don't have to worry about I spraking down your door.
Yeah.
Don't you like that?
It's kind of the same as the Brian Regan thing when you're talking about something serious you're going through.
And some, this all happens constantly in LA.
Yeah.
At least you're not, you know, one of the people falling under Trump's oppressive policy isn't.
It's like, can I not go to brunch and vent anymore?
You cow.
Yeah, you go.
You go, you go, sir.
Could I, would you please just take my order?
Yeah.
He's got a grievance there too.
I probably shouldn't be complaining about my life to the waiter.
But no, I hear you.
I actually never slipped up and sent that text back to the ex-wife, but not for lack of trying.
I mean, for four years, I would be like, you just, I always imagine just somebody on my shoulder just grabbing my hand and be like, no, baby, no, you don't want to do that.
It's terrible.
And they're going through it too, you know, every ideally, maybe they don't think about you at all, but probably.
That's, that's the hardest part.
If you had a feed that let you know how the other person was, was feeling.
Yeah.
It could, it could be tremendously bad if it's like, oh, she's feeling ecstasy right now from the touch of another man.
But if you could just see when you feel like this, hey, man, here's a report.
She feels exactly the same way you guys are doing the same thing.
Yeah.
You'd be like, okay, we're just doing what we got to do.
It's the mystery of how they're doing, I think, that makes it so hard.
Because you just fan, you have these fantasies of the worst.
Of course.
10, 15 years ago, you broke up with somebody you never heard about them, saw them again until somebody like three years later is like, oh, you know, Jackie, you should got married.
You're like, oh, you take a knee and then you move on with your life.
But like now with Instagram and everything, you can be constantly updated if you were dating somebody who's one of these heavy posters.
I was very thankfully blocked by my ex, which is just like, oh, thank you.
What a gift, you know, well, she blocked you.
Yeah, but that means she can't see me and I can't see her, which is ideal.
Yeah.
I think I think she and I will remain on good terms.
And I think eventually we will have a friendship.
You know, and also too, we're both in the same business.
So, you know, there's, there's that.
But when you're at the next standup comedy board meeting, she's going to be there.
I will, yeah, I will say this.
And this is one of the things I really like about her.
If we were ever in a situation publicly where this somehow got brought up, she would lean into it and have fun with it.
Yeah.
Like, like in other words, if, if we just happen to get booked on the same podcast or something,
and it was like a live podcast and we showed up and it was like, oh, hi, well, you know, and we,
she's the kind of personality that would be like, let's just, let's just, let's just get it out in the open once we're out there.
It'll be fun and funny and we, you know, like, she's cool like that.
So, so that part of it is in case that ever happens, I guess, is really well, Joe, we're about to let her into the Zoom room now.
If you could come on in.
No, it's, it's all tough.
Everything's tough.
Nothing works.
I, this morning, was walking around cleaning up the house a little bit.
I had my phone in my pocket, but I'm wearing like gym shorts.
I just got out of bed.
And I go into the bathroom and I'm like gathering up the towels for the laundry and everything.
And I set my phone down on the sink and I look at it.
And in my pocket, it has opened itself, scrolled through.
Instagram is open.
There's a female stand-up comedian doing a bit with the sound off.
And I have a bar taking up half my screen that says, shake your phone to report this user.
I hadn't even looked at my phone.
It's insane.
Now, let's say all that happens because it's sloshing around in my pocket.
Okay, all right, even though it was locked and everything, I don't know.
I'm like, okay, that was really weird, but fun.
Why shake your phone to report it?
Why not make me do something to prove I'm there and I'm real?
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's an orchestration to, it's not an accident.
To tell you, shake your phone to do this as opposed to like toggle something or click something or push something,
it's like you're teaching a baby like how to, it's like a baby toy.
But like why?
Think about it.
It's so you can do it more easily accidentally.
But why do they want you to report somebody?
I just don't get any of it.
It's not.
It's got some, it's some peak.
My assumption is that it's all that, that thing is part of the plan to put people in a position where they're, they are more at the mercy of the app.
And the, and the corporation running the app.
So in other words, hey, if we allow this shake thing to potentially report people, there's a higher chance of accidental reporting happening with a higher chance of actual reporting it more people getting reported when more people get reported, they're more at the mercy of us that lets us move more towards this policy.
We can in state where we say, if you pay this much or you do this or what it, it's all, I think that's it's all it all goes hand at hand.
I don't think any of this is, I think, pardon me, I think the initial shake idea was probably innocent.
Like people like to use the phone in an innovative, intuitive way.
Like, you know what, be good.
What if you just had to shake it to do that?
And then I think people went, hmm, that's interesting.
Well, what if we use the shake for this?
Yeah.
You know, and then it goes from there, but, but what shakes your phone?
Everything.
Yeah.
So fucking stupid about it.
Well, also, have you ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever in the, what are we in a decade now the iPhone?
More.
Away more.
15 years of the iPhone.
Excuse me.
Have you ever been scrolling through your apps where your finger is touching the phone and accidentally opened the wrong app?
I never have.
No, never.
If I have, it's a, it is such a negligible amount of times.
I don't even remember.
My point is this, when I'm touching the fucking screen with my finger, things are not opening accidentally.
How are they opening multiple times over in my pocket?
Yeah.
What's touching it?
There's nothing in my pocket except the phone.
That's insane.
I wanted to kill myself about my screen time reports until I realized that it just keeps clocking you as on these apps even when you're not.
You know, like it'll, it'll say like you've been on Instagram for four hours today and my phone's like in the opposite room.
Like, well, no, I haven't.
So if you don't close it before shutting your phone, then it tells you it's like everything about it should be after 15, 20 years, whatever, perfected.
And it gets worse with every year, with every update.
And I have to assume the reason is so we keep buying more and more phones.
Well, of course, I do, I do no case.
My, my phone's all scratched up.
I don't replace it until it absolutely stops working.
It doesn't take a charge now.
You have to tightly wrap the cord around the phone to charge it.
And that's happened on every phone I've ever had.
And then you're like, well, I'll get a flip phone and then everyone in your life calls you, you know, names.
I'm going to, I'm going to get the new iPhone.
I haven't got a new one in a long time.
Me neither. When's a new one drop?
I was just looking into that.
I, I just mean whatever the new, not the new.
I know there was another one coming out. I should have because it's been eight weeks since the last one came up.
But, uh, no, I'm just, I just mean like I'm going to get the newest one because I'm going to switch carriers.
Yeah.
And, uh, I never upgraded my current one despite throwing it against the wall.
170 times at this point, literally throwing it.
The back is covered with duct tape because it was shattered and all this stuff.
But, um, so I'm going to get the new one.
And I'm going to actually, I think I still owe on this one.
I'm actually going to pay off this one because I want to use this one as a camera.
Uh, in my game room setup.
Why? Because the fucking perfectly good functioning iPhone I have up there that I was using as a camera.
That's new enough to be HD no longer takes a charge.
Yeah. And you can't keep it plugged in and keep it running reliable.
It's, it's ridiculous, man. It's ridiculous. Like, yeah, if any, if any other item that you owned and you had to spend six to eight hundred dollars on just broke every couple of years,
you would stop buying it. But we don't because there's no equal competitor.
I had a book of conspiracy theories that I'd purchased in God.
It's got to be probably 2006 ish somewhere there.
Um, and you know, it was like these are the top conspiracy theories.
And it was, it was not written.
It wasn't scoffing at the theories, but it was also not being like, this is probably true.
It was kind of like, right now, here's some wild conspiracy theories that are out there.
And one of them was that Microsoft was purposefully outdating the operating system of windows in order to force you to keep getting the newest version.
Right. And it was, there's like a, there was like an eye roll about that idea.
There was an eye roll back then. Like, oh, give me a break. Yeah, guys, their purposefully making it not work that well.
So you have to buy the new sure guys. That makes sense. And it's like, yeah, now it's just in your face. It's like, that's exactly what they're doing.
Well, it's what it's what's happening on a million times larger scale now with Elon is that we pretend that the innovators are also humanitarians.
It's like, no, no, no, very often they're, they're, they're not Einstein. Very often their reason for doing this shit is money.
And it has nothing to do with making the world a better and more livable and sustainable place. It's, it's just ridiculous.
This is a wild, this is, that's wild too. We're not going to get a political thing, but that's wild too. Cause once again, once again, and I don't participate in any of this, but, but it's just interesting to me.
Once again, the public is in that conundrum of two guys we hated for working together. Now hate each other. Are we supposed to side with one of them?
I'm not. I mean, say it definitely appears Elon is trying to be welcomed by the left because he's so hated by the right. But it's like, dude, you're done, you know, unless you actually do something, you're done.
I got, I got a bit of news that's appropriate for the show here. Play, this is one of my, I also wanted to say before we move on, because it is interesting.
The iPhone was introduced on June 29th, 2007. So we're almost exactly 18 years of.
That's amazing. Go ahead.
I actually saw her talk about this on a podcast clip. And then I got the story for somehow I'm on, I'm on people magazines email list, which I'm not mad about. Sometimes they said me fun stuff.
You know what? One year you're on the email list. The next year, you're Hollywood sexiest man alive. You just gotta stay, stay consistent.
So they emailed me the story. And this is a day or two after I'd seen the clip. And I was like, oh, we got to talk about this. I didn't want to think of that.
So I'm reading from people magazines article now. Okay.
And I believe that she is telling 1000% the truth. I believe her 1000%.
Rose Ann Barclaym, she was asked to guest star in the Conners as a ghost.
She said on the pocket, and I believe her because of what we've seen Hollywood do.
Yeah. She said that in season two of the Conners, they called her up and they said, what if you came back as a ghost?
I probably, I can almost guarantee you could coordinate that phone call to a week, the ratings dipped.
Yeah. Yeah. And she said, what do you, and then the host of the podcast goes, what do they mean? Like in like in like in like in a flashback or something?
And she goes, no, as a fucking ghost. And he goes in one episode, they want you to be a ghost. And she goes, no, they wanted it to be recurring.
They wanted me to come back as a ghost. Like she's almost screaming. He's like, like, creamer. Yeah.
Ghost. I'm not a bad show. It's it's beetle juice. It's they wanted to do beetle juice. So.
And this is, this is one of the reasons I believe her, not just because the idea is so bad shit. And I wouldn't put anything that's all I would.
She, she says this and she says it. She throws this part away. She tells the whole story and then she's like, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to do that for a 10th of the fucking money you paid me the first time. Like, and I was like, I think this is real.
They offered her shit money to go bet. Like that was the detail where I was like, oh, wait, I think this is real.
Because she could have she should have come out with that at that time. I mean, like why don't really just stain them and been like, listen, you fucks.
Look, you got to get up pretty early in the morning to get me to side with Rose and bar at this moment in time.
But against the Hollywood producer. Yeah. I'll talk. I'll think about it.
The her quote is you're asking me to come back to the show that you fucking stole from me.
I killed my ass and now it was a show up because you got shit fucking ratings.
And then she goes, I'm going to be bowling that fucking week.
That's why she's a legend. That's why you can't take it away even though she's lost her mind.
I do want to shout out our mutual friend, Jay Ferguson, who was a regular on the Conners for the entire run.
They just wrapped the head of lovely time. And I just saw Jay for a really fun launch.
I did. I texted Jay and didn't hear back really weeks back. Oh, Jay Ferg.
He had a store. I got to tell the story. We're behind a Patreon. I don't think he would care.
I don't know. That made me nervous. He just said, no, no, no. You got to cut that in the future.
I guarantee I won't have you cut this.
But you know, people like to behind the scenes stuff. And it's a story. I think he'd be called it.
Tell you tell on the podcast because he doesn't make anybody look bad except somebody comes off a little jerky.
So Jay is wrapping up the Conners. And like everybody in this business right now concerned about the future of his career.
So even though he's been on Mad Men and such smash hits as CBS is living Biblically with Joe D'Rosa.
He is a little bit floundering and he's kind of, you know, taking auditions. And there's a new John Madden movie coming out with Nicholas Cage as John Madden slash Oswald Cobble pod.
It looks like they've got him and some sort of Penguin style fat suit.
I know somebody in the movie.
Oh, yeah, that's what's announced. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. James Christian Bale. Yeah. All kinds of heavy hitters. John Malan is in the film.
It's a comedy. Who's who?
But Jay was telling me he had to do his first taped audition. And he, you know, Jay's 50 years old. He's like, I hate this shit.
And he always gets so nervous. And he was just like, all right, let's go.
And it's David O'Rossal.
And Jay is auditioning to play Pat Somerall, who's an older sportscaster.
And the Zoom starts. It's David O'Rossal. Now David O'Rossal, look up his accusations allegations, courtrooms, and just going from the Lily Tomlin shit where he called her a cont on camera.
And, you know, blowing up at his cast and crew, he felt up his trans niece at the gym.
There's all sorts like that's that's the weirdest one that nobody knows about.
But a lot of problematic stuff in his past. And I, the camera turns on. Jay's sitting there.
He's dressed up. He said he's dressed exactly as Pat Somerall dressed in this famous interview. Ready to talk.
And Jay's like, ready when you are, sir. And David O'Rossal mutters to himself audibly.
Okay, didn't wear a tie.
Should have worn a tie.
You always, always should do more than what is asked and expected.
He's like writing while muttering this. Always do more than what is asked and expect. And Jay's just sitting there.
Like ready to audition. He knows he can hear him. He's just dressing him down. Like, all right, here we go.
So he goes, so say your first line. And he says it and he goes, no, no, no, no, no.
Mess your hair up for me.
Jay messes his hair up. He's like, uh, no, did you have you seen the man?
Jay's like, yeah, you asked me to audition. Like I feel like I, you know, I'm trying to make myself look like him.
But we're not twins. Like, you know, I just want to audition for the role.
He's like, mess up your hair. Like he had him do it like 50 times.
Pull all your hair into your face. He's like, no, no.
Then he looked down and be like, always got to do more than what's asked. Always.
So it's like all his rage and weird shit. They have made him force inwards.
So now he's just like this asshole exuding all this like shit.
So like, how are you supposed to audition in that environment?
It's very hard. And then they gave the part to Joel Murray, Bill Murray's brother, who was also on Mad Men.
But it's like, if you're auditioning Joel Murray and Jay Ferguson, you don't have a type in mind for the part.
They're very different. And I will say, I will say I'm friends with Jay.
Yes. Yeah, right. We're friends, you know, I haven't seen him in 80 years, but we're friends.
And I would like to see Jay work all the time. But I will say too that I'm almost like happy for Joel Murray.
I feel like Joel Murray is probably not going to get as many of the shots as Ferguson true.
Joel Murray definitely gives more sports and answer than Jay does. Maybe. Yeah. Yeah. Oh my god.
He's still playing the leading man, the hunk. Yeah, I didn't even think of that. Like, yeah, that's.
Let's go to the corner. Yes. Have you seen that clip with of Lucas Gage, the guy that eats the ass and the white lotus where he's auditioning for something?
No. And the director, it's like a Hunger Games thing. And he's in this apartment. And he's like, just give me one second. I got to turn off my, you know, kettle or whatever.
And he walks away. And the director is talking to his assistant. He's like, can you, could you imagine having to live in a fucking shit hole like this?
Jesus Christ. Can you imagine like you're a movie actor, but then you come home to this fucking box like they just, and he gets back on the camera and he's like, I can hear you guys.
Are you ready for me to go? You're uncomfortable. Did he get the parts? No. No. I mean, this is, this is why people go, how could this monster, you know, like in an extreme example? Yeah.
How could Harvey Weinstein have, have done what he did for so long without any concern? Because people will ask that question without any concern for getting caught. Don't these guys think they're going to get caught?
That what you just told describe is obviously not a, not an offense in an illegal sense. It's offensive to a human spirit. But that, that's a microcosmic example of why?
If I was auditioning somebody and I did that, yeah. And they were like, I can hear you. I'd be like, well, and you've got the part. Yeah. How do I make this up for you? First off, I'm so sorry. Yeah.
Which was never said. I mean, these, these people are, are awful. Like you, you wonder how something like that can go unchecked, but we've all been in dozens of rooms where this behavior goes unchecked.
And I've sat in these rooms and thought, Pat, as a man, you should stand up and scream in this guy's fit. And I don't. And you don't, because you're worried about your career. I'm at a point now where I'm much more likely to not give a fucking get involved. But,
so I really admired about Leslie Jordan, by the way, four foot 10, you know, proud, I'm guessing as a gay man in the South at age 70, he was bullied severely. And if he sensed any injustice, anyone being an asshole, and there was plenty of assholes in the year that I do him, he would get right up in their face or as close as he could get without a step ladder and be like, what the fuck's the matter with you?
Like just a hero in that way, really, good. You never would have won any physical altercation, but he didn't give a shit.
Well, I'll kick things off. If you don't mind. Yes. Cause this is, has to do with overly checked behavior. And that's potentially maybe potentially some underchecked behavior. But I watched the documentary of P. We Hermann as himself.
I'll join you with in talking about this. I watched it in one night. All right. So let's make this our number one. All right, both are number. Yeah.
Part of me just Fleming up.
Fleming over here.
I watch both in the in the same day. I enjoy the documents very well done.
The first half is, is joyful. It's just about P. We and his rise and the adoration of the character and basically everything that leads up to him getting P. We's playhouse.
Yeah. And it's just joyous. And Paul Rubens is really funny.
The fact that he's doing this without letting the filmmakers know that he's potentially dying.
But it puts a whole adds a whole other layer to the watching experience and to see how charming and funny he's being.
Yeah.
I'll clip him on Conan right after from when I was there. Cause I remembered I was so excited. I didn't even watch him on the show. I was such a fan.
And his interview was so fucking funny. Yeah. He tells this story about how his dad was, you know, obviously not super cool with what his son was clearly becoming.
But he wanted to do a tea party. And he said his dad like the one time he really connected with him was like, oh, let's let's have that tea party. You wanted to let's go ahead and do it.
Yeah. My dad sitting there and sipping the tea and I was like, I never loved this man more. And I finally felt like he got me and he understood me.
And then he was like, could I get another cup. This is really good tea. And I went in and made him another cup. And I was like, my dad loves me and let.
You know, it's a great little story and really cute and sweet. And then at the end, he's like, give me one more cup and young Paul Rubens goes, I can't the toilet bowl is empty.
He had been refilling the cup with toilet water and giving it to his dad Conan cracked up. And I was like, of course, the man behind Peewee is like hilarious in real life.
But you sort of forget that because he was so rarely out of character like him talking to the camera in this. He's really like caddy and funny and sarcastic. And he he clearly doesn't want to be there, but is also loving the attention. So it's a lot of fun to watch.
It is fun.
And second half, the second, well, and here's the thing too, a lot of the interviews I had seen with him. He was so fucking uncomfortable, not being Peewee Herman. He wasn't funny.
And so you got to remember too. I was trying to put myself in his head space.
It's hard enough going to these fucking Hollywood events with anxiety and being scared and all that.
Not feeling like you don't fit in and whatever. But now he's got to face all these people who loved him. And they all think he's a pito.
Well, that's that's well, yeah, that's that's what you'd want to retreat into the character of Paul Rubens who does not have the Peewee who does not have.
Well, it's the opposite of that though. That's the opposite what happens. He he embraces Peewee first and says, I'm going to rise. My star will rise with this character. And I will live this character.
And that's the whole first half. And it's super charming and super sweet and super fun and all that crap.
The second installment is when he gets caught in the movie. It's kind of begins with him getting caught in the movie theater, which the authorities claimed that he was.
There was this whole thing where he didn't want to do some charity thing. And then they were kind of out to get him or something.
Yeah. And they caught him in the porno theater. They said he was jacking off. He was like, I didn't even have my pants undone. I was just sitting there.
It doesn't matter. He's arrested stories out damages done. And now it's the sort of now it's kind of the downfall into the third act come back.
And for second act and then and well, okay, there's a lot here. But the point is is now it's yeah, I mean, it's basically stand up.
And we get the amazing all time classic film. Two lesser films and a big scandal. I mean, those are the kind of the three acts of the thing and and fall outs with friends and family and so forth.
Well, the second that's what kind of a bummy out and watching the second half. And this is why I say overchecked versus underchecked overchecked meaning he didn't deserve what happened to him with the porno theater thing.
And then he's been in a different time. People had a different level of tolerance with this sort of thing. And it was very unfair.
Then he gets to come back and be a normal actor, meaning not as pee we just as himself. And now for the first time ever, he's being himself.
And blow mystery man, Buffy is the highlight of all those films. And he's not quite as comfortable. But he's but he's doing great work.
But then also in this stretch of the documentary is when they start to reveal the opinions of him from everybody he came up with, including Phil Hartman.
And I was like, oh, Paul Rubens is kind of a selfish fucking asshole that stole a lot from people. And isn't this story familiar? Isn't this story familiar?
This sounds like a lot of people I've known in the industry. And they won't cop to it. They ask him flat out a couple times. And he goes, don't mean to sound call us.
But hey, that show is kid. You're like, oh, wow, dude, you're like, this is not that very really stung that clip of Phil Hartman, who I have never seen.
Should exhibit any anger or hostility at all in any interview. And I was obsessed with this guy since I was a little kid.
And they interview him about pee we and he is hurt and pissed off. And he's like, I do not need to see or speak to this man again.
The truth is when you watch Peewee's Big Adventure, which is one of my favorite movies of all time, a lot of the dialogue, like, I'm a loner, dotty or rebel, you know, all that stuff.
That's like, that feels like a Phil Hartman sketch. You never know in these situations who wrote what, but my guess is a lot of the funny in that film comes from Phil Hartman in his sense of humor.
You see it in big top Peewee vanish when Phil Hartman is not involved. And a lot of times it's sour grapes. A lot of times people think they were more involved in something than they were.
But Phil Hartman was not a guy you ever heard talk shit. And that bothered me, you know, and especially as you're saying, the fact that Peewee wasn't contrite and apologetic about it bothered me.
Now in Phil Hartman even says, Stern, it's a Stern interview and Stern goes, you could have, could you have sued him? And he was like, yeah, he wasn't a lot of people did. And I was like, wow. And then as the documentary goes, you're kind of seeing more and more of Paul Rubin's interaction with the filmmaker and trying to control kind of what it is that's going to camera and what he's comfortable with.
So it's just so and then the second scandal happens, which is when him and Jeffrey Jones their house gets get rate their homes get rated.
And I say I forgot that second scandal happened. I that hit me like a twist in a movie. I was like, oh, right.
Well, that's the that's the one that's the nail on the final nail on the coffin, because that's the one that that was even more stupid.
But everyone who knows him said that he had a museum level collection of antique erotica weird thing to collect, but you're allowed to collect whenever you want.
So they show you and it looks almost like the end of Raiders of the Lost Ark with like these giant boxes and containers and things marked by year and decade and everything.
But when the police did this endless search of all his materials, kind of the same thing they did with Michael Jackson.
So when they arrested the kid who had been posing nude for Jeff Jones, they go, did you know any did you did Jeffrey Jones introduce you to anyone else and they it was like, yeah, Peewee Herman.
So that's what led them to Peewee. And they found one image according to the documentary in all these archives, one image of like a kid's bear ass that was questionable.
And that's what led to him being shook. It wasn't even that it was just a magazine where the kid on the cover was shirtless.
Yeah, posing.
I guess it was a witch hunt to end all witch on. But anyway, this is the one where he gets labeled as Pito.
Yeah.
But this is the part where I was like, come on, dude. That's not the fuck you fuck this up.
They're like, they're like Paul realized he had to go on camera and he had to do an interview to clear his name.
And he was going to have such and such reporter ask all the hard questions.
And it was going to prove that he was innocent, which we all knew he was and blah, blah, blah, blah. And I'm like right on, right on, right on, right on, right on, right on.
Then they show the interview.
And Paul says, I'm allowed to collect whatever I want to collect. And I'm like, that's not the response to this, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah. With what people are saying, you say, hey, dude, I, yeah, I collect old erotica. I always vet everything to make sure it's on the up.
There was one thing in here where I fucked up and didn't realize it or it came in a lot with a bunch of other stuff I bought.
And I didn't even know I had it. Say something, dude.
Yeah.
Don't say I can collect whatever I want to collect because what that sounds like is, hey, if I see a picture of a naked young boy and it's considered antique erotica and heavy quotes, I will purchase it because I am an American and I have the right.
And it's like, dude, come on, man, that's just not the response. And then yeah, the big, the big like kind of.
You know, like a summation of everything.
And the final chapter at the end of his life is is, you know, his his last redemption, if you will, is he does this final movie, which I'm sorry for it to anybody that was involved.
Fucking sucked.
And yeah, I mean, maybe slightly better than big top, but yeah, not need to.
It's worse than big time. I'd have to see him back to back. Yeah, I don't know. It's it's terrible. It's worth like there.
There, there, it's at a point where they don't even know what the character is anymore. Right. Yeah.
You know, you got him looking at a stop light and not understanding what it is.
It's like, guys, what is, what the fuck is this? Anyway, it doesn't matter.
And then doing like jack off jerk jokes with a milkshake to Joe.
Yeah.
Anyway, he had been talking for 20 years. They don't mention this in the doc, but he had been talking for 20 years about doing a pee.
Like a bio pick like he was now he's been hardened by Hollywood and he's like, you know, living in a castle or whatever and pissed off in the rise and fall of pee.
Wee's alcoholic and all that. And maybe they thought it was too close to the real story him having these demons, but that sounds like a way funnier take on a modern day pee wee to me.
Well, they they they so so so so the big again, the final redemption where everyone go.
He makes this movie in the in now in the documentary. They're like, this is all positive. Yeah, it wasn't to me because I'm like, yeah, that movie sucked.
It was even worse than the second movie. They tried to get back to the original thing by putting big in the title and making it a sort of road movie. Yeah.
None of it works. Now Phil Hartman's vitriol and absence is even more validated. Yeah.
Now everything you said about like the people that helped you make the early stuff brilliant and there none of them got anything is even more validated.
Yeah. And then the last thing is is and then they redo the original show on Broadway. And I'm like, yeah, and this is the thing everybody's pissed off about.
This is the thing that everybody was suing you over. Yeah. And now you do it without any of them. And I just I was like this. This second app didn't do you know favors Paul.
Like it just didn't. But I mean, there's a lot of stuff to say here. I saw that the revival of the the P.W.V. live show here in LA. I fucking loved it.
I loved this documentary so much because it is not what we have been shitting on Brian Wilson died this week. R.I.P. an absolute legend. God only knows we're talking about one of the top songs ever made and he's got many more.
But I say Brian Wilson or Williams. I hope I said Wilson. You said that Beach Boys doc that was on Disney Plus the Beach Boys career, you know covers 50 years. The doc is 90 minutes long at the end. The Beach Boys sit down for the first time to have a conversation in in a decade.
I think the camera pans away and the credits roll. And I just sat there like what a way, especially now that he's dead what a way they had the man there to talk about what a wasted fucking opportunity that was.
And Disney Plus and Netflix are two of the biggest offenders with these shitty surface level docs that go nowhere that eight hour prints documentary that we were going to get is now never going to be released because of the family didn't like that they said negative things.
And maybe it's because he's dead. I don't know. I really love that this documentary told us all that and gives you the full portrait of a man anyone with a great deal of success, especially in comedy is going to have their demons.
There's a whole show on vice over it like whatever that's called comics were fucked up or whatever. But I loved I just love that I know the whole story. I love that it wasn't white washed. I love that it wasn't a whole you know they could have done a 90 minute version of this where P.W.
was Captain Kangaroo and we allude to this scandal but we move quickly pass it in the dock or whatever. I like that we sat with it. We got what felt like the truth about it.
We didn't like a lot of the details about it, but there we are personally I don't like Jeffrey Jones having a kiddie porn collection taking pictures of little children and being close friends with P.W.
and introducing one of the kids to Paul Rubin that all feels I must say we're to me than how the story was originally presented to me it feels like how these things happen which is kitty porn rings which is middle aged men who gather and send stuff back and forth to each other.
Don't have any proof of that the documentary certainly isn't making that claim but hearing that that's how they got to P.W. started making me feel like it was a little less of a witch hunt than I thought.
Yeah how they how they got to P.W. was he was he was the kid was at his house.
Exactly you can went to his house like why the fuck are you okay with the guy bringing a kid to your house like 16 yeah like or I don't know if it was like one of those like right up against the line of legal or not but like the point is is like anybody that's even eight.
eight weeks underage like why are you okay and now look it could have been a big fucking pool party and and that you know and there were kids there and there were just people there that's so I get that but at the same time it's like.
You know a dude who's your friend who's bringing young boys around yeah you know your boy is up to something weird yeah why you still friends with your boy.
Which makes it real weird like I said when P.W. goes I can collect whatever I want and then for me it then now we're in the zone of okay well there's one side of the story where it's they had nothing and then the only thing they could press against him.
Was this one magazine image that they said was whatever see this was a witch hunt this was bullshit there might be just given this elements this is where you start to go well maybe maybe there's another side of that story where the authorities might be like oh no there was way more yeah but we weren't allowed to use it because of x y and z so this is the best we could do which is it becomes the Alcapone tax evasion argument.
Right where Alcapone till the day he died would it was like I'm an innocent man they they got me on tax evasion you know what I mean and it's like yeah well no no no they got you on tax evasion because they couldn't they couldn't prove the murder.
So so you're impression of Alcapone just just now was more convincing than either to near our performance in the Alto nights but go ahead.
So anyway my point is is and I'm not saying that's the case either and I'm not trying to bash Paul Rubens and the doc isn't the HBO Michael Jackson doc by the way it's not like we're talking to victims or anything and nobody ever stepped forward and that says a lot but I definitely had questions at the end of it that I didn't have before and I appreciated that I was presented all the information guess what guess what yes
yes it is a documentary that is made here's a fucking novel idea the way a documentary is supposed to be made yeah they present the information the guy is just trying to be the arguments he's having with Paul Rubens throughout the thing or like
did I'm just trying to tell the fucking story yeah I think it's important that he included those those arguments only to show you how prickly and particular and controlling Paul could be not even in a nasty way just like here's the real man without trying to be funny and put on a character what what a lesser
documentary would have done and it I'd say half of today's documentarians would have done is inserted themselves into the story and the documentary would have been called my year with Peewee and it would have been a two hand or like Morgan Spurlock or what's the fat asses and Michael more sorry I called him a fat called him a fat
that's not a child I don't know where that came from it's fine but he's a big fat man anyway what happened I love that the documentary is like I a documentarian is like people need to see these discussions but he's never on camera he's never involved to the extent where you're like which which one of you have been watching a movie about here I'm going to Google something really quick because I can't believe nobody did this back in the day.
No, I just Google the Peewee's big erection because I was like how did nobody ever make that as a porn or movie sure somebody made the joke but I just Google that I can't I can't yeah I mean Joe you go on stage tonight and dust that off see how does current we talked enough about Peewee but the documentary I thought was exceptional it's my favorite documentary of the year it makes you notice and realize how late it is.
I'm not easy and non informing and non real so many of these docs are I also want to say Matt McCarthy our listener and our dear friend Vince Avril went to a Hollywood memorabilia show on Friday night and who was there signing shit with pictures of all his classic films behind him Jeffrey Jones I that made me laugh so hard and yeah here's what's what I really loved.
When I thought it initially was was way worse than actually even Jeffrey Jones being there signing stuff yeah I was like I thought it was just a guy that had a bunch of Jeffrey Jones memorabilia I was like that somehow would be worse yeah yeah if the guy's specialty is focus in his collection yeah then you say what are you doing he goes I can collect whatever I want you know.
Peewee sir.
My guess is Jeff Jones you know he really only had about a decade he was a big character actor a guy I was always thrilled to see in a movie if I'm being honest with you.
He's an Amadeus and of course all the Tim Burton's and Ferris Bueller and so forth one of the one of the greatest it was such a it was heartbreaking yeah it was heartbreaking yeah and then he was in deadwood and then they had him back for the movie he was that's the only job I think he's had as he came back to reprise his part in
deadwood which kind of surprised everybody but he's clearly getting back out there and I was thinking to myself Jeff Jones got to be 70 years old 75 maybe I know he auditioned for the cool kids I didn't do the pilot so I wasn't on the show at the time but Charlie told me he auditioned and did a great job but obviously
there's a little bit of heat around that casting so they couldn't do it.
Sure my guess is that guy residuals can only take you so far he's got to be just about broke so make sense that he's doing these things I don't think he ever started another career after acting so he's been not working for 30 years.
Yeah yeah it's it's it's a real it's that's wild man that that circuit is as you once said this is a dark circuit.
Oh yeah I still remember our our big convention we went to in Littleton Colorado where we saw Tobin Bell and the twins from the shining and all kinds of people.
I've got another well hang I'm sorry one more thing yeah if you're in the Los Angeles area and if this post today meaning Friday.
Tomorrow night I am going to see the 30th anniversary is it 40th Jesus Christ I'm so old it's the 40th anniversary of P.B.
He's big adventure it's at the Alex theater in Glendale it is a screening of the movie in 35 millimeter the score played by a live orchestra which I think is going to be awesome.
And then an event with all kinds of cast and crew from the film moderated by one time guest of this podcast the great Dana Gould.
Oh wow I will of course be there it's the Alex theater in Glendale if you see me say hello.
Joe I've got another movie that falls my number two here is falls into the category of again overchecked maybe underchecked.
Yeah so under under over check any haul by the way where what do we we're in an hour here Pat we're rolling I don't want to obviously I don't want to rush through the next movie.
I'm going to throw something out here and then we can continue leisurely with our movie corner yeah I'm going to throw something out here.
I suggest we do something has never been done ever before on this podcast.
We do a two-parter where this is part one and part two is not only our alto nights review but our review of known us.
And we do a mega review of the latest in Italian cinema and and we can also begin that episode by leisurely finishing this movie corner we've begun because I almost feel like we just did a review on Pete.
You did that's true.
Pat Pito's case.
Bewas bigger action.
I also want to point out.
So do you want to yeah are you going with that?
Yeah let's do it.
All right do you want to point it out in this episode or the next episode?
Oh you want to wrap this one up?
I'm saying we're going to do a two-parter so let's let's bring it on over all right then yes I want to point out that Joe.
Won't watch the sopranos.
We'll watch in one week the alto nights and known us.
Yes.
Criticism of the sopranos.
It's not an accurate representation of the Italian lifestyle.
That's all I have to say for this week.
We'll see you next time.
See you next time.
And we'll see in hell.
I did your line.
You did mine at the beginning.
Okay.