I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the shine of your screams
Becomes a thing on my dreams
You know I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean
it doesn't work and I hate to shit on comedy at this time, especially when I am constantly complaining about they're not being enough, but we got to try harder than this is my opinion.
That is very much happening in this movie with Damon Wayne's Jr. He's playing Amy Schumer's original boyfriend.
That guy is so charming and so delightful and I was just watching him on shrinking and he's really great on that show, great on happy endings and whatever.
And he looks furious that he is in this movie. You feel it. You feel it. You feel it. You're like, oh, wow, like he's not even giving it, you know, 2%.
It's that kind of movie. It's just it's it's it's filling up the the slots on Netflix until the next one comes along. Unfortunately, they do the most generic action movies, the most generic comedies.
They're just they're not great movie makers. They're just not the Netflix team.
All right, fair enough. I well, I mentioned it in the last episode. I watched a
Dirty Harry again. I remember talking about this a while back on the show and saying that like I wasn't really feeling the dirty Harry movies.
In the way I thought I would and I do believe I gave the best credit to the first one, but I will say this. I was very wrong.
Excuse me or at least too underwhelmed in my praise of the first movie. I don't remember exactly what I said, but
and maybe it was the experience of rewatching it on DVD and seeing the grit of it and all that stuff. I don't know, but
it was a hell of a 70s cop movie. I mean, it is a wild fucking flick.
You know, there are plenty of people out there that would find it problematic for numerous reasons.
I find it to just be very of its time.
And impressive that they are able to walk the line they walk with this character.
The, you know, it's Clint Eastwood at Clint Eastwood's bed. It's everything you want from Clint Eastwood.
There's just no two ways about it. And it's everything you want from Andrew Robinson who plays the Scorpio killer because the first movie is sort of based on the Zodiac.
Yeah. I love it. That's why it remains my favorite.
So, you know, Harry isn't quite yet a superhero in this one, which he eventually sort of becomes.
But it's a gritty, just old-fashioned kickass action movie. I also really enjoy Rennie Santoni in it, who is known as playing Poppy.
On Seinfeld, he's also in a movie called The Late Shift, where he plays one of the executives over at NBC.
But anyway, Dirty Harry, you know, if you haven't seen it at this point, I'd say it's a fun rewatch. And I'd say if you can watch it in a gritty or form at it, it adds to it.
There's something enjoyable about that.
I'm a big fan of the Dirty Harry franchise. All of them, I think, are, you know, at very least above average action movies.
I think that stayed pretty consistent through the end. The Deadpool, I was really surprised by A, that Jim Carrey is playing Axel Rose in it, basically.
And B, that it's like just nuts and kind of fun. One of my favorite late period cleanses The Rookie with Charlie Sheen.
I think that one is severely underrated, if you've never seen some great car chases and stuff. I was written by the guy who co-wrote Evil Dead 2.
My last is a rewatch of a romantic comedy and definitely one that I considered a modern classic. And I'm happy to say it held up beautifully. And that is forgetting Sarah Marshall.
I watched Shrinking, which was just setting my teeth on edge at first. I was like, I'm curious about Harrison Ford in a sitcom, basically.
And it, at first, it was too cutesy and too quippy and it was just really bothering me. And over time, I think it became a really sweet and moving show about fucked up people. And Harrison Ford is far and away the best part of it.
By the way, I don't think it got really good until the very end of season two. It takes it a while. But to me, I'm glad I stuck it out. I liked it.
For getting Sarah Marshall is Jason Segal, who's a guy that I guess I like, you know, but to me, I was always like, how did this guy become as big as a Rogan or a Jonah Hill or something because he's nowhere near as funny. He's just bringing a different vibe, I guess. And I think that's a great idea.
While I enjoy him in Shrinking, it's not his show, even though it is his show. It's not to me. It's about the supporting cast on there. And so is this movie. And yet, Segal wrote it.
You can tell that it's extremely personal. He's very likable in it. But this is a movie that's really about the people on the fringes.
And so, I think it's a great idea to have a couple of friends. I think it's a great idea to have a couple of friends on the fringes.
Kristen Bell, Meal Akunas, both of them. I don't think I've ever been more charming and delightful. Russell Brand before he went haywire. Very, very funny. Bill Hader, very early hater, Jonah Hill, Jack McBrayer, my old friend, Maria Thayer, Paul Rudd, in the only character that doesn't really work for me, even though I love Paul Rudd, I did not, I don't like his like,
I don't like his movie just because that Paul Rudd can't make that believable. You don't buy him as a pothead. It's why he never played one of Rogan's cronies in those movies, you know.
You got Jason Bateman, you got Kristen Wigg, you got so many funny people popping up in this thing. And the movie itself is just an example of a really strong example of the best of romantic comedy,
which is equally romantic and funny, just like it's nearly impossible to get the horror comedy right. I just mentioned Evil Dead 2. That to me is maybe the definitive. And that is because it is equally very funny and equally very scary, gory, you know, crazy horror.
Usually, you know, the biggest rom coms, your miscongenialities or your pretty womens give you a chuckle or two, but they're very sweet stories and you're rooting for the couple.
When Harry Matt Sally is probably the definitive half comedy, half romance, where there are big, hard, genuine laughs. And yet, you're also completely swept up in this couple and their love for getting set on Marshal is more a movie about getting dumped.
And getting broken up with angelic see. So it's a good companion piece with like Albert Brooks's modern romance. And there aren't enough movies made about this.
They do say now that it was kind of dangerous making these type of guys the hero, making somebody who is essentially stalking his ex girlfriend, the hero or like Lloyd Dobler and say anything holding the boom box up after she's clearly dumped him.
Like that's not great behavior to celebrate, you know, and sure, but it is great behavior for comedy, just like the heartbreak kid with Charles Groden or any of these movies where a guy is just not his best self in pursuit of love because we are not our best selves in pursuit of love.
That's why they're always a lot more funny and true if you get the balance right. And I think this one does. I really enjoyed it. More dick, you know, we talked about Sebastian Stan dick last time.
You can definitely see why Jason Seagull wanted to show his off a show or not a grower flaps it around. There's big laughs.
The romance is sweet. The the Hollywood satire because if you remember the Kristen Bell character is an actress on like a CSI type show.
All of it works. And then it's also in a beautiful Hawaiian locale. So I don't know. To me,
of that period along with knocked up, this is one of the great romantic comedies of my generation. Joe.
All right. You old Virgin by the way. All Appetite joints produce or directed.
Let's slide into that movie of the hour. It is companion starring Jack Wade amongst amongst others.
And then he's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's
a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy
He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very
very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy. He's a very good guy.
She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She
murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders him. She murders
He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He murders him. He
I mean, that could be suggesting that, you know, as robots become more human, they're going to become more shitty because humans are shitty. That's kind of how I took it as sort of a dark twilight zone style ending. I like that ending. That could be I didn't get the vibe of that. I got it that it was supposed to be a, you know, you go for yours girl kind of thing. Well, yeah, I'm a more cynical view of it. It would be that it's setting up a sequel that I don't think we're going to get because it was not extremely successful. Even though it did.
Well, but I, I debated Pinkstone on this for a while because he he kept. He kept saying like, well, that didn't bother me because you know, she was, she was in as a moral as the other characters. And she needed money to start a new life. And I'm like, she's a robot. She could literally live under a rock and go work every day and make money until she had it. Like, what the fuck are you talking about a new like, or okay, so then take both a robot and a beautiful woman. She'll be fine.
Yeah. Take 50 grand and start a new life. Yeah.
Six 12 million dollars. Like, well, I don't understand. Like starting a rich guy, you'll be fine in three hours. There was a, you know, I was like, they, they go out. I go, then, and here's the thing. Then don't make it that he's married.
And, and just make a detail that there isn't another person this money should go to. Right. Just it's just a simple thing. Like, it's like, I don't know. Like, and it
that ending point reminded me of the ending of don't breathe or blink twice. What's like, so she's just cash and in and not turning these guys in for all the horrible things they're doing on this.
You know, at this retreat home of theirs, like, like, no, no, no, no, that's, that's not good. So yeah, I don't know. It didn't bother me as much as the end of blink twice. I thought the movie.
All made sense. And I'll even go with you on the leave it up to interpretation as to why she takes the cash. But I thought all in all companion was a good film. It was suspenseful. It was fun. It was quite funny at times.
And they did a great job. I didn't know at any point where exactly it was going to head. And I enjoyed it. My hog is up for companion up enough that I could stick it right into a companion.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Totally. I thought this was extremely well written and directed by first time or drew Hancock produced by Zach Krieger from the White as Kids You Know.
Guy I've hung out with many times who also did Barbarian, of course, and it's now going to be doing the Resident Evil franchise.
I thought this was just at every step of the way better than it had to be. And that's all I'm asking these days. You know, it's really, really solid. And it's fun.
And it's well written. And there's a twist every 10 minutes. You know, at the beginning of this thing when I see that Lucas gauge who's very like Abercrabby model is dating Harvey Gillian, who's a heavy set dude.
I was like, cool. Love that. Great. Then you learn that Harvey Gillian is forcing this man, this great looking man to be his sex robot. And you're like, oh, it just there's a million little moments like that where they just tweak what you just saw.
And tweak your perception of things. So even when it's not a giant plot twist, there's just a lot of little emotional twists and turns amongst the characters. And that's where I think the movie really shines. Like I said, I didn't need the money caper really.
But I think the movie has a lot to say and it's super well done and congrats to our boy, man, McCarthy for doing a great job in it.
We'll be back folks. Yeah, we'll be back with Mickey 17 for sure. And it sounds like we're going to do here. And we'll see what else possibly Mickey 70. Yeah, for sure here. It's maybe the monkey. I got it. I'm traveling a lot on the road. So I got to see what I can get to see in the theater. But definitely here and something else. But hopefully it's one of those two.
All right, folks. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.