I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, it's We'll See You In Hell, 300
Now, I could do a bit here about how we're going to talk about the movie 300 as a funny misdirection
but I did that already and then Pat had a really funny thing to do
and then we had to start the recording again
So there's your fucking anniversary episode, okay?
We could have just done it again, I mean
Let's do it again
No, it's fine
I liked when you said that he had so many six -packs you were diamond hard
Yeah, I was talking about how that was I think my first exposure to Jerry Butler, Gerard
He was a real rip back then, it made me hard
Now he looks like he's doing just enough working out to appear on camera
Like maybe he has it contractually, you have to work out to this point
and he goes just up to it
He looks like he's drinking up till when they call all action
I like it
He's the new, you know, Bronson or Norris or something
He's got a low profile, he's churning out these low budget hits
I'm happy for him
I like that
Crow, Russell Crowe
Yeah
Did the thing where he's like
Well, I'll just play those kinds of roles now then
I'm just going to be this fat, I don't care
Yeah, I mean
He's like, just give me the fat parts
I'm not running
I'm not going to be the gladiator
Now if the gladiator has an obese father
I'm happy to pop in
Like Anthony Hopkins and Troy
Once in a while and I'm drinking out of a big goblet of wine
Sure
That was one of my favorite
You know, last episode we discussed Silence of the Lambs a little bit
And that's one of my favorite things about Red Dragon
When Hopkins is just in Red Dragon with a huge gut
And it's supposed to be before
The other movie
Come on, guys
Jesus Christ
Like, the movie was made ten years too soon
Right before they could have de -aged them down and just, you know, fixed it
Yeah
You hate to say that a Brett Ratner movie is better than a Ridley Scott movie
But Red Dragon is probably slightly superior to Hannibal, I would say
Well, I think you
Because as we were saying last time
It's a similar
It's almost the same story as Silence of the Lambs
And I think
Well, it's Manhunter
It is the same story as Manhunter
Yeah, and I think like you get a little more of what you want out of it
He's playing cat and mouse with a cop
Who's trying to solve a murder
And then you have a really interesting psycho character
And that one played by Ray Fiennes
Which you can't really beat
With Emily Mortimer as a blind
Ed Norton
Yeah, it's a big cast
Philip Seymour Hoff
Very good cast
I would imagine all those names saying
Yes, I have to work with Brett Ratner
I guess he wasn't as controversial at that time
He was not at all
Nothing had come out at all yet
He was just the Rush Hour guy
Just the guy who had done Rush Hour
Yeah
I never saw
Did you ever see Hannibal Rising
Which was like Hannibal in junior high or something
Like Hannibal but with Riverdale vibes to it
I looked it up because I was like
It's kind of
After I watched Silence of the Lambs
I was like
These sequels have to be better than I think they are
And I looked them all up
Red Dragon I think is the best rated of the three sequels
Hannibal Rising
Which I was like
Maybe this is some hidden gem I wasn't aware of
I think it had like a 13 %
It was like
I never saw it because it was real hated
Real hated
Yeah
And I never saw Hannah Bowe the show
Which I've heard is phenomenal
And I own it
I just never watched it
And he did Rising I think because
I think that's the one where De Laurentiis
Dino De Laurentiis or something was like
He was like the author wanted nothing more to do with Hannibal
He was tired of it
And then he was like
Well I have the rights and I'm going to make this anyway
And that like was his scheme to get the guy to do it himself
Right
And then it still sucked
So
Daniel De Laurentiis
Has seemingly been producing movies since the silent era
It's crazy
Like you watch a movie from the 70s
They're like well obviously we had to go to Dino De Laurentiis
You watch a movie from two weeks ago
There's Dino on set
I just don't know how he's still alive but good for him
Yeah it's wild
It's very very wild
It's wild
Producing movies with David Lynch
He also like he'll produce anything
An art house movie
You know a 300 million dollar franchise
It's whatever
I thought he had the dune rights actually
I wonder if he shared any profits of this big dune franchise
I watched a video
It was an old Charlie Rose interview with David Lynch
And David Lynch was explaining his meals
That he eats the same meal every day
Okay
He's just so odd
The meal itself isn't odd
It's the way he describes it
And you're like this is why he's David Lynch
He's like for lunch
I have a tona
Some sliced tomato
And a little bit of olive oil I sprinkle on
And then he goes
And then Charlie Rose goes
And what about dinner?
And like Charlie Rose is like laughing
Because he's like
Right
You're odd man
And then he goes
For dinner every night I have broccoli
With little pieces of chicken
Put a little soy sauce on it
And Charlie Rose goes
Okay
Is it good?
I assume it is if we're eating it every day
And he goes
Yes it's very good
And it allows me to free up my mind to not think about it
I think is what he said
Okay
I mean I would assume
Have assumed that he had never had a vegetable in his life
He just gives that kind of vibe
He looks like he eats the way
The Kyle McLaughlin eats in Twin Peaks
Like when he's like
Give me those eggs as hard boiled as
To harden my arteries
Whatever the fuck he says when he orders his bread
Yeah
He sounds like you'd see him at House of Pies or something
Yes he seems like a pie guy
A pie guy
I think because there's that special feature on Twin Peaks
Where he takes them to eat pie
Yes
And he's like this is very good pie here
And they're eating like apple pie as he's telling one of the actresses
You're so hot
And like no one's bothered by it
Just because he doesn't seem creepy at all
He's odd
One of the oddest to ever do it you know
Yeah
Anyway
I went on a date last night
Sober girl
Tough
And I'm like what do you want to do?
She's like well
Here's the other thing
Women
Maybe it's I guess let's say women on the apps
And keep it a little more
A little less generalized
Women want you to either plan everything
A lot of people have this on their profile
They want you to be like
Great person I've never met
I'll pick you up at 730
We're going here for dinner at 8
Then we're going here for a show at 930
I've planned it all out
I've made reservations
They want the man to be a man
But basically translated
They want to do nothing
They want to do no work at all in the dating process
And hide it under chivalry
Pretend that that's chivalry
And not just complete laziness on your part
And some women I'll go
Hey
How about I meet you here at 645?
How does that sound?
Oh, okay
So you're just planning everything?
Like I have no say in the matter
And you don't know who you're dealing with
It's 50 -50
So that's fun
But this girl I've been out with her before
So I'm like
So what do you want to do?
You don't want to say come over to my place
Because everybody knows what that's all about
Even though that's not usually my intent
I have a nice home
I'd like you to come over and watch a movie
And whatever
But like, you know, it's got an ulterior motive vibe to it
So I give her a bunch of options
And she picks one
It was like this thing
This event happening at Hollywood Forever Cemetery
It was quite late
Quite late
45 minutes
Really late
She was 45 minutes late?
Yep
That's date ruined
That's I would almost leave at that point
That's wild
Because she was communicating with me
I didn't
Okay
I've had other people not communicate that
All right
That's different
So we then this event that she chose
It blew
It was supposed to be like a concert
And they had all like fun
I thought it was going to be like booths and fun activities
Like a fair vibe
And it was these two 21 -year -old
My assumption is their parents are famous or something
But they're like rolling around on a stage
Lipsyncing some of the shittiest music I've ever heard
As people pretend to be interested in it
And I was like, you want to get out of here?
She's like, yeah
So there's $80 down
You know, just the worst evening
So I'm like, what do you want to do now?
And now I'm thinking
Well, now let's just go back to my house
Let's just end the charade
And she goes, well, let's go to a movie
I haven't been in a movie in a long time
I go, okay
I mean, I was talking about this today in my podcast
It's weird
I don't think you want to see John Wick 4, right?
Have you seen any of the John Wicks?
She goes, no, I haven't seen any of them
But that might be fun
I'm like, all right
I want to see John Wick 4
We go see a 10, 15 p .m. show
This girl goes to bed at 9 p .m. by the way
10, 15 p .m. show of John Wick
20 minutes of trailers
Nicole Kidman doing her AMC shilling
Which is another five minutes
And then a
Folks, I am not exaggerating
A three hour John Wick picture
Which I knew and somehow forgot
But at some point she's like
Hey, I'm sorry, I'm really hungry
Can you get me like a pretzel?
I'm like, yeah, yeah, sure
I go out, check my phone
And I'm like
We've only been in here an hour 15
We're like a third of the way done
I mean, it seemed like the movie was ending
That's like the pretzel thing
Made me want to do the boys in the hood
When Ice Cube's like
You better take your ass to the star with that
When the girl drinks his whole 40
Yeah, yeah
I mean, look, I believe in chivalry
And I'm always like
Hey, can I get you something or whatever?
But it is a little weird to be like
I'm really hungry
Could you go get me?
It's like to not be at all
A little, be a little proactive
Am I wrong here?
She goes, can you give me a
I'm just assuming, hope praying
She doesn't listen to this
But she's like, can you get me a pretzel and a Sprite?
I go, yeah
I go out to the booth
I'm out there 25 minutes
Because they got these kids on a Friday night
No idea what they're doing
I've been there, kids
But you know
When people are leaving a movie
You could try to speed it up a little bit
I missed 30 minutes of the film
So I go to have pretzels
Nowhere out I can do pretzel bites
This girl seems real picky
But I'm like, yeah, let's do those bites
And then I make myself a big Sprite
Bring it to her
Takes one sip of a 64 -ounce Sprite
She goes, oh, did you get diet?
I go, no, it's regular
This is, this is, this is
You never again
There's no second date
I already called it off
Alright, alright, thank you
This was the second date
But I already called it
Jesus, crap
Tries it, she's like
She goes, I go, no, it's regular Sprite
She goes, oh, it must just be something off
With the syrup then or something
Like, okay
Then she opens the thing and she's like
Oh, you can see she's disappointed with the pretzel bites
Even though it's just
It's merely a pretzel broken into bites
And she didn't say anything
But that O said everything
The movie John Wick was a blast
The running time is madness
But I think they were like
Let's just have every battle go on for
30 minutes
And they do
So it's good
And it's on as hell
It's exhausting
You feel at the end like you are John Wick
Because you've been watching this movie for so long
Better than three?
It's the best since the origin, yeah
Oh, wow
Alright, I gotta go see John Wick
We should review John Wick, I'll go see it
Okay, great
It's fantastic action and they've added new characters
That I assume they're gonna spin off
But they're really cool characters
Like they, you want them to spin off
They're neat
So I dug it, I dug it
And they had a really good balance surprisingly
Of the mythology and the butt kicking
It was like 80 -20 as opposed to
You know, how it was getting 50 -50
Anyway
It is our 300th app
In honor of that
I thought of
A little Joe
On with the Joe song
I know people have been requesting those
And I haven't done one in over a year
But I thought of one right before we hit record
And I'm gonna do it for you now
They tried to make me go to rehab
I said Joe, Joe, Joe
Very good
And it works because Joe should probably go to rehab
Probably
Anyway
You, I wish they could see you now
Because if anyone looks like a guy who's in rehab
It is Joe now
He's got the skull cap
Some sort of punk black t -shirt
The tats
You look like the guy from Good Charlotte they sent to rehab or something
Yeah, I look like that
I got a little bit of Tom Hanks
Late second act Philadelphia going on
Yes
You look like a guy from Good Charlotte who was sent to rehab
Who also has full blown AIDS
I
I had a late night last night
Ari Shafir headlined The Beacon
It was a huge night for him
I'm very happy for him
I'm very proud of him
And he packed it out and he was great
And he had me and Joe List and Andrew Schultz go on as surprise guests
It was a fucking blast
And then we all went down afterwards
Not all of us but me and Ari and some other people went down to my bar
And we drank down there
I was almost beaten up by some drunk that wandered in
It was a wild night
So I'm hurting a little bit today
But I am feeling good about this episode 300
You can hear it in my voice
I got a milky voice happening right now
We said that for this episode we would still review Knock at the Cabin
But we'll do that at the end
We won't do any segments
We're just going to kind of reflect for a while on the show
The origins, what it's meant to us
How it's been a part of our lives
All of you
So on and so forth
And you know it's funny
When I think back to the very beginning of the show
I forget
I fucking forget
That this all started with Fangoria
That will escape me
And that we at one time were the first ever Fangoria Network podcast
Which I don't even think we do podcasts anymore
But good old Ken Hanley
The man who planted the initial seed
Literally in me and Joe
He fucked me and Joe raw
And that was kind of like the blood oath
We all formed a partnership
Now I signed on to the
Joe was like hey you want to be my co -star
My co -host on this Fangoria podcast
I was like yeah sounds great
I had pretty much just met Joe recently
But I do wish Joe had told me
That he signed away 90 % of the money
For the duration of the podcast to Fangoria, Inc.
Yeah
The fact that I send them
So much of this money every month is annoying
Because they have nothing to do with the show anymore
But we did what we had to do
We're kidding
Sometimes you got to make that clear
People get worried and upset
Everything's okay
We're just kidding
No we're good
I mean that's
Look we can start at the beginning
And I think we've talked about that in the past
But maybe a long time ago
But like the real beauty of the show
And you know look
We get annoyed sometimes
But it's like a mom who cares about you too much
You're like mom shut the fuck up
But then when you really think about it
You're like she cares about me and I appreciate that
Is this me? Am I the mom?
No I'm talking about our fans
Oh the fans do get concerned
They do get motherly which is very sweet
Yeah I mean when I looked at the Patreon page
By the way I don't think people know this
But there are tons of comments on the Patreon page
And it's not as much as like the Facebook or something
But there's a lot of hellion interaction there
And it's always fun to read
And I do read those comments
So check that page out
But I'm just talking about everybody
Like there was 30 comments
Some of them were just like
Where the fuck are the episodes?
Okay fine
But then there's a lot of like
Are Pat and Joe okay?
Are they still talking to each other?
Is everything great?
I mean we were maybe
We weren't even late
You get four a month
But we were maybe a week later
Than we would normally post the episode
And everyone's like where are they?
But it makes you feel good
They care, you care
It's good that we're a part of your month
That you look forward to
There's not much to look forward to these days
And if it's us
I greatly appreciate that
And we also do appreciate too
That in this economy and this climate
Anybody spending money on anything
Is greatly appreciated
And that's in fact
That's why we didn't say
Here's a strict schedule
Because we were like
If we can't meet it
We're not giving people what we promised them
And we wanted to be able to
Number one rule of podcasting
Don't promise anything you can't deliver
Right
And that even comes down to
Our release schedule
If you say you're going to do it one way
You just do it that way
So that's why we said
We'll give you four a month
Somewhere in that month you'll get four
And you have our word
We could drop four on March 30th
We probably won't do that
We could drop four on March 1st
We never know
But we could
You never know
This all started
This show originally
This is another thing I can't believe
And it wouldn't have lasted
But you know my podcast before this
Was just called Down with Joe DeRosa
And a lot of the episodes
I just did by myself
So this podcast originally
Was going to be called
I'll See You in Hell
And it was going to be me watching movies
And doing commentary on them
And then I thought
Right
This is insane
How the fuck am I going to do this alone?
And then I said
Well my new friend Pat likes movies
So I asked you to do it
You said I don't like horror movies though
I said it doesn't matter
You're just reviewing movies
And you used to review movies
And here we are
So here we are now
But the bigger point I'm getting to is
In that initial phase of
Let me see if Pat wants to do this
This is kind of cool
I'm going to do this podcast with Fangoria
Oh cool, Pat said yes
We're going to do it
Oh cool, we'll change the title to
We'll See You in Hell
If you had told me that
We'd still be doing this
Seven years late
Whatever the fuck it's been
And that it would have spawned
Friendships amongst the fans
And these fan groups
And these
Especially
To on trips together
Yeah
And I especially took notice to all of it
During COVID
Like the groups going online
When nobody could hang out
I mean my God
What a beautiful
I never would have imagined
That two old fucking lugs
Like me and Pat
Anything we did together
Might have led to
A thing of beauty amongst other people
Yeah it's really great
You know I feel like our
Our fan base
Judging by our live shows and stuff
Has a bit of a
A misfit quality
An outcast quality
Not that you're all nerds or something
You know
But I just mean like
I feel like it's a group
That maybe
Didn't have
People of their own
You know people with the same passions
And now immediately
You got all these great friends
That love the same things
It's really cool
Like you know
Ten of the fans
Went to Vegas together
You know they rent houses together
It's a great thing
It reminds me of
And this is why I love
The convention circuit
Like it's
It reminds me of cons
Like you know
Going to cons
Like
And I was
Pat and I
We say that by the way
Because we were those people
I don't know
Of course
People make fun of
Like my collecting
They're like
What's wrong with you
You know you
You know there's Netflix right
And I'm like
Yeah I know
Get the fuck out of my apartment
I actually had a date recently though
Where the girl was like
This is the coolest apartment ever
Oh my god
Look at all this
This is
And I was like
Marry me
Right here
Right now
Let's do it
And then she left
Yeah
No but
Love that call
Pat I married a girl
She liked all my collectibles
So I married her
Oh great Joe
Great
We've got nothing in common
Like Joe's saying
I think I'm going to buy a car today
And drive it across country to New York
Okay
Alright Joe
And I did it
Fine
I love it
You did
But Pat and I were
I was always that person
Where when I found somebody else
That was so passionate
About the stuff
I liked
It lit me up
I'm doing these things now on
And I'm coming back to the fans
But I just
I'm doing these things now
On my Instagram
Called Show and Yell
Where
You know the hook is
I exclaim about things
That I
That I love collecting
And I'm doing them about
You know right now
It's very music focused
I'm going to do video games
I'm going to do all my collectibles
Because I get stuck
I'm collecting constantly
And just seeing like
The feedback from people
Where they're like
Dude
I love that Cure album
I didn't get into them
Until I was in my 30s
And like
Oh
It's just awesome
It lights me up
It fills me with such joy
So to see that happening
Amongst the fans of this show
And you know
Like Pat was saying
Like it reminds me of
It very much reminds me of
Like the con thing
The convention thing
Where you go in
And you suddenly are surrounded
By all these people
With similar interests
It was what made watching
Evil Dead Rise
So cool
Was because everybody
In that audience
Was a massive Evil Dead fan
Yeah
And you're like
There was such a connection
There amongst everybody
And it was so fucking cool
And god damn it's a thing
You don't get to experience
Much anymore
Especially since COVID
So I love that
The fans experienced that
With each other
And I'm sure you'd experience
It with other people
In your regular lives too
But yeah I mean
Look Joe you're a comedian
So you get stopped and stuff
I used to get stopped
In the Vine days
When I had a little Vine fame
But on the rare occasion
A hellion comes up
Like this very nice gentleman
I was talking to at the
Grocery store the other day
It's a day maker
Even though I did look like shit
So it's a nice feeling
And I would like to add
That I would like you guys
To recognize me more
When I am out with women
And not when I am just
Out by myself
So I could get that bonus
Residual appreciation
From the date I was on
Ooh this guy gets recognized
I was on a date once
In my neighborhood
It was a day date
Yeah
And I wasn't quite sure
If it was a date
Because I had been friends
With this woman for a while
Yeah
She doesn't live in New York
We were distant friends
And we went and got lunch
And I'm like god damn it
This is a fucking date
I think it is
I'm not sure
Yeah
And then it was like
God was just like
I'm going to hook you up dude
We start walking down the street
The second place we go into
Some guys like
Joey Rose's best bar
In the Lower East
I'm like alright
Thank you man
We go in there
Get a drink
Then we go to this
Other place
It was a plant
She's been to plants
It was a plant store
And the guy is like
Helping us
And half way through
He's telling us everything
He just goes
I'm really sorry
To do this
I'm a huge fan
And I wanted to be
And I'm like
Yeah
Oh yeah
And like
This is my town baby
Yeah
She like put her arm
Around me
As he was saying it
And I was like
Here we go
Yeah
They're pretty obvious
With it
You know
So do that for Pat
When he's on a date
Is what I'm saying
Please
I need all the help
I can get
Nice hook up
No it's
It's just been awesome
You know
When Joe said
That I told him
I don't like horror
That actually kind of
Surprised me
And then I was like
Yeah
I didn't like horror
Like my favorite
Horror movie
Remains poltergeist
I've seen some horror
I'm a big movie buff
But that was a genre
I pretty much
Left alone
And this has made me
A massive horror fan
I mean you can't
Help but feed off
The passion people have
For these movies
I go to shutter
More than any streaming
Service now
I'm a full fledged
Horror fan
So
The
I love this podcast
For that
And you know
The true
The true reason
This continues
The
Well we wouldn't have
Continued without the money
Because
It's just the truth
It is a hassle
You know
It's not like it's
This is like
It's a job
It becomes a job
It's a
Well I wouldn't say
It's a hassle
I just mean
To have to schedule
To have to
Set up the mic
Whatever
It's not that
It's a job
It becomes a fun job
Yeah exactly
But what I'm saying here
But I hear you
But it's still a job
Like yeah
If you
After
We almost ended it
When we were like
We've done it for five years
For free
We've got to monetize
This in some way
Or we're going to
We also used to fight
Constantly
And it was like
Dude
What are we doing here
We're not making any money
We're fighting
Yeah
It's hurting our friendship
The only time we're hanging
Out is to record
Yeah
You know
So the Patreon has been
A godsend
It's
You guys came through
In a
Honestly a bigger way
Than we even expected
We're so
Thrilled to be able
To keep doing it
And you guys do support it
It's like
You're paying for it
But
The real reason
I think that we keep it
Going
Is that this is
With us living
Across the country
Our opportunity to
Communicate
For at least
Four hours
Every month
And it's great
It's like
You know
Me
It's my issue
When Joe calls
I tend to go to text
Calls give me anxiety
I don't know why
Even from friends
But
You know
We text all the time
But
This thing keeps our
Friendship strong
You know
You're texting somebody
Across the country
You stay friends
But it helps to
Put in the face time
It's just a beautiful thing
You bring us close together
We bring you close together
I don't know if you guys
Know
But there are
At least two groups
That meet
Who are Hellions
One
Is a movie discussion
Group on Thursday nights
I think
If that's still ongoing
And the other
Is like Hellions therapy
Where everyone talks
About their issues
That they're going through
And their struggles
And they help each other
Through them
I mean
That's incredible
It's beautiful
You
You'd think that this
Would be the thing
That made Pat and I
Cry on the podcast
But no
Just talking about
Movie scenes makes us cry
Any real human talk
It's like
You know
I'm kidding
Yeah, no
I'm never gonna cry
Because of a
Human thing
That occurred in my life
Pat and I
As to go back to
To the beautiful connection
To witness amongst the fans
I failed to say
That that's what
Pat and I connected about
We were two
Similar guys living in
A city that
We didn't feel
We could relate
To a lot of people
And when we met each other
It was like
Oh, finally, man
Here we go
Yeah
And I say that
As I can see
Pat's movie collection
Behind him
In this shot
And the movie I see
Is 120 Days of Sodom
Which I'm the only
Other person I know
That owns that movie
Yeah
Say low
Say low or solo
Solo
I've never watched it
I bought it
Because it was when
They were like
Manning everything
And they were removing
Everything
I was like
I better buy this
Before it gets removed
I'm like
I never want to watch it
I just want to own it
For posterity
I have it on DVD
And then of course
These fucks put out a
Blu -ray finally
On Criterion
Yeah
And now I'm like
I gotta
Upgrade a movie
I've never even watched
I thought you were
Going to say Godzilla
Because it got that
Big Criterion Godzilla
Thing up there
But the fact that
Say low is
The one showing
To anyone who comes
To my home
You've just made me
Realize I need to
Move its placement
That's one that I can
I can move its
Alphabetical placement
For a week
And not trigger my OCD
Just so people don't
Think I'm a big
Say low enthusiast
Have you
The movie itself
And people do call it
Horror
Even though it's not
A horror movie
There's something about it
That from the
Opening second
You feel sick
To your stomach
It's just
Before any of the
Horrible things
That happen
Happen
The vibe of that movie
Is just pure evil
Similar in a way
To like Caligula
Yeah
Where like you just
Feel dirty pushing play
And Criterion's coming out
With this giant
Pasolini box set
That's the only movie
Of his I've seen
And the only movie
Of his I cared to
But I might dig
A little deeper
He seems like a freak
I was going to buy
When they did that
Criterion flash sale
This week
I didn't end up
Buying anything
I got
Overwhelmed
And put it away
But
I was going to buy
Oh, Antichrist
In 4K
And I was like
What are you doing?
You don't need this
You don't
This is never a thing
You pull off the shelf
And say
Hey, hon
Watch Antichrist
It's such an upsetting film
Like
It is
You know
And like I said
I bought Sallow
And I bought the Devil
The Devils I bought too
For the same reason
That I bought Sallow
But I actually
Enjoyed the Devil
There's something fun
About the Devils
Even as depraved as it is
Yeah, it's
You know
It's a walk in the park
Yeah
Compared to Sallow
It really is
I've never seen Caligula
I mean it's notoriously
Trashed but
I mean
Caligula is an interesting thing
Because it's porn
But they weren't allowed to show
Porn things
So like
People are fucking
It's orgies top to bottom
I mean that's Caligula's vibe
But when there are cum shots
And there are many
They switch to a
Visibly fake
Almost like a paper mache dick
That spurts like toothpaste out the top
It's very, very weird
Because the rest of the movie
Is like pretty graphic sex
Helen Mirren is in Caligula
Oddly enough
Yeah, I know
There's fisting
There's like horse fucking
There's all kinds of shit
That's weird
I had a dream last night
I'm not kidding
The Sopranos was at the bar
Yes
And
I don't know
For some reason I had Sopranos dreams
And I had dreams that they were showing
Like real sex and the Sopranos
But the way they did it
Was exactly how you just described it
It would cut to like a clearly fake dick
Yeah
And in the dream I remember being like
Oh, David Chase
If you can't do it for real
What's the point?
This looks ridiculous
That's very weird
That that was my dream
You even hated the Sopranos in your dream
Say again
Well, there was a fan of the pod
I'm blanking on her name
But she was at the live show
At the bar
And she was talking to me a lot about it
I apologize
I'm blanking on your name
But I'm terrible with names
But she was talking to me a lot about it
And she was like
Is this the joke that your bartender plays on you?
And I was like
No
She likes the Sopranos
Right
Yeah, but you hate the Sopranos
I was like
Well, yeah, but I'm not the bartender
The bartender likes the Sopranos
And she's like
Yeah, but isn't it just like a fuck you?
And I'm like
No, no
The bartender likes the Sopranos
You think I'm fucking coming in here like
Like Steve Jobs
Yeah
Not at all
I had when I worked at Blockbuster
My manager Matt
One of the saddest people I've ever met in my life
We had him
And then we had another manager who got arrested
For going to the casino with money from the safe
Oh, I love it
Yeah, and then he lost it all
This guy
When I would be working on a Sunday night
Let's say at Blockbuster Video
We'd be open till midnight
Even on holidays
Even on Sundays, Blockbuster
And no one comes in after 10
Maybe a young couple or something
So I would put on movies
And I would never put on an R -rated movie
No matter if it was tame or not
People did
But you know
I'm watching some PG -13
Maybe Wayne's World or something
While I'm putting the movies back on the shelves
And the door opens and I don't look
But I'm like
Good evening, welcome to Blockbuster
And then he's like
I turn around and it's Matt
He'd been parked across the street
Watching the Blockbuster to see what movies we watch
On his night off
So
You know we're not supposed to be watching PG -13
I'm like, yeah man, I'll turn it off
There was nobody in here
It doesn't matter
Jesus Christ
Okay
Alright, cool
Alright, I'm sure Blockbuster took great care of Matt
When the end was nigh
Yeah
God
I mean I was making $7 at the time
Remember
Here's another thing about the pod
That I will remember that we did
Yes
Because I always forget that we did it
Remember when we did
We changed the format to talking about sin
I do
And those are actually very funny
And kind of beloved episodes
Yeah, that was a you idea
Yeah, another great idea
I think I was like
Well Joe, that's only seven
But that was at a time when we were doing seasons of the show
Now, technically this Patreon season has been three years with no break
We never really structured that properly
Once you monetize a show
You're never allowed to stop ever
I've learned it with this and with taste buds
It's like, no, that's it
You're like, well wait, that's it
They're like, yep, that's it
That's it
You're like, okay
Yeah, we did do that
We used to do a couple commentaries
We probably did four or five
We still get requests for those
But man, that's just a cross -country commentary record
Is not something that's easy to do, unfortunately
Well, actually, if I may say so
Not to crit -
Correct me
Christ, not correct you
Criticize me
Not criticize, contradict
Jesus God
Actually, with the Zoom thing now
It probably is kind of easy
Because you could just open your browser and we could just play a movie
I mean, it wouldn't be ideal
But we could probably do it pretty easily
The problem is you -
Well, no, I don't even think you'd have to mute the movie
Because I don't think what was playing on your browser would be recorded by Zoom
So we could try it
We'll run a test
The bigger problem is the technical issue of running a two -hour Zoom
Because these fucking things go sideways
But I don't know
I'm going to get some coffee
Give the people your thoughts on -
Share a memory, Pat
Sure, sure
I mean, for me
The shows
Got me through some hard times
When I listen back to those early days
It's a good way of kind of watching the slide of depression as well
Because when Joe and I started, we were a couple of bitter guys
We drank a lot more on the show
We probably made fun of each other and got angry a lot more on the show
Probably because of that alcohol
Yeah, you can hear just more life in our voices
The early episodes are great
Because you can kind of get a snapshot of my and Joe's friendship forming as well
We were kind of feeling each other out
We didn't know each other as well
So yeah, I don't know if anybody's ever done a start -to -finish listen
But I would imagine you're just listening to two men grow deeper and deeper into a depression
And maybe that's interesting, I don't know
But I know we've always said, boy, I know I've been bad before
I've never felt as shitty as this
I got nothing in the tank
And then we've doubled down on that millions of times
But I think that's a big part of the beauty of the show
There's a million movie podcasts
There's a half million horror movie podcasts
I think what makes this one special is that we give an unvarnished look at our lives, our mental health
We don't tell you everything, but we tell you about as much as we possibly can
And I think that it helps us to share in our failures and triumphs together
I would agree with all of that
And it's funny, the first time Pat and I ever had an argument
It was directly related to this podcast
I take a lot of blame for the early arguments we would have
I was not in a great space, let's put it
Let's put it as a space
Sure
I was in LA, I wasn't really happy
And I was stressed out about everything all the fucking time
But anyway, the first time we ever had an argument was when we went to do the Denver Mile High Horror
You were late picking me up for the airport
We got into a big argument on the way to do our first ever live show
It's just funny, the moments, the mile markers, that's a good way to put it
Of our friendship being so tied to this podcast
I remember on the way to the airport just being like, maybe we just don't go
Maybe we just don't take the trip
It was reaching that kind of a point
Yeah, it was like a married couple
And then we pulled it out and had a blast in Denver
We did
Denver, that trip is my favorite, hands down, my favorite memory
We've got a lot of good memories
The live shows in particular are great memories
But my favorite memory ever of the show is that trip
Because Ken Hanley brought us out
We woke up at 6 a .m. on Saturday after getting in very late
To do an 8 a .m. screening of Maniac Cup 2
We started drinking
And we were not a big podcast at that time
We had just started
I think about 12 people came, right?
Yeah
We did a live commentary of Maniac Cup 2
And we started drinking
Drunk at 8 a .m.
Yeah, at 8 a .m., literally at 8 a .m.
And we drank until 4 a .m. without a nap
Without any real meal break
I don't know, how the fuck we did that
The Ski Lodge place
And we were there for like 3 hours sitting in big wooden deck chairs
And we went to a strip club
I mean, we went everywhere
We met a group of people at that Ski Lodge place
There was a woman talking to me
I thought I had met my wife
I was like, this is it, this is how it happens, what a story
We were really connecting with people all over the place
And that was just such a fun, such a fun trip, man
That was, you know, we saw Final Girls on that
With Adam, I almost said driver
What's his face? Adam
Brody
No, from...
Is that Adam Horowitz?
Oh, Adam Devine
Devine
We saw the 11 p .m. screening of Silver Bullet the first night
That was great
That's right
We drove to the airport with the twins from The Shining
Yeah, we rode on the elevator with the bartender from The Shining
That's right
He was like, they don't give you any goddamn towels in this place
He was like the most Jewish New York guy ever
And I'm like, you're the creepy bartender from The Shining?
Yeah
It was very funny, sounded like Regis Philbin
We met some other people on that trip I'm blanking on
But we also saw that horribly disturbing picture about the landmine
We didn't see it, the guy told us the premise, but we didn't go in
What we saw was a horribly disturbing movie about a Spanish actress who dies
And then everyone in the morgue takes a turn fucking her dead body
And then she like comes back to life and gets revenge on them
We watched the corpse fucking movie, not the landmine rape movie
It was, it's a category
That's another thing we could discuss with the history
What has come from doing this show?
I have learned, as we talk about 120 days of Sodom and whatever
Like I said, I bought it for posterity
I learned on that trip, and it's only evolved since then, that I do not like that genre of horror
I was never fully aware of how much I didn't like that genre of horror
But I do not like, let's watch how depraved somebody gets
Right, like endurance horror?
Yeah, is that what it's called? That's a great way to put it
I don't know if that's an official term, but like a movie you have to sort of suffer through
Like Irreversible or something like that
I fucking hate Wolf Creek for that reason
It's just that fucking big Aussie, or is it New Zealand? I don't remember
But you know, where the guys are like, I'm gonna tie you up in my garage, I aim
That was like a cockney, I can't do the accent right now
I didn't remember Dick Van Dyke playing that role
But yeah, I saw Wolf Creek in the theater, and Never Again, that was enough
But it's weird, I mean like a Hostel is fine for me, but I don't like torture porn
You just gotta be good with it, you know, you gotta be like
Like Hostel, you watch it now, they're cutting away from most of the most brutal stuff
You think you've seen it, but you didn't
Hostel, I've always loved because, you know, and I said this from the first time I saw it
I was like, everybody thinks it's torture porn, it's not, it's kind of like a weird adventure
Like this kid gets out at the end, like I've never rooted for somebody so hard
As I did for the kid at the end of Hostel
Yeah, that's like an action movie
Yeah, when he runs the girls over with the van
Yeah
Like I saw it in the theater during the day, and people were like, yes!
Everybody was so fucking pumped, man
Who has had a more interesting career than Eli Roth?
I mean, okay, I'm gonna be Mr. Horror, and now he's doing like kids movies with Jack Black and Cate Blanchett
I mean, I don't know what he's doing
Yeah, Eli Roth's a guy where, like, if he was a stand -up, he'd be like, what do you want me to say when I bring you up?
He'd be like
Still Hostel?
Director of Hostel wrote The House with the Clock and its Walls and played the Bear Jew
Yeah
And you're like, okay
Yeah, quite a career
Yeah
Anyway, what can we say, folks? We love you, we appreciate you
We thank you for coming out to the live shows, we're always trying to pepper in a few more
I know I have promised my parents that I will come to St. Louis this year, and I would love to do a show there
But, you know, you guys keep it working
I know it's hard to sort of recommend to people because we're Patreon only and it's a big investment, but they can always hear the old apps
Also, something I'd like to address, the ads in our old podcasts are updated to current ads
They interrupt stories right in the middle of stories, they'll cut in with ads
We don't have control over that, it's very tragic, I wish we did, we are not getting paid for those ads
It sucks, but I guess the benefit is these places are still paying to host them or are they even not doing that?
I just thought of a resource I could potentially tap to figure that out
It just came to me right now
Alright
We'll try to explore that, but yeah, I don't know what's going on with that
It's not right, but anyway
If you're annoyed by the ads, and I'm sure you are, I think people are also annoyed by how we used to record this podcast
Because the channels are really hardly separated and stuff, we just didn't know what we were doing
But let's just say that even if Joe and I aren't getting paid for those ads, let's say that's what's keeping them hosted on iTunes
and able for you to listen to them, and that's at least one benefit that comes from all this shit
I think it is, I mean I think it's that or we gotta find a new one
I'm assuming that's gonna be the Starburns excuse is, hey guys, you're welcome to host these yourself
It's a giant catalog and we need to get something out of it, we can't just do this for you as a favor
I'm assuming that's what the explanation will be, but I'll look into it
Okay, but anyway, 300 is an incredible accomplishment
If you do a hundred episodes of a TV show, you're syndicated, you're gonna be on forever
You're considered one of the biggest hits of all time
So I know a podcast is different, but 300 is very impressive
A lot of these shows don't make it, or they do make it, no one gives a shit and listens
We have had a very sturdy, reliable fan base for like seven, eight years
So thank you very, very much, it never dips, you know, it never dips substantially
So we love you guys, thank you very much and thank you for telling your friends about it
Because I'll ask people, how did you hear about the show or when did you come on board with the show
And it's always a friend, talked it up to them
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Joe, are you ready to move on to our film?
Yeah, well I want to say my thank you too
Please
Otherwise it just looks like you just said it
That's what I was going for
No, I echo Pat's sentiment 1000%, thank you for everything
The support has been mind -blowing, and I mean that, we both do
Thank you to Emily for all you've done over the years, starting the initial group
And your involvement in every aspect of the podcast
Thank you Ken Hanley, the godfather that raw -dogged us in our butts
And exploded into us, birthing the idea of this podcast
Thank you Ken, we appreciate it
Thank you Will Potorf for all the art, amazing art over the years
So much amazing art has been done in honor of this show
Not just Will, but Will's definitely been doing it probably the longest
Talk about Kismet, Pat, Driscoll, the first, not the first, but basically the first bartender we ever hired at Joey Roses and still there
Is Will's cousin
Yeah
It's weird how it all kind of ties into your life in a weird way
And there are so many other people whose names, it's too many people to name, number one
And I'm sure people's names are escaping me, but please know that all of you are appreciated
Your undying support is appreciated, and it's not because, oh, thanks for paying us to do this, folks
It's because you've helped us realize that we're doing something that you appreciate, it's made us appreciate it more
And it's just a beautiful symbiotic relationship, if you will
And, you know, here's to, Pat, here's to 300 more
See you back in seven years
Yeah
Does it get sad at that point? Does it get sad at that point if we're in our 50s talking still about
I mean, I think we're like the Rolling Stones of podcasts at that point, you know
You can do it till you're 100, but we should probably have some sort of end date in mind
But not anytime soon, don't get upset, everybody relax
Not anytime soon
Anyway, yeah, this is like when you make a joke to your mom, like, I don't know, mom, maybe I'll just kill myself
No, don't say that, I'm just, I'm not gonna kill my, alright, sorry
Yeah
Easy
I might, but
So I dance around the idea, big deal
Like, you give a shit
So I'll juggle knives occasionally, you know, I just like to feel alive
Um, a knock at the cabin
M. Night Shyamalan
Speaking of wild careers, I mean, when this man came on the scene, it was, okay, here's the new Spielberg
This is it
Uh, this guy, his, I mean, Sixth Sense, his breakthrough is arguably better than Spielberg's early movies
You're like, this guy is a genius
And then he followed it up with several really effective movies
Um, then things fell to shit
A very dark period after Earth, of course, with Will and Jaden and all that
You know, the happening with Wahlberg and Deschanel, really bad movies
I got the movie, I got the movies here, ready?
Yeah
First of all, he's got two before the Sixth Sense that I've never seen
Well, there's Wide Awake with Rosie O'Donnell, which I've never seen, but he just wrote, I think, maybe he directed it
Which is like a nun comedy or something
That's Wide Awake, yeah
Jesus God, look at this thing, Dana Delaney, Dennis Leary and Rosie O'Donnell in a baseball nun comedy
It's directed and written by M. Night Shyamalan
And he's got one before that called Praying with Anger that he stars in
Oh, no
In addition to writing, directing and producing
Uh, it did go to some festivals, I have no idea if it's good
It says it's an independent drama
You know, it looks like a typical, just from what I can see here, you know, debut
Like, you know, you're gonna make this, whatever
Anyway, so he does Sixth Sense
Guy more than cements his footing with Sixth Sense
Follows it with Unbreakable, polarizing but amazing
Yeah, great
Follows it with Signs, I didn't like Signs, but people love Signs
Love Signs
Follows that with The Village, which I think is horribly underrated, but appreciated
Yeah, kind of a long -term, twilight zone
Little kooky, little dumb, but ultimately I think a pretty cool movie
That if people revisited, they would like a lot more
I just saw an article on MovieWeb where they said it's his most underrated movie
And I agree, or underappreciated, I agree
Yeah
Then, then this happens
Lady in the Water
Quick pause there
So that's where things fall apart is Lady in the Water
I mean that, that is one of the all -time bad movies
I read an entire book about the disastrous making of it
Where no one had the heart to tell them how much it sucked
Because they all thought they were wrong
They were like, this guy's on such a hot streak, what do I know?
But this doesn't seem great
Man, it's a bad movie
I remember when he announced, my next movie is going to be a dark fairy tale
That I tell my kid at bed every, I was like, this sounds fucking awesome
And then I saw the movie and I was like, oh my god, this sucks
There's a 30 minute scene where Bob Balaban is playing a movie critic
And then they eat a movie critic
And it's like, Shyamalan, your movies have gotten pretty good reviews
You don't need to do this
The Happening is arguably worse
He clearly lost his confidence
It is definitely worse
Yeah
The Happening is definitely worse
Because The Happening is not just bad
It's poorly cast
Yeah, oh yeah
Oh my god, maybe, do you think it's the trees?
Oh Jesus, please guys
I've been crunching some of the numbers on some of the theorems
And it looks like, you're like, no
It's like when Denise Richards played a scientist in the James Bond picture
You're just not buying it
What's after The Happening?
After Earth?
Wahlberg, real quick though, Wahlberg as a scientist in this
Wahlberg as a college professor in The Gambler
And Wahlberg, again, as a scientist in Transformers
It's like, guys
Oh wow
That's like, for me, the worst casting ever is
James Franco is the Wizard of Oz
Where you're like, Jesus
How did that happen?
Guys
Alright
It's M. Raimi's worst movie by far
Yeah, go ahead
After The Happening
He adapts The Last Airbender
Never saw
Did you see that one?
No
What was that?
The Slumdog Millionaire, Dev Patel?
Dev Patel, Noah Ringer
It's based on the anime avatar, The Last Airbender
I'm not an anime fan
There was just no way I was ever gonna see this
Yeah
I'm trying to find what the reception of it was
It did
For Christ's sake, come on
Jesus Christ, it made a lot of money
Got a 5 % on Rotten Tomatoes
Well, it did
It was a $150 million movie
They gave this fucking guy a $150 million movie after those two bombs
Post, Lady in the Water, and Happening
But
Insane
Made 319
Okay
It had to be worldwide
I don't remember that doing well here
He made the money back
Then?
After Earth?
Then after
Didn't see it
After Earth
Budget
Gross
So now the money's going down
And in this business
If you didn't at least double it
They're like, get the fuck out of here
It's a failure
It is insane though that those movies
Clearly made way more than I thought they did
That's wild
This got a 12 %
Joe Morgenstern of the Wall Street Journal
Opened his review by asking
Is After Earth the worst movie ever made?
Maybe not
There's always Battlefield Earth to remind us
How low the bar can go
Yeah
Rex Reed goes throughout that one
Wow, dude, that is a great opening to a
That's the best opening to a review I've ever seen
Then is he
Does he come back with the visit
Is my guess of the next picture
So then he does the visit
Now the visit
He had a good time with the visit
The kid rapping is a disaster
Everything else is kind of fun, I thought
Pat and I were split on the visit
Look, it's a $5 million movie made $98 million
The guy went back to his roots here
And it was wild
Seeing a director that had done this large
This large scale of projects
Going back and doing a found footage
It was clearly like, okay, dude
I got to reset here or I'm fucked
The visit
I figured out the twist like 10 minutes in
And I was like, yeah, shit
And that kind of ruins it
But I also, the kid
I don't remember him rapping
I just remember him doing the fucking chant
The football chant at the end
I was like, this sucks
But it was good enough
If it had enough scary moments
I did buy it on DVD
Probably never watch it
But it was on sale for Amazon Prime Day
Once for like five bucks
But the visit is well received
He then comes back and does Split
Very well received
I believe one of the few movies we saw together, Joe
Yeah, Split was pretty good
Back in action
$9 million budget made $278 million
So now the kid's back
Despite the controversy
From the mental health community
Split did very well
He follows Split with the long -awaited
Sequel to Unbreakable
Glass
Glass budget $20 million makes $247 million
Still not bad
But Glass was not
God damn it
Glass started so cool
And it just didn't stick the fucking landing
And it's such a bummer
But I will say this
In the way
In the traditional way most trilogies go
And I would say
A near flawless trilogy is the original Star Wars trilogy
And even in that
You're like
God damn it
The first half of Return of the Jedi is so awesome
And then they get to the Ewoks
And you're like
So I'm like
I'm willing to go that far with the Unbreakable trilogy
I'm willing to say the first one is my favorite
Second one you could argue is better
Third one is good enough for enough of it that you're like
Alright
We got an ending here
I don't remember what our review was but
I think we like Split
I mean it ends with that big battle like in a hospital parking lot
And you feel like they just didn't have the money to do what he wanted to do
And it is super anticlimactic
Then he does
Now here's where he starts slipping again
It's old
The beach that makes you old
That movie was so stupid
Yeah it sucked
God it sucked
Yeah
18 million dollar budget
Gross is 90 million
This guy's in trouble again
God I hated this fucking movie
And it had a big dumb twist at the end
They all do
Well except for the one we're talking about today
Knock at the Cabin
Now Knock at the Cabin is based on a book called The Cabin at the End of the World
Again though not good
20 million dollar budget gross 54 million
Not good
Yeah you got Dave Bautiste
The movie is this
There is a gay couple
With their young Asian daughter
5 years old
They go on a weekend trip to a cabin in the woods
Which 50 % of people call this movie Cabin in the Woods
I had many friends say hey you gonna go see that cabin in the woods
Dave Bautiste comes upon the young Asian girl in the woods and says
Hey
I need to talk to your parents
He's trying to kind of be nice to her, befriend her
But there's something very off about him
And he seems to have a mission
Yes
The girl runs back, tells her parents
Hey there's this guy in the woods that approached me
He was creepy
Something's going on
And before you know it
Bautiste
Ron Weasley from Harry Potter
And two other women
One a sort of middle aged nurse
One a younger woman
One the daughter from Mad About You season 7
Or whatever
I didn't know that
When they brought it back she was the daughter
It was driving me crazy
The whole time I'm like
Who is this?
I know this girl
I was like oh she's the Mad About You daughter
They come into the house
They basically are
The four horsemen of the apocalypse
Let's say
They are arriving
To share the news
That unless
One of these three people
Meaning the gay couple and their daughter
Dies, kills themselves
Then the world will end
If you do not do that
No I'm sorry
If you don't kill yourself
One of you
The world will end
No no no you can't kill yourself
You have to sacrifice somebody
Sacrifice yourself
You have to be willingly sacrificed
If suicide is
They said doesn't count
It's like a cheap way out
It has to be done
If you don't do this for us
We will be
The three of you will be alive
And the rest of the world will end
If one of you sacrifices yourself
You will save the world
But one of the three of you will die
Yes
Great premise
You know
The trailer definitely hooks you in
Somebody describes to you that plot
You love it
This book
People really really love this book
I had not heard of it or read it
But Shyamalan apparently changed the ending drastically
And that was very controversial
But
Well you know
We'll get to spoilers on the movie
Let me say too
Real quick
I just want to add a detail about the setup
Yes
The other part of that is
Every day that they won't willingly sacrifice one of them
Right
Then the group has to sacrifice one of their members
And that unleashes a new plague on the globe
Which Bautista is showing them on the TV
Yes
And they're questioning the validity of any of this by saying like
It's easy to predict something like that could happen
Or that was news footage from a week ago
Right
They do a decent enough job of being like
Is this real? Is it not? Are these people crazy? Are they not?
Blah blah blah blah
Anyway go ahead
Yeah no
I think
You know it's basically just these eight characters or however many
Seven characters
And Shyamalan himself has a cameo as a guy
You know
Testing out something on QVC
He always has to do the little Hitchcock thing
But
The movie really as it goes is a
Is this real or isn't?
It's sort of like a
The movie Take Shelter
One of my favorites with Michael Shannon and Jessica Chastain
Is this
Are these people crazy?
Or is the world ending?
And the actors who play the couple are great
Really effective
I've never really thought much of Bautista
But he's good in the role
I just on this second viewing because I was like
I saw it in the theater and I wanted to refresh myself
And it's on Peacock
I watched it yesterday again
This thing's got plot holes upon plot holes baby
Like I had so many questions and I started asking people
And they were like
Oh no that doesn't make sense
Including the question I asked you is not answered in the movie
So
You don't know the whole time is this real or is this not?
Here's my big issue
Here's one big issue
Ron Weasley
When he shows up
The gay couple recognizes him
And
Weasley gay bashed one of them
Years ago
And it went to court like it was a big deal
He broke a bottle over his head
It's a very violent attack in the movie
He flashed back and see it happen
And the guy leans over and he's like
That's the guy who gay bashed me
I know it
And that's their way of saying
There's no way there's an apocalypse
This guy found people who were easily swayed
And he's coming back to get revenge on us
Because Weasley had to do some jail time for this attack
Now that's revealed to be true in the end
Because spoiler alert
The world does end
They're not wrong
They're not bullshitting
Well it doesn't end
They save it from ending
Correct
But the world really is ending
And they save it from ending
Yeah
It is going to actually end
And they do save it
Which is
Right
Well no
The gay bashing thing didn't bother me
Because
Well let me finish
Sorry
So they find out that
So my issue is why would Ron Weasley walk in
And not recognize these guys
But it takes the gay guys a little
It takes the gay guys a little time to recognize him even
So I'm fine with that
And he was wasted when the incident went on
And I get that
Okay fine
But
When it is revealed that
Okay the world was actually ending
How are we supposed to believe that Ron Weasley just randomly shows up
At the cabin of a guy that he gay bashed
Because that's what Shyamalan is asking us to believe
But he's because the
Because Bautista says
Like you were chosen
For a reason
There's a reason that your family was chosen
I think it's just supposed to be
That there's a connection there
And that's why
God put them there
Yeah
Like they had these visions
It brought them to this family
Why us?
They asked that
And he's like we don't know
It's just you're the family
And I think that's why
And it's like oh so this
So in the end the husband
Can realize
They represent the
Is it the four horsemen?
Wrath
You know wrath
This that like and that
That is allowing us to now
It evokes our own emotions
So we can do what's right
That didn't bother me at all
I thought that actually made sense
I just found myself with a lot more questions
On a second viewing
Because I was just
You know if we're just supposed to believe
That God's involved
And it's some mysticism
Okay all right
But I'd rather not
I find Shyamalan and old was the same way
I find he's not super concerned
With the details of this shit
He's just concerned about kind of like
Plan your emotions and stuff
I felt that old had some major issues
Yeah detail wise
Logic wise
This I didn't
I think what you're in my opinion
I think what you're running into here
And my friend Chrissy said this to me
We were talking about it
She goes because we randomly watched it
Separately on the same day
Yeah and and she she was like
It was very like God heavy
I was surprised by that
And I was like
Yeah it almost was like a pro religion movie
And I was like yeah
But but that's the thing
Nobody's expecting M. Night Shyamalan to do that
Nobody's expecting a Hollywood movie to do that
So I think like you're watching it
And you're going
Well it's clearly not a God movie
But it is
You know what I mean
So then once you go
Okay that is kind of what he's saying
It's a sort of a
Then you go okay
Then this all sort of makes a lot more sense
From that perspective
I also will say this about Shyamalan
I'll say this
Well two things I want to say
Number one
I am not saying Dave Bautista
Has never been a decent actor
Or a good actor in anything before
This is the first thing I ever enjoyed him in
I actually liked him
I liked the character
I really liked him in this
I think with Shyamalan
You know he's painted himself into a corner
And you're sitting there the whole time going
Where's the big twist?
What's gonna happen?
And this doesn't have it
It's literally just by the end of it
You're like oh my God
They were telling the truth
And it was gonna be the end of the world
And these people did save the world
Which I would have liked a little more ambiguity
Did we?
Didn't we?
We're not sure
But Christ what a fucking ride that was
And let's never go to the cabin ever again
Also here's my question
Is this an Airbnb?
What's the policy on a bunch of dead bodies
When they go to clean the cabin?
Like you assume these guys rented the cabin
They show up there's a bunch of dead bodies
Aren't they in trouble?
I think the cabin lights on fire when the fire starts going on
Oh no you're right
You're right
Sorry
So that's gonna destroy the evidence I guess
But you'll probably still find some bones in there
I mean yeah it might be a problem
Or maybe it's the kind of thing where the cops are like
Okay it was the apocalypse we all did what we had to do baby
Good luck to you
I feel like it would just be like there were body remains in this cabin
These people died in a fire
I don't feel like it would be
But because I don't think anybody got
But wouldn't you speak to the people who were staying at the cabin that weekend?
The guy and his daughter?
Yeah but I just took it as
I just took it as he would just be like
Yeah we got home invaded
And then the fucking cabin got on fire and we left
The movie was not liked
It has a C rating on CinemaScore I believe
And audiences are usually pretty kind about movies
You know generally movies get a B or an A
A B, an A
And I get that
There are people, there's film Twitter type people
And letterbox type people who talk about Shyamalan
As though he is one of our great directors
And these are the people who loved Old
And loved Knock at the Cabin and loved him
He is a great filmmaker still
This was shot really well
You're never bothered by it being basically a play in one set location
He keeps things moving, he keeps things interesting
And I admire him churning out these low budget movies for a tidy profit
Maybe they're not massive hits anymore but they're making a little profit
I think that's where he should be
I just as I have been saying
Now for 20 years
The man needs to let other people write sometimes
This is the first movie I've seen of his in a while that had two other credited writers on it
I assume one of them is the writer of the book
And I'd love to hear what the differences are from the book
My assumption is that
What's the ending of the book that he changed, do you know that?
Well my assumption is that in the book the world isn't actually ending
Because it's supposed to be a massive change
So I don't know, I'll give it a read, I hear it's a good book
I got the, can I, I'm going to read it
Yeah please, if you got it
The couple
Okay that's Andrew and Eric, that's the main couple
The couple follow Sabrina into the forest
Sabrina
I'm just trying to see if that's the daughter
No, she's one of the four
Sabrina taking Wen's body
Sabrina recovers the car keys and a gun that Redmond had hid
She tells Eric that there is still time to prevent the apocalypse
Then commits suicide
Sabrina's the black nurse
Okay, then commits suicide before she can be further compelled
Eric considers taking his own life but Andrew argues that even if the apocalypse is real
He refuses to obey a god that does not accept Wen's death as enough
Oh, Wen is the daughter I think
Yeah, oh the daughter dies in the book
They decide that neither wants to leave the other alone by dying
Grief stricken Eric and Andrew head for Redmond's car
And with Wen's body declining, deciding to stay together through whatever comes
That is a cooler ending
And much more ambiguous and much darker
So yeah, you know
But I mean this movie wants to have the missed ending
You know, not exactly, but it wants to
It wants to hit you with this like gut punch at the end
That just leaves you devastated and it doesn't
It ends with a little cutesy disco song playing and everything
And you're kind of like, alright
But I mean to me, you know, my hog is
It's not limp, but it ain't hard
I mean I think this movie is not very good
It's a step up from old for sure
But yeah, it just didn't work for me
I don't know what to say
It held my interest certainly
But I just didn't think it was a great movie
And I think it
It's not
What you're saying
It would have been better with some ambiguity
Something left vague
You know, a really dark ending
What they did just kind of feels like a shrug to me at the end
And you've been through so much
You just want something different than what it is I guess for me
I got regular hog on it
I enjoyed the watch
I wouldn't
I don't think I'd rewatch this
But I enjoyed it enough
I was intrigued
I enjoyed the experience
I certainly thought it was 10 ,000 times better than old
I definitely liked it more than The Visit
I also just thought from a directing standpoint
It was
He did a better job with this than he had done in a while
I thought he really worked those flashbacks in very well
In telling the backstory of the gay couple
How one of them was very proud and supported by his family
The other one was very closeted because his parents were
You know, shameful of him
I liked all that stuff
I thought it really helped me appreciate the characters
I liked the flash forward when you saw the one husband older
With the grown daughter
That stuff all really worked for me
I gave a fuck about the characters
And I thought everybody's performance in this was great
Particularly Bautista as I said
I got regular hog
I ain't mad at it
I ain't excited about it
But I could push one out
Sure
You'd have to seduce yourself a little bit to get there
But I hear you
Folks
We'll be back
Thank you again
Glorious episodes of the show
We'll be back next month
We could have reviewed 300
That actually would have been kind of fun
I can't watch 300
I can't watch any of those Zack Snyder
Where it looks like
Like a Terry Gilliam fucking cartoon
I can't do it
We will return with discussions of
Probably Scream 6
Probably John Wick 4
I'm sure other things are coming out
Evil Dead Rise
I think that's April 4
Also too
Brian Quinn of the Impractical Jokers
Wants to come on the show
And he was in one of the Hatchet movies
And he loves horror
So we should have Brian on
That'd be fun
Thanks again everybody
Thank you everybody
I know we don't usually plug on the
Second and fourth episodes
But I'm going to be in Michigan
And Chicago this week with a bunch of shows
Go to JodorosaInfo .com
I just want to get as many people out as possible
And I hope to see you at one of those shows
If you're in that area
That's it, right?
We'll see you next time
And we will see you
In Hell