Hello everyone, welcome to the Thanksgiving edition of We'll See You And Hell,
the podcast brought to you by the Fangoria Podcast Network for more information about the network
including other programs how to follow this show and other shows and find past episodes of
any show. Of course, including We'll See You And Hell, please visit Fangoria .com and here we are.
I am on one side of your head and my man, Pat Walsh. Hey, yeah! On the other, we're still getting
a few complaints about why the audio is split. We just do it so if you want to watch these movies with us,
you can send that right up the middle and it'll feel like you're sitting in between me and Pat
on the couch in a nice sandwich. Every young lady and gentleman's dream. Yeah,
our podcast today finds us in Los Angeles about 11 30 in the morning,
T -minus about 12 hours from T -gives Thanksgiving Day. Yeah, and we have whiskey in our coffee.
I'm not embarrassed to admit that to anybody. No, I put a splash on there.
We're doing the prophecy today. Not really a Thanksgiving theme movie. We did thinner last.
We should probably do this in thinner today, but whatever. Well, you know, oddly enough,
until I was doing the introduction with you for thinner, I didn't put together
that I could be making a Thanksgiving show. I just used my sweet, sweet improv head and I said thinner
even though you get fatter on Thanksgiving. But it's not like we planned it. It was very true.
That was right off the cuff. So let's not beat ourselves up too much. I'm not beaten. I'm not beaten
anything. Prophecy, I currently I can't tie it to Thanksgiving in any way. I'm just thinking there's
a religious element. Okay, pretty good. There's not very religious stuff to do with Thanksgiving is there.
Also, it stars Christopher Walken, and you'll be walking to the bathroom after you eat that big meal.
Yeah. Perfect. Chris starts Christopher Walken who looks like he hasn't eaten ever.
Looks like he's never eaten salad food in his life. Yeah.
Cue it up now. Get to your Netflix. Find the prophecy. We're going for the first one now.
Not any of the sequels. The original prophecy. Cue that up as we talk here for the next minute or so.
And then we'll get going. Pat, what are you most thankful for this year?
You and this podcast, Joe, it gives me a place to go. You know, otherwise, I just be wandering the streets
masturbating into bushes. You know, life was bleak for me until we got this podcast gone.
If there was any, for two hours a week, I'm off the streets now. If there was any
thread of sincerity in that, it would have meant something.
Did it mean the sarcasm? I'm thankful for you. I am thankful. That was a hurtful,
almost. I am thankful for you. I am this podcast. I am too. But, you know, what am I going to do?
Like, family, you know, well, I didn't say do that. I'm thankful for a lot of things to be honest.
Yeah. That big dicky urge, that big old dong. Yep. You know, I got good things going. Yeah.
Yeah. You're gainfully employed as they say. Rich, others would say.
You know, got a beautiful house, beautiful lady. The world's my oyster.
And I'll take a baker's dozen. What?
I agree. You look, I'm thankful too, you know. All's going well. I seem to have had a roof over my head
for telling what I consider to be almost substandard jokes for the last 12 years. You and America.
Yeah. I mean, we're doing all right. You know, a lot of people out there who don't have it so
lucky. That's something important to remember. They're, yeah. Yeah. And there's other people out there
that look lucky, that are unhappy. And those are the unluckiest folks of all. Right. Right.
You know what I mean? Let's start the movie. Now you're hitting way too close now.
Prophecy. You should be paused on the first frame so we can count off together and hit play.
One, two, three, play. Here comes that old Miramax logo. That old Miramax opening logo.
I rented this movie as a kid when it first came out. Yep. Based solely on the scene in the trailer,
it were Christopher Walken goes. I kill you. I kill you first born child or whatever. He says something
like, oh, he's a Southern black woman. I was thinking we'd be dueling impressions during this.
But now I realize I'm going to win the impression. We both did very well last episode doing impressions
of Sam. I was at Sam Waters. Sam Rockwell? No. I do have a Sam Rockwell. Oh, Sam Elliott.
Sam Elliott. Yeah. That was fun. But we were doing, you want to hear my Sam Rockwell?
Yeah. I've heard it. And you've done it on the podcast. But do we have? Yeah. It's not very good.
It's all right. This is, by the way, I went to film school. They're using an orange filter on this.
A light orange filter. Well, what's wrong with that? Nothing, Joe. I'm just, I'm pretending that
I'm telling people something they don't know. Oh, okay. Because the screen is pure orange. Oh, I
forgot Eric Stoltz was in this. Stoltz, the original Marty McFly. I forgot he was in this.
Yeah. I saw this too. My dad rented it probably thinking it was a religious movie and then discovering
it was a horror movie. And as I did with every movie, I saw when I was a kid, I had to sneak it after
he went to bed, which was like 3 a .m. So I would set my alarm for three, take a movie downstairs and
watch it with my ear press at the television. And that's why I watch this looking for nudity. And I,
I pretty vividly remember they're not being any nudity. Now, but you do have your Virginia Madsen in
here and never been attracted to her. I realized she is an attractive woman, but not my, for my money,
nobody, nobody hotter. Okay. Back, back in her prime. I mean, she's still beautiful woman, but I'm
talking, if you're talking prime, if you're talking prime vergetes, Adam Goldberg is in this also.
Is that the guy from Saving Private Ryan? Yeah. Days are confused. He's in this apparently.
It's got to be. He's got really one, one trick and he's been playing it for 30 years. Like
Rappaport. Where's he been? But I'm always happy to see him. Michael Rappaport. He's around. He's on
the Jim Gaffigan show, which I think is a pretty funny little sitcom. Amanda Plummer is in this. I didn't
come here. Vigo Mortison is in this. Vigo Mortz. Jesus. Who does he play the devil?
Or does Stoltz play the devil? Well, Stoltz just had glowing orange eyes, so they were black.
They were black eyes. Oh, but not from the orange filter. Not from being abused. Like his eyes
literally were black. I actually am wondering if after I made that joke, this might just be the movie
or maybe your TV needs to reset its colors. Because everything looks orange. Unless that was a choice,
maybe they'll be coming out on Halloween. No, because the menu screen for the Apple TV looks fine.
That's true, Joe. Sorry. I think that we're in some sort of a flashback sequence here. Of course,
once again, we've got the subtitles on. Haven't filed a fucking lick of it yet. No. Why do we put
these subtitles on? It's good to look down or sometimes you get a funny subtitle. Like when somebody
yells fuck, and it says fuck with an exclamation point. That's always kind of funny. That's kind of
funny. Casey Jones, but I'm glancing down now. I'm seeing sons of apostles. I'm seeing worthy priests.
These words, I wouldn't be able to read this fast if I wasn't doing a podcast. There's too many words.
This is the guy that played Casey Jones in TMNT. He was. Yeah, Casey Jones. He still shows up in
things. He's a solid little actor. Elias Coteis. This is name. That sounds like a demon's name.
Yeah. Or the name of an angel. Elias Coteis. That's an insane name. What is that? Is that Greek?
What is that Greek? I tell them it's all Greek to me, Joe. Hey, what does that expression mean?
It's all Greek to me. Yeah. It means like, you know, like it's like you're speaking a language
it already. I don't understand it. Yeah. I don't know why they picked on the Greeks for that. No.
I feel like you could do with any language that you don't speak. It's all Japanese to me. Yeah,
it's all Spanish to me. That makes more sense. It doesn't have the same ring to it. The Greeks
probably the most similar to English. This movie I'm looking up the movie online right now. It's
going to only have 43 % on run tomatoes. I think I honestly think standards were a little higher
than because movies that came out were good and no movies that come out now are good. So Vigo Mordensen
does play the devil. Gabriel Stoltz is just a demon. Well, no. Stoltz is Simon who's
clearly an angel because he had black eyes. Right. Adam Goldberg's character is named Jerry.
Assuming he's not a supernatural being in this film. Who do you play in this new horror movie about
the devil? Jerry. I'm playing Jerry. He's a car salesman with quite an evil streak. Yeah.
They all have one. All right. You ever tried to buy a used car? Folks.
This people are demons. As with a lady friend recently and we drove by
we drove by a meditation center. And she said, have you ever gone to that meditation center?
And I said, it's a center that you can go to to get centered.
And she said, I knew you were going to say that. And the disgusted dripping off of her
center. I knew you were going to say that. I mean, she was just disgusted by the joke.
And you thought, why don't I tell more people the joke? I thought you would like it because
it's a dumb joke. Oh, fuck you. I don't mean that as an insult. I just mean like, I feel like that
you're kind of joke. No, it's it's all right. I thought your joke was going to be, does it
look like I've been to a meditation center? Because you were probably seconds ago screaming in a car
or something. Yeah, she's going to say as I scream in a car. Yeah. Here's some other stuff under
the director's belt. Kotea says the same haircut as my aunt. Yeah. That is true.
Uh, this by the way, this movie is almost a complete copy of the Constantine story. Yeah.
Wow. If you're watching this, go ahead, pause rewind back. That was the worst actor in film history.
The guy that just came in. Why? He goes, Hey, you're not supposed to be out here.
And then Kotea holds up a cigarette and he goes, sorry. No, no, a badge. Badge, you go, sorry.
I didn't I'm terrible perform. We can't rewind is the people running the podcast. You can't rewind.
Well, that's something I've learned from working on a TV show as you're like, okay, that character has
one line and they'll go like, uh, miss. Where's my salad? And you're like, well, we don't need to audition
people for that part. Obviously anyone can do it. And you get an actor in and they'll be like,
miss. Like, they don't know how to say the words. It's like they've never been a human being before.
Well, it's there. It's there. There are no small parts, just small actors. That's true.
Now, Simon, now what we have so far here is Elliot Kazan. What's this fucking guy's name?
Elliot Kazan directed on the waterfront, which is Elias Koteas.
Eliza Schlesinger, who was playing the main cop in this. Right.
Elias Koteas, he was a priest. Yeah, Elliot. Right before her tragic.
He is, he was a priest. Now he's a cop and this angel played by Eric Stoltz named Simon has come
to them come to him. Now, I get the feeling that Simon is a bad angel. Yeah. And not a good angel.
And walking is sort of a bad guy, too, sort of. I mean, he plays the angel Gabriel, but he's
if I remember correctly, sort of like an anti hero in this, because the premise is that God started
to care more about the humans than the angels. So the angel started to go, fuck the humans.
Have you seen the other prophecies? I tried watching two once. Okay. Couldn't get through it.
Walk and stuck in there, though, for good three, four of them. Yeah, it really seems like he'll be
in almost any movie and he's such a great actor. I think he's just a guy that works. If he likes
the idea, he'll do it. Yeah. Other credits under our director's belt, Gregory Wyden, he wrote
back draft. Yeah, he did. He was also the engine lieutenant in that movie. Okay. Highlander, he wrote.
He wrote another movie called Weekend War. Not familiar. Another movie called Space Rangers. That was
a TV series. I'm not aware of that either, but CBS, all right. Running episode of Tales from
the Crypt, I love to hear that. Also created and wrote Rescue 77, which I'm assuming is some sort of
like fire person show, right? I don't know, Joe. I just want you to be here and present with me.
I just like giving the people little facts. Yes, it was a show about firefighters on the WB. Well,
he was a firefighter. How did you know that? Because I did my research prior to the film. Seconds
prior to the film. I was in the bathroom. I heard a drop in a douche. More like a trace. Sounded more
like an Ocho to me. Now, another angel is just landed who looks evil. Yeah, subtitles are saying
ominous music continues. Yeah. That's how long the ominous music subtitles been up there.
Horror movie, there's probably going to be ominous music throughout. I don't know that we need this.
What are your thoughts on the Stoltz, man? I have always enjoyed Stoltz. He reminds me a little bit of
your friend Jim who's coming in today. Yeah, they have a similar problem. Jim doesn't have long
stoltz. Have you seen the footage of Stoltz's Martin McFly? Yeah. I liked it. Yeah, I mean, it wasn't
it wasn't Michael J, but what is, you know, I wonder where he feels about like that being like
especially because back in the future, winds up in the news every two weeks because they went to
some date in the movie and it's like, Oh, no, it's that date that's happened 10 times in my life.
Right. They went to a lot of dates, folks. Right. It's not that exciting. They're time travelers and
fake. It's a fake movie. Anyway, Stoltz, like anytime it comes up, there'll be news articles,
magazine articles, every documentary goes into how Stoltz was bad in the role. Like he probably
doesn't like that. Probably hurts his feelings, folks. I mean, I'm hard pressed to believe he was
bad in the role. He just didn't have the charisma. Like when I watched it, you're like, no, that wouldn't
work. I mean, the guy who's the guy that wrote it with Bob Gale. Yeah. But like you shoot this thing,
you shoot for like three weeks, they fire you and then it goes on to become a three movie international
phenomenon. It's got to sting a little bit. Well, Bob Gale this last time came out and was like
because people were showing you say, like, well, you should release the Stoltz cut. We don't like to see
it. Yeah. Bob Gale came out this year and was like, I've seen the Stoltz cut. There's a reason it's
never been released. It's like, jeez, you'd have a little fact. It's so shit. I think he went as far as to
say, had it been released, it wouldn't we wouldn't be sitting here talking about the movie today.
That seems unnecessarily harsh. What I'm saying, like Stoltz doesn't deserve this.
I like Stoltz, you know, Pulp Fiction singles. He's a good bit part guy and I like him in a
pretty underrated indie movie called Mr. Jealousy. I've heard good things about Mr. Jealousy.
I love him in Pulp Fiction. He could be my favorite character in the entire movie. He's
just perfect in that drug dealer part. Yeah. What was the other one you just said?
Oh, singles, he's like the mind. He has a very small part. Oh, that's right. Oh, that's right.
And he's like a real dick. He's great in that. He's funny in that. He's a great character actor.
Where's he been? But maybe not a lead. Maybe not. He's still up to. You see Stoltz, I think he
directs TV now if I'm not mistaken. I think he did like a bunch of CSI type shows, but that could
be wrong. Not a bad gig. No, that's big money. Not a bad gig. Your boy Fred Savage went into
television directing for a while. He did. It's so smart. He's like, you actors waste days and days
standing around doing nothing. And he was like, hey, instead of whining about craft servers,
maybe I'll learn how to direct. And he's got a second career. Yeah. Smart. Very smart.
That he shows that beautiful face in the almost called it the Terminator. It's not called
the Terminator. Yeah, whatever that lawyer show is, it's very smart. It's very smart. The grinder.
Yeah. Yeah, like the grinder quite a bit. And I think Fred steals a show and he's a great
looking man to this day. Older than me looks significantly higher. Love seeing the Mrs.
Charlie day in that move in that show too. Mary Liz Bethellas, I think we've talked about the grinder.
I think we talked about it so long ago that you had seen an advance of it on a plane. Yes.
And I expressed my, I almost call it love for Mrs. Charlie day. Yeah. Find her to be just
a blast of sunshine. Okay. Take it easy. It's not love. It's, you know, I don't know where I'm never
married. I'm in this music continuing. You jumped off of that quick. Was it that weird?
I was just being funny. It wasn't weird at all. I used to hang out with her. She's great.
She's delightful. They're all good people. She seems like a girl. You could sidel up to in a bar
just throwing back for a while with probably, you know, seems like fun. I don't know. Now people
get married and have kids and then they don't throw drinks back in bars anymore. Yeah, I call that
turning on the pussy switch. I think most people turn on that switch or else their lives quickly
become a shambles. Not Jojo. Well, you're not married with kids. How can you, Virginia Madison first
appearance in the film? How can you not find this woman attractive? What's the matter with you? She
certainly is pretty. She's not my type. That's all I can say. Oh, either is this girl. Talk about a
girl that looks like you could throw them back. Mads. Mads looks like you could do. I mean,
you know what my dream drinking situation would be? Virginia, Madison, Michael, Madison. I'm right
in the middle. Are they bro and sis? Yeah. Oh, okay. I did which actually came out today. The Gilmore
guys podcast and it was a pulp fiction or a Tarantino themed episode. And I dressed up like anyone
would do who has no wardrobe. I dressed up like Michael Madison reservoir dogs because it's just
a black. You have to dress up as a character. It was a live show at UCB and they're like we're all
dressing up as Tarantino characters. So my buddy, Demi was Django. Neither buddy was the Asian schoolgirl
from Kill Bill. Why would you not go in in the Stolts costume? I don't I had a black robe that's not
gonna work. Go buy a blue bathrobe in three minutes. And then I thought maybe I'll be Tarantino. He
also had a bathrobe, but it was like a checkerboard robe. I had looked good. I had a I had a cup from
fast food place. I had a knife. I had a pocket full of ears that I cut out from magazines. It was a
cute little costume. All right. Fair enough. People enjoyed it. Fair enough. And I did my Mads
impression, which sounds exactly like Christopher Walken to tie it back to this movie. Go ahead. Are
you gonna walk all day little doggy? Are all you gonna bite? I'm getting douche chills. That's
such a bad impression. Are you gonna walk all day little doggy? Here's Mads. Are all you gonna bite?
I'll do it. I've never done it before, but I'll do it better. Ready?
You gonna bark all day little doggy? So it's like it's your voice. There's no difference. Look at my face,
though. Were you looking at my face? Were you giving me that? No, I mean, you were doing a
Christopher Walken. Yeah, pretty much. But everyone applauded. Here's my favorite impression to do
from Resardarx. Ready? Yep. He says, Dad, he's coming down. He's fucking pissed.
Chris Penn, I just re -watched that is so funny in that moment. He's tremendous. Don't you point
that gun at my dad? He's tremendous. Yeah. He's really funny. He's tremendous. When he's driving the car
and he's going, Larry, he's a wet back. He's a waiter. He's a friend of mine. He's just, I mean,
he's so fucking funny in that movie. That's a, that's a, it's a kind of a, well, not even suddenly
the dialogue in the movie is pretty racist. But it's, you know, in tune with the characters. Yeah.
That scene in particular is like five minutes of just kind of rough racism from those guys driving
around in the car. Look, that's me, everybody. That scene is nowhere, in my opinion, near the level of
the scene in the, in the office when he wrestles Michael Madsen. Yeah. Yeah. Gets into the amount of
black seeming that's been pumped up his ass hole. Yeah. That, that, that, that's, that gets a little
uncomfortable for me. It's wild. And for it to be your first movie, like, before, like, now I feel like
everybody knows Tarantino's a pretty good guy, I guess. People don't know that back then. It's like,
who wrote this thing? Yeah. But I think that was still a time when, like, especially in those gangster
movies, you could have racist characters. And it was like, for some reason, oh, yeah, good fellows,
they're all really racist. They're not all racist, good fellows. Only peshy.
But, well, I mean, no, no, Leo to two, Leo to drops an end bomb. You're right. I forgot about
that. Yeah. The heroes of the movie. But peshy's the one where it makes me really uncomfortable. Yeah.
When he's giving like that, like speech about like, you, you got to, the lady says that she finds,
Sammy Davis Jr. attractive. And he's going like, that's not, you got to watch what you say. Yeah.
And we'll just might take it the wrong way. It's very upsetting. I don't want to lean over you and
find out I'm kissing that king Cole. Yeah. And then Leo does laughing. And he's like, no, and
peshy's like, am I right? And he's like, no, you're right. You're right. Yeah. No, you're right.
Like, he doesn't really, he doesn't tell him like, hey, Joe.
Well, it seems like Joe, he's not playing himself. Kenny Banya. Yeah.
Kenny Banya. Yeah. Kenny Banya's in this. Wow. This is a star -studded affair. It's like,
you do one of those previews where it puts everybody's name up. And it's like Banya because no one
knows his name. I introduced my mom to curb your enthusiasm. Earlier, much earlier this year, she wasn't
very familiar with it. She fell in love with it. But I showed her, I started out with showing her the
Seinfeld reunion episodes. Yeah. In the table read episode, when it cuts to him, and he goes, it's
gold, Jerry. Gold. My mom lit up. Yeah. Sure. I just thought to myself, my God, that's how
transcended. Is that the word? That's the reach of Seinfeld. Oh, yeah. I was like, my almost 70 -year -old
mother just lit up at a character from Seinfeld that I would consider almost inside baseball. Yeah.
It's almost like an all -comedy joke. It is, really. You know, and like -
Gallery. Yeah. Yeah. And then that show also, it works on its own. It's super funny if you don't
have any interest in the entertainment industry. But also the whole gist of it is how Banya is a time -slot
hit because he's going up after Jerry and he's getting his laughs. Yeah. Because he's like, I killed
and he goes up there and rides the wave. Then he goes, he's like a shark who eats laughs. And George
goes, I don't see how a shark could eat laughs. Jerry's like, it's not the point. But anyway,
what they're commenting on was that any show that aired after Seinfeld, they'd be like, check out
this new comedy smash. The only reason anyone to watch this garbage show. I didn't even pick up that
that was a commentary. It is. And when you go back and rewatch them now, you're like, man, this show
really hates the entertainment industry. It holds up tremendously. Yeah. I just watched the pony
episode. I had the pony. I mean, it's his tirade at the table is so funny when he's trying to
explain how out of line this woman is. Yeah. And just the line, who leaves a country full of ponies
to come to a ponyless country? It's crazy. Yeah. It's also like almost everything that happens now
in certainly alt comedy, but kind of comedy in general. If you really want to point to things,
almost every TV show, every standup, everything, you're like, that's Seinfeld. Sure. You know,
they'll take a nugget from Seinfeld and take it in their own direction. But the influence goes
beyond pretty much anything else. Certainly in my generation. Any time anybody's doing a bid or
talking in a voice or what you're like, you are doing Seinfeld. I think all of my favorite shows
comedy -wise that have existed after Seinfeld are all undoubtedly and probably would be admittedly
heavily influenced by Seinfeld. Thousand percent. You know, I love it's always sunny. Clearly big Seinfeld
influence on that. Yeah, of course. Curb, obviously. You know, I'm trying to think what other shows I
really love. Even Peep Show, which I'm really, I just got, I started getting into Peep Show hardcore.
I can't stop. They're really funny. They're great. They're influenced by Seinfeld for sure.
Rest of development. Pretty much everything. Yep. How great is Peep Show, man. Peep Show is really,
really funny. Those guys are really good. Yeah, I watched it obsessively. And then I was like,
what else did these guys do? And it's like a couple comedy specials and that's about it.
No, they had a very popular sketch show called the Mitchell and Webb look. Okay, I thought those
were like one -off. No, they had a radio thing called the Mitchell and Webb sound that was a comedy
radio thing. And then it became the Mitchell and Webb look because they turned into a TV show. And
then there was also another thing. They've done a couple movies together. They've done a lot
together. They've really gotten the, that's walking by the way. It looks like a young, a young old
Pacino. Yeah. He looks kind of like a beautiful woman when he came in the window door here. He
does look good. This is, this is walking sexy age. This is getting into your beautiful Gaysha.
How much Coke do you think this guy has done over the years? Walking, I mean, he could also be
a guy who's never done Coke. He does have that thing. You never know with these people. He's either
never done it or done it a billion times. How much do you think Pacino's done over the years?
There's no way Pacino hasn't done it. Chino's doing Coke now. And his wife's like,
Al, we got to put the turkey in the oven. And he's like, no, I'll be right out, baby. I'll be
right out. I just got to finish washing my hands every fucking year. I got to put this turkey in an oven.
Can I just have a good fucking time? You know, you're supposed to cook. You're the woman.
I don't know why you have to paint him as a sexist. He's a sexist. Let's be honest. How was he a
sexist? I assume with these people, we're just assumed Christopher Walkins of Coke at it.
Now we give him the benefit of the doubt. I'll put my money on Pacino. But you know, Danny Collins
carries. I told him this last week. I'm going to watch it this week. I believe that in real life,
he carries a cross filled with cocaine around his neck. I saw him once in New York. I almost walked
into him because I came around a corner and he was coming down the other side. I literally almost
walked into him for two reasons. We were just in our each other's paths. But he also was so focused
on the ground. Right. Like he was walking and talking and he just wasn't looking forward. He was
looking down as he was talking. Yeah. Anyway. Well, Pacino in New York, he's probably getting stopped
800 times a block. But here's the thing. I bet you never get stopped in New York. New York's
got a big stop people terrible. But here's the thing. I remember this, the cab went the wrong direction
that I was in and this wrong turn that he made cost me like it just fucked the whole trip. It was like
this deadlock traffic to the point where I had to get out and walk because it would be literally
three times faster. Right. And I was so mad because it was like 100 degrees in New York. It was so hot
out. And I was so pissed that this guy made the wrong turn. And now I had to walk 10 blocks in this
heat and arrive to your thing sweaty. I walk around the corner almost run directly into Pacino who's
wearing not just long pants and a like dress shirt but down dress shirt. A wool sport coat. Yeah.
That sounds right. And a bandana tied around his head. That's not even more right. And I was just like
does this guy even look at what the fuck like it was crazy to me. Yeah. I think I mean, well obviously
he's a little nutty. This is disgusting. Yeah. Whatever scene we're in now, there's food all over the
floor. By the way, every time we're in Jerry's house. Goldberg can do better, man. Here comes Jerry.
I got a little walk in story. I used to work at Conan, O 'Brien in New York when he was on at 12,
30 on NBC. And I was the desk page. So I would have to kind of bring up the guests from the street.
Make sure they were comfortable getting what they needed. So walkin comes up and the musical guest
was Wilcoe. And Wilcoe was like, hey, man, is there any chance we can say, hey, Christopher
walkin? Sometimes like even the actors and beef, you know, like I want to meet so and so.
Right. I was like, yeah, I said I think real quick. And I'm like, but we got to do in these situations
to just gauge really quick if he's into it or not. Because you know, I can't be responsible if
and they're like, yeah, no, we got it. We got. So it's walking in his wife and he comes out of his
dressing room in a complete tuxedo. Right. And his wife, George Ann walkin, who's a huge casting
director, cast the pranos and all kinds of shit. She's trying to tie his bow tie in the hallway.
And the Wilcoe guys come up. And he goes, hey, excuse my impression. You guys the band?
Right. And they go, yeah, he goes, I didn't get a chance to hear you. Are you a good band?
Yeah, we like to think we're pretty good. He goes, that's important. Confidence is very important.
And like it was a dream for everyone involved. It was like, so then she was like, Chris, we got to
go and he's like, where are we going again? He's in a tuxedo. She goes, Chris, I told you we're going
to this whatever charity thing. And he goes, see, Phil is when you get married, you got to do what
he said. You don't get a say. She puts a bow tie on me. Now I got to go to an event. I got no say.
And they're like, yeah, we know we're married or whatever. And then he goes, let me ask you one question
before I head out, fellas. Which one of you here is the drummer? The drummer raises hand. And he goes,
now I have often heard it said that the drummer in a band gets the girls. And they just stare at him.
And he goes, I'm asking you, is this true? They go, the drummer laughs. He's like, that's not really
been my experience, Christopher. And they all kind of laugh. And he keeps, doesn't smile. The band is
laughing. And he stares at the drummer with his hand out, pointed at him. And he goes, no, it is
true. I've always heard that the drummer gets the girls. And he goes, that's probably true of a lot of
bands. He's like, maybe Ringo got a lot of girls, but you know, it hasn't been my case. And he goes,
no, it is. I've always heard people say in bands. I got friends in bands that the drummer is the one
who gets the girls. And he finally, the drummer was like, yeah, you know, I guess it's true.
I, the drummers do get the girls. And he goes, see, that's what I'm saying. And then he's like,
it's nice meeting you, fellas. Shake their hands, get to an elevator with his wife. I was like, that was
the greatest thing I've ever seen. And all that scene was missing was Kevin Spacey going. And just like
that, it was gone. Yeah, yeah. For like the end of usual suspect. Right. And that's a perfect story.
He was so weird, but like very delightful. He could kind of hang in conversation.
Did I tell you when I was on Carson daily and Jeff Goldblum was the guest?
No. And I wanted to meet Jeff Goldblum so bad because the fly is one of my favorite horror movies ever.
And I just love Jeff Goldblum. But it was my first TV spot I ever did. I had nowhere near
the golf to ask if I could meet this guy. Right. And I was standing in the hallway.
Plus, I mean, you're already flustered because you're getting to meet Carson daily.
Yeah. Yeah. I was all wound up about that. And I was very scared.
First TV, I was beyond nervous. Right.
Anyway, I'm in the hallway pacing and my manager goes, don't look now. Here comes your hero.
I look up. Goldblum is walking toward me with his entourage. Yeah. He passes me. I don't meet him.
This is all I hear as he passes me.
It's a Western, but it's a tolerable Western. That's all I heard.
And I was like, that was better than meeting Jeff Goldblum.
What's he talking about? I guess he was in Silverado.
I guess he could have been talking about movie he wasn't in.
I think he was just talking. I was just talking about a movie of some kind.
Yeah, it was the end of the world.
Yeah. Do you see him on Conan when he like, oh, sure.
And Letterman will bring his wife out. He'll be like, my beautiful wife.
She can do a handstand. Yeah. Honey, honey, come out here and do a handstand.
Yeah. That's great. It's really weird.
I've seen him many times at like any time I've gone to a health food store like four times in my life.
He's been in there with a new like very hot 21 year old yoga girl.
So I guess he's single now, but no, he's married now.
Oh, he just had a kid. Well, I hope I didn't blow something up there for him.
No, this was in the past. This was years ago.
I did hear that years ago before he settled down, he was quite,
oh, sure, quite the man about town. God bless him.
Did he hook up with like Nicole Richie?
I think so. I think the tabloids.
He's like, you know, at least 55 I think still looks great.
He plays jazz up at that rock well up on Vermont, which I know.
I want to go, but I just want to go to meet Jeff Goldblum.
And I know he probably doesn't appreciate that.
Like he, you know, he probably just wants to go play music.
He's an amazing piano player.
I assume he's got great banter.
I mean, I never need to go see anyone play jazz as long as I live.
Must have written Miles Davis sitting the face of an entire genre of
beautiful American music.
I mean, look, I respect that it's the notes that you don't play that are important.
Here we go.
Speaking of Carson daily, when my parents came to New York and my sister,
I got them all tickets to Conan in like front row.
I was working there. It was very easy.
I was like, can you get in the front row with them?
So they're going in and they're like, who are the guests going to be?
And I was like, I don't know.
And the night before the guests had been,
I think it was Bruce Willis and the band was you two or something like that.
It was like the hugeest night of Conan's life.
Actually, I think it was Springsteen looking back.
Wow.
So my parents are like, who are the guests going to be?
This is so exciting.
We're going to be so close.
Here were the guests.
Carson daily, who came down one flight of stairs to be a guest on the show.
He's a great guy.
He's a very nice guy.
Carson daily, a professional surfer was the second guest.
And the third, the band was D12.
Well, that's cool.
Eminem's, not for your parents.
Was Eminem there?
No, Eminem was not there.
Oh, G12.
D12 parentheses.
Not featuring Eminem.
It was Sans Eminem.
Yeah, oh boy.
Wow.
All right.
Not that my parents would have been like,
ooh, Eminem.
I'm actually jealous that your parents got to see proof before he died.
And I never got to see proof.
I'm a big D12 fan.
I'm not.
And I know I love rap.
But I don't know anything about proof to be honest with you.
He's the guy that got killed.
It was in D12.
He was like Eminem.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
But I would have very much like to have seen him before he passed.
Yeah, absolutely RIP.
He was a great rapper.
I just realized in this moment, as usual,
the half fast fashion in which we're watching this movie,
Eric Stoltz is a good guy.
I think he's a good demon, let's say.
He's an angel.
No, he's an angel.
They're all angels.
There's no demons in this except the devil.
Yeah.
But I just realized he's a good guy.
And I think he teams up with Virginia Madsen.
Okay, because she's the skeptic at first when she meets him.
Why did that?
How did this girl get this role?
What is going on with the pants?
It's a child in 1990.
And she's got like,
I've never seen a child in like full mom jeans,
like belted under the where the tits would be.
He's got to put like, he puts like his soul in her or something.
Okay, does she start talking like him?
I don't just think I don't remember.
No, I just forget.
He's got to or he takes her soul.
Is he going to kiss this girl?
Well, that's weird.
He's not kissing her.
He's just like sucking her soul out.
But wouldn't that be a weird scene to shoot?
Yeah, it would be weird.
I would say gang.
How about you, we maybe shoot this as a reverse?
Yeah, it's any other way than me passionately kissing a young girl.
Yeah.
That was weird.
I'm upset now.
Now she's puking like it feels a little molesting.
Speaking of molesting, as we always have to do in these episodes,
I just saw spotlight the new film with Michael Keaton and Mark Ruffalo
about the investigation into the Boston Catholic Church sex scandal.
They're fantastic movie.
How's my boy Keaton in it?
Keaton has never been anything but amazing.
How's my boy Roof?
Roofalo is great and everybody's raving about him,
but he was better in Foxcatcher and I don't know why people kind of
slept on that performance.
He's tremendous.
He was amazing.
When I wasn't a huge fan of that film,
but I thought all three of them did a really nice job in that movie.
I agree and I was a fan.
I like creepy shit like that.
I like creepy human.
Foxcatcher was another black mass for me.
It was tremendous performances.
It was well done, but I just kind of found it a little,
a little uneventful or something.
I completely get what you're saying.
And they do have a similar tone.
They both have that icy blue filter over them the whole time.
Yeah, exactly.
That just makes you feel fucking hopeless.
So all right, I got to go see that.
I was excited to see there was a new Keaton movie out.
They're going to send spotlight as a screener.
It'll probably be up for best picture.
It's a great, great movie.
Now who plays, do any people that we know play priests?
They don't.
It's not like that.
Really?
There's a couple, there's a side priest here
and there that they talk to.
But it's really mostly about the journalism aspect.
I love the one with, I love the one with what's it called?
What was that one?
It was called like our fathers or something,
but it was, it was the made for HBO one about that scandal.
But you had, you had Brian Denny, he is a priest.
Yeah, that was a good flick.
You had Christopher Plummer as the,
the bishops that always create me move everything around
and hit everything.
Yes.
You had, what's the lady from the exorcist?
Ellen Burstin.
Ellen Burstin is the mom whose kids went through it.
I think Ted Danson's in it.
Danson is in it.
Yeah, that's a great movie.
Fucking great flick, man.
Yeah.
It's, I mean, really, if you're going to tackle that subject,
the movie better be pretty good.
Otherwise, it's going to feel pretty exploitative and gross.
Yeah, it was really good.
And then I also saw Brooklyn,
which I think will be another awards contender.
And that is my favorite movie currently of the year.
Which Brooklyn?
Brooklyn is a very simple movie.
Nick Hornby wrote the script.
I got a wrote high fidelity.
It's 50s Irish Catholic girl moved to New York from Ireland.
Falls in love with this Italian dude.
And then she's got to go back to Ireland.
And she's kind of trapped between the two places.
I know that I'm not selling this well.
But it's a...
So far it sounds like the most boring movie I've ever heard.
Sure.
And maybe you wouldn't be into it.
I don't know.
I really fucking loved it.
I think you would find it.
The star is Siorci Ronan.
The girl who played Hannah.
Okay.
Which is an awesome action movie.
Yeah, I like that girl.
And she's great.
There's nobody else really in it.
I'm not selling it well.
Is this a comedy or drama?
As I started to tell you the plot,
I was like, I'm spoiling something.
So I'm not going to say it.
Is this a comedy or drama?
It's a drama.
A couple funny moments.
It's like a romance to be honest.
Which is not generally my bag.
But it's really good.
But you left out a big plot point.
Like she's actually a cat demon or something like that.
She...
You know she's a cat demon from the first scene.
Right.
But there's more to it than that.
Okay.
Very good.
And I thought the tagline should have said
a young Irish immigrant cat demon.
But they left it out.
I guess they didn't want to.
Right.
Or at least...
Because, you know,
order doesn't do well at the Oscars.
At least young Irish anime
grant parentheses cat demon and parentheses.
Do it like that.
You don't see enough parentheses in tag lines.
No, you don't.
Get out.
I think our podcast description has a parentheses or two.
There's one...
You and I kind of wrote the podcast description in a rush
and we wrote it together.
There's one wording in it that I hate
and I want to change it if we can.
But I think it's too late.
What is it?
I don't mind I have to look at it.
I get really weird about...
You know what the tagline?
Like a word of shit.
You know what the tagline for that green inferno
Eli Roth movie should have been?
No, tell me.
Welcome to the pain forest.
That's what it should have been.
Yeah, that would not have...
It would have been even less of a hit
with the tagline.
Welcome to the pain.
Either that or nobody saving you in this rainforest.
Uh -huh.
Or how about this?
Some rainforest shouldn't be saved.
There you go.
That's what I was trying to do.
That's much better.
What tag would you give black mass?
Black...
What tagline?
Yeah?
I don't have something off the bat.
And I was fascinated by what Walker was doing.
Yeah, walking right now is in a grave and he's growling
and saying he loves this corpse he's standing on.
He said he's a beautiful, mysterious monkey
and now he's sniffing the corpse.
Yeah.
That was probably an improv line if I had to guess.
Hey, yeah, I want to do something here about a monkey if I could.
Oh, this is the guy.
They're in the grave of the guy.
Stolts already took this guy's soul.
Okay.
You can take a soul.
I guess.
Walking his out of control.
By the way, I love that the angels are sent down dressed as reservoir dogs.
Well, that's because this came out like right around that time.
You know, that's why plumbers in it.
That's why stolts is in it.
Miramax is like let's get anything to do with Pulp Fix.
He looks exactly like
Travolta and Pulp Fix on the back.
He's got the same hair.
This was a good time for these for these art house flicks man.
A lot of really cool movies came out at this time.
My favorite that I so infrequently hear anybody talk about was
things to do in Denver when you're dead.
Which I was liked it.
I really like that movie.
It's a good movie.
It was clearly an attempt at making a Tarantino -esque thing.
But I love Andy Garcia.
He never disappoints me.
I love treat Williams.
I love that he plays a guy that eats shit in the movie.
Literally.
Yeah.
And walking is in that movie.
Yes, he is.
Walking is also in Pulp Fix.
Which people.
Walking is in that movie.
And he accuses Andy Garcia's character of being gay
because he does like charity stuff.
And Andy Garcia says, I'm sorry.
How does that make me homosexual?
Christopher Walkins line is,
it's always what happens.
One day you save in the rainforest.
Next day you chuck and cock.
He's Irish in it.
No, it's just my shitty walking impression.
Oh my god.
That was just a straight -up walking.
I wasn't trying that hard.
I just remember he says chug and cock.
I had an accent or something.
That was crazy, John.
Sorry.
Maybe he was chug and cock.
He's obsessed with monkeys.
Well, he calls humans talking monkeys.
Oh, okay.
Got you.
That's his problem.
He's like, he's trying to kill off the human race
because he's like, they're...
He's saying the only talks about monkeys.
When I'm looking at these lines of dialogue.
Walkin was saying the angels were second to God.
Right?
And they did all God's work and everything.
And then the humans took God's place.
Okay.
And walkin is like, fuck this.
I was the main angel.
I was gay, bro.
I impregnated Mary for Christ's six.
Oh, shut up.
You know, but I guess that doesn't mean he boned Mary.
No, it was immaculate conception, but gay...
Well, I'm sorry, he didn't impregnate me.
He was the angel that came to Mary and said,
you're with child.
Okay.
He gave her the bad news.
You're prego and you're out of wedlock.
Yeah.
Good luck not gettin' stoned in this town.
You do the hunger game shit?
You fuck with that?
No.
I have now seen three.
The fourth one just came out and I'm like,
I was so bored, so amazingly bored by the other three,
and now I'm going to go see the fourth,
because I have to finish this.
Well, apparently I couldn't care less how it ends.
I don't remember the other ones.
The ending, you won't believe your eyes,
or so it's one of those things.
I don't believe my eyes.
The only reason I liked the last one is because
it seemed more Hoffman's last stand.
How was he, man?
He's great.
And Julianne Moore is solid in it.
But it's just like, man, it's boring.
All that young adult shit is so boring to me.
Except Terry Potter.
Oh wait, I know what just happened.
Sorry, I just realized something happening in the movie.
Stoltz wasn't taking that girl's soul.
He was hiding the soul of that general in her, gotcha.
So Gabriel can't find it.
So that's a very important soul for some reason.
I look at this.
Goldberg plays his right hand man.
He also was doing a walk -in impression with walk -in,
which is Balsey.
I don't say this with any disrespect.
I'm a tremendous fan of the actor.
But I saw Pacino and Bobby Canavale
in Glingreg, Leross in New York.
And Bobby Canavale was playing Roma.
And he was almost doing a Pacino.
As Roma impression, two Pacino.
Sure, it was.
It was very strange.
What was this?
Because I saw it with Alan Alda.
I was the second, it was the revival after that revival.
Oh, okay, I didn't know that.
I saw it twice.
I saw it once with Pete Holmes.
Yeah.
And then I saw it.
And then my friend bought me tickets for Christmas.
And I was like, I already saw this,
but I'll gladly see it again.
Was Pacino playing Shelley the machine, Lameen?
Yeah, yeah.
Everybody was great in it.
He was good in that.
He was great.
He was fucking great.
John C. McGinley played Loss.
I don't think I'd want to see anyone other
than Lameen play that part.
Even more than Pacino is Roma.
Lameen to me is as good as you're going to get.
And Alda did an okay job,
but you're not touching what Lameen did with the bar.
It was hard for me to see anybody
in any of the other roles outside of that movie.
Sure.
Because I was introduced to it from the movie.
And that movie, to me, is the most perfect cast.
It's 100 % flawless casting to me.
Yeah.
Which is hard to say about movies.
So it's hard for me to see anybody in any role,
but it was good because it was a very different approach.
They really played up the comedy in it.
Right.
Which was interesting.
Like the McGinley scene
with where it's Moss and
Aaron Al.
Yes.
That scene was like hysterically funny
in their rendition of the play.
Whereas in the movie,
you're just like, you just feel so fucking bad for Alan.
And Alda, you're like, this guy's going on a hustle.
Oh, Alan Arkin, excuse me.
Can you do an Alan Arkin impression?
I've never tried it, but I will.
What are you talking about?
Wait, it's not what I told you to do.
I'll read the next line as Alan Alda.
I guess I could have done the best one I can do it.
Right now, it just says chanting in parentheses.
I like how anytime a thing in a different language happens,
they just write chanting.
Yeah, put the fucking words up.
I just realized my Alan Arkin is the same as my Christopher Lloyd,
so it's probably not a very good impression.
Marty!
Great Scott.
Yeah.
Did you see when they appeared on Kimmel?
No.
Oh, it was so great, man.
Yeah, we'll find it online or whatever.
It is online.
But they did a thing on Kimmel,
where it was the day from back to the future, too.
I remember.
And the time machine comes into the studio
during the monologue and Marty and fucking dock it up.
Yeah, it's cool.
It was great.
It lit me up.
I've never seen and I have a couple friends
who have written or are writing for Kimmel.
I've never seen Jimmy Kimmel.
It's pretty good.
I don't watch late night like I used to.
When Conan went off, I was like, I can't do it anymore.
I don't really like watching any late night,
but I mean, I think Kimmel does a nice job.
Yeah.
He did a 100 % Star Wars episode the other night.
Okay.
And he had Carrie Fish.
Sure.
He had Harry Ford.
Do you already have your Star Wars tickets?
Of course I do.
Seeing it first screening on the East Coast.
Opening night.
There's, yeah, I'm really hoping
and it is a strong possibility
that there's going to be advanced Oscar screenings
and we might get in a little earlier.
I don't think there is because I just read a thing
about the premiere.
Yeah.
And they said people are having trouble
getting into the premiere.
Right.
Like they're like, it's like so closed off
to just people that were like involved with the movie.
Like nobody can bring family.
There's people like, you know, Andy Dick
is like, uh, I'm Andy Dick
like at the gate.
Yeah.
Like that might work sometimes, Andy.
It, uh, it, uh, what's it called?
It broke the, uh, shattered the presale box office record.
It's made $50 million in presales already.
Sure it would.
I can't wait.
I bet my friend Keith Robinson, $500
it would outgrow the Avengers 2.
It will.
It absolutely will.
And he swore to me there was no way
it held.
It was going to happen.
There's actually a 100 % chance
it will happen.
Yes.
Easiest 500 % record.
Can I bet him too?
He's regretting it now.
He's been calling me and being like,
God damn it.
I mean, I was, I'm a fucking idiot.
The other night I went and saw
Uncabaret, which is like a storytelling show.
My boss did it.
And, uh, Eddie Pepitone, who makes me like,
scream laugh.
I think it's like one of the funniest people in life.
He did our show the other night and he told a joke
that's so funny.
I keep saying it out loud to myself.
What was it?
Maybe I heard it.
He goes, my grandmother,
sadly just died.
She was murdered by two men I owed money to.
They needed a name.
He didn't do that.
Like, he is the funniest man alive to me.
I mean, you know, he's up there.
I just, I'm like helpless laughing when he does his shit,
when he's screaming about anything.
But he had, he did this bit.
I'll come back around.
Because Andy Dick did the show too, which is my point.
But, uh,
Pepitone did this thing where it's a little one
of the funny people in Los Angeles,
but he was talking about how he uses ways here.
Maybe like this app,
I fire up ways the other day.
I'm stuck on the 405.
I've been sitting there for three hours
in traffic, not moving.
I get on ways.
Help me out ways, I say.
And ways says,
buy a gun and shoot your way up to the getting museum.
Like the audience was like breaking glasses.
They were laughing.
And then his other deal was,
this guy came up ahead of time and did a beautiful song
with no jokes about his sister being a multiple schizophrenic.
Right.
And because some of the show is serious.
And it was like people in the audience were kind of crying.
Sure, sure.
I was not, but whatever.
So, Pepitone gets up and he goes,
I didn't know it was this kind of that elegant night.
He goes, I guess I could make up a song about my brother.
Here we go.
A one and a two.
He goes, he's addicted to porn.
He eats terrible foods and weighs 400 pounds.
Heavy foods and jacking off is all he does.
He's 56 years old.
I was like, like tears were splashing out of my eyes.
I was laughing so hard.
So funny.
Just a funny looking dude.
Oh my god.
I love it.
I hope you hear this, Eddie Pepitone.
Why don't I ever tell him?
Why don't I walk up and say you were hilarious?
Oh, I should have.
One of the greatest, I swear I'm not saying this
to compliment myself in any way.
But we're talking about Eddie Pepitone.
And it was literally one of the greatest moments of her
at his comedian.
I finally met him in person.
Last year at the Montreal Comedy Festival, I'd never met him.
And I saw him in the lobby at this party and I walked up to him.
I was like, Eddie, I just want to say hi.
We've never actually met and I go, I'm Joe DeRosa
and he goes, Joe, hey man.
Yeah, I dig you, dude.
I dig your stuff.
And I was like, thank you, man.
That's a huge fucking compliment.
That's very nice.
I was like, I think you're just the fucking greatest.
You're so funny, man.
Yeah.
And then he did our show and we had a great time.
He's done the show I write for twice in two different roles
because he's just like, I don't know why he does get more
like little supporting parts as like scuzzballs because he kills it.
He played an underground subway suit salesman in an episode that I wrote
where he was like selling suits underground.
He was like, he had this bill where he talked about the different colors of the suits
and he was like, this one's a must -aid.
It's a beautiful must -aid.
It's really, really funny.
I think the whole scene was cut.
Andy Dick gets up.
Oh, yeah.
He's like, I only got a couple minutes to talk.
Oh, gross.
He's repealed off faces on screen.
The guy that played Casey Jones.
What's his name?
Ezra Miller?
Better than Ezra Miller.
Okay.
He opened a box full of faces.
Yeah.
This guy collect.
And it seems oddly unfazed by it.
So Andy Dick gets up and he's sober, but he's like,
he said he lived in a facility and it was kind of sad.
And he seemed a little shaky.
He's living in a facility.
That's what he said.
Like, what kind?
Like a rehab?
I don't know.
I didn't ask him because he was giving a performance.
But then he said, he was talking about how he dated a girl for a year
and he kept reaching between her legs to jack her dick off
and then realizing she didn't have a dick
because he was trying to go straight for a year.
And we were like, okay, boy.
Then he goes, I just got back from Ben Stiller's 50th birthday party.
He's like, you know, I turned down the Will Ferrell role in Zoolander.
And we were all like, okay.
So then the host goes, why did you turn that down?
He goes, because I thought I didn't want to live in Ben's shadow anymore.
He's like, now I would literally eat shit out of Ben Stiller's asshole
to get one line in a movie of this.
We were all like, okay, this is getting a little dark.
And then he goes, I also turned down a fuck.
It was some huge role in a movie that he probably wouldn't have been as good in.
But, you know, he's just talking about all these big roles.
He turned down because he thought he was too good for them
and now he can't get any roles.
And then he said he got blacklisted by Howard Stern
and somebody was like, why did you get blacklisted by Stern?
He goes, I called him on the air.
I called him a hook -nosed money -grubbing Jew.
The audience was silent.
It was like a couple audible gas.
And he goes, I know, you don't call people hook -nosed money -grubbing Jews.
Isn't he Jewish, though?
I think.
I also find it hard to believe that Stern would ban him for that.
I feel like Stern is like a...
Well, Andy Dick is clearly the type of person who thinks everyone hates him.
You could tell him even from five minutes.
He's like, he hates me, he won't talk to me.
My friend was telling me he did the show a few weeks back with Andy Dick
and he goes, it was Rosanne was on the bill as well.
I'm on the show.
And Andy, that's great.
I wish she didn't, I wish that she doesn't talk like that anymore.
I wish she still talked like that.
I love Rosanne.
I love her.
Good.
No, Andy Dick's like, boy, this is a big 90s.
Like for people in the 90s,
he's like, remember the 90s Rosanne when you and me were on top?
And Rosanne was like, we at the crowd laughed for like 25 minutes.
Is we, Andy?
I do love Andy Dick on news radio also, man.
I love him and everything I've ever seen.
And his get show was hilarious on him too.
I'm upset that he's fallen on such hard times.
I know he seemed okay.
He's a self -destructive guy, but for sure.
You know, but he also did the show I worked for and he was sober,
but he was like three hours late.
And we're like, come on, man.
Yeah.
We had Lindsey Lohan on the show, same deal.
It's like, you can't just show up three, four hours late.
This like, and then act like you're a victim.
Patty, what do you audition the dirt over here?
I mean, you're like Perez Hilton right now.
Yeah, this is like you're us weekly rant last week
about Matt Damon's divorce rumors swirling.
Good lord, feeding a kid a mint now.
There's a lot of action with children's models in this film.
I'm not loving.
Also on the bill, Julius Sweeney played its pat,
the character that ruined my childhood.
Why?
Because my name is Pat.
Oh.
So I was like, that things are going okay for me in school.
I've also had a hard time despite the beer tip
telling if you're a man or a woman.
Well, it's why I grew the beard.
It doesn't help.
Yeah, but they all stop calling me at Brenda Walsh,
which they were calling me at this time,
and then switched to call me.
It's Pat, is he a bluer?
Is Brenda Walsh from 90210?
Yeah.
And I would be like, I've never seen it.
So I don't know what you're making fun of it.
Is it's a girl's name?
That is rough stuff.
Brenda Walsh, that's a tough one.
And it's not just that they were calling you Brenda Walsh
because it's a girl.
It's almost like they were calling you like a saucy bitch.
Yeah, exactly, which that hurts.
Well, I'm sure a comedian, Brendan Walsh,
had to deal with that in school as well.
I haven't talked to him about it.
That's a great point.
I never asked Brendan that.
I like Brendan. He's a good guy.
I love Brendan.
One of the funniest guys I know, you know,
can't tell if when he's speaking to me
if it's real or serious ever.
He plays more pranks than I've ever met.
Yeah, I'm not a real prank guy.
I'm also sarcastic all the time,
but whenever anyone talks to me with sarcasm,
I just believe it, which is an annoying quality of mine.
He started tweeting me one day with a profile he made
for a guy we both know who wasn't on Twitter.
And he made a profile of this guy
and tweets people as this guy.
And he's a comedian or he's just a friend of yours.
He's a comedian and I know him through comedy.
Okay, we're friendly.
I don't know him very well, but
but I'm in, I'm playing the city where this guy lives.
Brendan starts tweeting at me, meet me at the mall.
Okay, meet me at the mall.
I go to the fucking mall.
I'm texting the guy like, where the hell are you?
I'm here.
He's like, no, no, no, no, that, I didn't tweet you.
That was Brendan, whilst tweeting you.
Pretending to be me.
Now you're up at the mall.
Oh, yeah, I mean, I didn't care.
I was going to go to the mall either way.
He'd buy a pair of slacks and you'd go home.
But he would also send messages as this guy to people on Twitter
and people like, hey, man,
I had a really weird dream about you last night.
Still shaking up.
Please call me as soon as you can.
Just odd messages.
This girl's going to have black eyes when her head raises.
There's no way.
There's no way she's not going to have black eyes when she looks up.
She's looking at the ground.
He was going to punch her in the fence.
No, that's, I already made that joke earlier.
But if you want to steal my stuff,
I didn't hear you.
How did it not come on?
Why do you have her look down at the ground?
They're blackish.
No, but she was speaking so creepily
while staring at the ground for three minutes
that she looks up in her eyes.
Aren't black?
I think they're blackish.
They're ABC's breakout hit family succumbed blackish.
She should have looked up with black eyes and went,
like that.
All right.
So she's got this soul in her of,
I guess the soul that stolt's put in her is him,
is instructing them now how to defeat this
threat of angels.
It's a weird plot, man.
Terry.
It's a little hairy, but that madson.
Good lord.
This independent movie, boom, and the 90s,
like there were as many independent movies,
all of them good, pretty much all of them good,
as there were blockbusters.
Because of like, kind of because of Tarantino.
Yeah, it's a shame because all the,
all the indie companies now got bought up by the majors.
And they still, they'll do like their signature films
with those smaller companies, but it's still a major.
I saw a talk after Spotlight.
A movie and the cast is Michael Keaton,
Mark Ruffalo, Rachel McCatams,
Lee F. Schreiber, John Slattery.
It goes on and on and on.
And they said three different times
the funding completely fell apart
with that cast in place.
And they couldn't get the movie men.
Whose dick do you got to suck these days?
It's ridiculous.
Michael Keaton coming off a best actor win.
Can't get the movie men.
He didn't win best actor for Birdman.
No, he didn't win the Oscar.
Yeah, he didn't win.
I'm almost positive he didn't.
He absolutely didn't because there was that clip
of him putting his speech back in his pocket
that was going around the internet.
So who won?
I'll tell you.
I used to know that I used to know every
Oscar winner from 1929
to whenever I was like 16
and then my memory started going.
It's nothing to brag about.
No, I was honestly, I'm ashamed saying it.
I was glad I don't remember it.
Winners.
He won the Golden Globe or something.
He won something.
I saw him give a speech.
Well, he might have, yeah, sure.
He might have won the
Matthew McConaughey.
For fucking Dallas Buyers Club.
Yeah, I have a tremendous performance, man.
All right.
Lido bet one best supporting actor.
That was just last year Dallas Buyers Club.
Yeah, no.
Well, I googled Oscar winner's 2014.
Another picture of Ellen.
He won in 2015.
I think we didn't have the 2015 yet.
Did we?
Oh, wait, yeah, you're right.
I guess, yeah, I feel like I watched Dallas Buyers Club
a long time ago.
You're right.
I'm thinking the 2015s are taking place sometime
before the Christmas.
It is confusing.
They're doing the year after.
Neil Patrick Harris hosted last year.
That was the worst it's ever been.
Best picture, Birdman.
You sub, me and you sub Birdman, right?
Yeah, together.
Hold on, trying to find it.
There we go.
Winners and nominees.
Folks, I really think I'm right here.
This is exciting.
You're 100 % wrong.
I mean, I bet you money on it.
Eddie Redmayne.
For oh shit.
Yeah, I lost my pool because of Eddie Redmayne.
Undeserved Redmayne.
No, that kid.
I mean, he came in swinging.
Movie was born.
Well, everyone's fucking everybody in them.
I go to see a Stephen Hawking movie
and like it's all about infidelity.
It's very weird.
Oh, they did get into that stuff.
I never saw the movie.
The whole movie is about everyone cheating on everybody.
Including Hawking?
Oh, yeah.
So he cheated before he was like in the wheelchair and everything?
I think both.
No, he cheated when he was completely incapacitated.
Yeah, like a few years ago.
Yeah.
Redmayne's following up with that movie
where he plays the first transgender man.
I mean, he's the Danish girl.
Yeah, that kid's not fucking around, man.
He's going after the Oscars.
He gave one of the most ludicrous performances
I've ever seen in the movie, Jupiter ascending.
What did he play?
Where Channing Tatum plays a half dog, half astronaut.
I mean, I don't know why you saw the fucking movie.
Because I still go, well, the Matrix was good.
But then speed racer and everything else comes out.
I mean, they never matched it.
Never even come within the ballpark.
Jupiter ascending is a real, it's a new low.
It's worse than like Cloud Atlas or any of that stuff.
So who was, who was Eddie in the movie?
He was the villain.
It was Meal of Kunis and Channing Tatum.
Also, they're fucking and you're like,
well, he's a dog, though.
So you are fucking a dog, just so you know.
I'm going to just say this.
I don't say it to be mean.
It probably is mean.
I don't ever need to see Meal of Kunis in anything ever again.
I could, I have no opinion either way.
I can give her take.
She can't change her voice.
Yeah.
And she will always sound like a girl that smokes pot from the 70s.
Like she, it's like, it's, it's, it's distracting to me.
The only time I ever thought she was pretty good was in Black Swan.
But anybody could have played that part for sure.
I loved her in a, I loved her in say,
saving Sarah Fisher, forgetting Sarah Marshall.
Oh, yeah, forget it.
She was, she was, she was, she's romantic comedy.
Yeah, she was great in that.
Sure.
But you know, I don't want to see her in Jupiter ascending.
No.
When they cast her as the witch in fucking the odds, I was like,
Oh, Jesus Christ, what is happening here?
That movie made my deck very solid.
They had her as the main witch and they had fucking Rachel Wies
as like the secondary witch.
Yeah, the fuck is going on here.
I kept saying, hey, which which is which?
You know, I said, oh wait, here's, which, here's, wait, this is the walk in line.
Which which is which?
This is the scene where walkin says the thing.
This is, this is where he says, I think it's, hold on.
I think this is, oh, maybe it's not.
I kill first born babies.
There he is.
Here it comes.
The audience isn't hearing you right now because they're still laughing at which, which is which.
This is the, these moments are the problem on the podcast if you're not watching the movie
because all they're hearing is me just going, wait a second, here it comes.
Right.
We're almost there.
Jerry just got shot walking as lipstick on now.
He does have lipstick on, doesn't he?
Yeah, just in that shot, he does.
Why, how here it is, here it is.
There you go.
What a great line.
Yeah, I remember that.
I kill first born, so I had a mama's watch.
I turn cities into salt.
That's very great.
That's a great line.
And the only thing you can count on for all existence is never understanding why.
Great dialogue.
Yeah.
Would you say it sings?
I would.
Joe was telling me earlier that somebody once told him the dialogue in a certain movie,
Sings.
Would you be, I'm asking you, this is this is the question of the week listeners.
Could you remain friends with a person who saw a movie and you said,
ah, how was it?
I tell you man, the dialogue sings.
I would end the friendship.
It made me want to see the movie.
It's a, it's a fantastic move.
I bought it on blind faith.
Still haven't watched it.
It's called Sweet Smell of Success.
Yeah, one of these days.
1955 -ish.
What's that?
Five -ish Finkels in it?
No, I said 1955 -ish.
Oh.
Finkel.
I've never seen five -ish Finkel before the age of 76.
No, I don't think his mother had.
Sweet Smell of Success is like a very, very, very dark movie about like a gossip columnist.
Uh, and his like protege and he kind of destroys him essentially.
It's just it's about losing your morals, losing your soul, et cetera.
Did you ever see a face in the crowd?
Love it.
I think that's directed by Eliya Kazan.
It is, yeah.
It is.
That is a rough one, man.
Yeah.
That is a rough one.
Make sure you realize that uh, Andy Griffith is a fucking tremendous actor.
Yeah.
I really have change.
I know idea.
I thought he was like good, you know.
I was like, okay, he's a good actor.
Yeah.
But I only ever saw him in Matlock and the sitcom.
You watch him in that movie.
You're like, Jesus Christ.
I mean, this guy's a fucking tour de force.
Yeah, he was great.
He never really got a lot of roles either.
Can a guy be a tour de force or can you just have a tour de force?
Uh, a performance can be a tour de force.
I don't think a man can be a tour de force.
I'm going to say this guy's a powerhouse.
That's what I'm going to say.
I know what you're meant.
Sorry, I'm dumb like that.
I'm a little dumb.
How much longer does this movie have, by the way?
That ominous music is continuing.
It's just keep saying it.
Where's your little Apple TV remote?
The fuck are you going to wind up turning this off?
Hardest to find remote in all time.
No, because I'll just hit the center button.
And it paused.
It paused real quick.
We got, with that 109, this is 130 set a half an hour.
Another half an hour.
Well, there's credits.
Folks, I hope you're listening at home.
Don't find this to be like an endurance test as Joe clearly does.
I'm getting nervous because I got to pick my friends up at the airport.
That's all.
It's fine.
They'll be fine.
I'm sure they're excited to see me.
Have you asked them?
Right.
My friend Jim coming in loves you tremendously.
He can't wait to see it.
All right.
He was very excited to hear your coming to Thanksgiving.
Yeah.
Hopefully you don't disappoint everybody this year by not drinking again.
Oh, I mean, I shouldn't even understand.
You know, our whole thing, Joe, is when you don't drink,
I never say a word to you.
I'm like, oh, good choice.
When I don't drink, you scream at me.
I don't ever scream while drunk.
That's not true.
Yeah, I'll take a video next time.
I don't play it for you the next morning.
Listen, we talked this out.
You fucking pussy.
Well, that's a drink of fucking shot.
That's joke screaming.
First of all, I'm not abusing volume.
A joke scream is as loud as a scream scream.
I don't think you could name a time where I told you I wasn't drinking.
You take breaks.
I take breaks.
My point is it's a holiday.
Let's celebrate.
I'm going to be drinking.
Good.
Leave you me.
I'm actually kind of feeling like getting wine boozy tomorrow.
You know what?
I'm not against it.
Yeah.
Okay.
He's caressing this girl now.
That shot from the back.
His hand was dipping too low, folks.
We were in a restaurant once.
It was actually the two of us.
It was you and myself and Jamie Lee
and our good friend Karen Coguerre.
I remember that.
Yeah.
We were at
Elkhampadra.
Yeah, somewhere.
No, no, the other time.
We were at Malo.
Eating Mexican food.
And do you remember there was the dad with his daughter?
Yes.
Rubbing her back and I kept through the whole meal saying,
guys, this is inappropriate.
He's inappropriately massaging this girl.
Everybody kept saying,
Joe, no, you're being ridiculous.
It's his daughter.
And I finally got a room to look.
And the second everybody looked,
they were like, oh no, that's weird.
I had looked and I was like,
Joe, you're fucking discussed.
You're being ridiculous.
And then I looked over and I was like,
no, these two have a relationship.
It's not father -daughter at all.
What I'm saying.
Maybe she had that Webster disease.
She was actually 37,
a little touch at the Simon Birch.
Yeah.
You know, some people just look young
and don't have the disease.
Ralph Moch is a good example.
Me as another good example.
Yeah.
Mochio, a little known movie trivia.
He was 52 when he made the karate kid.
And my cousin Vinnie, he was in his late 80s.
Still looks good.
Bless his heart.
He does.
Now, this has to have been floated around at some point.
They did the fucking disgraceful remake
with Jaden Smith and Jackie Chan.
Sure.
But why not a Rocky Balboa style
Daniel is the karate kid.
You know, I understand that Mochio is not
as big a star as Stallone,
and maybe couldn't open moving.
You hear me, you hear me objecting?
Why wouldn't anyone would go see that?
You hear me objecting?
And we just said he still looks fucking great.
I would kill to see that.
Mochio comes in.
Mochio is trying to, you'd have to get a big star
to play the new karate kid
because Mochio is not going to open your movie.
But you get somebody big in there as the kid,
somebody not Jaden Smith.
I respect the next karate kid more than that remake
because at least your next karate kid was still canon.
I agree, Joe.
That new karate kid,
A, it was two hours and 20 minutes.
And B, the karate kid, Jaden Smith,
and I'm not projecting what I know Jaden Smith's personality
to be, his character was an asshole.
Really?
Why would you make the karate kid an asshole?
Why was he an asshole?
He's just like cocky and like a dick to everybody.
And then through the movie,
he becomes less of a cocky dick
and learns from Jackie Chan.
But like Mochio was a sweet kid.
They got picked on.
And needed to learn how to defend himself.
And this thing starts and like Jaden Smith's like,
Hey, you fucking assholes.
He's a prick.
Hey, karate kids in the house.
That's the exact line is, hey, you fucking assholes.
The karate kid's that he actually kicks through the scene
screen during the title sequence.
Yeah.
And that's how the movie starts.
I said, how does this thing get a PG rating?
If that's the first line.
Yeah.
I heard he actually says at one point,
it's called sweeping the leg you cunt.
Exactly.
I heard that was a line from the movie.
I just bought karate kid one and two on Blu -ray.
A little box set.
And I looked at the Amazon reviews
and this guy was like,
the Amazon reviews are always hilarious.
This guy was like five stars.
If I could give it more, I would.
He's like, the picture on this movie
is the stuff dreams are made of.
Oh boy.
I never, I only seen it on VHS.
It was like having a new world opened up to me.
Oh boy.
Just on and on and on.
So I'm excited to see the picture.
I don't, I never liked two.
I always liked one and three.
Oh, I like two.
Two is considered the empire of the karate kid series.
Fill your mouth with your mother's feces.
He's the devil.
What do you expect him to say?
He's devil.
Oh, I heard this part's cool.
The devil's got like little like creepy minions around him.
Yeah.
Okay.
I never liked part two.
I didn't like that they went to Japan.
I think it's a great idea for a secret.
Or do they go to China?
I wish I knew, but I don't.
I think it's Japan.
Okinawa is Japan, right?
Yeah, I didn't like it.
It was too like serious.
Or we didn't have the fun of the fur.
I missed the Kobra Kai.
Okay.
I love that the guy comes back in the third one for revenge.
Did I ever tell you that show I pitched with Robert Kelly
and I pitched a show to Ralph Machio?
I think you did tell me about that.
Yeah.
Can I tell you about it on the podcast?
No.
Years ago, Robert Kelly and I had a meeting with Ralph Machio.
We pitched him a show where we played two agents
that got fired from William Morris
and had to start their own agency.
And the only way they could think to make money was by finding
actors that weren't working and exploit them
by making them do terrible gigs.
That's a good idea.
And we said we want you, Ralph Machio,
to be like the third guy in this because you have
like the premise of the show is you have so little going on.
You're just you just hang around the office all the time with us
and end up working with us.
Did you phrase it tactfully?
Or were you like it is?
We phrase it tactfully but he also was very adamantly like
look, I like the idea but you can't make it sound like
I failed.
He was like I walked away to have a family.
He was like so that's my one thing.
I don't know what to say.
Okay, that's fair.
But the premise was that
Williams Vodka who played Johnny right
was having a big Super Bowl party at his mansion
and he wants to hire Ralph Machio to host the Super Bowl party.
So we tell him like you got to go do this.
This is good money man.
And Ralph Machio is like I'm not doing it.
You don't understand that guy really is a fucking asshole like
there's no way and we're like it'll be fine.
And we can't take him to the party.
Williams Vodka is really nice.
We're like you got this buddy
and then we leave and as soon as we leave
they turn on him like Karate Kid's down.
Right.
The shit out of him.
Vodka is like I paid 25 grand to get you here
just like kick the shit out of you one more time.
That's funny.
Machio ends up in the end of the episode.
He really like this part.
Face down in traction.
Said and we're going to shoot it like the end of the
outsiders when you die.
Except you're calling us cock suckers.
And it's not sad it's funny.
He was like I love that idea.
Yeah.
He's like as far as fighting Billy's vodka.
Called him Billy's vodka.
He goes people been trying to get us to fight again on screen for 30 years.
There's a reason we haven't done it.
And I was like okay.
I guess maybe they have tried to reboot it with them or something.
He just didn't like retreading that.
But he loved the outsiders idea.
Did you feel like Machio really walked away to have a family?
Yeah.
Yeah I did.
He's like lives in Long Island he had.
He you know he was still doing stuff when he stopped.
Like he was in my cousin Vinnie and you know.
Right.
There's like a very clear end to him doing movies.
Yeah.
It's not like he did a bunch of bad ones and faded away.
It's like it just stopped suddenly.
Yeah.
So I believed him.
But now what's weird is like Machio let's say first karate kid he probably made
let's say max $250 ,000.
Then each additional one he might get a mill or something.
Like how is that money hanging in now 30 years later?
Well dude you're forgetting that he was like a huge box office draw for like five years.
I guess so.
He had that run where he did like crossroads.
Yeah.
All right.
He did uh.
He got his money.
He made his money.
He does TV stuff.
He works when he wants to work.
Like he made that clear and I'm sure he's I'm sure he's sitting pretty.
All right.
He also might have got to deal with the karate kid where they're like look man
this was going to pay shit up front.
But if it's a hit you'll make it on the back end.
And he might have made a lot of fucking money on the back end.
They didn't know better about those deals back then.
Yeah.
That's why it was a better time to work.
That's why Lucas is so fucking rich.
You know.
Yeah.
How did that guy have that foresight?
How did he have the fucking foresight to be like?
I'd just give me the merchandising money on this movie.
It's just to have a complete belief in yourself.
It's so crazy that he knew that he knew to do that.
He's uh.
Walkin is now sitting in a diner with blood all over his shirt
and with a mental patient.
And a mental patient in a hospital gown played by uh.
A man of plum.
A man to plumber.
Related to Christopher plumber.
Daughter?
I believe so.
And his Michael and Virginia Madsen bro and sis.
Yep.
Okay.
Oh, we got the whole thing connect in here.
I love Christopher plumber.
He's a great actor.
The insider is a fantastic movie.
What am I going to do?
Beat him to death with this notebook?
Yeah.
I like that part a lot.
Plumber fucking kills on the insider.
He kills it.
He's also in Danny Collins.
He plays his manager.
He must be friends with tremendous.
Tremendous.
It's the only time I've ever seen him play a character like this.
He's like a like a prickly like old bastard kind of.
Okay.
You know?
Yeah.
Like he's got a lot of line.
Like he keeps having to go to Jersey to deal with Pacino.
Right.
Like he keeps going for two reasons.
Number one, I'm your best friend.
Number two.
Do this so I can get the fuck out of New Jersey.
Like I've never seen him play that kind of guy.
Yeah.
Did you see beginners?
No, I heard it was very good.
It's so good.
I own it.
I'll own it too if you want.
It's actually on Netflix, incident.
I was supposed to audition for that movie.
What part?
Do you own McGregor role?
I doubt it was the McGregor role.
The dog?
There's a cute dog in it.
Yeah, no, I don't know.
I wasn't able to do the audition though.
Is that a commitment?
I couldn't make it.
But it's weird because I can't think of any role
that you would ever could have played.
Maybe it was cut.
It's a numbers game where you go in and fucking,
you know, yeah.
I also auditioned to play the role
that Zach Galfanakis got on board to death.
Okay.
So you're like, did I really ever shot at this?
I auditioned for another thing once the David Cross got.
Of course, she hired David Cross.
Yeah.
Why would you even bring me in here?
Speaking of David Cross,
I just saw a preview for the new Chipmunk movie.
Is he in it?
I'm sure he is.
It was just a little teaser.
I have not seen any of the Chipmunk movies,
but it was, I'm not a Chipmunk,
the second one was called The Squeak Cool,
which is a good title.
Let's be honest.
The third one,
they dropped the ball so hard.
It is called Alvin and the Chipmunks.
Yep.
Road Chip.
Yeah.
And I looked at it for like two minutes until I was like,
oh, like Road Trip.
The Road Chip.
It's a terrible title.
Took me 10 minutes to remember
that they're Chipmunks and not squirrels.
And I was like, wait, why is it Chip?
Yeah, well it is called Alvin and Chipmunk.
And then I was like, wait, is Chipmunk
or Chipendale in this?
No, that's the rescue rangers.
Yeah, I couldn't, I couldn't wrap my fucking head around it, man.
It's kind of amazing that Alvin and Chipmunks
for whatever reason makes $500 million.
I guess kids always love that sped up record player sound.
But the Chipendale people aren't like,
hey, let's reboot Chipendale.
Or maybe they are.
Maybe right now and some.
They're gonna reboot.
Yeah.
Your favorite co -host, Pat.
Joe.
Just got an audition
to read for Launch Pad McQuack.
In the DuckTales reboot.
Movie?
No, TV show.
Oh wow, that's big.
That would be some juicy cash.
That's big.
Can you get my hands on that?
Animated?
Or are you wearing like a bill and...
Everything's animated except me.
And I actually play a...
I'll get you ducks.
I play a human.
No, Launch Pad's their friend.
He's like the dumb guy that flies the ball.
Oh yeah, the big.
It's like, I got juice guys.
Yeah.
One of the notes in the, uh,
in the, uh, you know, they give you notes.
I'm like, this is how we want the character to be.
Uh -huh.
Said, uh,
we're not looking for put on cartoony voices here.
Make it real.
Wow.
Get back to the real Launch Pad McQuack.
Yeah, I don't know.
Every time I audition for a cartoon, it says that.
Yeah.
It always says, like, don't put, don't put a voice on,
like, just, they want it to just be your voice.
Which means I'm not getting it.
Cause does this sound like the voice of Launch Pad McQuack?
To any of you?
Not from what I remember.
No.
No, like Jeff Garland has a Launch Pad McQuack voice.
That's true.
Pete.
That's the tail of that McQuack voice.
Yeah.
That's my Jeff Garland has Launch Pad impression
if you didn't figure it out by the way.
I got it.
Yeah.
You don't like the how?
These, did Christopher Walker just say it's your night to how?
Or you'll like to how?
You all like to how?
Terrible stunt double.
What does that mean?
I missed the first part of the line.
I love walking is putting a certain
effect on to his voice, not post, like he's doing it on purpose.
Where he's making it real growly and it's great.
I've never heard him growl like this.
It works really well for him.
That's very good.
Yeah.
That rag rat he just called Virginia medicine.
Well earlier he was telling people to watch their profanity,
you know, it's calling people rag bitches.
Well, because the guy said God damn it.
Oh, he said you're going to have to watch that profanity.
He's an angel.
He's a soldier of God, Pat.
You understand?
Yeah, I do.
Dude, they I'm sure they explained it and we missed it because we're fucking
yapping for the sake of the listeners.
Yeah.
Did they explain why God never comes down to help out the way devil does?
I don't think so.
He keeps going on with this monkey thing.
I'm going to say this monkey business.
Maybe the sequel is God's revenge or something.
But God's a good guy.
Yeah, I know, Joe.
This is exactly the plot to concentrate.
Joe just told me God's a good guy.
Well, thanks God's revenge doesn't make sense.
There would be no revenge with God.
Well, maybe the sequel is God turning the other cheek for 90 minutes.
The other butt cheek.
Then it's a the sequel is a lot zany or this one.
The yeah, this is the plot of Constantine,
but Constantine was a comic book long before a film.
So I wonder if the prophecy was ever accused of taking stuff from the Constantine comics?
Probably.
How is Constantine?
The movie?
Yeah.
Fucking awesome.
I have it on my DVR.
It's fucking awesome.
It's Keanu Reeves and Shia LaBouffe.
Yeah, it's great.
All right, I'll watch it.
It's great.
And it's, I mean, that's like, that's like machino and an arrow and heat.
That pairing.
Finally, LaBouffe and Reeves.
My heat pairing would be Justin Long and LaBouffe together.
And something.
Wow.
Met Long the other night.
It's hard not to have a man crush on that guy.
I've met Long is a nice guy.
Very nice guy.
Irrally nice.
What was I just going to say?
Oh, Constantine.
It's the turn, it's the Reeves turn when Reeves became cool.
Okay.
Now there's that turn with Reeves.
It was like, Keanu's like, you love Bill and Ted and all that stuff.
And then he did all those movies where everybody was like,
what is with this guy?
Yeah.
And then he turned and got cool again.
Yeah, that's like right in there.
Like Const, he plays like a badass.
You saw John Wick, right?
I didn't, I want to see it.
It's fucking awesome.
I want to see that new one where he knock, knock.
I like knock, knock a lot.
I didn't see it.
You saw it already?
I did.
I watched it on demand.
Was it out already?
No, it was one of those you could buy it for five bucks on iTunes.
The day it came out in theaters.
And it was good.
It was.
Eli Roth, I mean, it's, uh, it's not perfect.
It's, that's Reeves actually has a couple scenes where he's doing like
Nicholas Cage and the wicker man.
Like he's just embracing the fact that he's not a strong actor.
And it's funny, but it's very ballsy because he risks becoming a joke.
But John Wick's got him now.
Uh, I, the guy from Big Bang Theory does the best Nicholas Cage impression I've ever seen.
Which one?
The kid that plays the, the kid that looks kind of like Ben Stiller
on the Big Bang Theory.
Uh, he also does an amazing Ben Stiller impression.
How about Johnny Galecki?
No, Simon Helbert.
Oh, that was good.
Make a good effect.
Was that the little girl?
Uh, he spewed out this fucking soul fine.
Well, that is not a good special fine.
That's not bad.
This thing is going to kill walking.
Anyway, he does an amazing Nicholas Cage impression and he did it on Conan and he
talked about the end of the wicker man when Nicholas Cage stands up and goes,
you bitches.
Okay, it was very funny.
I met, I had a meeting with Simon Helbert, and he was very quiet.
He must just be like one of those people who turns it on.
I always see him at one of my local bars.
Not always.
I've seen him a few times at one of my local bars.
Which one, the arrest?
I don't want to give up his spot.
Not Joe's.
Let the guy go.
I give him a little more credit than to think you'd be at Joe's.
Where you always want to go.
Joe's?
There's no bars.
You mean Jay's bar?
I hate that bar.
Why do you hate it?
I've said a million times I hate it.
You're always like over at Jay's.
It's fine.
There's nothing splashy about it.
It's not diving.
It's just a bar and you go in and you fucking
wish you were somewhere else.
You have a nice time.
It's a good bar to get a drink with a lady.
I find.
I would take a lady to good luck.
Good luck is fun.
But it's a little, it can be a little depressing because it's dark in there.
And it's very dark in there.
All right.
It also doesn't open until like
it's not open at like happy hour.
Well, I like to take a lady out at about 2 a .m.
Do you?
Yeah.
Because then you know you got a better chance of sticking your prick in.
I'm like, let me just get you home.
I put my cape around.
I like to wear capes on days off.
Sure, of course.
A long flowing cape.
That when you are having sex with a girl,
do you refer to your member as your prick or your hog?
My sweaty hog is usually my son.
Right.
You're ready to take this sweaty hog is usually what I'll say.
Take it all the way, bitch.
I'm kidding.
I'm just I'm totally joking.
I just thought of a Freddie Kruegery way to say it.
Yeah.
So I said it.
I like sweaty hogs.
Subtile just said lead the light on Thomas.
So whoever did the subtiles for the prophecy,
let's focus on your job.
Should have said leave.
All right.
I'll also say,
take my cum hose.
Oh god.
I'll say that.
Uh huh.
I'll say when I'm about to have an orgasm, I'll go pull the rip cord baby, pull the rip cord.
There's a friend of mine who has this killer story.
She's a beautiful young lady married now.
I won't reveal her name obviously.
But she was having sex and she told me the story.
She was like, I don't know what to tell you.
I had sex with this big fat guy.
Um, I just liked him.
We went out.
We had a good time.
I liked him.
I went home and she was on top having sex.
And when he comes, he puts his hands out like jazz hands.
And does this like waggles his hand.
Both hands out like jazz hands and shakes him around.
And he goes, I'm gonna explode.
I was so blown away.
She was like, I've never been less turned on in my entire life.
But I love that story.
You hear, you just hear the creaking sounds of vagina drying.
So I got to read those bags.
That guy that after he's done has got to be like, so sorry about all that.
So eggs?
I'll show myself how.
I had sex with a girl once years ago.
And while we were having sex, hopefully we'll see.
Well, we're having sex.
She went, Joe, Joe, Joe is fucking me.
What?
hilarious.
She was narrating it.
It was so hard not to laugh.
That's somehow worse.
Quite flattering too.
Folks, we just hit the credits.
I'm sorry to leave you with the image
of someone yelling Joe is fucking me.
These people are going to have to take a shower.
The subtitle during the credits, by the way,
is upbeat music parentheses.
This is upbeat.
Folks, this is the show.
And this was the prophecy.
Thanks for listening to.
We'll see you in hell presentation.
The Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFao.
Executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment
for press opportunities, advertising inquiries,
and information about we'll see you in hell contact, Ken.
He's a Ken at Fangoria .com.
If you're in the New York area,
I'm headlining Gotham Comedy Club December 18th and 19th.
Five shows over the course of two nights.
Please come out to see that.
And happy Thanksgiving.
Follow me on Twitter, Joe DeRosha Comedy.
Patty, you want to plug?
I am at the Patrick Walsh.
Twitter, by Instagram, etc.
And, you know, that's all I got.
I want you to have a good Thanksgiving.
I'm doing fun.
I don't need you to come out and see my shit.
Happy Thanksgiving to you.
Keep tweeting us.
Give us five stars.
Give us those great reviews and iTunes.
We really appreciate it.
Thanks folks.
Take care.