Welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast talking movies,
movies, movies. I'm Joe.
And I'm Pat Walsh. Hello, everybody. This is we'll see you
in hell as Joe just said, and if you're listening to these two
back to back, you've heard it now, five, six times, you know
what you're fucking listening to? Yes. We're going to be
talking today about jackass forever, the fourth in the
jackass franchise, and also of course, the series that came
before it, the spin off easiest title of the jackass films, yet
another part four, where they call it forever. What's the
other one? What's another Shrek? Oh, why you had Shrek
ready to go?
Pat, I'd love to hit you with some good news. Oh, please. As
we start here. Ted lasso season three is officially started
filming. Thank God for that. Joe, why do you ask me to talk
about things that we know people who work on? There's no there's
no gives a shit. They'll never hear this. No, they won't. But
it's a widely beloved show. Actually, I do know somebody who
will hear this, but that's fun. You know what I look at it like
this. We're out here naming people doing awful things. Ted
lasso is getting thrown into the mix. You know? Okay. Well, you
know, we're calling everybody out for everything they do. I'm
going calling up Ted lasso too. It's a shit show. It's boring.
It's milk toast. It's a Yeah, it's a perfectly harmless show.
I'm not gonna speak. I, you know, I know the fucking guy who
created the show. It's a juggernaut. I think most comedy
writers frustration with it is that it became like the biggest
thing in the world. And it is this kind of innocuous show
about a nice guy going about his day. But that's it's the old
William Goldman expression about Hollywood. Nobody knows
anything. You never know what's going to hit what's going to
seed. But yeah, it's just kind of, for me, it's the explosion
around it that that grows. I definitely get why people like
it. But the the explosion is as it's crazy to me. I wanted to
share here another bit of good news. It's the criterion flash
sale today. Oh, the 24 hour 50 % off sale. I always recommend
that. And I also recommend that you order through Criterion
again, this is another company that has given us $0. But you
order from Criterion, they send you gift certificates all the
time. For every, I don't know, 500 you spend, they give you a
50 or something, which is a really good loyalty program. The
Citizen Kane came out and the the blu ray was like there was
one like sound issue, some tiny sound issue. And they were like
break it in half, take a picture of it, we'll send you a
replacement with a $10 gift certificate. And they did like
they're just one of the few places you've heard Joe and I go
on and on about customer service all over the globe, as we've been
doing this podcast. But Criterion are one of the goods.
I just dig what they do. Check them out.
Criterion finally got my Sid Kane in the mail.
You check it out. Yep. I have not watched it yet. You know,
it's a film though. Yeah, many times. But that's not when you
just pop on.
No, you got to be in the mood. But it is always I forget how
entertaining it is. Because when something is called the best
movie ever, it's sort of attains a homework type quality. But
it's also just a super entertaining movie.
I'm going to go in on this Mulholland Drive blu ray
finally.
To me, one of the great films.
One of the yeah, and I own it on DVD. But why not jump into this
blu ray? Finally, the the blue velvet Criterion is great as
well. A bunch of deleted scenes can't stand the film can't stand
the film.
And we discussed this.
I don't know. Why don't you like blue velvet? I hate it. I think
it's I think it's as masturbatory as a movie can
get. I just don't like it. I just it just does nothing for me.
Like Dennis Hopper, sucking oxygen and being like,
I just think it sucks.
It's a good impression. But it's not.
But it's just, you know, sometimes he steps too far left.
And I'm like, All right, buddy. Yeah, I'll see when you come
back this way.
But blue velvet is considered one of his least. Like that's a
you know, it's traditional for him narrative. It's kind of like
that like Mulholland Drive is way more obscure Lost Highway is
way more obscure.
I think Lost Highway. I'm not crazy about either. I think I
think Mulholland Drive is a wonderful, experimental,
absurdist horror film.
I don't know. Blue Velvet just doesn't I just don't give a shit.
I'm not into it.
Fair enough. Do you know, it was written that Dennis Hopper would
be inhaling nitrous oxide like at a dentist office?
That would make sense.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Helium. He is he is basically doing nitrous oxide.
Helium. So he was going to talk in that helium voice for the
entire film.
All right. Well, then.
And Hopper was like, I'm not doing that. Basically. I mean,
they somebody wisely decided not to but that we'd never be
talking about that movie if that was the case.
That's really funny. Yeah. Well, I don't know. Maybe you know,
but
um, anyway, big fan, big fan.
I know.
Miller's Crossing. If you're looking for for a new one to
get. I mean, I know a lot of people have seen Miller's
Crossing. It's a great Coen Brothers film. But I that was my
first add to cart. I'm so excited to have a criteria in
addition to that movie. It is one of the great mob movies. And
I it's so weird. There are so many great mob movies. It really
is like, for being kind of this little sub genre. There's such a
high percentage of a quality mob movies. But Miller's Crossing
is is definitely stranger than most. But it's it's a very,
very, very cool movie. Have you seen that one, Joe?
I have. I enjoyed it when I saw it. Yeah.
John Totoro is magnificent in the film.
Robert Finney.
I don't know if it's one I want to buy or not. I not because I
don't want to buy it. I'm just not sure if I should buy it or
not. I only saw it once. And I really liked it. I remember my
favorite part being that really weird scene with, you know, the
guy that looks like Danny DeVito.
John Polito.
Yeah, where he's like hitting his kid and being like, baby, I'm
sorry. It's so weird.
Give it another watch. I mean, it's it. It is a pretty fucking
great movie. Did you know Polito was gay?
Yes, not till he died. But yeah, interesting.
He you know, it's throwing me for a loop is menace to society is
in here. I had bought a blu ray of that before it went to
criterion. We talked about on the show. You know, I liked it
when I was young. I really liked it on the rewatch. I liked it.
But then the more I thought about it, I was like, I don't
want to delve from that into it. And I was like, I take it or
leave it. And I remember that same day I bought juice. And I
was like, Oh, juice is a keeper hands down. I mean, that's what
a what a movie. Yeah. And now menace to society has made it
into criterion juice hasn't. But now I'm like, was I wrong about
menace to society? Like, I don't know, like, maybe I need to
maybe I wasn't in the
I love menace to society, but I and juice, but I slightly
actually prefer dead presidents, their follow up, which
presidents I think is better. And I'm shocked that that's not
in here. But I guess that, you know, the debut was menace to
society. I mean, God forbid, they don't leave room for the
next four fucking Wes Anderson movies.
Yeah, no, I know. You know, they, um, Christ, to me, I know
Ebert really, really, really love menace to society. To me,
it pales in comparison to boys in the hood, which came out
around the same time as and I don't know, they're those are
filmmakers. I didn't really like they're from hell. They're
they're Johnny Depp picture about Jack the Ripper. But
you didn't see that one.
No, I know zero interest. I couldn't use don't like that.
You just don't like Jack the Ripper, the character.
A huge fan. I didn't think they did. No, I'm kidding. No, I
know. I don't know. I just didn't give a shit. I was a
fan of all the rips that he did. Do you ever seen Jack's back
starring James Spader where he is like the modern day
reincarnation of Jack? I used to see it in the movie store all
the time, but I never watched it. I know amazingly boring
cover. It's a it's about a reincarnated Jack the Ripper
and the cover is like a Polaroid somebody took of James
Spader on. Yeah, it's the poster they used. It's it's always on
prime. I've actually never seen it myself. Is thief worth
buying? Oh, thief is fucking awesome.
Good gangster movie.
Thief is fucking awesome. You would love it. It's all right.
You know what it is is in the cart, baby. It's Michael Mann.
For starters, it's Jimmy Khan. And it was a huge inspiration
on a movie. You do not like drive, but the things you don't
like about drive are not present in thief. You will love the
All right.
Yeah, and I don't know what's new with Criterion. I'm excited
to get in there because I haven't I haven't done a buy in
a while. But
Miller's Cross is a new one. Yeah, so and so is dead. That
documentary about the ladies dead.
Oh, oh,
Dick, Dick, whatever is dead.
Chaney. Yeah, not Chaney. That movie is fucking incredible.
It's on Netflix. That's the other weird thing is all these
Netflix is go directly to marriage stories. I guess they
have some sort of weird partnership. Not Wow. Oh, my
god. I just have a stroke.
What happened?
I said all the Netflix is go directly to marriage story.
What does it mean meant to say is that all these Netflix
original movies, like marriage story, go directly to Criterion.
And that Dick Johnson is dead is one of them, as was the
Irishman, as are many others. But yeah, this new thing of
like, I don't know, there's no board deciding what's Criterion
worthy or whatever. But I do wish they'd open up the process
a little bit or at least ask people what they most want to
see a Criterion of I know it's rights issues. But more often
than not, I'm realizing I can't keep going with this collection
and keep buying like, I can't buy one night in Miami, for
example, I hated that movie.
I'm surprised you hated it so much. I really enjoyed it. I
don't know if I liked it. I almost want to buy it. Because
Malcolm X is in my 10 favorite, one of my 10 favorite movies of
all time. Yeah, and I'm tempted to buy this because I, I, I
feel that it's a pretty good companion piece to that movie.
But I also don't know how often I'll toss on now one night in
Miami, you know, never happened.
Um, now what I will recommend is Miami blues starring Alec
Baldwin. That's a great movie. That's a really good movie.
George Armitage, there's a really underrated and I'd like
to recommend to use some Miami bass. I think you'd enjoy the
the genre of music.
Is that like Miami sound machine?
No, Miami bass is like, to live crew and like 95 South, you
know, give it a tootsie roll.
Oh, sure, sure.
Miami vice brings us back to Michael Mann, and Miami sound
machine. When I landed the other night in LA from Atlanta, I had
a little two week break back home. I listened to two men as
I waited at the Spirit Airlines baggage claim for upwards of an
hour and 10 minutes for my bag to come down. And these two men
stood behind me and talked for that entire time about Gloria
Estefan and the Miami sound machine. And they I heard them
meet. They weren't friends who both arrived with a shared love
of Miami sound machine. They when I finally turned around and
looked the guy was dressed insanely. He's dressed like, you
know how like an 80s music producer like won't give it up
or like Steve, let's say Steven Tyler, he's still dressing like
your aunt, you know, like with the jewels and everything. Yes,
this looks ridiculous. So the guy was one of those he was a
musician, because he had a big he's holding a big guitar case
or saxophone case for him. And this other guy just comes up
starts talking to him about music. And before you know it,
they both have they both have encyclopedic knowledge of Gloria
Estefan and the Miami sound machine. They were not Hispanic,
not that you would need to be to know about her. But it's
like, she'd be a legend in that community. You know, I was I
was shocked. And I just sat and listened to them talk about
album by album. I mean, this was just two ships in the night. I
was like, if these two men are gay, they need to either fuck
or get married tonight.
Here's all your mind job.
No, I left you didn't hear me laughing. No, I didn't. It's
thing. Well, you turn your head away when you laugh, which always
makes me sad because then I don't get to hear the laughs. And
the people at home don't know how funny I am. I'm facing the
laugh track. I'm facing full forward. You fuck. I wouldn't
know because I can't see you, Joe. Good. You can't see me,
bitch. I don't know why I have my camera on allowing you to
watch me in my private moments. Well, if you didn't, I wouldn't
be able to coach you through how to fix your headphones on the
last step. I couldn't hear a word you said. Yeah, I know. I
after five minutes of trial and error. Here's something that
bothers me with Criterion Devil and Daniel Webster, one I've
been wanting to buy forever from Criterion. Yeah, I like the
movie quite a bit. Why the fuck is it still only a DVD available?
Why have they not? It's like one of three movies in the
collection that they have not upgraded to a blu ray. Come on
guys. It's always it's always rights issues, you know, like
that's it's easy to forget, but these people got to get, you
know, but what rights issue you got the rights you've got you're
already putting the movie out. I don't I bet it'll come out
because I always sell my DVD copy when Criterion like I'm
going to sell the last waltz when they come out with the new
last waltz. I am down to like four Criterion DVDs that have
not been replaced by blu ray. They usually do it. It might
take a long time, but they usually do it.
I want to Yeah, I don't know. I'm gonna just probably pull the
trigger this time on the DVD. I'm tired of waiting. And I keep
like going on YouTube to watch clips of the movie. Okay. Okay.
It's stupid. Like I just want to own the goddamn movie so I can
watch it again.
Didn't Al Baldwin do a remake?
Yeah, it's okay. It's not bad. Yeah. But I really like that
original. I you know, the other movie I wish they would put or
maybe they did. Did they put the Andy? Andy Griffith face in the
crowd? Is that on here?
Andy Griffith face in the crowd? Yes, it is a lot like that is a
lot like the devil Daniel Webster.
Yeah. I don't know. Speaking of screaming in. There was an
article today that Al Baldwin is being sued by the husband of the
woman who was shot by the prop gun on the set of this movie
rust. And like, look, if this had happened to who's a beloved
actor? Who's somebody everybody loves? I don't know. Let's say
George Clooney, George Clooney. Yeah, exactly. If it was George
Clooney, there wouldn't be a single person on earth calling
for retribution from George Clooney. He would do his
tearful interview. He would be like, Oh, my God, we got to have
safer restrictions, blah, blah, blah. Nobody would be against
Clooney. But simply because Baldwin is a little outspoken,
he's a little blowhard, he's got a bit of a reputation as an
asshole. The the Twitter vitriol today, like Baldwin was like, I
feel like they're just trying to shake me down because of my
money. And everybody's like, well, what else would they shake
you down for you fucking insensitive asshole screen? You
this is a man who was handed a gun by a prop master and said
this is good to go. He then accidentally shot a woman which
is deeply unfortunate. He's got to deal with that for the rest of
his life. It is in zero way Alec Baldwin's fault. And I don't
personally see that there's any other way to see it.
Well, speaking of Clooney, Clooney was very critical of
Baldwin in this scenario. And really, yes. Yeah. And said, I
don't know what he's talking about, about a hot gun. I've
never even heard the phrase before. Like, there's never been
a hot gun, as he calls it on a set. And the fact that he was
saying, I'm paraphrasing. Yeah, the fact that he was saying,
like, who handed me a hot gun, like, I took it that Clooney
didn't have much sympathy for him. Right. And was kind of
I've never even heard that term, because it's something that
should never happen. And,
well, yeah, I mean, however you want to say it, whoever who
handed me a hot gun just means who handed me a loaded weapon
that will actually fire and kill. Sure, we all know what it
means. But I just mean, you know what I mean? Like, I'm just
saying, like, that to me, it's just entirely on the prop master.
This guy is not so in the prop master, because the prop master
probably has 10 grand in the bank. And Alec Baldwin has $25
million. So I do think you hate to say about a man who was
grieving the loss of his young, lovely wife. But yeah, he's
suing Alec Baldwin to get his fucking money.
Maybe that is the case. Maybe it also is the case that there's
information out there that we're not privy to and maybe Baldwin
is more at fault here. I don't know.
I hear you. I just don't know. I can't imagine that. This is why
I always just let me say this real quick. Sorry. Yeah. This is
why I always even with the worst accusations, I always say,
look, hopefully the person's telling the truth, but we don't
know, like, it needs to be investigated, you know, like,
this, this idea that we're just going to decide Alec Baldwin
gets it over this and the other guy doesn't. And, you know, I
also get the whole where there's smoke, there's fire. Alec
Baldwin has a history of being an asshole. He's a condescending
arrogant prick. Yes. I bet you if you met him in regular life,
he's probably really nice. But then like, you know, you know,
once I saw that he wrote that book as Trump, I was like, Oh,
for Christ's sake, you know, like, you're just like, dude,
get off terrible Trump impression, by the way. Yeah. So
Baldwin came to Conan when I was there and was insanely nice.
Insanely nice. I mean, like one of the only celebrities to ask
me where I was from, you know, my interests, etc. So granted,
could have been a good day. I've heard nothing but horror
stories about him. Otherwise, I told you about the watch story,
right?
No, real quick. It's on set. That multicam he was doing with
Kelsey Grammer, which I'm sure would have been a lot of fun for
anybody on that set. But they said they kept he kept Kelsey
Grammer waiting on stage every day for at least an hour. Yes.
And they're kind of equal stars, you know, then wardrobe,
because all these crews talk whenever they have like a
monster on set, wardrobe came up to him and presented him with
five watches, really nice, you know, Rolex type watches,
because his character was going to be a millionaire or
something. And they were like, any of these strike your fancy
any of these want to wear on the scene, because he said he wanted
to watch. And he knocked the watches to the floor out of the
woman's hand and said, usually on a movie set, they'd give me a
hundred watches. Oh, wow. All right. So you know, obviously
the man and look, I know people involved with 30 Rock and all
kinds of projects, the man, the man ain't no good, but obviously
a brilliant actor. Maybe my favorite he's ever been was
departed.
I love him and departed. I was just watching that we had it on
the bar the other day, replacing, replaced Dennis
Leary in that role.
Yeah. And you know that, I think I might have mentioned this
already on the show, leota was supposed to have a part in the
Irishman, and it didn't work out. Who was he gonna be? I
don't know. But he talked about it in an interview. He's like,
Yeah, we talked about just didn't have he was gonna be
young De Niro. Yeah, yeah. But how great would that have been to
see, you know, if the Fliota would have been in there with
everybody else, that would have been nice to see. Anyway, for
but no, we had the we had departed on in the bar, we always
have the movies inside on mute while music plays. And I was
just reading us literally sitting there reading the
subtitles. And I was like, still loving it.
It's great. I think, you know, like, people's the grievances
people have about movies sometimes, like, I have friends
who are like, I could never get over it. Honestly, this sounds
like an issue that you would have and why you would hate a
movie. All right, take it easy. They they couldn't stand the
actual rat crawling by at the end of the movie.
It's such a stupid grievance with that movie, especially
because they're so everybody that has a problem with that is
so dumb. They don't get the point. Yes. They go, I get it.
He's a rat. That's like, no, stupid. That's not what it is.
The beginning of the movie is him looking up at that spire.
Right. And thinking that if he could just get up to there, he
made it in life. He's whatever. And then that rat running across
to saying even rats get up this high. Yes. In buildings. It
doesn't matter. Like you're never you're you can't escape
what you actually are. It's it's a fucking great moment. And I
just Oh, I get really mad about that. That's one of the things
I get. That's like when you argue the Irishman and people
go look so fucking stupid when he kicks the gut. Shut the fuck
up. Moron. You don't deserve movies. But Joe, that's you
too.
Fuck you.
And and actually, I'm going to sit here until you admit that
that's you too. Because you know, that's you too.
I have many other points. It's never just one thing. Okay. I
admit that I'll get a little petty about a movie but get it
but at least admit that I have many himself isn't as petty as
you about movies.
Who's Oh, God.
Admit at least at least meet me halfway and say, agree that when
I hate something, I have a lot of points I make that I hate
about it. That's true, which I'll be doing today. Jackass
forever.
Sometimes getting increasingly stupid as the points go. But
all right. Come on.
Oh, thank God. One of the new criteria releases is a hard days
night. That's been out for two years. Joe, Joe, a hard day's
an incredible film. It's under new releases. I don't give a
shit. Give me juice, baby. Give me boys in the hood.
I think I think you are getting juice. I know. Well, they're
finally the movie. No, I know. I think you're getting juice or
they're at least on the rumored list. No, it is. Okay, because
they are. They got called out rightly so for being painfully
white, the criterion collection. And they immediately put forth
a major effort to releasing black films, like deep cover,
you know, which is awesome that that's getting a wider audience.
They got love Jones in here, which I remember being an okay
romantic comedy and love and basketball, which I remember
being an okay romantic comedy. So juice is not out of the
question. I mean, they're doing basketball for Christ sakes. I
know. What are we doing here? I mean, if it's a rightish, right,
like you said, if it's a rights issue, and, hey, we're doing our
best with what we can get rights to fine. But I mean, the fact
that that's in here before any John Singleton movie, or spiky
movies. It's like, what?
Yeah, no, I completely agree. Malcolm X needs a criterion, of
course, should be a massive undertaking. But they're do the
right thing is beautiful, beautiful print and amazing
extras. And hopefully, they're going to get to him. But
this is what's cool about criterion, by the way, is even
if it's not out yet, when they do the sale, you can buy the
coming soon at the sale price.
They let you do a few. Yeah, I always try to go a little further
than they let you. But but yeah,
what do you mean? By all? What do you mean?
You can't buy all the coming soon. You can only buy the ones
that are coming very soon.
Well, yeah, it's if it's on the website as a coming soon, you
can buy it at the sale price.
Not least, that's what I'm looking at.
Currently.
No, wait, I had something I wanted to say. You said, Where
are the Spike Lee's? And what'd you say? Oh, I know what it was.
Okay. So my wife just watched the Janet Jackson documentary,
the four four hour Janet Jackson documentary and enjoyed it very
much. And she said, it really made me want to watch Poetic
Justice. I've never seen it. So I dust off my old four
Singleton classics, DVD set, which I got for I think it's on
Amazon for $7 .99. And I looked at it and I was like, fuck, John
Singleton was good for movies in this baby. And the worst by far
is Poetic Justice. It is boys in the hood masterpiece, baby boy
and truly unsung masterpiece that I saw twice in the theater
and I fucking love baby boy. I think it's an incredible movie.
And higher learning. Oh, which is also excellent. I mean, the
guy, the guy made great shit.
Does hiring hold up? I feel like now that it's aged, it'll play a
lot like traffic, where it's like, it's like racist, cliche
after cliche, you know what I mean?
I think higher learning completely holds up. It was it
was way ahead of its time. But if you compare it to like
something that's trying to do the same thing, like that dear
white people show on Netflix or something, it's a way better.
And it's got Jay Ferguson as a rapist frat boy, my old friend,
Jay, so good to say I miss all Jay, part of the original title,
the pussy posse.
He really doesn't like that being brought up. But yes, he
was. I wouldn't bring it up if it wasn't all over the internet.
He doesn't like it being brought up because one of the things is
like him yelling a slur at Elizabeth Berkeley's boyfriend
or something like that.
What is the Mississippi masala is one of the new non white
films.
I've actually never seen the film with Denzel, right?
Never had an interest always sounded like some sort of
Italian dish or something to me.
It's honestly, let's just I'm going to say it now without even
giving it any thought. It's the worst title for movie I've ever
heard. Mississippi masala. Just no, no, not
It's not a great title. Look, mine will always be Hotel for
Dogs, followed by a wrinkle. What was it a wrinkle in what?
Oh, no, not not the new one. The worst title of all time is
the movie that hasn't even come out yet. And it's called Needle
in a time stack.
That's it.
That one's that one made me sit down and catch my breath a
little bit.
I thought I missed something. I was like, I guess that's like a
play on the I guess there's a thing called a time stack.
And there's so much discussion over movie titles and like what
it should be. So like I have this new thriller about how I
got my house me and my wife story with the crazy neighbor,
or whatever you're not supposed to say crazy anymore. But it's
a thriller. It's in the Cape Fear unlawful entry Ray Liotta
again, style. And it's got some comedic elements to it. It's
I can't come up with a title for this thing. And finally, through
asking a bunch of friends, including Joe, the one that I
wound up selecting is closing costs. So like the costs of
buying a new home is that you get this guy who's trying to
kill you basically. And everybody seemed pretty happy
with that. I have a guy now who wants to finance the movie. He
goes, I got two things I want to say. I said, Okay, he goes my
note on the script. You got somebody getting killed off
screen. I want him killed on screen. I was like, yeah, great.
I get that makes sense. He goes, number two, this title fucking
sucks. This title just fucking sucks. Are you married to this
title? Like, no, I'm not. I go, what would you call it? I got no
idea. I got no idea. But like, at no at what point? Nobody
stepped up and said, you can't call this thing needle in a
time stack.
No matter how many times you say it, it's fun.
Promise you it was not called that from the jump.
No, but that's okay. That's somebody coming in a haystack.
I know.
Which means, okay, it's a small thing. needles look like, hey, I
got it. needle. So what is a stack of time? Why would it be
hard to find? I guess it's something maybe it's something
it's hard to find in time is the premise, I guess is the only
way I'd buy it somebody looking through time traveling through
time looking for something. But still, you would never call that
movie needle in a time stack.
It's terrible. It's terrible. I'm disgusted by it.
Let's go to the old.
By the way, if any of you come up with a title. If you come up
with a title that gets used, I'll give you a free year of the
Patreon.
I'm just give them money.
I don't I don't know. I just it was spur of the moment. It just
came out of closing costs. Yeah, it's not a great title. But it's
not like horrible.
No, I know. Yeah, it's it's not great. Can I read this title
ready for this? Yeah, neighborly. That's a good title.
Neighborly was one of them. I think well, you probably pitched
that to me actually. But there's neighbors with Seth Rogan,
which was a huge movie. Yeah, so you know, neighborly. That's a
different word.
Our mutual friend, the hilarious comedian Lizzie Cooper, man,
gave me one that I liked quite a bit called buyer beware. Yeah,
but that's a little corny. Maybe. Yeah. Dream home doesn't work
because you're expecting like Freddy Krueger or something.
Neighborhood Watcher.
No, neighborly is a great title, dude. I'm telling you, that's the
best title of any of them. House Hunter. No, neighborly is your
title. There you go. Give me a free year Patreon.
All right, fine.
By the way, I need to say this too. So Emily once in a while
will send me a text and Hello, Emily. Thank you for all you do.
But she will send me a text saying like, Hey, there's an
issue with the Patreon. And somebody got double charged for
something or whatever. No matter how long it takes us, I swear to
God, we will get you your money back. And really, it is it is a
12 step process for me to log into our Patreon, especially
when I'm in Atlanta, because it makes me verify my address on 10
different things. Me and Joe have a special we'll see you in
Gmail account, I have to get into that, then that triggers Joe,
he has to press something to get me in. This is why my movie
corner was late last month. And it's very annoying. But we hear
you, I have the information, and I will get your money back.
Don't worry that we're trying to fuck you over a rip.
And also moving forward, just do this. If you can send us proof
that you were double charged and your Venmo information, we'll
just Venmo you the money.
That's what I was trying to do. And for some reason, this person
didn't want to do that. And they were insistent on get it.
They I think they thought they were putting me out and didn't
want to be a bother putting us out just just let's just do it
like that from now on.
It's actually much easier for me to just shoot you the Venmo. So
but you'll get it. We are we are never trying to screw you out of
your $7 or whatever it is each month, I promise to you. Okay.
Now then, Joe, do we have a movie corner? I'm actually going
to do three trying to spotlight on three movies. I think people
should check out because I haven't seen it yet.
Yeah, I can go through three.
Okay, if you start, I'll be right back. What are you starting
with?
I'm going to start with we talked about Michael Mann a bit
earlier with the movie thief. Yes, I'm going to start with a
movie that I watched last night. That when I looked up who
directed this, I couldn't believe Michael Mann had directed
it. It's a little picture called public. Yeah. Yeah, we
said what you're gonna guess.
No, I was actually gonna guess last the Mohicans because it's so
like he's usually a modern day crime kind of guy. No public
enemies I saw in theaters, I get it mixed up with black mass the
other Johnny Depp gangster movie, but I remember hating
public enemies. But go ahead, Joe.
It sucks. Yeah, it's painfully boring.
It's a period piece gangster movie about John Dillinger,
babyface Nelson.
Pretty Boy Floyd, Frank Nitti.
Who else is in this damn thing? What other characters?
I want to look this up.
Because I don't want to forget anybody.
So Johnny Depp plays
John Dillinger.
Oh, we're off to a good start, right? You got Michael Mann
directing. We're going to make a movie with Michael Mann about
John Dillinger. Okay, I'm listening. Johnny Depp is going
to play John Dillinger. Okay, I'm listening.
Christian Bale is going to play Melvin Purvis, the guy who was
one of the founding members of the Federal Bureau of
Investigation, who's going to be his adversary. Okay, great. I'm
going to be babyface Nelson.
Okay, who else you got in this thing? Well, we'll toss in
Giovanni Robisi. We're going to have Channing Tatum. We're going
to have Stephen Lang. We're going to have Stephen Dorff.
We're going to have Carey Mulligan. We're going to have
Lily Sebesky.
I'm in.
Let's watch Public Enemies.
Holy shit. It's a boring movie.
It plays like it plays like the pilot to a UPN show about
gangsters. Everything is too clean looking. Everybody is too
pretty. There isn't enough grit, not that there's no grit. But
there just isn't enough. And it sort of romanticizes that error
of the gangster, which I get that they're probably doing that
on purpose. That era is is sort of romanticized. These these men
were like public figures and celebrities and heroes to a lot
of people. You know, they actually cared what the public
thought about what their crimes were. There's a scene in that
where Johnny Depp speaks to that. So there's a lot of
interesting elements to the movie. And this is certainly an
interesting time period and certainly an interesting story.
But the movie is just a snooze and it carries none of the
Michael Mann trademarks you know that he's so great with with
directing and God Almighty, it's just boring, man. It's just
really, really boring. Did not like it. And he had a bad
period, you know, like that. I thought Ali was really boring.
Mm hmm. You know, and like three hours and just kind of like hit
every biopic trope, you know, but when he's on, there's
there's few better. He's got a show coming to HBO Max starring
Ansel Elgort, which I have very low excitement about.
Well, I cringe just in the opening scene of this thing when
I saw Jason Clarke get out of the car and I was like, this man
has never been in a good movie ever. Ever. Yeah, you're kind of
perplexed at why he's allowed to keep working, but he is. Well,
he's not a bad actor. He's fine. He's just, he's fine. But
there are plenty of actors that are as competent, if not more
competent than him, that never work again, after the amount of
bombs he has led the charge on. So I think wasn't he even in
black mass, which you and I saw together seems to love. Oh,
yeah, you know what he is in black. I think is he I love
No, I don't see him in black mass. I'm looking here. I really
love black mass. In fact, I just bought the blu ray. But
I actually the only thing I've ever really liked him in was
Brotherhood, which is a very underrated Showtime original
mob show that lasted three seasons. I thought that was a
great show. But it's Jason Clarke and also Jason Isaac's
to Jason's both actors who have just been in so many duds and
who you know when you see him, but you kind of don't care. But
it did work. Jason Clarke was in the Pet Sematary reboot, of
course. Can you believe that was only two years ago that we saw
Pet Sematary?
No,
Just awful, just awful.
So his Michael man's next two movies. One of them is called
Enzo Ferrari, which
God is a so it's like, okay, your three hour Muhammad Ali
biopic was boring. How do you think your Enzo Ferrari biopics
Yeah, and he's got driver playing Ferrari.
Which mini?
So I'm not excited for that. I'm sure Adam driver will be fine
in it. But it's just weird to me that he's got driver. We're
coming back now to play another Italian historical figure.
Right. Maybe he was like, we need to find a driver. And they
all look at each other like, oh, fuck.
Doesn't that seem like he saw House of Gucci and was like,
let's get Adam driver to do this. I don't know why you're doing
it in a post Ford versus Ferrari world. Like, how much of this
shit do we need?
This one I'm excited about potentially. He's doing a movie
about Sam G and Kana. And Chicago crime boss, Tom, Tony
Ricardo, that I'm in, I'm interested in that Sam G and
Kana. You know, he's he's he's featured in the Irishman. He's
featured in the Rat Pack movie. He you know, he's a big figure
in the in the election of John F. Kennedy and potentially the
assassination that that that sounds interesting to me.
Anyway, that's my number one movie corner. And also not my
number two. Well, no, I'm going, I'm going.
I thought you were just gonna name three movies people should
see. That's what I'm doing for my own corner this week.
And I'm actually I thought it'd be like really fast to just do
three in a row. Well, I'll be faster. No, no, I'm not saying
you need to forget it. Let me speak.
I didn't understand.
I'm actually doing three movies that start with a letter A that
you may not have seen, but that I really think are something
special. For starters, I'm going to start with a picture that
made me realize that what was wrong with my father was deep
depression that would also be passed down to me. That movie is
called Affliction. You seen that one, Joe? No, you would love
this movie. And if you're in the market for something real, dark
and depressing, but also I just think an incredible movie, I
recommend that it is written and directed by the great Paul
Schrader, who fumbled this year, I would say with the card
counter, but otherwise, has written and or directed a lot of
great films. And it stars Nick Nolte, I would say Nick Nolte's
best performance as a I'm just gonna read the sentence, a
deeply troubled small town cop who was investigating a
suspicious hunting death, while other events jeopardize his
humanity. And that is a good description of it. It is Nick
Nolte trying to solve this crime, while he has a horrible
toothache. And his father, James Coburn, who one best supporting
actor for this film, torments him at both in the past and
present. He is a completely sick, abusive father. You got
Willem Dafoe, who's always in the Paul Schrader films, you got
sissy space, who's fantastic in it, the murder mystery elements
of it, you know, traders, traders never been the best at
like plotting. But as a study of a deeply troubled man, and as a
study of depression, and how fathers can fuck up sons, both
chemically and also with their actions. I just think it's an
amazing movie. It blew me away when I saw it in the theaters.
And I watch it every couple years since I think it's great.
But I remember coming home one night, I was a senior in high
school or something. And my dad was sitting staring into
darkness. And I said, What are you doing? And he was like, I
just finished this movie, Affliction. And I was like, Oh,
I wanted to see that I heard it was really depressing. And he
goes, Well, sometimes that's what you want.
Oh, wow. All right. I was like, Okay, cool. I'm gonna head to
bed. But anyway, that's that's a conversation I look back for a
lot, especially given the the thematic nature of the film. My
guess is my dad was thinking about his own dad, giving these
demons on to him and thinking about how he was giving those
demons on to me. And it's just that kind of movie. It's deep as
fuck. And I think even in Paul Schrader's canon, it is
underrated and not talked about near enough. Check it out.
I watched I got on a little kick there for a minute where I was
buying blu rays of made for TV horror movies. Don't be afraid
of the dark I picked up trilogy of terror I picked up. Another
one I picked up was called Bad Ronald, which is a lot of fun.
Always wanted to see that. Highly recommended. Highly
recommended. You got Dabney Coleman in there. First of all,
love that.
This is a movie I would love to remake, like an art like to
make an R rated version of it. But it's about a kid played by
Scott Jacoby, who accidentally he's you know, he's he's been
raised in a strange, potentially abusive setting. He is bullied
by the kids in his neighborhood for being a weirdo. Yeah, a
young girl starts making fun of him. He shoves her and
accidentally kills her. And instead of turning himself in,
his mother hides him in the attic. Okay, and, and he lives
in the attic and then slowly goes crazy. His mom eventually.
This is spoilers. I'm going to give you spoilers here. His mom
eventually dies. He's stuck living in the attic and a family
moves in. And as he lives in this attic, he he draws and
creates draws pictures of and creates a fantasy world where
he's a magical prince. And things unfold from there and go
go right.
Yeah, I'm gonna watch that. So it's on prime. So keep that.
Keep the secrets to yourself. But this guy looks like my
friend, Rick Glassman. You know, Rick Glassman does look like
Rick Glassman.
So yeah, yeah, I know it is Scott Jacobi. If you don't know
who he is, he played Dorothy's son on Golden Girls. That's
that. Yes.
That's I've been watching so much Golden Girls. I'm in I'm
deep in season six, which means I'm nearing the end.
There's wonderful episodes in season six and seven. You can
you see the drop off in the overall product, but there's
still wonderful episodes in there. Anyway, bad Ronald, you
can purchase it on Amazon, I think for like for the blue
is like 12 bucks or something. It's worth grabbing.
What was their big hit? Bad Ronald, remember that like they
were a shitty rap rock band? No, I had a hit. All right. It says
Let's begin and first time I can't, I couldn't sing either of
those songs, but I know they had hits. Bad Ronald, good call,
Joe. I'm going to check out that one. I urge you to check out a
picture called Arlington Road. Have you seen that one?
Yes.
Arlington Road is a very, very good thriller. Its production
was extremely problematic because and again, I don't want
to get into any sort of spoiler territory here, especially for
this one. But it is as dark as it gets. It's got a actually,
both of these that I'm giving you affliction and this are just
almost nihilistically depressing movies, hopeless
movies. And honestly, that's what I kind of gravitate towards.
I got to be honest, the wrestler I watched the other night,
another hopeless masterpiece. But Arlington Road is actually
coming back into the public eye because somehow they are making
a TV series of it, which I don't even understand. But I don't get
that at all.
I will absolutely be watching it. I guess it could be
something like The Americans. I mean, Arlington Road is
basically a guy, Jeff Bridges and Tim Robbins. And Tim
Robbins moves into this neighborhood and his wife is Joan
Cusack and Bridges becomes convinced that something is off.
And that is kind of the premise of The Americans. So maybe you
could do that as a TV show. I just don't know how you keep the
tension going that long. But I hope Davis plays Jeff Bridges
wife. And the deal is, there is a boy played by Dennis the
Menace from the film, who's stumbling in the middle of the
road with these horrible injuries on his hands. Michael
takes him to the hospital, Bridges takes him to the
hospital, meets his parents Tim Robbins and Joan Cusack, they
become friends. And then they find some blueprints, all sorts
of suspicious stuff going on. And they're worried that this
guy is some sort of terrorist. It is written by Aaron Krueger,
who did some of the screams the ring. He's a horror guy, he did
the new Top Gun. And I just think he is a really good
screenwriter who does good shit. This movie is very well
directed. It is very tense. And the ending is an all timer. I
will never forget seeing this in the theater and hearing people
just not be happy about it. And sometimes that's fun to be a
part of. People were really pissed at the end of this movie
and I get it. Actually, so the tagline of Arlington Road is
fear thy neighbor. Could that be a title of my movie? Fear thy
neighbor?
You want to steal a tagline from another movie, instead of just
using a word that makes sense, because the root word of that
word was used by Seth Rogen.
Yeah, I think so.
It's ridiculous. It's so all right. I'll throw neighborly
out, Joe. Yeah, throw neighborly out. But um, yeah,
Arlington Road is a thriller that like most people I don't
think have even heard of. There are a lot of these like that's
that's something people pitch me is like, just make it the
street. That's definitely what happened with Arlington Road, by
the way, they were like, what could the title be? And they
will just call it the name of the street or that one with
Samuel L. Jackson, Lakeview Terrace. Yeah. So clearly,
they're they're a hard genre to name, but I'm not going to call
it Lyric Avenue or whatever the hell I want to call it. So
we'll see.
Um, by the way, Hope Davis, prime candidate for actor who
has played the most amount of unlikable people on screen.
Oh, she thrives at it. And I, I thought I didn't like her with
leota. Yeah, no, for sure. Yeah, she I was when you said it
just now, I almost said, Oh, yeah, the most boring actors
alive, but I just don't like her in anything like about Schmidt
is one of my favorite movies, but I hate her character in it.
And I hate her character in American Splendor. And in a lot
of movies, she just plays unlikable people so well that
it's easy to mistake it as her sucking, but she's good at
playing them. So
all right, my last pick is also technically, I guess I made for
TV movie. I have a subscription to room org magazine, if any of
you are in I guess this is a bonus scary stuff. If you guys
are interested in reading about horror, what's going on in the
horror business, mainly cinema, but they also get into records
and video games and books and all kinds of stuff. But it's
primarily focused on cinema. Both now and then there's a lot
of stuff in there about rereleases and special editions
of blu rays and whatever. It's a lot of fun. I like the magazine
quite a bit. It's worth the subscription.
I read about a movie in there called slap face. It sounded
interesting. It got a decent review. And I found out that it
was debuting on shutter. So I was excited to see that it had
finally premiered on shutter. I watched it. I was very excited
given the plot that a boy who had lost his parents in a car
accident forges a very dangerous friendship with a monster he
lives in the far who lives in the forest. I was like, well,
this sounds fun. Find out at the beginning of the movie. The
monster is a witch, even better. Okay. And it's called slap
face because his older brother who is now tasked with raising
him. In order for them to deal with their past trauma, they
play a game called slap face where they hit each other in the
face repeatedly to toughen each other up, which is mildly
disturbing to watch, but it's not terrible. Anyway, the movie
focuses mostly on the idea of bullying, whether that's his
brother bullying him into playing slap face. So he doesn't
become weak, whether it's the girl he likes bullying him
because she's embarrassed that she likes him back, or these
twin girls that live in his neighbor who bully him and beat
him up and are really rude to him. Or a monster that he
becomes friends with basically bullying him by doing terrible
things on his behalf under the guise of look, you know, I care
about you when it when it doesn't. All the elements are in
play. For this to be great. Movie sucks. Okay, it just
sucks. It's it's it's another one of these like we talked
about with antlers. Everything is just dreary and hopeless and
boring and moping and somber and whatever. There's nothing
exciting. It's when you first encounter the witch, it's pretty
exciting. And then it never goes anywhere. You got this thing
walking around in broad daylight through most of the movie.
Everybody is so unlikable, including the main kid eventually
who you feel bad for. Dan Hedaya turns in a pretty good
performance as the police chief.
Or the sheriff. He's probably 70. No, he's got to be more than
he's probably 75. He's been 70 in the 90s. Yeah. So
Can I what if Zendaya married Dan Hedaya?
Her name would be Zendaya Hedaya.
She should carry on his legacy and start rebooting his big
roles. And why wouldn't the most beautiful and talented
actress of her generation marry Dan Hedaya at this point? I just
don't she's dating Superman. Really? You got Hedaya out here
the dad and clueless baby. She's dating Tortelli. Spider -Man.
That's what I said, right?
He said Superman. I thought for a second.
Anyway, look, all you need to know about this movie is, in my
opinion, is most of the reviews you read about it are going to
say things like, but the true horror. Yeah, bullying.
shove it up your ass, get out of my face. I don't give a shit.
Here's the thing. The idea of humans being the real monsters
is interesting when it's an occasional delve in the horror
genre, not when it is the standard which it is becoming
and it's annoying and stupid. Yeah.
I did not like the movie.
Okay, fair enough.
What's the new one they got on shutter? This it's called like
the scary of that's one I want to see because I hear it's very
polarizing. The scary of 61st. That's another terrible title.
It's terrible. And I read about it. And I was like, I don't
care. But I mean, I'll watch it if you want to do it on the
show. I'm losing my faith and shutter almost. We've talked
about it. But I mean, even they're made for originals. Now
I'm just like, God, guys, like, I don't remember. Like, I think
I liked the one with Clancy Brown. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Fine. Like, but it wasn't great. It was just like pretty good.
You know, like,
I think shutter clearly has limited resources, limited money.
And they are often buying the horror movies that don't get
bought by anyone else. And they can get them for a good price.
They do put they throw up great old shit all the time. And always
something where I'm like, Oh, yes, that's on here. I've always
wanted to see that. And of course, Joe Bob makes it
worthwhile. But I guess but he's just playing like he's just
playing. Now it's just like, they got Joe Bob doing like the
most obvious movies that I know that are on there already.
There's nothing exciting about it. Like, I'm not excited to see
Joe Bob reveal four movies he's going to host that have been
sitting on that fucking streaming service for eight
months.
I agree that sucks. However, I love Joe Bob so much. I love
him too. I love the man. On the scary 61st, which I just brought
up the scary of 61st doesn't even make sense. It does say
several prolonged and extremely graphic scenes of explicit and
exclusive female masturbation and simulated sex. Then it says
in a second thing, gratuitous and exploitive, full frontal
female nudity. So there you go.
All right, I'm back in. Let's see. frequent strong references
to Jeffrey Epstein's crimes and references his sexual abuse, sex
with minors and sex trafficking.
That's odd.
Yeah. All right. Whatever it is, I don't even know the plot, but
I'm going to watch it. My third is because I was talking about
David Gordon Green and his great work with Danny McBride. They
have been friends forever. And the first time I saw Danny McBride,
it was either this or The Foot Fist Way, which is a
masterpiece, a precursor to Eastbound and Down. But David
Gordon Green wrote and directed this movie, a true indie called
All the Real Girls with Paul Schneider, Zoe Deschanel before
she became completely annoying. Shea Wiggum, who now you
recognize from all kinds of great shit, and Patricia Clarkson.
The gist is it's it's a very true indie. It's like a young
womanizer living in a small southern town. He's fucked all
the girls in town. But then his good friends younger sister, who
is I believe very young in this like maybe 16 or something, comes
home and now he wants to get with her. But she's a virgin and
kind of makes him decide that he wants to be a better man. It's a
very small movie, very low budget. It stayed with me
forever. I think you can only get it on DVD. I've had my copy
forever. It might be one of those that cost a dollar on
Amazon. It might be one that's now worth 100. I don't know. But
I would never give it up because I love it. Danny McBride plays a
character named Bustass. He is very funny in this. But for the
most part, this is a really, really good moving young people
romance that is way better than you would expect by that
description. Check out all the real girls.
All right. Here we go. Here we go.
About jackass forever.
Tell the Joe, I'll say this, sometimes when you text me while
you're watching a movie, like when you're texting me while
you're watching the Batman, which as I told you last night,
our friend Matt McCarthy said is a masterpiece.
I will call him yell at him about that later. But man, I
can't wait to review the Batman on this show.
Well, we're going to but when you text me during a movie, and
you're like, I don't know, this is kind of boring, or as it's
getting kind of old or whatever it is, if, if, if I go, I don't
know, I haven't seen it, then we drop it. But if I if you get a
rise out of me, if I go, wait a minute, I like what are you
talking about, then the texts start coming hard and fast, and
they get meaner and meaner. And I think then you just you dig in
and you hate it because you want to
know, I only do that when you have a condescending response to
my saying I hated it, which is probably most of the time, I
can't, they're too far, there's too far back into my text to
my to find it because I was also doing that. Yeah. But I tell
luck, it's jackass, there's not a lot to explain here, right?
It's, it's, it's, it's the remaining members of the crew.
And they're bringing in a new group, I called that they were
going to do this years before a year before they announced that
they were going to do this, I said, they're going to do, I
was saying it to Sal, I go there, I bet you that new jackass
is going to be them ushering in a new generation, it's going to
be like their force awakens or whatever. And he's like, No way,
no way. And I was like, I'm telling you, dude, they're gonna
do that. And they did. Rachel Wolfson, who I know from stand
up and is a friend is in it. She does some crazy shit in it. This
guy poops, he kind of steals the show. This new guy poopsie.
Yeah, the new fat guy. No, no, no poopsies. Not the new fat
guy. Oh, no, you're right. He didn't like poopsie. I don't know.
I don't get poopsie. He's clearly willing to do anything,
which I guess what I mean here, but that's what I didn't have
the personality. Like for jackass. I'm just like, this guy
is a gym. He'll let you hit him in the balls repeatedly. And she
doesn't care. fat guys funny. And there you go. I mean, here's
your movie. Let's get in. You like well, I did not at all. I
liked it a lot. I pretty recently watched all three over
the pandemic when I was at my most depressed and it actually
helped. I think these movies help not only not only because
they're so laugh out loud funny and they hit that place that
makes you make noise, as Joe discussed on the last last
month. There's aha funny and haha funny jackasses,
unquestionably haha funny. But also the camaraderie of the
friends of the boys, them cheering each other on them
liking each other. It. That's part of it too. You know, I
always liked the show, but the movies seem to really get their
together. One blew me away. Three because of the 3d aspect
also blew me away. And I think two is the masterpiece ending
in that thing with the guy with the pubes and the trunk of the
cab, which is one of the greatest pranks ever ever done.
Jackass four is nowhere near those heights. But when I did
it on letterbox, I had five stars for the first three and
this one was a four. You know, I think that it certainly does its
job, which is that it's laugh out loud, funny, and you care
about these people. I don't think the new people really make
a great impression. I don't think like Tyler, the creator
made a good impression. I don't think I can't believe they let
machine gun Kelly on this.
So let me interject real quick, because there's a lot to touch
on. First of all, this movie is padded like like a 12 year old's
bra. I mean, it is just should have been 90 minutes. It's an
hour 45.
Yeah, they are shoving every fucking celebrity were willing
to walk on to set into this thing, because they know they
know that it's ailing. Why? Because Ryan Dunn is sadly
deceased. And Bam is not there. Bam's absence is painfully
obvious, not just on camera, but from behind camera. You can tell
Bam thought of a lot of the great shit that they did. And
it's not there. You know who else isn't there? Rab himself.
And that Rab himself, that whole extended crew from can't kill
yourself, the Westchester guys, none of them are there. The
entire and then you also don't realize they get in there. Oh,
yeah, without Bam, we don't get April and Bam's dad either. So
they're gone. So all of the this whole like familial part of the
jackass crew is just gone. Gone. Ryan's gone. Bam's gone. Bam's
parents are gone. Bam's skater friends are not there. Brendan
Novak is not there. None of them are there. So to make up for
this absence, they now have Eric Andre and machine gun Kelly.
And who else did you say?
Tyler, the creator, Tyler, the creator, and it's Eric Andre
fits right in. I mean, Eric, Eric, one of these, and I
thought it was very fun. Eric fits, Eric fits right in. Eric's
a friend of mine. Put Eric in the goddamn new crew then.
Yeah. You know, at one point, they've got a new guy's dad
doing stunts. That was weird. I'll grant you. I think they just
found him funny or something. And he was funny. But there's no
like, here, here's the new crew kind of intro. They're just
sort of there and a part of it. And that's sort of weird. And I
agree that it fucks with the camaraderie. Certainly, having
these new people, I'll give you. However, in a world where
theatrical comedy is almost non existent, comedy in general is
going away, but theatrical comedy is pretty much
non existent. I find it hard to quibble about something like
that. You can quibble, don't get me wrong. But I laughed
throughout, I absolutely did. And also, I think it's important
to know, because it shouldn't always matter with movies. But
this one, it does. You got to be with a group, you got to be
with a crowded theater. And if you're drunk or high, obviously,
that's a huge plus. Joe, when I first talked to you, you said
you were waiting to find a friend because I can't go
alone. You wound up going to a solo show on a Monday. What do
you want from me? I couldn't find anybody to go I had to
watch it to do the damn review. I was out of time. Nobody could
go when I could go. And that was it. I mean, look, I went in. I
saw I saw double feature that day. I was excited. I saw the
cursed first, which we're going to review next time. And then
after after that, I was like, Oh, I'm like gonna get to go see
Jackass now. And I was excited to like go in and laugh. And I
can tell you this right now, we you're in trouble from from the
first moment. The second that opening, they always do a big
crazy stunt opening to these things. That's very cinematic.
The second this opening to this movie was scripted. And I mean,
scripted with like Johnny Knoxville playing a character
where it was like a sketch. I was like, here we go. Like, here
we go. They're not able to do what they used to do. So we're
off to a bad start. Oh, it's Chris Pontius is dick attacking
a city. It's not real. This none of this is real. Oh, the
stunts that are folded into this opening are like clearly
enhanced and whatever. And it's just I'm like, I'm sorry, the
bites gone. We're not in this theater watching this because
these these guys are great actors. We're here to see one
thing, then get the shit kicked out of each other and have it be
hilarious. Right off the bat, that's gone. And then the first
real stunt in the movie is like the is like the bike ramp thing.
And you're like, it's pretty funny. But it can't hold a
candle to like the hand slap with the soup and all that. And
here's why I can't hold a candle. Because as you just said,
the camaraderie is gone. I was talking to be homes about the
movie. He hasn't he hadn't seen it yet. I said, Pete, it is the
Michael Bay version of a jackass movie. There is there is a lot of
spectacle and staging around stuff that means absolutely
nothing. The big showpiece stunt at the end has like bombs
going off around them. You know goddamn well, none of those
bombs are going to hit anybody. Who cares? It's stupid. You know
goddamn well, when the bear which they teased in the trailer
comes into the room with danger, Aaron, there's no fucking chance
in hell that bear is going to hurt him. You know that. So it
just doesn't have any of the bite of anything. It's just
boring. They rehash stunts that they did on the TV show. There's
like six exploding chair gags in this. It just gets fucking old.
We see Johnny Knoxville get hit by a bull for the 77th time. I
don't care anymore. There's one sequence that does have bam in
it. And they don't even call attention to it. And then like
halfway through it, you see that it's bam. And you're like, that's
making me sad, especially when the entire campaign of this movie
was when's the last time you got together with some friends to
laugh your asses off? Well, you've got a hard, disgusting
lawsuit going on around this thing. It's not being done
correctly. You've brought in new people because you guys can't do
the stunts anymore. I mean, granted, what's bam suing them
for? Like they thought he should have still been in it even though
he was on drugs and wasn't saying they forced him into a
program that was horrible for his mental health and physical
health. It was actually more dangerous than him just being
drunk. Whether that's true or not, who knows? Bam also went
off the fucking rails and threatened Jeff Tremaine, right?
So like, it's like, dude, you know, it's all fucked up. And
you're sitting there. What this is like, the thing I would
compare it to is like when Wu Tang was beefing Rayquan and
RZA were having like all the ugliness they were having, they
didn't put that last Wu Tang record out until that shit was
over. And then on that first track, they reference it and
it's like triumphant and you're excited and it's awesome that
everything is good again. And that's what needed to happen
with this movie. This is not a movie that needed to be rushed
out by any stretch, by any stretch, especially in this
fashion. I'm not, I'm not watching this movie to watch
Chris Pontius tell a bunch of young people, we already paid
your, our dues, so now it's your turn. I don't give a fuck. What
am I hearing? Danger Aaron is the only one that does anything
in the movie. And then Knoxville does a couple of things. Even
Steve -O was like way backed off, which I was surprised to see.
I hear you. I hear you. And I think that there is a better
movie to be made than this by assembling both Jackass 2 .5,
which was the direct to DVD sequel. Yes. And a bunch of the
deleted scenes from the other three. I think there's a better
movie to be made out of those odds and ends than this. However,
as a fun night out with friends, a lot of it, you know, I was
seeing a guy I hadn't seen in 10 years in Atlanta and we went out
and had a good time and a couple drinks and saw the movie. You
know, I was happy to have that experience. I'm happy to be able
to laugh in a theater because it happens so rarely. In my being
too kind to it, probably because so I just brought up the list of
stunts from the film. And as I was scrolling through, I what I
wanted to be able to do was to say, well, what about this one,
Joe? What about this one? And the truth is, I kind of can't, you
know, like, there wasn't there wasn't really that amazing thing
like, Oh, my God, could you believe X? You're right, there
wasn't. I loved in furniture shopping one where the fat guy
jumps on the thing and sends that was great grandpa through
the ceiling. That was, you know, there are some good moments
when Preston shits his pants for seemingly no reason. You know,
that made me laugh. That was getting hit in the nuts with the
machine. That was great. You know, machine nuts thing was
great. It's not without a furnished furniture store gag
was great. The Eric Andre prank was great where he just gets hit
buying the coffee. Yeah, great. So sometimes the simplest stuff
was the funny. But it didn't have. It's like the tarantula
fight. Okay, that's pretty cool. Why is it? Why is it a guy's
dad? I don't care. Yeah, that was weird. How about Steve Oh,
with the bees covering his dick? That wasn't that wasn't
nothing. No, it wasn't nothing. It was crazy. It was horrifying.
But it was also just like, this is just horrifying. Like, I'm
not like, and they always had stuff that was horrifying. I was
texting with a with a friend of mine, and I said, I'm sorry. It
was 1000 times funnier. When they revealed the prank that
they did during part two, that they had jerked off and Johnny
Knoxville's face lotion. Yes. And he was using the face lotion
for a month. That's 1000 times funnier, smaller, more endearing
of a prank amongst friends, then in this them spraying literally
gallons of pig come on people. Right? Like, what does this even
mean? Who cares? Like, it's just stupid. Like, it's not even it's
supposed to be stupid. But like, there was supposed to mean
anything. There was nothing like the doorbell ring from part
three, when the fucking balloon is coming out and hitting them
in the face when they're going to Johnny's house. There was
nothing like the fire hose rodeo. There was it just it was,
you know, like, you know, like in the in the very first stunt
with the bike ramps. Preston Lacey immediately is like, get
me out, get me out, get me out. You know, you're like, these
guys are too old to be doing this. Like, it's
well, that was I listened to an interview with Lance bangs,
who's the guy who's always filming it and puking in the
corner. He's a friend of mine. I love Lance. Oh, great. He's
how when they had a period of like, I don't know, do we have
enough to make a movie, that kind of thing. And apparently,
the very first stunt was the bike ramp thing. I think that's
why it's it's first up in this. But yeah, I mean, you've almost
convinced me that I was disappointed in it, even though
I didn't feel like it at the time. But you know, it's, it's
worth seeing. And if you're a fan of jackass, you're going to
enjoy it. And I think it's better than bad trip, which was
the Eric Andre Laurel version of this that went straight to
Netflix. And that was a pretty funny movie, too. So it's not
saying nothing to me that this gave me a lot of good laughs.
But I also agree with a lot of what you're saying that there
were some disappointing aspects.
This was also better than any of the scripted Knoxville Tremaine.
Oh, yeah, they did. Yeah. Although I don't know if it was
better than bad grandpa, because that had some great stuff in
it. I think it was because this was more bad grandpa to me was
more prank based. Yes, yes. And this is obviously more stunt
based. But
well, they also talked about on that interview how, like when
they got out in the world, and, and we're like, okay, let's get
going. And they were like, wait a minute, we can't be pranking
people during a global pandemic. Like, their nerves are shot. I
think that that added a lot of trouble to the production as
well.
That's what I mean. It's like, and you're doing this. And then
like halfway, it's ridiculous halfway through the movie,
everybody's suddenly wearing pandemic masks. Yeah, yeah, guys,
you just put like bees on Steve O's dick. You're worried. Come
on, guys. Like, so
you know, some of the stuff that new people like I said did was
impressive. It was impressive seeing Rachel do the stun gun
on the tongue thing without making a noise. Yes.
Poopsie, poopsie getting bit in the face multiple times by the
snake was impressive and scary. But even that part where Johnny
Knoxville is like, is this snake poisonous? And the guys like,
and Johnny Knoxville was like, it's like, we know it's not
poisonous. Yeah, stop. Like, we know it's that point. Also, like,
I'm sorry, man. I don't know why this bugged me so much. This is
a nitpick. I'm admitting it before I even say it. For some
reason, it bugged me. After the great thing they did to Eric
with the coffee thing. Yes. When Johnny Knoxville comes out
and he goes, What did you guys do to Eric? It's like, Oh, God,
like, it was just so like, Oh, I get it. You're all wild boys. You
know, like, there was none of the hair. I still love Knoxville.
I mean, he's not a great character. He Listen, I'm not
saying he is. I said I admit it's nitpicky. There was just
something about it where it was too. I get it. We're the bad
boys. I don't know. It just bugged me. There was just even
like in the second, in the third movie, when it's like the dick
cam and they're pissing on each other. Yes. Or the clipper cam
and they're cutting, they're shaving everybody's it was so
fucking funny, dude. It was so the rocky glove coming in in
slow motion was so fucking funny. It's just basic shit.
Like that that that this just didn't have it just didn't have
any of that. And you know, knowing that there's this
disgusting, nasty court feud going on around the movie. And
then it really also just undercut the beautiful ending
of the third movie where the credits roll and it's the
retrospective of them as kids and how they give you that I
don't bring the tear to your eye this but that still exists. You
know, I'll give you that though it this what this should have
been is a is a point five a directed yes if they still did
that sort of agree. I agree. Anyway, folks, my hog is down
for jackass forever. It's down. Damn. Mine is up for sure. And
I think a good night out with friends. I think beer is a
almost crucial element to this entire franchise beer or weed
friends camaraderie, etc. But you know, manage your
expectations a bit.
I saw I saw the first three stones over. Okay, and left my
goddamn ass off. Like, I don't think that beer or weed should
have to be a prerequisite. Shouldn't I do admit that not
seeing it with if I'd seen it with a group of friends, I
might be at a at a almost half mass maybe. Yes, but I just was
like, I never thought I'd see the day that a jackass movie
was a grim reminder of mortality. But this is here it
is. This is this did it. I left the movie theater depressed.
Yeah, I mean, that honestly a bit and this is a horrible way
to go out. But very often, recently, I asked myself, was
this movie that bad? Or am I severely depressed? Sure. And I
know what I know the answer is is both in most cases, but I do
know that it's really hard to like anything when you're
depressed. So I don't know, I think you got a perfect trilogy
and you can you can saddle this right up with with jackass 2 .5
or one of the other lesser jackass films. Very great. We're
going to be back with the Batman starring Bob Pattinson. By the
way, would he have been as big a star if his name was Bob
Pattinson? I say no, we wouldn't know who he had a chance. And
we'll also be talking about The Cursed, a movie which I saw at
virtual Sundance a year ago, but still went to the theater
thinking I had not seen. I've done that. I've done and left
the movie still not sure if I've seen it. But we'll be talking
about The Cursed and the Batman. And see you and help pod
Instagram, the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram show.
Joe DeRosa comedy, Twitter and Instagram. I can't stress it
enough. Please come see me in Philadelphia. If you're in the
New Jersey, Delaware tri state area. I'm there this coming
Thursday through Saturday five shows. And then please come see
me at South by Southwest. I am doing a bunch of stand up shows
there. But the big event is I'm doing a 5pm show on Tuesday.
The whatever that Tuesday is this 15th, the 16th of March,
whatever it is at the creaking cave. It's called the sandwich
summit roundtable discussion with me and other sandwich
makers and some comics to pepper and sweeten up the
discussion. It's gonna be a lot of fun. Anyway, we'll see you
next time. And we'll see you in hell.