I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Ha ha ha hoooooks it's we'll see you in hell.
We're here today to talk about from beyond, the classic to some.
From beyond.
Yes, a classic to some, correct, would you say so Paul Walsh?
I think this is considered by some a classic.
I mean, Reanimator is probably your Stuart Gordon most beloved.
But from beyond is sort of the redheaded step child.
I feel like it's got its passionate defenders and fans.
I would call, from beyond the Pinkerton of Stuart Gordon's catalog, it's where things
take a darker turn, but maybe it's even a better product, who knows?
We'll get into it.
And then the one he did where Mina Suvari gets stuck in the hood of a car is their Maladroit,
probably.
What is that one?
It's called Stuck.
I saw it.
Is it new?
I bet it's 10 years old.
If I remember correctly, it's Mina Suvari in a white trash role.
She's drunk and hits a homeless man played by Stephen Ray, who seemingly doesn't even
act anymore and was never a very compelling actor despite working for 30 years.
His body is lodged in her car and she can't get it out, so she pulls into her garage and
kind of lets him, leaves him in there.
It's based on a true story.
Okay.
Jesus Christ.
It was more dark comedy than horror.
It was an okay movie.
I think Stuart Gordon makes cool shit, and I have recommended on here numerous times
King of the Ants, which I think is one of his more underrated movies.
We I think have discussed it, but Stuart Gordon did Edmund, the adaptation of the David Mamet
which I saw in the theater on opening weekend, and it was the most uncomfortable I've ever
been in a movie theater next to when I watched Gerard de Pardue have full penetration threesomes
in Welcome to New York.
But yeah, it was uncomfortable.
The exclamation of the N -word throughout that entire movie.
Yeah.
It's uncomfortable watching that in a public place.
Now I remember seeing Edmund, but nothing about it.
That is William H. Macy as just a guy who's racist.
That's the plot.
It's, well, it's a dissection of race, of violence, of a lot of things, and the basic
premise of the movie, or the basic theme of the movie is you will become whatever you
fear the most.
And at the beginning of the movie, it's established that William H. Macy is in a loveless marriage
with Rebecca Pigeon.
He's in a dead end job where he gets no respect and that he feels he's in a prison.
And he, the movie, the catalyst of the movie is him telling his wife, I'm leaving or I'm
going.
And she says, well, if you're going to the store, get milk or whatever.
And he goes, no, I'm going.
And she's like, what are you talking about?
And he goes, I'm going and I'm not coming back.
I don't want to be married anymore.
And he leaves.
And he has the most wild, insane, catastrophic night of his life that does involve encounters
with him being violent, with him being racist.
And then ultimately he ends up, at the end of the movie, in prison for life because he
murders, I think it's Minasavari, no, it's not Minasavari, it's What's -Her -Face from
10 Things I Hate About You.
Julius Stiles.
Yeah.
He murders Julius Stiles and ends up in prison with Bokeem Woodbine, who is his cellmate,
who rapes him the first day.
And then they end up being madly in love.
And that's the end.
So I guess the idea is that he feared other races and he feared being in prison and then
he ends up, but it turns out that's what he wanted.
He finds his happiness being in prison in an interracial relationship.
It's a very intense movie.
It's very strange.
I don't remember any of that and you'd think I would, but yeah.
Well, there's a scene where he kills a pimp with a knife.
And it is, the story I read was when they were shooting the movie, I forget who the
actor or actress was that was shooting on the soundstage above them or next to them
or something.
They had to go over to where they were shooting and be like, guys, what is going on over here?
Do we need to call the police?
Because he, the scene, he screams the N -word so many times and so crazily and so you're
in the theater and you're sort of just bracing yourself because you know the scene is coming
and then it does.
And it's not comfortable.
It's very uncomfortable.
But I guess that's kind of the point is it's supposed to make you uncomfortable.
Anyway, yeah, I mean, I'm looking at the man's the man's career here.
It was pretty great.
He mostly stayed in the low budget world, but probably made most of his money off, believe
it or not, the Honey, I Shrunk the Kids franchise, which he wrote the stories for, correct?
Yeah.
And the characters and he did a first draft of the Honey, I Shrunk the Kids script.
I know he was supposed to direct it at some point.
Here's the writers on this PG rated movie that I loved so much as a kid, Ed Naha, I
don't know who that is.
Brian Yuzna, who did Society, one of the most sexual and disturbing films ever made, and
then Stuart Gordon, who did Reanimator and all this stuff.
Interesting that Yuzna is right on deck in this from beyond.
And I got to tell you without spoiling too much, Yuzna's fingerprints are all over this
movie.
Yeah.
I mean, Yuzna is clearly one of the great freaks that there is.
I've been learning more about the Screaming Mad George who popped up on those five hour
horror documentaries that Shudder put up in Search of Darkness.
He seems like a fascinating character.
But yeah, in terms of their gore makeup effects, especially on a low budget, unparalleled stuff,
we'll get to it.
We'll get to it.
What's happening, Joe?
Nothing.
I got a busy week.
Um, you know, a lot of recording during the days and stuff like that and bar business.
And then at night, I've got like, it's one of those weeks where there's like a social
event every single night this week of some kind, which is fun, but overwhelming.
I find myself hating that.
I find myself planning up my next week, oh, yeah, I do have Thursday free.
I can hang Thursday.
And then when Monday rolls around, just dreading all the shit that I made plans to do because
I was going insane and thought I needed to make plans for the following week.
I don't know.
I prefer never having plans.
This is, uh, this isn't like plans like, you know, I made plans with somebody.
It's every, it's, it's like, it's like an event, like, like there's a, there's a party
for comedians at this place and galas, you know, going to a concert, you know, it's shit
like that where I'm like, you're like, I can't miss this.
So, so last night I went to a panel at the photo, the Togariska museum, I believe it's
called in Union Square.
They're doing a 50 years of hip hop photo exhibit there, which was really great to look
at.
And they did a panable about cannabis and hip hop, uh, at the museum.
And the panelist.
Panable?
A panel.
Maybe I said panable by accident.
Panable Burruss.
Uh huh.
That would be a MADtv sketch if MADtv was still on.
One that, one that didn't quite make it to air.
No, no, it would make it to air.
Panable Burruss.
Um, they, uh, they, they did a panel there, cannabis and hip hop.
And it was cool because, uh, uh, Dead Prez, uh, M1, who's one of the guys in Dead Prez
moderated it, Fab Five Freddy was there, was one of the panelists who I'm a big fan of.
I didn't get to meet Fab Five Freddy, unfortunately, one of my childhood heroes, but I did get
to meet M1 at the dinner afterwards and we hung out a bit and he was very cool.
It was a cool night, man.
It was a fun night.
Had drank a bunch of wine, had fun, hit it right off with him because as soon as I met
him, we started talking and I, and I was, you know, I knew who he was and I was like,
Hey man, sorry, dude, I've had a few too many pops tonight.
I'm just going to let you know.
And he goes, Oh, me too.
And I was like, Oh, we're fast friends.
And we just started laughing and I was like, Oh, I don't like this.
Uh, anyway, it was a fun night.
What concert are you going to?
This is cool.
You'd be into this, uh, Jizza.
Yeah.
With special guests, uh, uh, big daddy Kane and Roy, is it Roy Ayres?
The R &B?
Oh God.
Not Roy Ayres.
What's his name?
I'll tell you this Roy Ayres does not sound like an R &B star to me, but I'm getting the
name.
Oh yeah.
Roy Ayres.
Wait, who's okay.
I thought Roy Ayres was like an old, like, like jazz guy or something.
Hold on.
Well, anyway, it's Jizza and big daddy Kane is the big, you know, yeah, composer Roy Ayres
is a composer.
That's what I thought.
I thought that's what I thought.
Like he was like a Herbie Hancock.
Oh, he'd sings.
Everybody loves the sunshine.
You know that song?
Yeah.
That's Roy Ayres.
Okay.
Um, so yeah, that should be cool.
I think.
I think so too.
Roy Ayres is 82.
Still playing.
All right.
Jizza and big daddy Kane is the big, you know, yeah, composer.
Jizza.
Um, has he, have they ever gone by GZA and RZA?
No.
No one calls them that?
And you'd think at one point, Jizza might've been like, I don't like the Jiz what I'm saying.
It's hard for, you know, I, I, maybe Riz has never appeared on Jimmy Fallon, but you'd
imagine he wouldn't be able to say Jizza.
Yeah.
On television.
Okay.
I mean, you, cause it's like saying like, like if your last name was, was, was shittle,
you could say shit.
I mean, you know what I mean?
You're not saying shit.
Uh, Jizzle is the porn site that I tend to go to.
You familiar with Jizzle?
Not a joke.
No.
Oh, you're joking.
I give a shout out to Jizzle.
It's weird.
I've been using it for, you know, 20 years probably.
And I ask people, Hey, what's, you know, what's your porn site of, no one's ever said Jizzle.
No one's familiar with it.
How did this get on my radar?
They do good work.
I believe it is Snoop Dogg's porn site.
It's not.
She has a carefully curated collection of videos that end in climax.
That's any porno movie.
What the hell are you talking about?
Well, no.
I mean, I feel like frequently, um, they cut the climax cause they think that you'll buy
their product if they don't show it to you.
Okay.
Is it just Jizzle delivers cutting just to the climax or is it a full video?
No, it's full videos.
I just like that they have a, a large, you know, like when you're scrolling down at your
is basically four to six shots of porn.
So you're looking at pretty big representative images of the video you're about to watch.
I don't like on the sites where there's a million tiny boxes.
So you're, you can't really see it and you're like, all right, I'll watch this one.
And it comes up and you're like, Oh, I wouldn't have clicked on this.
Had I known you people were fucking Jizzle shows you everything in HD before you click,
you know what you're getting into.
I asked the money shot question that I just asked because I knew a girl once that worked
in a porno shop back in the day.
Yeah.
And I remember she was going off once.
That's the start of a Bob Dylan's latest single.
Oh, great news by the way.
Timothy Chalamet is going to be singing all his own vocals in a Bob Dylan biopic that
he's doing.
Cause that's what we all wanted.
I know you've been worried about that all week.
You said, I want to hear Timothy's original vocals though, if I'm going to go down this
journey with him.
And I was like, Joe, you had tears in your eyes.
Could there be a life less interesting than Bob Dylan's?
Yeah, Timothy Chalamet is.
That's never had, there's, as far as I know, there's never been any controversy.
You know, the rebel, the big rebellion, forgetting that, that once at a concert, he switched
from an acoustic guitar to an electric.
I was just going to say that.
And every dumb fucking hippie kid I was friends with in college would be like, and it's great
because off, off mic, you hear Dylan go, fuck him.
And he just rips into his electric and you're like, shut the fuck up.
Oh, you mean he does?
He does what 90 % of rock musicians do every time out plays an electric guitar.
If you were in that room that you need to know, like what was going on in the culture
at that time, like he was down in that East village scene.
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
This would be like a movie.
This is, this is the equivalent of like, if they made a movie about Mort Saul, where I'd
be like, regardless of if I respect him or not, I don't want to see a movie about it.
Who cares?
One night at Mort's.
He would go, he would read the paper and write his material as he, who gives a shit?
I actually like the music of Bob Dylan.
Speak for yourself.
You know, I think in, in that kind of singer songwriter mode, I'll take Elvis Costello
day of the week over Bob Dylan as a lyricist and certainly musician and certainly singer.
You mean because Elvis Costello bothered to inject melody and catchiness into his music?
Yeah, I would agree that I prefer Costello for that reason.
I like how he writes down notes and then aspires to hit them when performing.
I like that when, uh, I, if I were to take my dad to see Elvis Costello, I could rely
on not driving three hours to Santa Barbara in bumper to bumper traffic to have Elvis
Costello sing me 90 minutes of out of tune, Frank Sinatra covers.
Yeah.
That's what Bob Dylan did when I took my dad to see him, my dad, the whole way up, Patrick,
this really means a lot.
In all my years, I've never seen him and I've loved him since I was a kid.
I mean, this means a lot.
Hey, I, it really felt good about it to take my dad to something cool like this, an outdoor
venue.
Bob Dylan comes out on stage, play me to the moon and let me play among the stairs.
What an asshole.
Yep.
I'll tell you a great off mic moment, which I was unfamiliar with, but the Woodstock moment
when the who's on stage, I love that they do this to Abbie Hoffman.
I love it.
Abbie Hoffman.
Loser.
I hate fucking Abbie Hoffman.
With that thing, when Abbie Hoffman runs up during the who, yeah, you all sit here.
Wow.
So -and -so rots in jail.
You know, another, you know, like, like, like this kid, this kid, Abbie Hoffman in 20, if
he was alive in 2015, if he was like a young person in 2015 would have been the kid in
back of nerd melt thinking he's making a difference by going to the alt comedy shows or whatever.
Like just what a fucking waste.
Anyway.
I would say Abbie Hoffman is alive and well and has dominated our cultural discussion.
His spirit is alive and kicking.
But he does that in the middle of the who, like uninvited and then you hear Pete Townsend
Mike goes, get the fuck off my stage and then says, at Woodstock, as one of the commenters
on YouTube pointed out at the Festival of Love and Peace, Pete Townsend says, anybody
else who comes on my stage is going to get fucking killed.
I am serious.
Try me.
Okay.
All right.
Another one of my favorite things, Pete Townsend said, I'm writing a play about child molestation
. That's why I've got hours of child molestation videos on my hard drive.
He didn't, but he didn't have hours.
He went to sites, which I get if he's like researching for a book, like, and he's trying
to expose what's out there.
Yeah.
Like, I don't think that that's that suspect.
He might be fine.
I'd need to read more about that story.
I mean, he's still out there touring.
It must not have been that bad, but speaking of, because I know the question's coming.
Why did I tell the Dalai Lama to do what he did?
I know you're going to listen.
Did you watch that video?
Did I watch it?
Yeah. Yeah, I mentioned this thing to Joe yesterday.
Just like, I don't even know what you're talking about.
And since I'm off Twitter, I get these stories late.
So I don't know how Joe missed this, but I saw this video or I read about the video and
I assume it was just your standard outrage culture thing.
It says the Dalai Lama meets with a young boy and asks him to suck on his tongue.
And I just said, no, no, clearly there was a misinterpretation.
They've, they're blowing this out of proportion.
I click on this video.
It is the Dalai Lama forehead to forehead, like a couple, two drinks in getting ready
to make out at dinner, like lovey -dovey with him and like a small boy.
Then the Dalai Lama sticks his lips out, going in for a mouth kiss with this little
boy and you're like, okay, I've seen that, you know, Tom Brady kissed his kid in the
mouth and that was controversial.
However, you parent your kids is how you parent your kids.
This is not the Dalai Lama's child though.
Everybody does clap when he says, kiss me on the lips.
Everybody claps like, oh, that's very sweet.
Kiss me.
Everybody claps.
It's being translated what he's saying, which makes it even awkward as there's a guy
there who has to translate kiss me little boy in the room.
Then the Dalai Lama goes in.
Yeah.
Then the Dalai Lama goes to really uncharted waters.
He sticks his tongue fully out of his mouth, says something in Tibetan.
And then the translator goes, suck my tongue.
The boy looks like he doesn't want to do this, but the Dalai Lama moves his tongue
closer and closer to the little boy's mouth.
At which point the video blurs out what I have to assume is a five -year -old
boy sucking on an 80 -year -old man's tongue as people watch.
One of the craziest things I've ever seen, he came out with an apology and they're
like, the Dalai Lama's, he's goofy.
He likes doing goofy things.
Do you think, no, no, who knows?
Who knows?
Do you think though, when I did watch the video, I read the apology first because
you couldn't find the video because every fucking news outlet now is so catered for
these child adults running around.
They won't put the fucking video in the, in the actual story.
Right.
Uh, because it's, it's, it's triggering or whatever.
So that's the level of childish society we're living in at this point.
So then I got to, now I got to go find the fucking video and probably end
up on the Pete Townsend list.
Uh, but anyway, so I read his apology first and I was like, that
sounds really suspect, man.
It's also suspect too, when they, when they're speaking for him in the
apology, which they were, and then I watched the video and I was like, I
don't know, this might just be an old man trying to be funny and then it's just
not funny and it's kind of weird.
Like, but, but who knows that you go, you go, it's the Dalai Lama.
There's no way he's a pedophile.
And then you're like, well, they thought that about the Catholic
church and boy, oh boy, do we open a can of worms there.
So, so who knows?
I don't know.
You know, I mean, that's, um, documentary I've been working on for
eight years is called, uh, the Catholic church colon, a real can of worms.
And it's going into the molestation scandal.
All I could think about through this whole thing was if MCA was still alive,
would he make a statement about this?
Cause he, out of all the beastie boys, he was the one that I felt like
was super into the Dalai Lama.
I bet he would make a statement, but you know, what, what weirdly makes it
seem like maybe this was just what you're saying weird old guy is that
he's doing it in public on a stage surrounded by people.
So you can go two ways for that.
You can go, this is a man who obviously didn't think anything
he was doing was wrong.
He was having fun.
He's surrounded by people.
He didn't think anything of it.
Or you could say, if this is what he's doing in public, what in
God's name is he doing in private?
There's two ways to look at it.
And there's a third, there's a third thing there too.
This is what he's been into all along and he's now got enough dementia
that it's coming out at the bad times.
Cause he's old and maybe that's what it is.
You know, who knows?
I mean, you know, how do you know if a Dalai Lama has dementia, by the way,
the guy just sits in the corner quietly.
You're like, he's, he's at peace.
He's centered.
You're like, no, he thinks he's
his aunt Lily.
Like, you know, like, you know, you couldn't tell.
That's true.
Um, disturbing shit.
And they go through like the other controversial things he's done in his
career.
And I was like, now we're really kind of scraping guys.
He is the Dalai Lama after all.
Now, do you think Stacey does a sequel to Kundoon?
God, I hope not.
Well, I liked it.
These are the years I want to hear about with the Dalai Lama.
I want to hear the wild shit.
Yeah.
Anyway, uh, I love that Scorsese has a four hour movie about to come out or
it's coming out in October, whatever it is.
I mean, has Scorsese ever had a health issue?
I know he had heart stuff off of cocaine back in the seventies, but it's like,
usually somebody who did as much blow as him dies pretty young of hardship.
It's just like, you know, what you can sense it.
It's like, that's bad for your heart.
He's hanging in and he seems just, he seems exactly the same as he always did.
Yeah, he, uh, yeah, he's still running around like a, like a, like a crazy
little Ross Perot, you know, like making movies with giant eyebrows, you know?
Uh, I got a, uh, scary, scary stuff for you here.
Well, not for you, but, but a scary stuff.
Oh, and I got a new psycho too.
Take it away.
The new psycho first final trailer for Indiana Jones and the
dial of destiny has been released.
This is a trailer finally, where they get into some plot points.
Um, I'm excited people.
First trailer.
I was, I was a little like, I don't know, man, the title it's weird.
Is it going to have time travel?
I don't know.
Second trailer.
Well, second trailer was super bowl spot, which was just the music
playing the theme and it made me cry.
This trailer is interesting.
Very different approach.
I don't know if you've seen it yet, but it's, it starts with sympathy for the devil.
It's very like 1960s, an original choice.
It's, uh, it's, uh, are you making a joke about sympathy that was
overused or that because it's Indiana Jones insanely overused, but it is sort
of interesting to hear it in the context of Indy Jones, I guess it is.
And he, I, I, I feel, I agree with both things you just said.
He's like in his life, it would be overused if we just looked at
Scorsese's use of the songs.
Exactly.
Uh, it opens with a shot of him asleep in his armchair, like jolting, awake
in the morning and he's holding a glass.
Yeah.
And I'm like, Ooh, I like this.
If they're doing like the Indy is like John McClane to sleep, you know?
Yeah, sure.
It shows it hits a few cliche points.
It's, you know, that in and of itself is a cliche.
The song is cliche.
He goes into work, they're having a party.
He says, I'm retiring.
It's like, okay.
And then Phoebe Waller -Bridge shows up and she's clearly the
catalyst for the, for the adventure.
And it gets moving and it's exciting.
And she does say there's a dial that can change the course of history.
They established that the Nazis are after it to fix Hitler's mistakes.
Okay.
She's saying we can find it and, and, and write every wrong you've ever done.
And she says, like, this is your chance to have one last great adventure.
It was fun, man.
And we got me going.
I was like, okay, I'm, I'm into this, man.
It's it establishes a little more of what the flashback stuff probably is.
Yeah.
Um, and I, I'm excited.
And the title, as I kind of thought initially with this, it did happen.
It doesn't really bother me anymore.
I'm just like, okay.
Like it's, you know, as you get further away from the initial announcement,
it doesn't bother me as much.
So, so I'm excited.
It comes out in June.
It's premiering a con film festival in May.
I very much look forward to hearing the initial reviews.
Um, and look, it's man gold, you know, man gold and other news,
psychos, uh, star wars, seemingly desperately trying to right the
wrongs in recent years and these major fucking mistakes they've made.
Uh, two things they announced, three things they announced that I'm excited
about, they get, they're giving man gold, a star Wars movie.
That's awesome.
He's doing a movie called Dawn of the Jedi, which is going to be about
the first Jedi ever, and I think that sounds awesome.
They're given Dave Filoni, a movie finally, that's going to tie together
the Ahsoka series, the Mandalorian series and the Boba Fett series.
Great.
Needs to be done.
Sounds good.
And year would the first Jedi have been 25 ,000 years before the
Phantom Menace, they said, so I'm curious is that a line with like our timeline
in, in the, in on earth?
Yeah.
No, no, I have no idea.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, and, and then they're giving their rebooting, not rebooting, but they're
bringing Ray back from the sequel trilogy and doing a new movie with her
starting the new Jedi order.
I think amongst all these things, they are going to right the wrongs of the
sequel trilogy and, uh, and make some good stuff.
I hope it's see Kathleen Kennedy has now officially.
Said in an interview, we fucked up the sequel trilogy.
We rushed it out to meet investor needs and we made a huge mistake and it's
terribly sad and disheartening to hear her say that and admit to it, but hey,
all right, what's done is done.
Let's try to fix it now.
So, uh, so anyway, there's your news.
Psycho.
Have you seen the Barbie trailer?
No, I'm afraid it's going to put me over the edge.
Is it, I haven't watched it, but, but my assumption, um, I was thinking
it would be funny if like it starts out very serious and they do whatever trailer
does now, which would be like a Johnny cash cover of I'm a Barbie girl in a
Barbie world, you know, one of those.
Yeah.
Let's do a slow shitty.
Charisma list version of a song you love.
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, to me, I have heard from various sources that the script is incredible.
I do sort of like that.
It was written by Greta Gerwig and Noah Baumbach them doing some big
budget comedy sounds insane, but I like their work.
I think the cast is interesting.
I do not care for Simu Liu.
Uh, he w he portrayed Shang Chi and then has spent the past three
years scolding all of us, um, for everything we do.
He's really like, he's annoying.
Um, but that said, the rest of the cast is pretty fun.
Gosling is Ken, you know, I'm going to, I'm going to see what it is.
I'm going to check it out.
I was like, uh, making some interesting choices.
I think he's kind of had enough of the.
Yeah.
Indie film thing.
Like, all right, guys.
I love that he gets to go home.
Yeah.
What's that?
I think he's happy.
I mean, he's got Eva Mendes waiting at home.
I think that he just probably doesn't want to act as much, which would be, I
guess she's done in retired too.
Maybe he's just bringing home the bacon now.
Um, but I'll see it.
I want to see what's the big horror.
Oh, there, there's some new horror movie trailer that premiered today.
That's supposed to be great that I want to see as well.
Okay.
Anyway, we need to go to that movie corner.
I was going to give you a scary stuff, scary stuff.
Carry on.
Yes.
Real quick.
Resident evil four remake finally out for the Xbox series X and the PlayStation
five, uh, resident evil four came out initially in 2000, whatever it was seven,
eight, somewhere in there.
Um, it is in my top five video games of all time.
It is my favorite, arguably my favorite.
Well, it's the, it's there.
I have two horror games in my top five.
This and devil's crush for turbo graphics.
Um, this is arguably my favorite horror video game of all time.
Um, I was very excited for this remake.
They did stellar jobs with the remakes of part two and part three.
This is an amazing, amazing remake.
If you like the original, you will love this.
Uh, and if you don't like the original, this might be different
enough and a new enough of an experience to bring you into it.
I doubt it, but whatever.
It's just an awesome action horror game.
Whereas evil four is the one that started it all with the, with the
horror action stuff, or at least perfected it, uh, and, and
certainly redefined the genre.
And, uh, this game is just a wonderful revisit.
And it's scary.
It is kind of scary.
They, they added some new jump scares that really got me like where I got startled.
So it's a lot of fun.
Check it out.
If you have one of those new systems, if you don't, then you're fucked.
There you go.
All right.
Um, let us take me, let me take you, let me take us over to that movie corner.
I will start this week with a picture called woman in the dunes.
Um, I was watching Ari Oster, Joe's favorite on the Criterion channel,
discussing some of his favorite films.
I was like, boy, I bet I was really in the mood to watch something
upsetting and disturbing, which I tend to be lately, which has me a little bit
concerned, um, but I want to see this new movie.
Bo is afraid I'm excited to check it out.
I'm hearing a lot of crazy things about it.
And I was like, I want to know what movies inspire this guy.
They got to be pretty fucked up.
Some of them, you know, like obviously you go see midsummer, you know, the guy
likes, um, the wicker man, obviously, you know, you, some of them, you can
tell what the influences are or Kubrick or whatever, but he discussed this movie.
woman in the dunes described it as like Kurosawa doing the Twilight
zone kind of thing.
And that's a perfect example of it or a perfect description of it.
I love this movie.
It is director, forgive me, Hiroshi Teshigahara.
I was unfamiliar with him, but this is his best known movie.
And it's, it's unbelievably beautiful black and white photography of this guy
just walking through the sand, like Lawrence of Arabia style.
He's exploring, he's looking around.
Um, these people come upon him and take him to this house because he's lost.
And they're like, oh, you know, you're, you're lost.
We'll, we'll give you room and board for the night, whatever.
He's like, okay, cool.
He goes to this woman's house.
They're like, you can sleep here.
She's really nice.
Have fun.
They lower him down into this pit where her house is at the bottom of this pit.
It's a weird mood.
Um, he's down there, him and the woman interact.
And he realizes soon that this is a pit that is slowly filling with sand.
Sand is constantly shaking down into this pit and filling and will someday
overtake the house and kill them.
Uh, he has been like the Sisyphus legend or whatever.
They brought him in and this is like his life now.
He's stuck.
He's got to spend the rest of his life shoveling sand with this crazy woman.
Um, there's no real explanation for it.
It's very kind of weird and confusing, but it's very twilight zone ish.
You know, if you were watching it as an episode of the twilight zone, you'd
accept it, but it takes a minute when you're watching this art movie to
realize that that's kind of what they're doing is this like really weird, uh,
almost sci -fi kind of fable, but I dig the movie.
It's really, as I said, hard to explain.
Uh, at some point the man keeps trying to escape and the town's people are
like, uh, fuck her, we'll let you get out of the pit if you just fuck her
and we can all watch, and then the movie starts taking a more disturbing
turn, as you can imagine.
Um, it's a wild one.
It came out in 64.
It's not like it's, it's not, it's really graphic or scary per se.
It's just very unusual and I got to recommend it.
It's on criterion channel.
If you like twilight zone, you'll love this.
Check it out.
Now, should I buy this thing?
Just buy it because I love twilight zone.
You know how I am with twilight zone.
It's a, it's a, it's a beautiful movie.
I don't know if you're going to want to go with a buy Joe.
I just, I was, I was impressed by it.
It is two and a half hours.
It doesn't need to be.
There's a shorter version of it.
You know, you lost me with beautiful movie.
I want, I wanted to hear disturbing and I was going to hit click on that purchase.
But I don't, I mean, beautiful to look, it can be beautiful to look at and disturb.
Doesn't look like it's for a sale actually.
I'm looking, I don't see it.
Anyway, uh, I only have two, uh, and I'm going to do two TV shows.
One that'll be on point with what I was just talking about.
And then the other, because it's on theme as it as another TV show, uh, the
Mandalorian season three is almost at its end.
There's only two episodes left.
My God, does this season suck?
Uh, I don't understand what the fuck is going on over at Lucasfilm.
I don't understand every time they do something good, they, they take three
steps back and season two of Mandalorian was so unbelievably awesome with the
storyline, bringing back Boba Fett, bringing in Luke Skywalker for the big
surprise ending, Luke taking Grogu, AKA baby Yoda off to train him.
You're like, Oh my God, that Yoda trained Luke and now Luke will train Yoda.
It was so perfectly fucking done.
This season, Jesus Christ has been one fucking episode after the next, where
they talk about why they can and can't take their helmets off because of the
load and the way and all this bullshit and these stupid adventures, nobody
gives a fuck about that have nothing to do with moving the plot forward.
And the cameos are just atrocious.
Last episode had Jack Black and Lizzo in it as a boisterous comical
couple, hosting a party.
It's a guy's stop.
Stop.
I have nothing against Jack Black or Lizzo.
It's distracting.
It's just stupid.
And they have them like playing like a Jack Black and Lizzo type.
You know what I mean?
Like, did I already bitch about this on this podcast?
I think just to me, you know, I might've bitched about this last week.
Am I losing my mind?
Um, I don't know, but, uh, I mean, that to me makes it sound like they're
going like the Muppet Show route.
It is.
And I don't understand and et cetera, which was never what star wars was about.
Christopher Lloyd's in the last episode.
I like Christopher.
Yeah.
It's distracting.
You were talking about this on the last podcast.
Oh, I was.
Jesus.
Once you say Christopher Lloyd, I remember.
Sorry, everybody.
Anyway, the season sucks.
Uh, did I also talk about everybody loves Raymond?
Did I do this already?
No, no.
No, you can get to that.
And I recently watched the first season of everybody loves Raymond.
So I can join you.
That's my other, um, uh, movie corner for today.
I'll just do it, do it now.
And then you can, you can do whatever you want.
Uh, I, I, I just, I, I, everybody loves her.
You know, I know my mom loves, loves the show and I always really related to it.
His family reminds me of my family very much on the show.
My, his mom reminds me very much of my mom.
Uh, I remind myself of, uh, of, uh, Brad Garrett's character.
Uh, like I just, I relate to the show.
Hello, Raymond.
It always bums me out that he doesn't talk like that in real life.
When you see him in an interview, his voice isn't that deep.
He like puts a voice on anyway.
I've been to his comedy club in Vegas.
He wasn't there, but I've been there.
I opened for him years ago at comics comedy club in New York city.
And, uh, the two memories I have were when he went on stage, he said, welcome to
the end of my fucking career, everybody.
Cause cause I guess he thought that there was clearly a step down to be doing
a headlining weekend club and I got where he was, I got the joke.
It was funny.
It killed.
Yeah.
Then we were in the green room and they had a really nice leather jacket on.
And I said, that jacket's awesome.
Where'd you get it?
And he went big fat fucks, which made me laugh.
Uh, that's funny.
Yeah, it was funny.
Um, he was very, very sweet.
Um, all right, good.
Anyway, I've met Raymond too.
I met Raymond once at the comedy seller.
I was teetering on blacked out drunk, uh, but he took a picture with me and, and
so I could send it to my mom and it was very sweet.
He seems like a nice man.
He's very nice.
Talk about an anomaly in this fucking business.
You know, he's like another Adam Sandler where it's like you got to the top
and you're still a decent man.
I don't understand how you did it, but congrats.
You did it.
Yeah.
It's like they just finished their business and go straight home to that wife
and kids and they've been doing it for 30 years.
It's very impressive.
Um, so anyway, I I've seen the show obviously, but I never really sat and
watched it and I've been doing that.
And, uh, you know, talk about just a, just something from a bygone era.
Yeah.
You just don't see a multicam like this anymore.
It is a grand slam almost every episode.
It's it's classic sitcom stuff.
I mean, it's like classic, meaning not like standard, meaning like, like, no,
this is why it's a classic.
Like it is, they all kill everybody bringing their A plus game in every
single episode, you can tell that they all probably get along for the most part.
Nobody's an asshole.
The network is letting them make a show.
Uh, you know, it's really good.
I mean, as I was watching the first season, cause I hadn't seen it, I mean, I
think that the stories that they are telling you can, you can pick apart each
one as a network would never allow this.
And it's not cause they're controversial.
The stories are like, um, one of the most famous episodes is they get home from a
vacation and it's this battle of wheels to see who will put the suitcase away.
First, just watch that.
Cause I started skipping around.
Yeah.
It's a great one.
It's one of their most well -known ones, but like you could, I could hear myself
pitching that to a network and they would just be like, that's, that's not a story.
What happens?
What, what are you talking about?
Okay.
That might be your cold open, but where do we go from there?
What do we learn about Raymond in this episode?
What do we learn about Patricia?
What do they learn about each other?
And they just wouldn't happen.
These are the most simple stories ever.
They're very well written.
It's not like it's not, you know, well thought out, but they're just classic
sitcom structures done extremely well.
And you don't, you don't see it anywhere.
Well, it's tragic.
It's also a thing where it's like, once you have that kind of success that they've
had, and we're having, you know, you're deep in season six or seven at that point,
I think, so it's like, they're probably at a point where the network's like, do
whatever you want guys, just keep them checks coming, you know, like we don't care.
Um, but yeah, you're right about the writing where it's like, it was a time when
on regular old television, the concept of metaphor was not lost.
You go, guys, it's not about the suitcase.
Yeah.
Suitcase represents X.
Right.
And you take it from there and, uh, and you know, that you just don't see
a lot of that anymore.
Everything is so stupidly spelled out and everything and not in everything,
but in these types of shows, even when they're on streamers where streamers,
even, here's the thing, and I will always say this forever and ever and ever about
why comedy will never be good again as a whole, you'll get lucky here and there,
but as a whole, it's never going to be good again in the mainstream space and
mainstream now means Netflix, the three major networks, Hulu, whatever.
When you start to say to people, certain jokes can get you in trouble.
And in fact, have you fired and ruined?
You do not then have a free environment in your writer's room and your work will
suffer.
You could be making the safest fucking comedy on planet earth.
You have to have writers who feel free and safe to make any joke that pops
into their head and the ability to say, let's take it too far and then reel it
in if we want.
Right.
And when you remove that, forget it.
You, when you have people pitching through a filter, you, that's it.
You're done.
It'll never be good ever again.
Uh, I, I definitely agree.
Did you ever hear the story speaking of writer's rooms?
And it's not a comedy, but Walter Mosley, who is black, and that's important.
I'm not just telling you that.
He is a great author.
He's written tons of great shit and they hired him on Star Trek discovery.
This was about three, four years ago.
Oh, and please, by the way, remind me to tell you a Star Trek thing after this.
Okay.
All right, go ahead.
Um, Walter Mosley, a very cool dude, a very cool dude, a novelist.
He wrote, um, devil in a blue dress, which became that amazing Denzel
Don Cheadle movie.
So they hire him on this show.
He's not even generally a TV writer.
He, he should, they should have been honored to have this
like legend in the room.
And the guy says the N word and the room and lost his job.
Says it for what reason?
This is a 70 year old black American novelist.
Oh, he said it.
Oh, that's why you said he's sorry.
I forgot that you said he was black and he lost his job, lost his job.
Um, and then he penned an op ed for the New York times that you can read.
He, well, actually he quit.
He was chastised by HR and decided to leave and then wrote an article about it.
Keep it up.
Dumb fucks.
Yeah.
Keep it up.
Dumb fucks.
Keep telling, uh, keep attacking man, uh, Lin -Manuel Noreanda.
Is that his name?
Miranda Miranda.
I can never remember Miranda, Samantha, uh, uh, Sarah, Jessica Parker.
These are sex in the city references.
Um, keep telling him that he's a fucking racist because he, he doesn't have
enough diverse Latino inclusion in it.
I mean, it's just fucking crazy anymore.
It's crazy.
Uh, anyway, so I'm sorry.
So he, he took a job on snowfall, which is the, the big FX drug show.
And he said he's been in the new room for a few weeks working and he gets a call
from HR, a pleasant sounding young man says, Mr.
Mosley, it has been reported that you use the N word in the writer's room.
Mosley said, I am the N word in the writer's room.
Oh yeah.
That's pretty good.
Anyway, um, my next one, sorry.
I spaced out there.
You were going to tell me something about Star Trek too.
Yeah.
Did you see any, I've been watching some interviews of this deep space
nine documentary coming out.
Okay.
So, so I've stumbled upon it because Jeffrey Combs was in deep space nine
and he's being interviewed a lot.
So the, he, he, and one of the other actresses, Nana, which is spelled Nana,
whatever her name is are going on some morning, you know, you know, Fox
affiliate, whatever, and talking about the documentary and Jesus Christ, dude,
the way she Combs is just like, it was a good show.
I was very proud to be a part of it.
I I'm glad people are discovering it, you know, the way she talks about this
fucking show and they show the clips, these people are in the documentary
going, going our show unfortunately was overshadowed by the original
Star Trek and next gen, uh, our show.
Every bit as good as in fact, better than those two shows.
Sorry.
It's like, are you people on fucking crack?
Like, what the fuck are you talking about?
Guys, be proud of what you did.
Yeah.
Every everybody's not a victim.
The cast of dark Star Trek, deep space nine have not been victimized because
fans are more excited about the Patrick Stewart and William Shatner versus
Star Trek guys.
If there was a movie to be made, they would have made it.
You're the only Star Trek where they don't go anywhere.
That was a huge criticism.
And what do they do?
Is it all just like they sit on the ship about the space station?
Deep space.
And she talks about this.
She goes, we were the first to do non serialized.
We told a story over a season.
Yes.
Because that's what everybody wanted from Star Trek was getting in deep
with the characters day to day.
That's what we all wanted to do with Star Trek.
We were all sad about that, but what does Spock do when he's not on deck?
Does he have a vacation planet that he attend?
I've never seen any of them.
I used to like, if I wanted to fall asleep when I was young, I would turn on one
minute of Star Trek, the next generation and fall into a deep slumber every time.
I just don't get it.
My dad is the biggest Star Trek fan.
I know he for years, I just keep buying him.
It's he's the easiest person to buy gifts for.
I just buy him whatever the newest bullshit re -release of the Star Trek
blu -rays are of one of the series, whatever.
They're always re -releasing one of the only one.
He doesn't know the names of any of the characters or it doesn't like is deep
space nine because he's like, they don't go anywhere.
Yeah.
That's the whole point of Star Trek is to go somewhere.
Trek.
Yeah.
You're trekking.
I watched on the shutter channel.
Nothing bad can happen.
This is a movie so disturbing that it's one that when you Google most
disturbing movies ever made, it's on a lot of those lists.
It's not that I mean, it's certainly an unpleasant movie, but it's not like
it affected me that deeply.
It is just to surface.
It's not a deep movie, so it can't affect you deeply.
It's about very deep, heavy subjects, but they don't, in my opinion, get under
your skin in the way they should have.
The plot of the movie is this young guy who's maybe 17, 18, 16.
He's in a Christian punk group.
And as it starts out, he's hanging out with these Christian punks and he's,
you know, he's found a faith in God, whatever.
He gets essentially, this is much like woman in the dunes.
Actually, he sort of like stumbles in with a bad situation.
He gets in with this bad family led by a really sadistic father.
And the father hates God and seems to think that it's his job to test this
boy's faith and little by little him and his wife, which is the other disturbing
aspect are putting this kid's faith to the test through a bunch of horrific
things that they do to him.
Very weird.
And then the most troubling part of this was to learn that this was
based on a true story.
So they torture this poor kid and he keeps saying, this doesn't bother me
because I have faith in God.
Entire time you're like, why in God's name wouldn't this guy fucking leave?
The only reason it works, I guess, is because it's a true story.
And in real life, the guy didn't leave.
So you got to go, okay.
But they're a long scene.
They find a chicken in the trash, an old chicken that they feed him for dinner as
he gags and gets a very extreme food poisoning from it.
Um, the father takes him to like a Jack shack kind of all male sex club where he
is sodomized and raped, um, and then he like goes home and is like, sorry, but I
still believe in God.
It just kind of, there's one horrible thing that happens to him after another.
It's on the editor.
It's on shutter.
Yeah.
Where, what, what's the horror part of it?
That doesn't sound horrifying to you.
It does, but it sounds like a, a terribly dark.
It doesn't sound like it's not a horror movie though.
You know what I mean?
No, it's a lot like the movie that we've, we've for some reason, never done on
here, speak no evil, where it's just kind of like a feel bad, you know, that
shutter has some of those where it's just like extreme.
I think shutter is also the home to kind of extreme stuff as well.
We'll be doing speak no evil eventually.
We should also do Sodom.
Now that we've 120 days, we should, I'll watch that fucker again.
It's been 15 years.
I'll watch it again.
I'll crack the seal on Sodom.
All right, good.
Um, but yeah, it's, it's an average movie with these, like really
tense, long, unpleasant scenes.
It culminates in the husband and the wife and like other people at some
point coming in and like they cast straight this kid, they're fucking up his face.
I don't, I don't know.
And there's no explanation for it.
It's one of those where it's like, there's just evil in the world, you know?
But if that's something you want to watch, go ahead.
Uh, in my opinion, if you're going to be presenting us with images, this extreme,
you have to have the quality of the film to back it up or else you're
doing that movie where Alicia Cuthbert is tied up in a basement.
You remember that movie?
That was kind of the end of the torture porn genre.
It came out and everybody was like, we need to stop making these movies.
I'd have to look up what that was called, but it just feels really, uh,
gross and unpleasant as you can imagine.
And then I'm going to throw out the hunted a late period film from Billy
Friedkin because I've been watching all the William Friedkin's movies.
Not as best.
This was during a period of 10 years where I would say nine out of 10 movies
involved Tommy Lee Jones tracking someone, either her Ashley Judd, or he
was, you know, he tracked every major actor in Hollywood and then he'd stop
off for a made for HBO where he played a racist of some kind called like in
the Sierra mist or like some, you know, some bizarre title you've never heard
of again, um, and then I guess those would lose money and he'd be back
to having to do the tracking.
He is literally in this movie, stepping out of helicopters going, all right,
we need an IPB on and it's, it is every movie he's ever made.
There is a scene where he tracks Benicio del Toro to a waterfall.
Oh boy.
There it's, it's the fugitive.
It's almost the same location as the fugitive for Christ's sake, but.
Um, the movie is very, very standard.
Benicio del Toro has killed some hunters in the woods.
He's like a feral guy.
He says, you know, he's one of these guys.
You don't kill animals.
I kill you and kills them.
They call in Tommy Lee Jones to find him because Tommy Lee Jones
trained him back in the day.
So the only one who knows the skills del Toro has is Tommy Lee Jones.
They have some fist and knife fights, Tommy Lee and del Toro that are awesome.
Friedkin, even when he's past his prime knows how to do a fucking chase scene.
There's lots of really cool, fun chases in the movie, but there's no plot to speak
of them.
The movie is just simply Tommy Lee Jones tracking Benicio del Toro.
It's 90 minutes.
It's on Amazon prime.
It's a pleasant enough film, but, um, yeah, Tommy Lee Jones, a fascinating career.
Remember he did fugitive US marshals.
We got to look up how many of the, cause I don't think I'm even exaggerating.
He did double jeopardy.
What happened to Tommy Lee Jones is the first thing that comes up.
That's gotta feel good when you log in.
By the way, there was a TV movie called the hunted that just from the picture
looks like the same plot that you're describing.
Yeah.
All right.
Harry Hamlin in 1998, who I always did say was the poor man's Benicio del Toro,
the homeless man's Benicio del Toro, playing a character named doc.
No vac.
Sure.
He did.
Okay.
Under siege fugitive was his big break, you know, big, everyone knew him, but
that was his big here.
I'm coming out.
I'm a star now.
You got the client.
I'm the good old boys.
He did a bunch of Westerns as well.
US marshals was the fugitive sequel where he was tracking Wesley Snipes.
Double jeopardy.
He's tracking Joe.
By the way, you want to talk about a left turn when you should have went right.
Guys.
Ford was the one we were into with the fugitive.
He was like, what else is this detective up to?
Nobody cared about that.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I'm crazy.
It was, that was so, that was like when they did speed two with Jason.
What's his fate?
Patrick.
Guys insane.
We were here for Keanu and Hopper.
Nobody was here for Bullock.
This is crazy.
Well, they just, they misunderstood Bullock did eventually become a big star.
Absolutely.
She wasn't why we loved speed.
Let's be real.
That's what I'm saying.
It's like, look, I love Tom Lee Jones.
I love Wesley.
But guys, this is not the formula here.
Yeah.
Um, well, let's get onto our picture, which is from beyond.
Starring the great Barbara Crampton, who I saw at Gelson's the other day.
Oh, you did?
I really wish I had said something to her, but I didn't.
Yeah, man.
That would have been awesome.
Look, Tommy Lee Jones, by the way, two movies coming out in post.
Well, good for him.
I mean, I, I have heard he's a raging alcoholic and impossible to work with at
this point, which is kind of interesting to me.
Well, one is called finest kind, which is a mystery crime thriller, which
about Richard kind, correct?
He is the finest guy.
And then one is a courtroom drama called the burial.
But I mean, these are the types of movies you'd expect Tommy Lee doing.
Yeah.
Uh, anyway,
what are they paying?
Uh, from beyond is based on an HP Lovecraft tale as Stuart Gordon's projects
often were, including reanimator and that franchise.
Yeah.
Day gone.
Uh, you know, you never saw a day gone.
Maybe watch that today.
I got to rewatch it, but, uh, I remember not liking it, but I also didn't like
this the first time I saw it, but you know, castle freak is also Lovecraft.
You know, he, that's, that's basically all he did.
I love that.
Castle freak.
Oh yeah.
Um, this movie is new to 4k where I find what my, what my big takeaway
with 4k is, and I've said it on here before, if the movie is colorful, if
you got a movie that's got like, oh, wow, look at that.
Like, look at, you know, um, our buddy McCarthy was telling me that
Blade Runner has an amazing 4k image.
Will I try it again?
Who knows?
I'm sure it does, but, um, can't do it.
This movie from beyond is neon.
You know, its color scheme is like neon pinks and purples and man,
it was so cool in 4k.
It really is kind of breathing some new life into some of these movies.
Sometimes 4k does nothing.
Sometimes you watch a movie from the eighties and 4k and it looks worse.
You know, I should up to 4k on this.
I thought this was pretty spectacular.
Yeah.
Um, but the plot is this, uh, it's a pair of scientists, one played
by the great Jeff Combs, um, the other Barb Crampton, they are, I
like to call her Babs Crampton, Babs.
They are attempting to stimulate the pineal gland with a
device called the resonator.
This has the unforeseen result of creatures from another dimension
being brought into ours.
The creatures drag the head scientist into their world and return him as a
grotesque shape shifting monster that preys upon the others at the laboratory.
That scientist, Dr.
Edward Pretorius, that's a really sort of troubling character for such a goofy
movie because he's like, he is the, I am God.
I control every, you know, he's that kind of mad scientist, but he's
also like a sex addict, so it adds this really kind of gross thing where
he's like, every time you see him, he's like shirtless and like hairy
chested and oozing and he's also horny.
It's very trouble.
This is another film that I think now I think it came out either at the same
time, probably right at the same time as hell raiser.
Yeah.
But there's a, there's some, there's some connective tissue here with hell raiser.
Again, you know, you're in a house.
There was a guy up to weird shit in the house.
Yeah.
A lot of it's sexual.
And then as a result of that weird shit in the house and this device, he is
now returning as a monster to torture the other people in the house.
So, so it feels, it's got a, it's got a bit of a hell raiser vibe to it.
Um, but it's lighter, uh, certainly more fun than hell raiser.
Yeah.
I mean, Stuart Gordon, the reason I love him is that no matter how gross and
insane and graphic things get, he maintains a very pitch black sense of
humor at all times that, that really makes these movies work.
Hell raiser has no sense of humor.
Um, so, you know, for me, this subject matter works great with a
little comedy and this movie occasionally goes big with it.
They got, uh, the guy from dawn of the dead, Ken Foree running around and in
briefs, he's awesome in this, he is the, as is Dr.
Pretorius, I mean, they're all perfectly cast Joe and I, you know, we, we try
to try to not be crass, but this cramped and in this movie, you know, she's,
they, they put her in like dominatrix gear for the back half.
She is something else.
I mean, that's, that's, you saw her in the Gelsons.
That was, you know, maybe the, maybe the marriage is on the rocks.
You never know.
You can go over and have a word.
Oh, sure.
I could have hit on her.
Who knows?
But, uh, I gotta say, um, it's interesting cause, cause, cause Babs there
in the, in the, in the, uh, interview that she does on the scream factory
version of this, she says quite the opposite of what you just said.
She said, well, first of all, she said, this is her favorite character she's ever
played.
It was the most interesting character she's ever played.
It was the most she got to do with the character.
Yeah.
Um, but she also said that the difference between this and Reanimator
was Reanimator had some humor.
It was a little tongue in cheek and it was fun.
This was deathly serious.
Excuse me, this movie, which I was surprised to hear her say that because
I did feel that this movie had some fun in it, especially with, he clearly
has combs hamming it up, you know, when, when combs goes.
It, it bit his head off like a gingerbread man, you know, and the
camera pushes in on him as he's, you're like that, that's supposed to be kind
of fun, like, you know, um, but, or maybe it wasn't and it just lands
like in the wrong way, but either way, it doesn't bother me.
I enjoy it.
Um, this movie playing a mad scientist.
I mean, of all the roles that you should be able to have a little
fun with it, it's the mad side.
Uh, this movie brings, uh, to it, the great, as we said earlier, Brian
Yuzna, who is a producer on it and does clearly gets in there with the effects
with and screaming mad George is on this one too, the same guy that did.
It's gotta be right.
I'd have to make sure screaming mad.
Um, go ahead.
This movie, I texted this to Walsh as I was watching it.
I said, um, this is a wild ride.
He didn't do this one.
Wow.
I'm surprised to hear that.
I said, because he, he was, uh, working on these, these little pictures, big
trouble in little China, predator, neighbor on Elm street three, three in a row.
Um, I, oh, I gagged a few times watching this quite literally.
There were things in this that made me really gag.
The, the one that got me the most was when, um, the guy from dawn of the dead,
I'm blanking on his name, Ken, for Ken, for who Barbara Crampton said, she spoke
very highly of everybody, but she's, when they talked about Ken, for, she was like,
he is that guy in real life.
He is exactly who you want him to be.
He is the greatest man that's ever lit.
Like she was like glow, like beaming.
Um, anyway, when they get, when like the bugs come out of the machine,
interdimensional bugs and attack them, like him covered in those bugs was so
gross to me and, and then like his body eaten by the bugs and his head.
He's like still talking to them.
That was a really killer effect, but also disgusting.
Um, it's given me like heebie -jeebies just thinking of it, but I, but in a
good way, I liked that it did that to me, but it was fucking gross, man.
This is up there with possession and, um, of course society in the physical
effects that will make you kind of want to puke depart.
Well, Stu Gordon said that they, uh, the MPAA was like, we don't know how to
tell you to cut this from an X to an R because our issue is with the overall
feeling and tone of the entire film.
They were like, it's just too much.
It's, it's excessive and we don't see this getting an R rating.
So he submitted it.
He said he didn't want to cut any sequences, but he submitted it a ton of
times with like a frame here and a frame there cut and they would just never
approve it and finally they contacted him and said, basically we're tired
of watching this movie.
If you cut this one really disturbing frame, we'll approve it for an R.
So they did.
And he was like, it wound up making the movie better.
It was too much.
The movie played better without it.
Um, but yeah, it's, it's riding the line.
It's very extreme to me.
This was not as extreme as society, but I might be wrong there.
Didn't feel like it.
Um, well, society was society is a little more, you know, because there's,
there's a sexual element to society with the monster itself that that's, that's,
it's here too, but not to any extent that it is in society.
And in society, there's quite literally people coming out of other
people's anuses and shit like that.
So, you know, it's, it's, it's, it's a lot heavier.
The final scene where Barbara Crampton has like a nervous breakdown.
Um, and she's like, it ate him.
And then she's like scared, but then goes into laughing
maniacally at the end of it.
It's the best she's ever been.
Uh, it's a very, very memorable ending to the movie.
I think it's Crampton's best scene ever.
Um, I like from beyond a lot.
I don't like it quite as much as either society or reanimator.
It's way better than the reanimator sequels.
It feels like reanimator too, and it's better than brighter reanimator or
whatever the third one is, which doesn't really even count.
Um, yeah, I really liked this movie.
It's a lot of fun and the colors, as I said, if you're thinking
about picking it up, I'd go 4k check her out.
Uh, I like this movie quite a bit.
Uh, I don't want to agree with Pat that reanimator three doesn't count.
That's a wrong statement, but, but what's it called?
Curse beyond reanimator.
I do agree though, that re it's, you know, that's the one
that Gordon didn't direct and, uh, in fact, did he, he didn't
direct bride of reanimator either.
I really like bride of reanimator.
I would put this, uh, on par with bride of reanimator, but I also haven't
watched that in so long.
I might be wrong.
This might be better.
I agree.
It's a, it's a tick below a reanimator, but I did like it better than society.
It was, it was a little more fun to me than society.
Um, and I just, I just like the wildness of it a bit more.
Yeah.
Uh, and I certainly liked it better than, and this is not, uh, this is
not meant to disparage any of the movies of Yuzna, but I liked it better than any
of the other Yuzna involved movies that I've seen so far, uh, meaning the dentist
and, you know, uh, I do wish, you know, Yuzna is never gonna, well, he's
never, I don't think he's going to get back on track no matter how much
people love him now, he's probably an old man, but, um, I wish that just
once he had gotten like a pretty good budget.
From beyond is about their biggest budget, you know, like, but these are
all hovering in the $2 million range.
Would have loved to see what that guy could do with just a nice 10, you know?
But we'll never know.
I, he's him and the screaming mad George and Stuart Gordon or whatever.
There's just, we always talk about how much we love the practical effects on
here, but when they're done on the cheap and look this great, always
really impressive to me, very handmade quality to these movies that I love.
Yes, that hasn't done anything since 2011.
So I guess he's just retired.
Yeah.
And he does hide his age on his, uh, his age is not listed on his wiki.
So I'm assuming that that was a strategic move on his part.
Yeah.
But, uh, and he directed beyond reanimator.
Who the hell directed, Oh, he directed bride of reanimated.
Okay.
So then I put this on.
Um, anyway, I say definitely check it out.
Hogs up for from beyond.
Uh, just, I would do it on an empty stomach.
Uh, hogs up here as well.
Coming up next, we are coming back with a reviews of scream six.
We are coming back with reviews of the new evil dead.
Yes.
Um, and those will all be up by the end of the month.
You'll get the solo movie corn.
I'm on Instagram only now at the Patrick Walsh, uh, and that's all
I'm pumping right now, Joseph.
Sorry to plug so many episodes in a row gang, but I got a lot of live shows
coming up and I got to push these things.
But anyway, I'm coming your way.
Depending on where you live, but, uh, hitting the road live shows in
Cleveland, Ohio, four 20, Columbus, Ohio, four 21 and four 22 the following
weekend, I'll be in Baltimore, Maryland, uh, may 3rd back in New York at the
crane theater, uh, and then may 4th and 5th in Pittsburgh, uh, every one of these
shows, I'll be doing this new hour one man show.
I never promised you a Rose garden.
Come on out.
Joe DeRosa info .com.
And of course, if you're in New York city, come to Joey roses.
Uh, that's it folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.