I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll See You in Hell, your favorite podcast to talk about the movies you love.
We review them. We discuss them. We bounce them around. I'm Joe DeRosa.
And special announcement, we make them. That's right. Joe and I are making a film.
Starting today, we're going to record it on our new podcast. It's erotic in nature. It's all
done on Zoom. What I'm saying is we've we've each got our own only fans account where Joe and I will
be posting videos of us sticking things in our assholes. Yeah. You can find us. It's a website
where people show their genitals because they don't feel like working at a regular job.
Well, look, as I can tell, that's what it is. If somebody's going to pay, I completely understand.
It's no different showing your asshole online than it is doing a podcast. We're showing our emotional
assholes. I agree. I mean, look, I'm not I'm not saying I'm Mr. Workass like over here.
I guess the only difference is if my dad Googles my podcast, that's fine. But if you were to come up
with a picture of me sticking a carrot in my butt, that's the part where it's a little like I respect.
I'm not saying I don't respect only fan people do your thing. I don't give a shit. But I have a
respect for porn because it's like you threw the gauntlet down. I'm going all in. Yeah. This is my job.
Damn, damn it all to hell. My name I might see this whatever. Only fans seems a little less
committed to me and a little sneakier than porn. That to me and granted, I started this by asking
what only fans was. So I'm clearly an expert. But when I see, you know, like hot comics putting
them up or whatever, I'm like, great. It is to me a podcast. It's a side hustle. People should be
doing anything they can outside of robbery to get one up on this government, for God's sake.
They're they're believe me. They're trying to clear out your bank accounts. So do what you can. Yeah.
And my only fans is me robbing them. That's videos of me getting armed robbery. That's a win -win.
You get you get the loot from the heist and then you get the payment later. Yeah. But I like it
because the the woman or man, I know men do it as well are in control. You're not at the mercy of
a of a porn producer, which is essentially like a pimple arrangement. You're doing this incredibly
physical, incredibly exposing of yourself work that will stay with you forever. You've made that
decision. And they're getting a cut of it because they're slapping it in the, you know,
hey, they're putting it online where people aren't getting paid properly for what they do anyway.
Why not only fans? You could see. I see it another way. Think of all the overlooked
female porn directors that you're further harming by preventing them from getting the work they
deserve by taking your work. Okay. That's a very very different way of looking at it. But,
yeah, since we can't be in the same room with the pandemic, I'm going to insert something into
myself and then FedEx it to Joe and have him inserted in his self so that it will be like we're
sure. It looks like an American tale, but with but plugs. I an American tale. We don't even have to
change the writing. The puns right there. I've never seen an American tale. I don't understand
how what you said could possibly work into the story of that film. It's about a cartoon mouse,
is it not? Yeah, it's actually really good. And, you know, Spielberg production, Don Bluth,
they made a sequel that's good too. But I think it was the first movie I saw on theaters and it's
so it's about immigrant mice. Right. He's Mosquits and he gets separated from his family. So the
the best scene or the most emotional scene is he's singing from across the world somewhere out there
and then singing harmony is his sister mouse, I believe. And they're singing somewhere out there
to each other. Like maybe somebody's looking at the same moon as me. Right. In moon, maybe we work
that into the title of the right. Right. Right. I like it. And they they I by the way, Jesus,
this is embarrassing. Just now for the first time realized the play on words that it's a mouse
and it's called an American tale. Yeah, I never even I never caught that. So right now a fine pun,
but good enough to be the title. Absolutely not. And is it that now is it about a land? Is it about
an America run by mice? Or is it like the mice come over on a boat of human immigrants? And it's
they parallel the story. They do. They're on they're on in the whole of the actual immigrant boat.
It's memory serves. And since I mean, I've seen this movie a ton. I actually own it. But it's been
at least 10 years. They basically go under the promise of there's a song. It's a musical. They're on
going to be this amazing. They find it. Of course, there are cats, one of whom I believe is voiced by
Dom Deleweez, of course. And then somewhere out there, you've never heard that song. It was a huge
song. I know that. I know that song. Yeah, I know that song. But in the key over Isom,
the cats represent like the the the rulership class that's mean to the immigrants kind of thing.
Like I believe so. Yeah, the people who would who would haul our slurs and that sort of thing.
Okay. All right. Only the Irish were real scum at the beginning of the century when they'd come over.
It's funny. A lot of people were my friend was telling me yesterday he's from a neighborhood in
Brooklyn. He's from this. He grew up in the neighborhood where Carmine, whoever was murdered,
the boss and Donnie Brasco that kind of launches the when they kill him and Donnie Brasco launches
a chain of events that unravels. Anyway, the owner of the Carmine's Italian family -style restaurant,
right? Yeah. Yeah. It's a shame. I don't know why we did how we got, you know, you can tell
with how good the cuisine is that it's from somebody from the old country.
The spaghetti is so good. You could die. Anyway, I like that place. I mean, they give you 45 servings.
It's great. It's great. Delicious. But he's from that neighborhood. He was telling me yesterday
that that was the neighborhood where I think he referred to it as the Sicilian invasion or something
where it was like every he's Italian and he and his father is from Sicily and he said he was just
saying like all these Sicilians came over and they were all hated because they were basically
like involved in organized crime and coming over in droves from Italy. Right. You know, they were
not treated very well. As you can imagine, he likened it to the when the Cuban
immigration influx happened in the 80s that Scarface is based on. Yes. Yeah.
You know, now I was just reading about Cuba, but when I get sent stuff to look over by my agency,
it's always like it's the story of a Cuban immigrant boy coming to moving to Miami in the 80s and
and they want you to look at it to maybe run the show. And I'm always like interesting.
You know, I'm reading up on it and it is a very interesting story and good luck to them. But I was
like, I don't feel comfortable, especially in this day and age, being like, yeah, I'm the right
guy to tell the story of a Cuban immigrant moving to Miami in the early 80s. You know, so like
I'm not turning down millions or something. I'm just waiting for a project that better suits me,
but it's it feels so weird. You know, it really does. I think the guy that runs blackish is white.
You know, like there's all this stuff where it's like at some point, these people,
hey, they're going to have to step down, but be just it's crazy that now I'm still getting these
kind of offers like it makes no sense. You know, Pat, I've watched blackish and then I moved on to
mixed -ish. Yeah. And I'm still waiting for funny -ish.
Well, it is funny -ish. I haven't seen any of these series. I've from what I've heard blackish
at least early on was was funny. It's it's not. It's like every other, I mean, it's every other
it's and it's every NBC, you know, that show. It's that show. It's every one of those show.
Have you seen this new holy, oh, he's Mike just wrote us the he is black, the man running blackish.
He's been named the new showrunner. So clearly they realized. Yeah, thank you, Mike.
Yeah, it was this guy and no sweats of him. I think I don't know why I won't even say his name.
I think I know it, but he's supposed to be obviously a very talented man. He kept this show a big
head for five years, but it's it's it's weird, you know. The, well, and it also doesn't
fare well that you said. I heard it was funny when it used to be funny. And then they're talking about
they just switched. I know all that means I know people who watched it when it started airing. I mean,
I don't know who these people are who stick with a new show at this day and age for like eight
years. Have you watched, I mean, I hate watched it. I don't know why I don't know why I do it to myself,
but I couldn't sleep the other night. And I'm laying in bed with my iPad. And I go on Hulu,
like I'll try to turn something on and get drowsy. Perfect harmony. Have you seen this show?
See, when you're talking about things on the air, I have to be careful because I know often
you have a rider, but I'll say everything. Go ahead. But when I saw the billboard for that show,
it really made my heart sink. And in fact, Mike, if you can find find actually, I'm going to do it
because there's a few while you talk to you, I'm going to find the slogan for it because it made
me sick. Go ahead. It stars Bradley. What's his face? From Whitford, from Billy Madison. I think he
Bradley Whitford get out, of course. And West Wing. Oh my God. So you know the show, I mean,
these shows are so, you know, you know, paint by numbers at this point. You can just look at the title
and the picture. And you know exactly what it's about. It's called perfect harmony. He looks miserable.
And there's six like gleeful people standing around him. And you go, he's got to run a choir that he
hates. This is clearly what the fuck this is going to be. It's a play on harmony. And of course,
that's what it is. This is how the show opens. He's in his car, drinking and taking pills,
sort of comically, but he's like going to kill himself. It's sort of a comedic suicide scene.
And he's talking to bad news bears, mighty duck style opener. Yeah. Talking to his dead wife.
Yeah. You know, I just need a sign. If there's any reason for me to keep myself alive for five
more minutes, I need to sign with that. Yep. Yep. Here's a here's a choir. Uh -huh. Cause he's parked
outside of a church for some reason. He's decided to drive and park outside of a church to come in
maybe it gets explained. Maybe it's a some detail they reveal eight episodes in like a law situation
where, you know, this is this thing is gets revealed. Anyway, uh, he goes, no, no, no,
which I thought he was referring to. No, I don't want to live. Like don't God damn it. I don't
want to sign. I want to just die. And then he, that's not what he's doing. The gag is, I will not die
with this being the last thing I ever hear. Cause he's so off put by how bad the choir is. How, how
not in perfect harmony. And I'm doing air quotes. Yeah. They are. And he runs into the church drunk.
Yeah. And goes. And then they do the horrible thing where, you know, he just starts making up
nicknames for everybody. Like you tattoos, blah, blah, blah, you haystack. You know, like that
awful thing. Then one goes way too far. Like you fat bitch. They all gasp. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And then he just starts telling them like, you suck. You don't sing it like this. It's not
hallelujah. Yeah. It's hallelujah. And then he passes out because he's drunk. And then he wakes up
the next day and go any cartoon birds tweeting around the said when he's on the grid. No. But
one of the one of the choir members does turn into a ham before his eyes. And he starts to lick his
lips. But he, uh, so he passes out because he's drunk. This is all in under three minutes. I mean,
they are just hitting the fast forward button on the pilot episode anymore. Remember the whole
pilot episode would be like, no, we're going to actually, it's going to be almost a different show
because we're going to show where the character is coming from. And at the end, they land in this other
place in their defense. That you are not allowed to do that anymore. You have to set up a world
of story, 25 relationships. You have to know about their family. You have to know that they're good
at their job. That's always most important. Yeah. Be good at their job. But, um, absolutely. I mean,
the cheers pilot is like, okay, we've got a task of introducing them to 12 people that we want people
just hang out with and enjoy. Yeah. So that's what we're going to do. Hang out with them. You know, you
can't do that anymore. Yeah. And it's up. And then so, so at about the three minute mark, he passes
out drunk. Yeah. Excuse me. And, uh, and then he wakes up the next morning with no pants on.
Okay. A curious choice. And then he says, where are my pants? Why am I not wearing pants? And a very
large man in the group goes, they were tough to get off. Good thing. I'm strong. It's not a rape joke,
but it's an odd joke. And I don't quite understand what it's weird. Anyway. And then he goes,
I got to get out of here. You're all a bunch of idiots. And they go, no, we need you.
You taught us things in three minutes last night that nobody's there. And there you go. There's
the show. And we're off to the races. Oh, it's not the writers fault. It's not the writers fault.
It's not the directors fault. It's not the producers fault. It's networks fault.
It's, it's what it's more than likely. Yeah. There are bad writers who go very far in life,
but it more than likely. Yes. It's the network studios fault. How was he a conductor in his life before
this? By the way, there is no podcast talking this much about the pilot of NBC's cancelled perfect
harmony. I'll tell you that much. He was a train conductor, which I also thought was a strange
choice. I don't know. You're assuming I got passed in the where I just told you up to.
I was, I was so, it made me so mad I couldn't even leave it on to fall asleep board to.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm talking about I need something just to fall asleep to. I can't, you would think
I just leave something like that on and go, who cares? I don't, I'm not invested. It was making
me so angry. I was, I have to, I'm more awake now. I have to turn this on. Yeah. I stopped, I stopped
being a hate watcher of television because you can waste years of your life if the show goes on.
Luckily, my last hate watch was cancelled after 10 or 13 studio 60 on the sunset strip. The, in my
opinion, the greatest hate watch of all time, a show about sketch comedy made by somebody who's never
said anything funny. But also, I think Bradley Whitford was on studio 60 actually, but he was,
my God, one of the, one of the, I used to, I used to paste my one bedroom, not even a one bedroom,
it was a studio. My bed was, my bed was the room. And I would paste it when I first moved to L .A.
and just watch studio 60 and go, oh, fuck you, fuck you, everything. That was, I felt so bad for
Chandler. Yeah. It was, I was like, man, this guy stepped out of a hit show right into another show.
Yeah. Honoli different. He's batting a thousand. He's got two movies coming out. The movie's just
fucking tangles Russian and, uh, fools Russian was cute. And the, and the whole nine yards was a hit.
And that was actually kind of funny. Yeah, it wasn't a whole nine yards. But yeah, no, no, he had
fools Russian and he had, um, something else. Hold nine yards got a sequel.
Whole ten yards. Yeah, the whole ten yards. Whole ten yards. Not, not as good.
But a comedian friend of mine once asked me, he goes, Joe, do you ever hate watch stand -up comedy
just to get yourself ragefully like inspired? And then he goes, I'm a game in Glacias man myself.
It's very fun. I, I love hate watching stand -up comedy. That like, that feeling you get in the
pit of your stomach, it's sort of a relief that you're not there also, you know, for me. Yeah.
I'm not going to name names, but my God, do I have some names? It's endless. Yeah.
The almost heroes with Farley was the other one. Thank you, Mike. Directed as I told you the other day,
by Christopher Guest, which is insane. The movie, it's, it, it, it, it's like, it looks like it
was directed by automated cameras. I mean, I've never seen a less inspired and I, Christopher Guest is
great, obviously. And he puts some of those guys in it, Levy and all them, but just nobody hits.
It's just not there are five hilarious jokes in that movie. Yes. But the movie is terrible. Right.
Wagon's East, which is basically the same movie. There are no funny jokes. But the, the production
value of the movie aesthetically visually, it's, it's a much better film. Yeah. But it's just not
funny at all. Ever once, not ever. Yeah. I saw both movies theatrically. And I remember being
quite disappointed with both. But the Christopher Guest thing was weird because I was a fan of
government and stuff at the time. You know, I was like, Oh, shit. And it was not that. That's another
movie that I heard was heavily re -edited and so on and so forth. It was not supposed to be a
farly Chandler vehicle. It was supposed to have much more like a Bill Murray type vibe. I don't,
what almost heroes almost heroes. Well, I think to like, I think like, I don't think he knows,
I think he's good at, he's one of those guys. He's good at what he does. He's like a Woody Allen type
where it's like, right. He knows how to do his thing. You like, if Woody Allen directed Raiders of
the Lost Ark, it would be fucking horrible. Yeah. Absolutely. He would have no idea what to do. And I think
with Christopher Guest was like, if he's not doing that docu, you know, like Gonzo style thing,
like he doesn't know how to do it. Yeah, one doesn't necessarily mean you'll be good at the other.
I mean, documentary filmmakers don't usually become great narrative filmmakers. Actually,
it's usually a low success for it. But before we get off perfect harmony, Mike did find the
the ad. Don't even look at it, Joe. Let me, let me, let me spoil it. I remember driving down
Hyperion right here by my house. And I see the billboard for perfect harmony. And obviously,
as a TV writer, all you do driving down the street is go, ah, fuck you. Oh, that piece of shit.
So I'm doing that as usual. And I see it perfect harmony. And the tagline says, he needs them.
They need him, H Y M N. Now that to me is the worst tagline I've ever seen.
And and taglines by nature are bad. He needs them. They need so they need one song of him.
Like the even the thing doesn't work. Yeah, they need him. They need a him, I guess, but they need
him as not a statement. It's also a joke you don't get hearing it. You have to read it.
So you're, you're already angering the blind community. I don't know. It's, uh, yeah,
the deaf people are watching, they can't hear the songs. You're cutting out half of your audience
here. Yeah, it reminds me of, uh, of another one that I've ever met and remembered for 25 years.
I mean, I always thought I would do well in advertising. And I might still wind up there.
I think I could make a good dollar at it. But I opened up my steak and shake menu in Missouri.
And they had this, you know, that they clip in the advertisements for like new things,
whatever. So it falls into my lap and I pick it up and look at it. And it says,
uh, blackberry cobbler available for a limited time. But oh, what a limited time it is.
That's the craziest, the craziest thing I've ever heard. And again, it's like, so everyone looked
at this and was like, yep, that makes sense. Forget funny. Like it doesn't make sense. Something
can't be like super limited. That's crazy. That's insane. What was your doctor giggles tagline?
Oh, the doctor giggles actual tagline is the doctor is out dot, dot, dot of his mind. Yeah. Okay.
That's right. I wanted it to be on the flip side or maybe one of those hologram VHS boxes where it
changes. Right. Uh, say the doctor is in dot, dot, dot, saying. Yeah, it's funny. I can never
remember which is the real one in which is yours. That's how that's how good yours is.
Oh, thank you. Mine is insane, which I think is a little better than the doctor is out of his mind.
I think so too. Cause you never say the doctor is out. You say the doctor is in.
Right. And I think the reason it's a little better is the doctor not being there isn't scary.
The doctor being there is scary. Yeah. The murderous doctor, he's, he's at Wendy's having
lunch. And it's not a great start to a horror move. Oh, okay. And then I won't go to Wendy's.
Yeah. Good idea. I just go straight home. Yeah. Skip it. Let's skip that baconator. Right.
Well, Pat, we're off to a nice start. We are. Well, Jim's for the movie corner today.
Should we head over? I think we should. Cause I got a few things I'm excited to talk about.
Right. Uh, you want to start? Yes. Okay. I watched Lemony Snicket's a series of unfortunate events.
Not the series. The movie. This is Barry Sonnenfeld, Jim Carrey, right? Yes. Never saw.
Don't ever watch it. Okay. It's very well reviewed. Really made a lot of money.
Was supposed to launch a franchise and inexplicably they just didn't. It's one of those things where
it's like this made money and critics liked it. Right. Why did you not make a franchise? Right.
Like there's nine more books that you set out to make a franchise. Why didn't you? It's one of those
things that head scratcher things with Hollywood. You go, you just didn't do a thing that made perfect
sense. They could have saved Jim Carrey's life. He wouldn't be out here hawking a surreal memoir right now.
Yeah. Well, you can tell that, uh, Carrey did it because, you know, he gets to put on
four prosthetic noses throughout the film and play different characters, whatever the fuck it is.
Visually fairly stunning film. Very Burton -esque, you know, early Burton.
Uh, you know, uh, that sort of, you know, uh, storybook, uh, neo -gameany kind of vibe, you know,
that Burton used to bring to the table. Uh, you know, like I'm talking, of course, with big eyes.
Guys was okay. It's all the movie of his in the last 10 years that was even okay.
Uh, although I didn't see Dumbo so I don't know. I tried to watch it. It's Burton. I mean,
we've discussed what a fall off. Jesus Christ. Anyway, we almost want to see it like a graph. You
want to look at a graph as like the COVID graphs of how it's progressing. That would be the
straightest down I think in the history of film is Timberd. It's, uh, it's up there, man. It's up
there. It's a real fall off. Anyway, uh, visually stunning film, uh, performances are fine.
Directions fine, you know, uh, it's just boring. It's just, they're just really not much to it.
Uh, they combine four books into one movie. Uh, which is fine, I guess. I guess not a lot
happens in the books. I was kind of trying to read the synopsies of each novel to see like,
what did they leave out? They all seem very boring and uneventful. Uh, but anyway,
it's, it's, it's, it just brought me to this, the reason I wanted to talk about it is
it brought me to this realization about Jim Kerry where it's the beginning of this phase
of Jim Kerry movies where when you read the reviews of the movie,
people are saying, oh my god, this is classic Kerry. He's back in full form in this film,
hilarious. Right. And then you watch it and you go, I didn't literally, I didn't laugh
not once. Literally never not once that I laughed. And they did that with Sonic the Hedgehog. So
finally the other day, I was like, you know what? I guarantee by now all the Kerry scenes are on
YouTube for Sonic the Hedgehog. I don't feel like watching the movie even as a video game fan I didn't
want to see it. Yeah. And I went on and watched the Kerry scenes. These things, I mean, it was like
watching fucking bypass surgery. There was nothing funny. And it was sterile. It wasn't even like,
oh, this is falling flat. It was like, this is sterile. This just, there's nothing here. There's
nothing to this. And then you go and watch the press junkets. And these people are like, oh my god,
it is so good to see you back being this hilarious again. They were talking about this thing,
like it was fucking Ace Ventura 3. Yeah. And that seems to be like I said, it's kind of started with
let me sneak it where it's like every few years this Kerry thing comes out and they go, you know,
because he does it around eight bullshit like Russian murder mystery indies that he makes or whatever
the fuck right. And they go, finally, we got Jim Kerry back. And then you watch it and you go,
he's not funny in it. Like they did it with Bert Wunderstone, which I think is a very funny movie.
Yes. I think Jim Kerry is arguably the least funny person in the movie.
I agree. Steve Buscemi gets more laughs in that movie. Yeah. And I just don't, I don't understand
what that is. And it just, I found it puzzling. I really was trying to wrap my head around.
Is it a commentary on entertainment and comedy? Is comedy fallen that far from grace, mainstream comedy?
Has it fallen that far from grace that people are like, he put on a mustache and walked around
funny. And we thought it was hilarious. It's like, okay. What was the last funny comedy? You know,
I immediately have to rack my brains. And it's like people have been saying bridesmaids for almost
a decade now. Like it seems recent because the movie holds up. It's still very funny. And it's on
all the time. But people are like, well, you know, bridesmaids, that movie was came out in 2011 or
something. Yeah. So it's been a very long time since we've had in my opinion, even an above average
comedy in terms of just like a laugh getter. Very rare. It's been a while, man. And I hate to,
I hate to shit on the both of them. It's not a shitting on it. It's just a criticism. But I mean,
even Seth Rogan's new movie looks fucking horrific. An American pickle.
Yeah. It's like the invention of the pickles, right?
It's a, you ready for this? It's a story of a man in the, I guess, 20s, 1920s or something.
Who falls into a, works in a pickle factory falls into a vat of pickles.
And then awakens in present day because the brine preserved his body.
Never mind. Never mind the insanity of that premise. Yeah. Nobody, I guess nobody checked on this
pickle that in 100 years. It just sat there. People were eating pickles. I guess they didn't
notice there was a body and it or whatever. Right. Also, you can see through pickle, bruh.
You'd see him in there like a mosquito in the amber.
Yeah. And then, and then he wakes up in modern day and meets Seth Rogan. Seth Rogan in a dual role.
Okay. You know, and it's like, you know, he's playing.
Has there ever been a good way with a dual role? No, no, it's terrible.
I thought other than the, other than the nutty professor, other than nutty professor.
I don't think I've ever really enjoyed a dual role. And both finger. I like both finger.
And Norbit. Let's not leave Norbit off. So Eddie Murphy movies, but other than that coming to America,
yes, he's the only one that can pull it off. This is what they do in every dual role movie.
And this is what they're doing in the Seth in the Seth Rogan thing. They're like, you're not
anywhere near capable of playing two different people. So what we, they use struggle with one.
What we need you to do is a heavy sort of Russian immigrant accent. So they know who the hell
which person is which right now that we're looking at. That's what they all do with these things.
One guy's got a zany accent. The other guy doesn't. And it's a, that it looks terrible.
And then the, the new will feral movie. Again, he's doing it.
I started it didn't make it. Accent. And it's like, and they're, what are they figure skate? What the,
is this is fifth figure skater movie? They're in a songwriting contest that Eurovision
thing that Abba won and kicked off their career. And you know, I'm not saying that couldn't be
interesting. But if you remember, American dreams with a Z, where they tried to make American Idol
into a comedy, it's like that doesn't really work. So I'm not sure why you're trying it again. But
whatever, I started the movie. It was Pierce Brosnan as Will Ferrell's dad.
They're both talking. They're both talking in these thick accents. And almost like they're laughing
at the end of each line. Like you can tell they think it's really funny, which makes it worse.
Because Ferrell's whole thing would be this dead -eyed, you know, like I'm dead serious about this.
It's what made him so funny. And now, you know, it's just, it's not the same. It's like watching,
you know what it is, is like, and maybe this was different with your dad, but like people's
dads are funny until you're like 10. And then every year after that your dad becomes
1 ,000 % less funny, you know, like until when he's 65, whatever, he's just this, his joke attempts
or seem like they're from another time, you know, like your fake laughs, not convincing anybody.
Yeah. That's what happens. Unfortunately, comedy is kind of a young man's game, except for a
select few people, young man and women's game, of course, but there are, don't get me wrong. There
are people who remain funny up until the day they die, but it's usually a slippery slope.
Larry David, you know, he'll take some swings now on curb. Herb is still, you know, the most guaranteed
laughs on television, I would say. Right. So it's not a criticism really, but sometimes he'll do
something like really kind of broad and zany and like three studios, and you remember like,
oh yeah, he's like 75, you know, he's got kind of a different sense of humor, but it still works
a lot of the time. Yeah, yeah, no, I hear you, I hear you. No, that was the longest movie review,
I think you've ever done on the show, we would be, you reviewed 14 movies in the span of one.
I will only do two in the movie corner. That was a lot. No, it's all good. That was a big,
that was a, that was a thickie. Speaking of old men who are always funny,
RIP to the great Carl Reiner. Yes. And Turner classic movies was doing a five movie
Carl Reiner directed marathon the other night. So it was a lot of fun. I didn't watch some of
them. I've seen like, I really like dead men don't wear a plaid. I really like all of me.
I love all of them. And I love man with two brains. Those are the three Steve Martin and the
jerk, of course, which is the best of them all. I never saw the plaid one or the brains one.
You would love both of those, but particularly man with two brains is they almost like a naked gun
style of comedy and Kathleen Turner's great in it. It's very funny. Okay. But all four of those
Steve Martin Carl Reiner things are worth watching. His other directorial stuff, you know, he did like
sibling rivalry with Kirstie Alley there near the end. And then there was fatal instinct,
which was his like loaded weapon. Remember that with Armando Santé and the Leslie Nielsen role.
Really quick. Remember the time you said Rex Reed was just a mean old bitch on the show.
Yeah. I read a review of a movie that Coppola made that I never even, it's called like time
against time or youth without youth. It's called I've never heard of it. I've seen the movie.
And not good. Hand by critics. But I read the, I think it was a Wikipedia Rex Reed. The snippet said,
you know, you're in trouble when the biggest star is Tim Roth.
Something only a mean old bitch would say. Yeah. Yeah. It's not necessary. It's not a necessary shot.
Yeah. He's filling a martini on the carpet while he says it. Anyway, sorry. Go ahead.
No, it's fine. So yeah, he, you know, he made some duds near the end. Honestly, kind of a similar
trajectory to Mel Brooks, who I'll get to another time. I recently rewatched all of his stuff.
But, uh, Reiner, I watched this movie enter laughing. That was like his first movie. It sucked
it was schmaltzy. But he did wear his papa, which is this notorious movie I had always heard of.
You seen that movie, Jim? They're in herd of it. It's like a cult classic. And it's Ruth Gordon,
the old lady from Harold and Maude. And George Siegel, who we discussed this week, you were talking about
just shoot me. And George Siegel's mom is played by Ruth Gordon. And she's a senile, very annoying
old woman. And he basically doesn't want to live with her anymore. She's like killing his
chances to hook up with women. He hates her. It's very throwm on it from the train. So he fantasizes
all the time about killing her. And he tries to kill her. And it's very dark comedy. And all I
never heard about it was it was very dark. And that you won't believe the infamous pushy scene.
And then I looked up posters from the movie at the time. And it was like the poster for the movie
would be a tiny picture of the stars. And then in huge letters, you will not believe your eyes when
the pushy scene begins. So I mean, I was like, what is this thing going to be? And I was excited
because it's out of print. You can't find the movie anywhere. So it was on Turner Classic movies.
The print they had went out of focus at various points. So it's a hard movie to find. And I realized why?
I'm watching. I'm watching. It's very dark. It predates like an always sunny,
sign -failed curb style of humor. And it's like 1970. So it's very jarring but very, very funny. I thought
real off -color jokes go on and etc. And the pushy scene pops up. And what it is is Siegel's got a woman
over. And he's like, mom, you got to be good tonight. I got the woman coming over. You know, that
scene. Right. And the mom clearly due to her senility mixes up her son and her husband who is
dead. Papa of the titular wears Papa. So she, I guess in the middle of dinner, mistakes her son,
George Siegel, for her ex -husband pulls his pants down and is kissing his bare butt, saying like,
look at that cute little Toshiyo whatever. In front of this woman, he's trying to impress. Now it's
funny. You can imagine at a theater in 1970, the theater would be screaming as if it was the
the hair gel gag and something about Mary. I know it's outrageous for the time. But I was like, this,
this is what I've been hearing about since I was a child and couldn't find this movie, this Toshiyo
saying. So anyway, I don't let it bring me down. I'm enjoying the movie. It's funny and very dark
and very short. George Siegel's actually great in it. Then they get to my favorite character in the movie
Ron Leedman, who you know if you saw him. But he's playing the brother of George Siegel and he
keeps trying to push the mom off on the brother. So every time the brother comes running through the
park to help out, he promised he'd help out whenever he could. He gets mugged in the park by a group of
black men. Okay. And they take his clothes or whatever else. One of them is Garrett Morris actually
of two broke rules. That's that right. Okay. This one time he's running through his brother has a
guerrilla suit that he's been using to scare his mom in the morning to try to scare her and kill her.
Okay. So the brother gets robbed. They take all his clothes. He goes, do you have anything I can
wear on the way home? And he gives him the guerrilla suit. So he's walking home in a guerrilla suit.
He gets mugged by this group of black guys. So they're all like walking together. It's, you're already
like, what joke are they going for you? I hate this. It feels awful watching it. Then the brother who's
like this, you know, 50 year old nice Jewish guy, they are all, they're going to kill him. But then
they get distracted by this beautiful set of legs coming down the stairs, this white lady coming
down the stairs. And they all start hooting and hollering. And then he's like, wait, what are you guys
going to do? What are you guys going to do? And they go, well, we're going to rape her, man. What,
you never done a gang right before? Then Garrett Morris says, and I'm not kidding. It's in our
nature. What? What? He says it's like a tradition of ours. So now, do they mean is that a black
joke or is that a gang like we're gang joke? I think absolutely it is a black joke. I don't think
anyway to look at it is good. But right, right. Yeah. Yeah. He's like, it's a tradition of ours.
It's in our nature. They run over. They grab this woman. They drag her body over. This is a comedy
on Turner classic movies, on Turner classic movies at 7 p .m. on a Tuesday to commemorate the death of
yeah. Exactly. So I'm watching this. I actually, I sat up straight and wound up in a standing
position by the end of the scene. I could not believe it. And they drag her body over, throw her
on the ground and start raping her. They're, you know, you know, Ryan or thankfully, it doesn't like
do shots of the face or anything like that. But they're raping her and it's being played sort of
for last. And they're like, what's the woman doing? Which she like, it's screaming. But I mean, I would
have met they don't they don't have her played in a humorous I imagine that's just disturbing.
Like how do you have all these three is like legs hair? You don't even really see face.
But yeah, it's deeply disturbing. Yeah, it's just just straight up. She's not going to stop it, boys.
It's not like one of those. At the beginning, it's like no, no, but then she has no voice in the scene
at all. There's just a quiet gang rape. So then they're trying to get the brother to do it, who's in
the gorilla costume still. And he goes, he's holding the gorilla head. And he's like, no, I'm not
going to rape. Not going to rape. They finally go running off because they are done or they get
scared or whatever else. He stays the brother and takes a turn raping the woman. The nice heroic
brother character in the movie. He dives in and starts rape. Then he called George Segal is all pissed
because his brother's not there to take the mom and it's messing up his big date. They cut right back
into it. And the brother calls him. And he's like, where are you? You're supposed to be here. I've
got this dinner. And his brother goes, I'm in prison. And he goes, why are you in prison? And he goes,
rape. And he goes, what'd you say? And he goes, what was that rape scream of this guy?
I am. My head is exploding. And I know I'm taking a long time with this review, but I feel it's
important to share the scene with people. He goes, right, right. So then he goes to pick him up.
And he's like, I think I think I think I'm in big trouble here. I mean, I shouldn't have raped.
I just shouldn't have raped. He's like, how could you rape? They start doing almost like a
sign felt riff on it. I'm going to say it's like a diner conversation. It really was.
Something tells me Larry David loves this movie. I have a feeling. But they're talking about rape,
etc. And incomes the guard with a dozen roses. Because they're worried, how's he going to get
out of this jail sentence? The guard comes in with a dozen roses and he's like, what's this? He goes,
it's from the, the cop was, what do you mean? Turns out that the woman they dragged over and raped
was a male cop in drag, trying to like entice customers and arrest them. But instead got gang
raped by this group of people, including the brother who took a turn. The brother,
they noticed that when during the rape that the woman had a penis and they had to have sex in her
asshole, that George Seagal, it's a much funnier joke. I don't remember what it was. George
Seagal's like, you didn't notice. And he's like, it was very exciting. He actually said it was very
exciting. I was very aroused. And that's kind of funny in a straight way. But I wasn't really
laughing because it was so nuts. And I want to kind of like rewatching segments of it because I couldn't
believe it. But he's like, yes, I raped him. And it turns out now that the guard or the police officer
who had just been raped gives a dozen roses to a guard and says, hey, give it to him because he's
fallen in love with him now. After being gang raped in central park, the sixth guy who gang raped
him. And by the way, the brother keeps saying that the black guys forced him to rape her even though
he does it voluntarily, which is also like not a joke. And just like a really weird dark detail.
Right. Right. Yeah. Um, he's keeps talking about how he was aroused by it. And then he gets the roses
and he looks at him. And for the rest of the movie, it's this running joke where the brother's
looking at the roses and like giggling, reminiscing on his time, participating in a gang rape of
this man who gave him flowers. So now I think these two men are supposed to be in love with each other
by the end of the movie. She just all lasts 15 minutes. I mean, it was one of the craziest stretches
in a movie I think I've ever seen in my life. And what is the advertising do? You won't believe that
Tushie scene. Yeah. It tells you how much more owls change, you know. Yeah. The Tushie scene.
I'm on Amazon as we speak, adding the movie to my cart. I got to see this. Can you find it?
Yeah. It's Blue Race 20 bucks on Amazon. Hmm. Sounds insane. Well, it's Christ. You know,
straight up, I always thought of Mel Brooks as being the boundary pusher and Carl Reiner is kind of
the gentle PG grandpa side of it because the Dick Van Dyke and all that. But I was blown away by it.
Really? It was crazy. I can't say I was like rolling on the floor the whole time. I just
admired it. You know, it was, it was very ballsy. And when I search it on Twitter, it's a holy mean.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. I mean, it sounds very irreverent for the time, especially.
Yeah. I search it on Twitter. And apparently it's like Sarah Silverman's favorite movie. And
there's a lot of people who cited as one of their favorites. So I think it's just sometimes a movie
that's hard to find becomes people's favorites because they feel cool that they've seen it. But
it's a good comedy and certainly insane as I describe. I'm trying to purchase any movie that I think
might get removed or banned or whatever. Like that one get removed. Yeah. I bought 120 days of
Sodom the other day. I bought the I bought a tough set. Yeah. I don't even think I want to watch it.
I just want to own it. I bought the devils. I had to get an import. Yeah. I don't like that
movie. It's visually very cool. Of course, but I don't like it. It's supposedly terribly disturbing
as well. Is it not? Didn't bug me. I mean, I was way more disturbed by where's Papa? Well,
I mean, speaking of rape, the the the infamous scene of the devils that's that's no longer in the
movie and has only been shown once ever to in a public screening in 2006. It's called the
raping of Christ and a bunch of nuns have sex with a statue of Jesus while Oliver Reed masturbates to it.
And apparently the scene is so disturbing. It's it literally was shown one time at one screening ever.
The version I bought in the movie is the Ken Russell cut and the reviews were like,
this is as close as you're getting to like the unedited version of this film, but like you're
not getting the unedited version. But speaking of, you know, this is what kills me with Hollywood
is, you know, as they, you know, triumphantly waive the flag of their ideals about what's not
appropriate, content wise, whatever they've perpetuated all of it. That's what always drives me so
crazy about the Hollywood people going, that's terrible. You shouldn't do this. You guys were the ones
doing it. Right. You know what I mean? Like, so which leads me to my next review, which is an
episode of Just Shoot Me. I'm going to stick on theme here. More seagull. The George Seagull,
sitcom vehicle, just shoot me. And it's in the air. What streaming services just shoot me on? Because
a lot of people are talking about just who Lou. Okay. This Emily Heller is a very funny comment
had tweeted. The show would have been so much better if it was a woman running it. And she was like,
it should have been Jenna Rollins as like a ball busting woman because women were the ones running
these fashion magazines at this time. And I tweeted at her, I was like, what woman in quotes was
going to bring the heat of a 1997 George Seagull? Because it's insane that he even got that part. He
was never a star in his career. Well, he was in flirting with disaster, which was a very funny movie.
I watched a few episodes of this show. It's not a key on it. Let's focus on Seagull for one
terrible. He's okay. I texted you. I said, George Seagull might be a horrific actor. I always
thought he was a good actor. I was like, did I just never watch anything with George Seagull? He's
terrible. He's terrible. You'll like him and wears pop. He's doing, it's like the Christopher
Guest thing. He's out of his element. He's doing, you can tell he's doing what he thinks you're
supposed to do on a multi -cam sitcom. Right. And it's very transparent. And it's just not good.
Even spade can't save this fucking show. I mean, it just didn't, it just didn't age well. It's
just not that great of a show. I tuned in primarily to watch spades. I've been listening to his audio
book and I'm a big fan. Love all his audio books. Yeah. And it's just, it's, I mean, you could never
make the show now. Spade is alleged on this thing like you wouldn't fucking believe. He's like
stealing naked photos out of models, portfolios. And you know, it's crazy. You know what I mean?
And the gag is he's going to go masturbate to that later. You know what I mean? It's just,
anyway, you couldn't, you couldn't make the show now at least in the way that they made it then.
But it's not a good show. I don't think. I never watched it when it was on. Maybe I just missed a boat.
But I bring it up because I looked on Wikipedia when I was watching it. I said,
did I, am I missing something? Wasn't this a huge hit show? And it was seven seasons. It's considered
a classic, you know, modern day modern age classic sitcom, whatever. And I saw on Wikipedia, it said
the episode slow Donnie is considered an all -time great sitcom, you know, classic episode or whatever.
It's like, I was slow Donnie. And since starting David Cross, guess starting David Cross,
I was like, well, I want to see a David Cross episode. No, I'd be funny. And I can't mean,
slow Donnie can't mean what I think it means. And it does.
It does. The photographer, they go to his house and you meet his brother,
slow Donnie, played by David Cross, who is a guy that fell out of a tree when they were kids
and has been in heavy quotes slow ever since. They don't use the word retarded because it's
all in good taste. I'm surprised they didn't, by the way. That word was still very much in use at that time.
Cross is introduced into the episode wearing a helmet and eating a giant turkey leg.
This is how the character is introduced. And he's going, Donnie hungry. Donnie hungry. This is the
character on the second, right? Mike just sent us a photo of him with a helmet. Yeah.
I brought this up on without a country the other day too. And we pulled up, thanks Mike.
We pulled up pictures. I can't believe that this was an episode of a sitcom, right?
Then comes the twist. You're watching this thing and you're going,
how is this considered a classic? I don't even understand. It's not that it's not like it's
getting huge laughs or anything. And I guess it's a classic. It was popular because here comes
the twist now. The twist is he's not slow. He's just pretending to have major brain damage.
Because everybody waits on him hand in foot and treats him like a child, as you would,
somebody who was mentally handy. That's the plot of the show. And then the main lady on the show,
I forget her character name. She's faced with the conundrum of, I know that he's faking it,
but his own brother doesn't know. And on top of it all, he's a creep. Donnie's a creep. He's also a
pervert. So it's a lot of like, you know, when he gets to the woman alone, it's a lot of like,
hey, baby, you want to get out of here? What do you say? And she's like, stop being a perv.
And then everybody's, you know, it's the gag you were saying, like, she yells the thing and then
everybody looks at her and goes, how could you be mean to this challenge, sweet man? You know,
it's a different time. Now here's the thing. I'm not saying,
I am a strong proponent of never censoring art. I don't have a problem that they did it.
I don't give a shit. I have no dog in that race. It's just crazy to me that this, this is the camp.
This is the camp screaming the loudest about we need change. We need to do this. We do. But you guys
were the ones doing the shitty stuff. You know, it's like, you shouldn't fat shame. I wasn't fat
shaming. You guys were fat shaming. You're the ones that made shallow how. I didn't fucking make that.
Sure. Yeah. So it's just, it's, it's, it's, it's insane to me. And also the episode still isn't funny.
With that outlandish of a premise, even, it's still not even that funny. How is Laura San
Jakomo on the show? That's true. Like her. She's fine. Everybody's fine. Like on the,
everybody's Pat Seagull's bad on the show. Everybody else's Wendy Malik's on it.
Everybody's fine. It's just not a funny show. I mean, maybe it gets funny. But it's like,
you know, dude, good. I just remember them letting Spade take over at some point. Like it was,
like Andy Dick on news radio where every promo just became him. So maybe by the end of it,
the show changed in some way. Spade is, is the funniest on it. But it's not,
it's not the, it's, you know, spade. Look, Spade's a hilarious guy. Yeah. But he's a hilarious guy.
He's very rarely in things that are hilarious. You know what I mean? For sure. Yeah.
He doesn't make like great movies and stuff. And he's been in one Tommy boy.
And Black sheep. Oh, sure. And Black sheep. And both Joe Dirt. I'm not a Joe Dirt guy.
I mean, either am I. I don't get it. Yeah. Dennis Miller being in Joe Dirt is the strangest aspect
of it all to me. They're like, good buddies. Yeah. I think I think I get the impression from Spade
reading like his like about his charity and Wikipedia. And like some of the stuff he says in the
audiobook, I get, I think he's probably a closeted Republican. Oh, sure. He just doesn't want
to talk about it. Right. Publicly. But, but he's very funny. He is. I watched dangerous liaisons,
which was like a big Oscar movie of like 1988. It is the story that was later adapted for teens
as cruel intentions. Yep. Which certainly a lot of people of my generation would call masturbating too.
Dangerous liaisons is actually really fun. I don't normally like these kind of period pictures.
This is in Paris. Oh, I really popped the mic on that one. Sorry. Paris.
And it is Glenn Close in the Sarah Michelle Geller role. John Malkovich somehow in the Ryan
Felipe seducer role. Yeah. Michelle Fyfer and the Reese Witherspoon role.
I love that you're, I love that you're retconning dangerous liaisons. Yeah, exactly.
If it was inspired by cruel intentions. Yeah. It was a play. It was actually a play where Alan
Rickman was playing the John Malkovich part. And apparently it was one of his greatest performances.
He played it for years on the stage. And they were like, no, we need a name. We need a name.
So they passed on Alan Rickman who went and did die hard. Right. That was 1988.
And they brought in the hot name of 88 John Malkovich.
So, and it's got a great supporting cast. A naked Uma Thurman, which was amazing.
It has a young Kiana Reeves. And why does Kiana Reeves always play the
British fop in these movies? Like, could anyone be less suited to play those kind of parts?
But he's always, he's in Bram Stoker's Dracula. He's in much to do about nothing. He's
in dangerous liaisons. I think there's more. He's not, he's not good at playing a British guy. It's
crazy to me. He honest, not good at playing most things. He's great as John Wick for most of it.
Yes. I mean, but even in this new Bill and Ted trail, which I was so excited. I'm going in with
a smile on my face. I hope it's good. I'm going to see it. Yeah. The day it comes out, I'm going to
see it. I was very excited when the trailer dropped. Yes. The trailer has not made me even smirk.
And the commentary that I keep hearing or keep reading online is, why is Kiana Reeves expressionless
through the entire thing? Like Alex Winner slides right back into the, like, you're like,
yeah, it's fucking Bill and Ted. And Kiana Reeves, he just looks like, almost like he has like a
paralysis or something. Like, he's just not, even when they do the guitar thing, he's not like
smiling or anything. It's very strange. Yet he's like, I had the time of my life making this
move. I've never laughed so hard. Right. Yeah. Maybe he's got paralysis in the film or something.
Maybe it's part of his part of the plot. I think that it's going to reveal. I think the reason
is going to be because he says in the new trailer, I'm tired, Ted or I can't remember who's who.
Yeah. I think it's going to be that he's really depressed. And then like, he gets his spirit back
or something. I think that's what it's going to be. But we'll see. I'm down for that. Yeah.
Low budget, by the way, you can tell like all the scenes that take place in the future were shot like
on the top floor of a skyscraper in downtown LA. You know, this place is a lot of windows.
Yeah. I think they did a quick and on the cheap pen. It was a labor of love.
But yeah, so dangerously, he's on basically the plot is these like, scheming people who are bored
and rich with too much time on their hands. Daring and betting and wagering on people's sexuality.
Like, if you can take this girl's virginity, I'll let you fuck me. He's like the plot of the movie.
Glenn Close says that to Malcolm. So then he's going to do that. And she gets kind of jealous of that.
So she says if you go fuck Michelle Fyfer, who's a very devout religious woman,
then I'll let you fuck me as well. So it's like they're all wagering their bodies for each other.
It's very like, you know, breathy romance novel. But the dialogue is great in it. They're all really
nasty to each other. It kind of reminded me of like closer that movie, but set 100 years ago, you know.
Way more than 100 years ago. Closer is a great. I really like that. Yeah. So it had great dialogue.
It won best screenplay at the time. It's it's a good movie. And Malcolm, which is good. Fyfer's good. Close
is good. I recommend. If you want something different, it was fun. Trash.
All right. We'll close it out with something positive because I was very negative on the first two.
I watched Dolly Parton. Here she comes again. All right. It was an ABC like hour long
bio, you know, thing about Dolly Parton basically. And what she's up to now.
And they tell her life story. They get into, you know, her bout with depression in the 80s,
her success. Obviously, her great success. And you know, it's just, you know, it's it's part for the
course, what you'd expect out of a television program like that. But it's fascinating and it's
uplifting. They say at the beginning of that they have a bunch of talking heads at the beginning of
the show and everybody's like, try and find a person who doesn't love Dolly Parton. Yeah.
And you watch this thing and you're kind of waiting for the other shoot or drop at some point.
And it just never does like, you're like, my God, she is just a magical human being.
Like, I was already worried about her. Yeah. I was already afraid. And by the way, she says stuff
that if anybody else said it, you'd be like, hey, fuck you. Yeah. There's an interview clip with her
where she's like, I want to be, I want to, I'm a star, but I want to be a superstar. And
Barbara Walters goes, how much money do you make every year? And she's like, you know, I make 500,
600 ,000 a year. And that's not count my record sales, but I want to make millions. And like,
and you're just like, yeah, you go, girl. Like, there's yeah, there's no part of you that's appalled by
it. Because and then a big part of that is because she does so much shit for chair. It's crazy. How
beautiful. There was like parts of the South and like where she's from where there, she has a
book thing that she does to distribute books to schools. And like they're interviewing teachers and
the teachers are welling up like, we wouldn't have books if it wasn't for Dolly Parton. Like, it's,
she's amazing. And then they get into Dollywood and she talks about how she fired her entire team.
Okay. Because she said, I want to make a theme park that celebrates where I come from.
The Smoky Mountains. And it's going to be called Dollywood. And they were like, are you insane?
Because it, it does sound like the ravings of a lunatic way to see it on paper. You're like, what the
fuck are you talking about? And she goes, but I did it. And then I fired all of them. And I was like,
yeah, Jesus Christ. She did do it. That's why I text you the other day. And I said, why have we never
gone to Dollywood? I'm scratching my head, watching this thing. Like, why have I never been there?
It seems like a wonderful place to go. Yeah. You might have given me that explanation. I was just
walking down the street and I get a text that says, why haven't we gone to Dollywood? I was like,
I'll go right now if you want to. I'm ready. I'm ready to die. Yeah. I knew that was,
would be your response. So I didn't feel like I need it really. And he always been a writer,
died for Dolly. Have you seen her live? No. We saw it the bowl. I mean, it's like getting a one -hour
hilarious stand -up routine mixed between all the songs and then all the hits. I mean, it's all you
could ask for. She's got zingers for days, you know, she's funny. She tells stories about her
life and they're actually funny and good and interesting. The thing I don't think I would,
I want to see her live. I would, I want to go. The one thing I don't think I would like about the
live show is the, is the live performance of nine to five. I don't like because they showed clips of
it. I don't like that she does that like, she doesn't almost like a monologue now. Like, like, she sings
the chorus, but then the versus she goes, she goes like, you know, pour myself a cup of
ambition, right? And she's like pointing like, getting the shower, what? And the blood starts pumping,
you know, and they're like, oh, sing, sing the song. Like, sing it. I want you to, you know what I mean,
don't perform it. Sing it. I think I recall her singing it. Sometimes as actors get up there,
they can't hit the stuff they used to. So they talk it. Like, you know, it's that thing that bands,
every band does this with their biggest hit. It's a lot of like, I'm giving the crowd the mic.
I'm sort of talking it like you, every line is delivered. Like, you know the words. You know what I mean?
And it's like probably because they're like, probably because they're like, I'm going to blow my
fucking head off. If I have to sing this song one more, absolutely. You know, but, but she's, she's
amazing. Sing us the song. Yeah. The piano. Sing us the song because we're all
also didn't 24 ounce Miller light on the piano next one. Just gotten from concessions. You just
walk down your song and got it from concessions spills it into the piano. It doesn't, it doesn't even
wipe it up shorts out. He looks like a creeper on stage, shorting with his hair standing on it.
Also didn't know this. I didn't, I had no idea she's been married her entire career.
Yes, however, and this is room of mind growing, but I've long heard she has an active lesbian
side life. And apparently coined the phrase, eat and ate cheating. That's, that is, I have heard
that for multiple sources. That she coined the phrase, eat and ate cheating. That dolly coined the
phrase, eat and ate cheating. Yes. It's a legend. It's a legend, but I've heard it from sources
that I believe it from. All right. Hey, I'll buy it. I'll buy that for a dollar. Yeah.
And by the way, I disagree. I think Eden is cheating. Yeah, except unless you're dolly,
that's what I mean. You can't get mad at this one. She could get away with it. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. And my last one, I'll just go quick with one. I don't really have any thoughts on. I have
always wanted to see Excalibur. It seemed interesting to me. I had heard it was a very,
you know, when I was a kid, my dad was always like, oh, no, that one's, you know, a hard or whatever.
I guess it sort of is. There's a little bit of sex in it, a little bit of sword fighting,
you know, but for me, the movie was very, very boring. It's painfully boring. It didn't really make
sense. And when I looked up like Ebert and other people at the time, all the reviews were like
beautiful. It makes no sense. So I was like, oh, I'm not an idiot. That's good. It was just
incompetently put together. But yeah, it was so uninvolving. The only person trying to give it
some life is the guy who plays Merlin, who's also in the end of exercise three. And his name is
eluding me, Peter Nicholson. Who's he playing that, the priest? The guy who comes in at the end,
yeah, I didn't realize that's the same thing here. Mike, all over it.
Oh, no, it's a painfully boring movie. There's also several different cuts of it.
Yes. So like, you got to find the, you know, proper cut. And I mean, there's, there's so little
anything you'd want out of a movie like that, that movie doesn't have. Like Merlin never does
any fun magic shit or any, you know what I mean? Like it's Merlin is Nicole Williamson. I'm very sorry.
Nicole Williamson. And also the priest at the end of exercise three. But yeah, exactly. There's no
lightning bolts coming out of the fingers. Yeah, no dragons. No.
It's like all the worst parts of Game of Thrones. Exactly. Like I never got into it,
even though I watched every episode of it, it just kind of bored me. But there was enough of the
horrifying violence and TNA and craziness that brought me back every week. And Excalibur just kind of
does all that with none of the fun. Yeah. They make it look miserable. And it's like,
guys, this is knights and shit. Like have some fun with it. All the, all the swords, none of the
incest. Exactly. That's my review. So there we are. Should, I guess we should get to the movie,
right? I mean, we've been having a Lucy Goosey affair. Yeah. We're a little over an hour, Mike,
just let me know. We can even discuss which episode this is and what we're going to do today.
Whatever you start talking about, I will go with. I feel like I would like to do invisible woman
because the other episode or the next episode, we're, we're going to review Becky. Yeah.
The Kevin James Nazi vehicle. And I would like to spend a little more time on Becky than I
feel I need to spend on the invisible woman. This movie was a big hit to remake of the classic
Claude Rames, I believe was his name in the original. But yeah, it was a big hit. And I think
an even bigger hit because it was half on the theatrical side and half on the Now we're all in prison
side. Yeah. I think it was really the movie that rode that wave 50 -50. I saw it like the week before
shutdown happened. Me too. Yeah. Like it was the last thing I saw in the theater. I was very excited to
see it because the reviews were through the roof. And I was hearing such spectacular things. And
what a just piece of shit film. This is what a paper thin nothing to it.
Message on its sleeve just beating you over the head with it the entire time.
Nothing fun. This is a universal classic monster's remake. This thing makes you want to slit your
fucking wrists. There's nothing fun about it. There's nothing enjoyable. It's there's no layers.
It doesn't make sense. It sucks. It's a bad bad bad movie that people were not allowed to say sucked.
Because a powerful Scientologist was at the helm of it. And it was a movie about gender issues.
That's how I feel about it. Counterpoint.
Counter me baby. And Mike is telling us that we meant to say the invisible man. I think you said
the invisible woman. But it is about a woman. For sure. Yeah. Counterpoint. I my least favorite kind
of horror movie is like the joyless no fun slog where everyone's miserable. And I thought this was
the exact opposite. I had a lot of fun with the movie. I enjoyed the hell out of it. I thought it's
attempts at humor were very well timed and not overdone. I thought it had sort of a 90s thriller vibe.
I mean, I saw it as part of a day with misery, fatal attraction,
gone girl. It was up. It was the last time I went to the movies. It was at American
the Egyptian theater up here. That's a good. I am a member. Good day.
But yeah. And the director was there and talked about how these thrillers influenced him. So
obviously, I probably was more inclined to like it than you. But I just had a blast and
seeing it in a theater helped for sure, the audience was very much into it. I really like
Elizabeth Moss in it. Scientologist or not. I like her. I didn't think it was perfect or anything,
but like the the kill for example and spoiler alert in the restaurant scene where she's basically
getting framed and the invisible man cuts the throat of the woman at the table. I'm sorry,
that was a great scare. Everybody screamed. I kind of let out a noise. I never do that. I was very
much into that kill. I thought it was great. I like that it had a low budget feel. You know,
I thought it was going to be like memoirs of a invisible man where the invisible man's always like
smoking a cigarette or jogging wearing leg warmers and a bandana or something. Yeah.
Yeah. However, the effects weren't amazing. You know, it was low budget and you felt it a bit. You
times where they really showed off like that scene in the hallway where everybody's shooting each
other in the kneecaps and all that. I thought was very well done. But it was low budget.
And to me, you know, this is what we always come to odds on these things, Joe. I'm like
how could anyone, especially a fan of horror, not enjoy a right down the middle entertaining horror
picture? I can tell you like the invisible man. I think you'd even want to root for the thing.
I have so many. I went in excited. I have so many boxes to tick right now. So I'm going to try to go
down them quickly. Okay. Let's start with Blumhouse. You know, my feelings about most of the Blumhouse
productions and Blumhouse is a notorious company at this point for being the message
senders. You know, everything now is they're very pleased with themselves, with the messages they're
conveying in their in their in their product. Right. Which is fine. But sometimes that message is
transparent and slowly conveyed. And I felt that this was a version of that or a good example of that.
Movie starts with a bang. First 20 minutes where she's trying to get out of the house and all that.
It's amazingly done. I was like, this is going to be fantastic. And from there, it just stopped
making sense. You never get to, you never get to, first of all, you never get to know the villain.
Ever. He's just a scary and visible man who's a real asshole for some reason. They never explain
it. One of the coolest things about the original invisible man is the, the being invisible, it makes
him go insane. Right. So had they started this film from a place of, I broke up with this guy
because he was a little overbearing and it wasn't for me. And then that personality type devolves
through the movie because he's invisible and going nuts. Now we've got something interesting.
Now we've got a layered character. There's, you might even have a little sympathy for him. They
don't do any of that. This guy is a paper thin villain. He's just a bastard from go. They never
explain why they don't get into any of it. It's, it's, it's, it's, it's just not good. It's just
not a good, it's not good character work. Not to me. To me, that is like, okay, the movie was already
two hours. They're just, they're hitting you clearly. This guy was an abusive boyfriend.
Maybe you have someone in your past like that. Maybe you don't, but you know you hate this guy.
You know he was an asshole because she's escaping in the middle of the night.
If we had seen the before like him hitting her, abusing her, yelling at her, whatever else,
I guess it could have helped you to hate the guy, but I got what I needed with her escaping from
his house. Things were that bad that she had to run out. But that was very economical storytelling
to get a lot of things. Something that's going to piss a lot of people off. You're a billionaire
genius. You can have any woman in the world, any Elizabeth Moss pal. And I don't care. I don't care.
You've got to justify this. She even says it in the movie. They had to write in a line where she
goes, you could have any woman you want. Why me? And even then they dropped the fucking ball
with explaining why she wasn't charismatic. She wasn't brilliant. She wasn't beautiful. She was,
she was none of the above. None of the above. You can't be none of the above. You got to be,
okay, you're not a supermodel, but God would have personality. Or hey, she's brilliant, but
but she's kind of an asshole. Or she's hot, but Christ, I don't know, she's just hot. There's
got to be some guys like this like the control. Maybe he liked someone who was not a supermodel because
he could control her. But then fine, fine. But then explain that. That's my point. When every
opportunity they had to explain why he might be obsessed with her and why he wants to control
this woman and why this is they go out of their way to say the only woman he's ever done this with.
You have to explain it guys. You can't just say, well, just because because you like to be the one
to tell Elizabeth Moss, now that we've cast you, we're going to add in some explanation as to why anyone
would be with you. It would be a poorly written script. Yeah, it would be poorly written script with
and I don't, here's the thing too, for anybody that's angered by my statements about Elizabeth
fuck Elizabeth Moss, okay? Fuck her. I'm tired of her being the fucking champion of women's rights
as she is a level 17 fucking Scientologist, okay? She's part of a church that abuses people,
particularly women and children. They have fucking probably murdered people, particularly women,
okay? If you watch the documentary, I'm tired of everybody going, oh, Elizabeth Moss, man,
she's really out there doing it for the gals. No, she's not. Well, I'm with you, Joe, about
Scientology, but why no fuck Tom Cruise? Because Tom Cruise doesn't make movies going, hey, guys,
I'm out here. He's hanging off of airplanes and he shuts the fuck up. That's fine. All right,
I said fuck Tom Cruise when he started going on talk shows and talking about it and I was like,
nobody wants to hear this shit shut up. Yeah, apparently he had a Scientology signup set tent on the set
of War of the Worlds. He insisted on his comment. That's when he did it. That was when he started
going a little baddie in public, whatever. But it's like if Elizabeth Moss was making fun popcorn action,
movies, I want to get every single thing she does. Handles tell this, that new movie she's in
Shelley, whatever it's called, every single thing she does, it's like this is a project about women
and the struggle. And she's she is a it's a hypocritical. It's gross. She's a gross person. She's a
her madman character was also very much, you know, about the struggle for women's rights and
equality as well for sure. She was very symbolic. She works it into her every acceptance speech.
She's a she's a gross human being to me. Um, I guess you I will say she's grown on me quite I
like I loved her on madman and I've seen her in a lot of different types of roles now and I do think
she's a good actress in my opinion, which I think I do all I really bring to it. I think anyone
acting in Hollywood is probably on some level of scumbag. I think though I do think she's a good
actress. I do think she's a good actress. I do. I say actor because I don't feel the need to
differentiate. But now she's a very she's a good white actress. It's that better job. I think she
is a good actress. I really do. I'm not saying she's not. I think she's good in this movie. Right.
I'm just I'm digressing a bit on my point of this thing hits you so across the face with this message.
And I think it's a very good message and I think it's a message that should be brought into films
and they could have done it properly. And I don't feel that they did. Now let's take all of that aside.
Let's put all that aside. The movie from a logical standpoint sucks. For instance, there are multiple
scenes where even though he's invisible, he suddenly is somehow like a kung fu fighting expert.
He's he's beating. He's like John Claude Van Daming 18 cops with guns. It's like guys,
just because you're invisible doesn't mean you know how to fight. So maybe put a detail in
that he did jujitsu something or that the suit gives you some sort of height and power perhaps.
Maybe that exactly. So that there's that because if you're going to build a suit that makes you invisible,
why would you not also add some other cool tricks to it? The the director. Okay. And in order to
justify this, to justify a man being able to beat the shit out of several armed men,
even being invisible, you'd get an idea and you'd be able to shoot him at some point. The way they
justify this is they have the cops doing things that cops would never do. They're literally
entering rooms with their firearms drawn and their firearms are at their side. So when they walk in
the room and they get hit, they're not ready to fire. And it's like, that's just bad directing.
A cop would come into the room, gun, fucking, you, we've all seen it two hands on the piece.
What the fuck? You're you're coming in around the court. You got cops like jogging into the room,
gun, just waving inside. They kind of security guys. They hit guns. They did have guns.
Yes, it's guns. They all had guns. So there's that. There's the pointless twist of it was the brother
in the suit at times and that it was, oh my god. Yeah, that to me was was one twist too many.
I'll bring you that. And then the science of the suit made no sense. It's covered in cameras,
so it's invisible. Okay. But you couldn't see through it if that was the case. Right. You would,
it would just look like whatever it was standing in front of you couldn't see what was behind it.
That's not how that would work. The ins and outs of the suits was a little confusing.
And I think they're going to make a sequel. So maybe we'll learn more about it. But also,
oh, sorry, go ahead. No, go ahead. Also, again, back to the poorly conveyed message. Okay.
He's nuts. And he's invisible. And he's terrorizing me. Oh, you're just crazy. They so badly wanted
to hammer home this idea of the woman not being believed, which is a thing. Yeah, obviously. Right.
That they took away the logic that the characters would have. My boyfriend, who was an optics expert
who was on the verge of discovering invisibility. I'm telling you now is invisible and fucking with
everybody goes, you're out of your fucking mind. What are you talking about? It would literally be like
if you were like, I dated Jeff Bezos and now he's fucking with my money in my bank accounts.
It'd be like, you get the hell out of it. What the hell are you talking about? It's like, well,
no, because people have been stealing from bank accounts for centuries and nobody has cracked
invisibility yet. So it's a little different. Here's a better, it wasn't a great example. I was just,
here's a better example. I dated Jeff Bezos. And now every time I get something in the mail from
Amazon, it's broken. He's fucking with me. You're out of your mind. It's like, guys, you,
you know who this guy is. You have an idea of this person. It's so fucking crazy that nobody,
not even they don't believe her, they get angry at her. Yes. And it's a, and again, it's a sloppy,
sloppy execution of a message. It's just not thought out. There's no nuance to it. There's
no wit to any of it. It's just point A to point B black and white paper thin. Nothing makes,
there's no logic here. There's no reasoning. There's no rationale. It's just, hey, this is what it is.
And you're supposed to go, oh, yeah, because that's how it is. No, right? A fucking script, man.
I think, and this is the guy who did upgrade, which I also liked with reservations. I think this is
a guy who makes very good B movies. I think this is a B movie and looked at like that. I had a good
time with it. Like if you pick up a horror movie that came out in 1985, you might, you know, you
might be like, okay, I'm not going to come at this like it has to be a masterpiece. And to me,
invisible man was no masterpiece, but a very good B level horror movie. And I think that is what
that dude makes. I don't know that he's, I think he makes well made movies with cool little action
scenes and kind of fun twists. It seems might have been a little explicit, but this is the horror
audience. You know, like horror movies tend to not be super subtle about what their masterpiece.
I 100 % agree with you, but when it's coming from Blumhouse and Elizabeth Maus and they're coming
at it going, we are saying something. And it's like, yeah, well, you're saying it in a bad movie.
I don't know what the fuck can tell you. It becomes that Ghostbusters reboot thing where it's like,
guys, I'm sorry, I was there on opening night. I was excited. I wanted to like it. It was a bad
movie. What do you want from me? It like don't wear it so much when you sleeve, man. Like, you know,
like, and I think I just disagree. I think Ghostbusters was a below average comedy and this is an
above average horror movie. And it's, I do think they could have made a much more interesting movie
with the same elements about women and what's going on and the invisible man. And almost the exact
same basic setup. They could have done a lot more. I'll grant you then they could have made a much
more interesting movie, a much deeper movie, but they didn't. I'm not going to hold it against it. I
saw black Christmas, which tried to do the same thing. The remake, you know, tried to be a very
feminist slant on black Christmas. And again, I guarantee if you watch that on a double bill with
invisible man, invisible man would look a lot better in your eye. Sure. I thought it was a very
well done B movie. My one thing. Did you, did you like the part where the wavy, almost sickly looking
brother was able to beat the living shit out of the 250 pound adonis mussely ripped black man?
Did that make sense? I mean, again, I guess, I guess I just looked at the suit as giving a bit of
superpowers. Maybe that's the glut of super super super how here are movies that come out every year.
But yeah, I could have been explained. I'm right. And then he said, and then he had my favorite
part at the end. How she in five minutes after walking with a dinner table figures out how to master
the way the suit works. You know that to then kill him and then walks out with it in a paper bag
as the cops are coming in. And nobody goes, Hey, what's in that bag? What's going on over?
One of the Catholic side, of course, also, that guy was like her friend, that character, by the way,
and we have not mentioned him yet, Aldo's Hodge, who was a very good actor of super jacks, dude,
for god's sake. Yes. But of course, yes, him. So when, when Moss first shows up at his place after
she escapes, it's this guy, this black guy living alone with a mixed race daughter. And biracial,
excuse me. Is she direct? Do you do, do you know for a fact she's by racial?
I don't, but I certainly saw it that way. So when she walks up, and of course, when a movie starts,
you're trying to make connections. And who are these people and what's their relation to each other?
You know, not every movie starts with narration that brings you up the day. Right. Right.
So Moss goes up and knocks on the door. And I'm like, ah, this is her ex -husband. And this is their
daughter. Right. I'm watching it. And then something in the dialogue, and I saw this movie four
months ago, but something in the dialogue makes me go, oh, okay, there, it's not her ex. And I'm watching.
And then I get to the point where he goes, he literally goes, because I thought that too. And he
literally goes, I mean, come on, would I your best friend do that? It was literally that sloppy.
You're not wrong. So then I turned to the guy I saw it with my buddy, and he goes,
as I turned to him, he is turning to me to ask what is his relationship to her. And we both had to
like bury our faces because I was laughing. And then finally, I'm like, what's going on? So because
if you'll remember, Elizabeth Moss's sister is also involved. She's in the next. So then I'm like,
okay, this is her ex -husband. And this is Elizabeth Moss's niece. So that's why she's choosing to stay
there. Then I'm like, because they're staying with this guy because he's going to protect her,
obviously, or to go. So then the sister leaves. And the sister seems to have a little bit of tension
with all this. So I'm like, oh, yeah, definitely, they had a marriage gone bad. But that's also not
true. So neither one of us, two 40 -year -old men watching this movie have any idea what the relationship
is. And by the way, I still didn't when the movie ended. I checked Wikipedia and it said that this
guy was her childhood friend. Elizabeth Moss's childhood friend. I guess I missed that in the movie.
But that is an insane way of bringing in diversity into your movie. It wasn't even
clear what their relationship was. It was really nuts. It couldn't have been more sloppily handled.
I was so confused. And you can't be desperately confused about two main characters' relationship. Pat,
it's a bad movie. It just has some cool sequences with invisibility. That's it. But if you take that
away, it sucks. Now, here's the. I just disagree. But I see your problems and I add my problems.
And I realize it's a movie with problems, but I had a good time watching it. All right, fair enough.
Yeah. I guess my thing is is, and I thought that throat cut in the restaurant is one of the best
horror kills in probably 10 years. That was a great kill. That was a great. I loved it. And to
hear it, it's honestly, I remember it well because I may never hear it again. To hear 500 people
at the Egyptian theater, all gasp and yell at the same time was awesome. And horror movies so
rarely deliver one competent scare that like that one being that good automatically elevates it.
And I wasn't bored for the remaining two hours. I have you and I you and I differ with this because you
you say that it's not a criticism, it's just where we differ. You say the same thing with comedy.
You'll say if there's, if there's, hey, if there's 10 laugh moments, then to me, it's passable and
whatever. Yes, I go the other direction. I say, I want a more complete experience. But so yeah,
I mean, from a special effect standpoint, I thought it was impressive. I thought it had some very
cool moments. And I thought I had some very well done sequences. But overall, I just thought it was
a very, very poorly, I mean, just in your, the things you're saying right now, I'm like,
oh, this is like what a good writer would have done with this. Like, oh, wouldn't that have been
interesting if this guy was her ex -husband who was kind of played like a cuck -roll in her life.
And then she comes back. And he's like, such a good guy that he's letting her back into his life.
And maybe she wasn't great to him. And then she starts saying, this guy's doing this to me. And then
about this guy, I'm tired. My God almighty. She's just like, he's hair about anybody.
Right. If she's complaining to him and he's her ex -husband, all this
hard. And she's saying, look, you're right. He was raw. I shouldn't have left you for him,
et cetera, et cetera. But then he's not believing her because he has animosity towards her.
She divorced him and left the daughter and everything else. So then if he has animosity towards her,
he's much less inclined to believe her and has a reason to not believe her when she's saying that he
is trying to put on the suit and kill her. So he's like, you know, any guy thinks his ex -wife
is crazy more than likely. So he's probably like, oh, you know, it's just you being crazy again,
whatever you'd buy it. They have a relationship. Instead, I got a note pad out and a pen and a light
in the dark. And I'm drawing charts and graphs trying to figure out how these two met.
So I'll, excuse me, I'll revamp my, I'm wearing a miner's helmet and the dark with the flashlight
in the center. Oh, I'll reword my review of this. I think this is a movie that could have been good
with a few very small, simple fixes. That's, that's my takeaway. A lot of it was done correctly.
Some of it was done very well. And I think it could have been good with, with some very,
very easy fixes. Some very, have him beat up two guards with guns instead of eight.
Have the black guy not be a hulking adonis. So when he beats him up, I'm not like, give me a
fucking break, man. Explain the relationship between them. You know, you shed a little more light on
the boyfriend and why he's this way. Develop Elizabeth Mothra a little more. So I understand why
he's so obsessed with her. Just, these are simple, simple, think their dialogue fixes really.
You know what I mean? Line here, line there. No, sure. It almost seems like it might have been rushed
or something. I don't know. And then Universal, who knows what they're doing with their horror? I
recently read that they gave Elizabeth Banks, they brought in Elizabeth Banks and they said,
you can have the rights to whichever universal monster you want to make a movie about it. And it's
like, look, cool, great. I'm all for it. Why Elizabeth Banks? Why, what in her history makes you think?
She, I think she did it. One of the pitch perfect movies. You know, she's okay. She's starting out
her directing career. And I know that's a good thing. That's how you wanted to helm a frank and
stined. But yeah, I mean, and less their thinking is we've tried these Universal movies so many times
and they've never worked. Let's try something off the wall, which honestly, good on them.
We'll see what she does. I hope she proves my skepticism wrong, but I've just never associated her
with horror in any way. Anyway, for me, this was a B movie that looked like an A. But at the end of the day,
still a B. I like to miss a lot more than Joe, but it's certainly got his problems.
She did pitch perfect two and Charlie's Angels, the new one.
Give her the wolf man. Let's see what happens. It's the Christopher Guest thing. Give Christopher
Guest. No, don't, don't do it. Don't give him a move. Don't, don't go. Yeah. There are, look,
I'm shopping or shopping. We're, you know, developing, I don't know what the term is, but we're trying
to get a movie made, whatever that term is. I've watched countless, countless short films and
movies and whatever by female, predominantly female directors, because the movie that I wrote is
there is some, what, of a gender commentary to it. We thought it could be great if we could find
a female horror director for this. That would be fucking awesome. They all passed.
Every one of them passed. But seriously, they're so talented. I saw the work.
There's somebody that deserves it more than who is also female who deserves it more than Elizabeth
Banks, who also is so so old and knows how to shoot this kind of thing. So it was funny. I got my
first real glimpse into that whole thing. Like when you hear the complaints about sexism in Hollywood
and why aren't more female directors getting a shot. Like when you actually have to send a script
out to a wide birth of people to see if anybody bites the hook, that was the first time I really
understood, like, oh my god, there are so many female directors out here. And this is just in one
genre. This was all horror. These were all aspiring horror directors or they had directed one or
two things. And we talked to male directors as well and blah, blah, blah, blah. I mean, Mary Lambert is
one of the strangest stories of all time. She does pet cemetery, which is a still beloved horror movie,
a smash hit, and is really never heard from again. I think she did the sequel and she was out.
And anyone else would have been given a decade -long career out of that easy.
It is weird. So yes, the question is, it's why is it why is it bad? I mean, I couldn't agree more.
I'm a fan of Elizabeth Banks. We're saying the same thing. Give her season two of perfect harmony.
That's her wheelhouse. It's about a choir. Look, I didn't see Charlie's Angels. I mean,
it's very possible. They were like, this didn't work, but she's clearly a great director of action.
Maybe there's good. I have no idea. Maybe she. Anyway, all right. We got to wrap this up.
Yeah, this was a thick episode. There was a lot in this thing. I'm very proud of it.
Put it in the time capsule. What do we got folks? My social media shut down these days.
I'll probably have to reboot it up again to promote podcasts and things like that. But in the meantime,
I will plug without a country. Corinne Fisher and I discussing the news, trying to find some
middle ground amidst all the polarizing tribalistic news that's out there. It's on the gas digital
network. You can use code WAC, get a free 30 -day trial. And we live stream from gas every Tuesday
night at 7 p .m. And then on Saturdays, that show drops to the public. And you can get it on iTunes,
wherever you get your things. We got a YouTube channel. Subscribe to that as well.
And my buddy, Sal Volcano and I have a little something in the works coming soon. So I'll be
announcing that soon, but it'll be another podcast. I believe Sal mentioned it on Twitter.
Yes, we are doing a podcast. If you saw the polls that he was putting up the other day,
it's food -related. That's all I'm going to say for right now. But it's very fun. It's very fun.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram. We are on CU and HellPod on Instagram.
And still, six months into this, I'm hearing from people, I just found out you guys are on Patreon.
So if you're on Facebook or whatever, let these people know. I can't believe people didn't know.
But thank you to all of you for spreading the word. The Patreon has not only been a success,
but it's growing. And it enables us to now, I think we can announce Joe.
Oh, yeah. Which to a four episode a month model.
Yes, there's a second tier now. This August is the first month we did it.
You still eat your two episodes for seven bucks. If you want two more,
bringing it up to a total of four for the month, there's a $12 tier now.
Now, $12 tier now. Christ, that's hard to say. If you're interested,
if you're not, it's okay. If you're not interested in the $7 tier, it's okay. We appreciate
those of you that are interested at all in the show period. So absolutely.
And enjoy the archives. You know, the previous hundred or so episodes, which remain free.
But like everybody else, you know, this is a gig economy. A lot of people aren't working. We are
amongst those people. And we thought, why not? We've got the time. So for $5 more, it's two more apps.
Thank you. And enjoy if you want to. No pressure. Thank you. And enjoy if you don't want to.
And it is. I like the way you're saying it now. When we were all fair and you said,
I want green out of these swine. I should have that. I don't think you should say it that way.
Yeah. These fuckers going to bleed green. I said,
tearing my throat open for some reason when I just. Yeah. Oh, and also too.
So what'll happen is is the first two episodes will drop on the first of every month,
as usual, unless we, you know, that will always happen unless we hit some kind of technical difficulty
or something. But that's the release date for the first two episodes. And then the second two
episodes will probably drop mid month. Or maybe a little earlier, that'll just depend on when we're
able to record them. But the goal here is August, you know, the first and 15th of each month,
you're getting your episodes. The goal and, you know, be gentle if we're a day or two late.
But that's it. And I am still keeping up the free monthly movie corners, which are always
about an hour bonus episode and those go for anybody who subscribes at any level to the Patreon.
Yeah. So yeah, and I also intend on trying to chip in and some I'm very podcast focused these
days are kind of taking a break from stand up indefinitely. I don't know when I'm going to do it again,
but now that I am so focused on podcasting, I hope to get some bonus content up as well.
Joe's got one up now. It's very funny. I hope for more as a fan myself. You know,
thank you. You're welcome, Joe. We will see you next time when we are doing the Kevin James Nazi picture
Becky. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.