Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Welcome to another steamy hot episode of, we'll see you in hell, I'm just chucklings
Pat read a, you probably won't hear it before this, they'll probably pop up somewhere
We're in the middle of the episode jarringly.
But there's the, we, Pat's read of the quip ad
made me laugh today.
It's your podcast that you turned to
for the, for the shakes and the quakes
and the what's happening and all the horror and sci -fi
and fantasy film stuff going on out there in the world.
My name's Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
Joe, how have you been?
I know how you've been.
We've been talking.
It's not good.
I know.
It's been a real ball break or week out here in La La land.
It's just been a lot of rejections this week on all fronts.
It's not a great week.
Had to really convince myself not to open a bottle of wine
in quarter to three p .m. today.
I didn't do it.
I fought it.
Yeah.
But it's one of those weeks.
where you're just like, oh, for Christ's sakes, who cares?
But other than that, I think I have my health,
I don't know, I have a physical on Tuesday.
Okay.
Or actually, God, by the time this comes out,
I've already had the physical.
So you could know that you're dying
while this episode is.
Yeah, yeah, so let's hope that I don't just,
it's not bad news and I don't replay this episode
over and over as I weep myself to sleep.
yeah of a simpler time when I was healthy but you know other than that I guess
everything's pretty good you know good almost never reading the news at all
anymore not you know not looking at twitch that's helps a lot I'm sure and I go on
these very long walks every morning about two miles that's great for your
well -being well important they I asked my doctor friend and he goes well you're
not really getting the heart rate up, but it's something, I guess, and it's like, I usually
recommend for like a senior citizen to do it two mile walk, but, you know, I'm happy
for it. It's a nice, I also do the elliptical, but I do, not every day, but I do the walk
every day. It's a great way to collect your thoughts and get some writing done. It is, you
know, whatever, answer some emails. It's just a nice to people watch it out in the world,
you know, sometimes I'll do them twice a day.
I'm on, you know, day nine of no solid food.
I did my cleanse deal and this is the last day of like,
OJ and stuff and then I'm back in the swing.
Joseph and I are heading to Vegas this weekend.
We do these podcasts a week behind sometimes.
And I hope when you're hearing this, I hope you came out to see Joe
at the South Point Casino opening from Bobby Slayton where I will be as well on Friday night.
The the rare reverse plug which is always helpful for getting getting asses in the seats.
Yeah, three listeners just went, I live right down the street from South Point.
Right. But yeah, we're good. And you know, I was engaging with people a lot in the Facebook page.
we don't know how to get you in.
I think you'd have to create your own Facebook profile,
which I don't recommend doing, frankly.
It's not worth it.
I'm not gonna do it.
There's a reason I got rid of one many years ago.
It's, I liked the distance of a fan page only on there.
I found Facebook quite intrusive after a while.
And it's the reason I left Twitter, it's infinitely better.
I have a pride when I say to people,
oh yeah, I don't really go on there.
You know, using your lead, I get on once a day
out to see what the news stories are and then I'm kind of like the state of the union
shit. I was like, you don't care Pat, be honest with yourself. Yeah. You know the state
of the union is broken, right? It's a shit. So why are you reading it? And I'm happier
too. I haven't been looking at it. And you could also get a more at least a slightly more
legitimized version of that news by just swiping right on your phone. That's correct. You have
a news widget. That's correct. So that's all I do. And I see what the big stuff is that's
happening. I read, I read, you know, I read it until I get furious, which is about, which
is any news story now. I'm not just picking on Trump. I'm picking on all of it. I just
any news story now. I can read about five sentences before I'm furious. I agree. So, uh, and
Since the departure from Joni loves Chaachi sure to pursue Charles in charge. Sure. I am
Convince that is what led to the demise of
actress
Nicole Eggert. No, Joni the darling Joni. Yeah, what was what was that lady's name?
I've never seen Joni love Chaachi. Well, she put Joni on happy. She just died
It was never really happy saddest fucking stories. I've ever read it was like yeah, like she
I love everybody's not in Hollywood.
It's like, we don't get it.
We don't understand what happened.
She went to, she wasn't getting work
and then she moved to a trailer park
and was like, went crazy.
And it's like, yeah, that's what this town does to people.
Right, you're not understanding?
You're Joni on the show, Joni loves Chachi.
Everyone loves you.
Then, no one will return your calls.
Yeah.
Then you're nothing overnight,
just as quickly as you became a star.
And then your life falls apart.
What don't you understand?
It happens to everyone who pursues a career
in the entertainment industry.
And then, you know, the residual money gets less and less.
Right.
After a while, you can't live on it.
I mean, remember the thing with Alf, the dad,
with Willie from Alf and like the crack house,
like having three ways with those,
those, the male prostitutes?
I thought I told you that, maybe on this show,
but I know everything there is to know
about Max Wright, the dad from Alf.
And I believe you did tell me and then I looked it up
And I was like, come on, man, he's not in a crack house.
And it's like, no, there he is in a crack house.
He was a married man and then one day snapped.
And I've known a lot of people who have worked with Norm Mcdonald.
I hope to someday do my dream show.
Norm Mcdonald has a farm, which is fully fleshed out
and ready to go, right?
But Norm Mcdonald and already lying
have all these amazing stories about him
because he worked on the norm show, right,
with those two.
And he apparently hated Alf so much that one day he snapped and beat the shit out of the puppet and was like they were like Matt
I could thought it was like a joke and he just was he couldn't pull him off of the puppet right but they said the set was like
really hot
That to shoot a half hour show they didn't do it with an audience at all Alf because of the comp the complications of the puppetry
Why was this set so hot it would be like a 20 -hour hot day?
I don't know but it's always described as hot. It snapped and they said when they shot the last shot of
the finale of Alf
He said his last line. They were like we got it and they had a little of course cast and crew party plan that he walked
Directly off stage got in his car and drove away. He said nothing to anyone. Holy shit. I know a lot about Max right
It's a dark tail holy shit now out. There's a show surprisingly
never
syndicated anywhere. I never catch reruns of alf ever. Not that I want to. I didn't I wasn't crazy about it when I was a kid either
But it was well, it was a hundred percent my favorite show on television
age, you know
five to ten or whatever it aired. I did it first and then I started to just kind of
Yeah, not give a shit anymore.
I thought Alph was really funny and I had an Alph doll that caught fire on my reading lamp
when I was a boy.
The one from Burger King that says like rock and roll.
He was like wearing the raw picture.
Wow, it was nearly a full -size Alph, it was a huge Alph doll.
Now would you have sex with a doll?
This was a little too early for me but if I had gotten it when I was 11 I definitely would
have been humping Alph until I came.
but, you know what, I like my ladies Bohemian, you know what, I'm about to reveal way too much,
but it wasn't too early because I just remembered, I see this is going to be talked about at length
in the Facebook page, I was just praising, and that's fine, but I did use to place my child erect penis
Yes, into the mouth of my alfdol, which was an open mouth, but velvety had a velvety tongue.
And into the mouth of my rulf from the muppets puppet, and move it around.
But never to ejaculation, because I was, I was going to jokingly answer and then I thought,
no, Pat, you got to be truthful here.
You did fuck that alfdol.
I'm not sure it's legal.
I'm not sure it doesn't count as beastieality.
both of those.
They're an animate.
But they're in animals.
They were fake.
Ralph was a scratchy surface within his mouth and very unpleasant.
Yes, he had it on the night you wanted it rough, but alchetta had a velvety tongue and
this was before I knew how to manipulate myself to orgasm, I would just kind of move it around.
The only worse version of the story is if it was Max right in a crack house
mouth -fucking at the alf doll. Yeah, that's the only worse version of the story. Well Max right got a
Throne off the norm show briefly already lying told the show on a stern told the story on stern
Because he was driving in to work one day on the norm show
drove directly into the back of a cop car
The cop gets out star talking to him and realizes that he's drunk on champagne to like go
So go in for like a 10 a .m. start time, which I'll and champagne is a great little detail
of the story.
That's why I'm laughing.
Yeah.
That's really funny.
A guy getting out just having a few bubblies.
First thing.
Right.
I mean, look, that's what everyone in Los Feliz does when they go to fucking brunch.
Is he?
It's not that crazy.
Is he cares?
No, wait, how did the cop know it was champagne?
Does he have the bottle in the car with him?
I don't know how that came out unless Max told them.
But I think there was a champagne bottle in the car. I could text my buddy Nate who also heard the story first
No, it could also be McDonald has embellished at some point who knows
But um maybe anyway before I forget I'd love to go ahead and get on
With the show mm -hmm and at the same time mm -hmm on
With a Joe
Pretty woman
I got to think of these like gun to my head that's very good. I I'm almost out. I mean I'm gonna have to start doing some research. I
Luckily somebody requested Jo Jo Jo. It's magic last week and that helped me out of a jam, but I get I get a slight panic every time you launch into it. I do too because I'm like I wouldn't
remember to prepare this? No, I don't. Well, there you go. But yeah, what I just wanted to say,
I spent a lot of time engaging with people in the Facebook page because I noticed a lot of people
were spiraling like doing exactly what I would have done back in the day. Like, oh, no, was it my
comment that pissed Pat and Joe off? Because I was talking about how they were all like being critical in
that. I didn't, nobody pissed me off. I didn't say that. I know because you're not in there. That's why
Well, if you don't go into these sites, you don't get pissed on them, but I explained to them that it is sometimes the show, but I'm like,
you know, usually you can say whatever you want about the podcast, you know, and I don't take it very seriously, but
there had been some people being like this shit that who wants to watch a fucking show about the Bible, etc.
And it was bothering me because I try to avoid anything about it, since it hasn't even aired yet, and
And I'm too fragile, but going in there and seeing it, I got pissed.
So I explained that that's what it was in a very long rant.
Somebody actually accused me of being on cocaine when I did the rant.
But I was just like, like, come on guys, like, you know, this is my, my other project.
And everybody was like, whoa, no, we're all very excited about the show, blah, blah, blah.
And it was a beautiful discussion.
We have a, we have the best fans in the world, especially in terms of podcasts.
They're wonderful.
Just delightful people.
And we're at like 800 fans.
Also before I forget a lot of business to clear up in this one
The merch store is up. Oh, yeah shit. I was forgot. Thank you. Emily Florence put it up yesterday
It's it's the descriptions of the items are funny like the site is great
And I love Emily I was telling this to our dear friend Vince Averall Pat and my dear friend Vince Averall last night. Yes, I
uh, I told him the legacy of the hog house bit on the pod, how much pat didn't like it, and I
love Emily that you called the merch store the hog house. Uh, I didn't tell you to do that.
I didn't tell her to do that. That was on her own. Uh, the fans have spoken. Well, let me give you
the address real quick, because I do not know it off hand.
But it is on Etsy, I know that much
and it is called the Hoghouse Shop.
And I assume that's all you do, right?
You search the Hoghouse Shop.
Yeah, and you buy stuff.
Yeah, search for items or shop.
The Hoghouse Shop will see you in hell.
You'll see it.
If you have comments, questions, concerns about the merch,
see you in hell, merch at gmail .com.
It's all we got.
They got beautiful stuff.
Stickers, these posters that Jeremy Benison and others did.
Yes.
It's a beautiful thing and there's only more to come.
So, please enjoy.
I think only the Benison posters are there now.
Yes.
I think some other stuff is potentially coming from other artists.
And I think we're hoping to get t -shirts in there soon.
So, hey, we're excited.
You guys are all awesome.
But also I'm going to start looking at our head gum demographics, like how many downloads
we're getting where, so we can start figuring out where we can go to do a live show that
enough people would come to that it would be worth going out there.
Why are we not?
There's been several requests for LA.
I guess if our podcast company ever did anything like that for us that we could do it through
them, but I'm not sure they know that we're actually on the head gum network.
But yeah, we'd love to do one.
Just once get invited to one of the, not even invited.
I'd love to sit in the audience for a while.
Just notified that there's yet another head gum live event happening.
They've never even told me that it's happening.
No, I think we're sort of the black sheep of the head gum family.
Well, look, we can easily do one in LA.
That goes without speaking.
I'd like to see, though, in what other cities we could actually pull out a nice, you know,
a nice size audience, meaning like, guys, we can get 50 people out to a show and find
the right venue, we can figure out a way to make this work, you know?
So we're doing a different festival, somebody was mentioning in Colorado this October, a different
one from the one you and I did, what seems now like 12 years ago, but that festival has
is ended and this is a new one, we do that.
If you got a horror festival in your town, throw us up.
We'd love to do it.
Yeah, anybody, especially in the next six months
because I am not really working until the show premieres.
That's totally legit.
If anybody has any connections whatsoever
to a horror festivals of any kind, fantasy festivals
of any kind, video game festivals of any kind,
anything that this would sort of fit into,
Pat and I are very game to come out and do those things.
We don't have agents that specialize in those types of appearances, so I don't know anybody.
It was easier with Fangoria because we could go through Fangoria.
But I'm sort of out of touch these days with anybody with their hands and those pies.
time. Joe, I'd love to take you down to the Paradise City. But first, I would like to take
you to Pat's movie corner. I thought they were the same place. You know, they might be
one of the same. I've barely seen anything. I don't know. I've been watching Frazier
incessantly and it's taking up almost all my worries when I came into it. I'm almost to the
end again, but it's taking up all of my free watching TV time.
That's I understand, but and I will say a lot of people are like lean into
Frazier. Let that be the new perfect strangers. PS I love you. I'm ready to I'm
ready. So maybe that'll be my contribution today to the movie quarter.
Okay. Can we call this segment Cran shots after my beloved joke? Yes. Yes. I
Joe the other night I was gonna come over here or vent or something and then Joe was like I'm turning in a little early tonight
I pictured you with a a night cap on your head one of those like three stooges once with the ball
Yeah
And a cup of sleepy time tea
So I was like you know what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna go see fan of the thread again in 70 millimeter
I they so rarely do that around here. It's very nice
I
I go, the show was sold out, which is crazy for a movie that's been out that long.
But, so I'm looking around, I'm looking through my movie pass, and we should talk about
movie pass by the way, because I think that the theater world at large is realizing that
they're about to get royally fucked.
AMC's starting to pull out, they're like, wait a minute, apparently everybody's doing movie
pass, and the company is a sham.
You cannot get help from movie pass when you call their helpline.
Well, and you know what man? I don't feel sorry one bit for these theaters
I love the cinema. I love going to see movies
But these fucking people have gleefully this industry is gleefully ripped off the public
Yeah, since I can since I was born 1775 is the current cost of a movie in LA
Yeah, and it's like beep you should be fucking ashamed of yourselves and and and don't give me the bullshit that we need to over charge
Because there's so much overhead and whatever. This is all the bullshit in Hollywood
Anyway, let me start it.
Any movie pass was asking AMC, so movie pass slides in here.
Their whole thing is a sham, like Heather signed up for it
and didn't get her pass for like six months.
Right, they have no support.
No one works there, apparently.
And yet, they're slowly taking over the movie industry
and they went over to AMC, like they're the fucking mob.
And they were like, you know what?
We've sent so many people to your movie theaters
that weren't there before that now we're gonna go ahead
and take 30 % of your concessions.
Good.
And AMC goes, they released a statement
that was like way more strongly worded
than your average PR statement.
Right.
And it was like, I wanna be real clear here.
MoviePass will never receive dollar one
of AMC's concessions or whatever.
And they just start, like, it's becoming a battle.
Very well.
And it's shaking the industry to its core.
But they let all these people do these one -year memberships.
So if MoviePass goes under, which I don't think it will,
then all these people are gonna riot
Because they put they paid the money for the year membership and then they can't use it
I think we're heading for a big problem frankly. Well lawsuits. I like big problems
I like chaos
You did it to yourself everybody. Yeah movie industry thrived and worked beautifully for a hundred years
And then these little this little offshoot rinky dink company that I did this for ages and nobody knew what movie pass was
They've toppled it in the span of about a year and it's amazing makes me smile
I know.
It does.
Now, wait.
What did you see?
Here's what I did.
Man, I go on some fucking tangents on these shows.
It's all right.
So, I look at the Egyptian theater
where you and I saw that crazy Nicholas Cage movie
that one time.
That was you in Vince, but you and I saw
the Ford Fairlane screen there,
with the Q &A with Dish afterwards.
Yeah.
So, I go up, I'm looking through the thing.
I'm like, what movies are playing
like in the next 5, 10 minutes?
and I see nine to five.
Oh wow.
Which I know is one of your favorite comedies.
All time.
And a movie that I realized,
I had only maybe seen half of when I was a kid.
I'd never seen the whole thing.
So I'm like, oh shit.
I go over to the theater.
They show an amazing print of nine to five.
The audience is cheering, laughing.
Yeah, it's a great movie.
And I realize it was kind of a me too event.
It was a women's lib kind of event.
And that movie, that movie made such a feminist statement
and at the time where it was not like hip to do that.
Like it was, it was, it's a really great ground breaking move.
I love it.
I love that I don't know how Dolly Parton did when the Oscar she's so fucking funny in
it.
And Tom Lennon is fucking great.
You know, Tom Lennon almost walked.
No, I did.
Uh, I just watched, you know, Tom Lennon, uh, uh, what's her name?
Jane Fonda got interviewed, you know, they're, they're plugging the new season at Grace
and Frankie. Yeah. And they brought up nine to five. I think Fallon brought up nine to five. And
and he's like, is it true, Lily, that you almost didn't do it? She's like, yeah, I was signed on.
I almost walked. Yeah. What for? She goes, he goes, why? And he goes, well, we didn't have
Dolly yet. And Jane's comedic skills at that time were questionable. Suspest. Yeah. And she's like,
and Jane was like, and Jane Fonda jumps in and she's like, and you didn't want to have to carry
the whole movie. And she's like, yeah, exactly. I didn't want that responsibility. But it all worked out.
Yeah. Because apparently Jane Fonda like produced it and like, yeah, it was her baby kind of.
I didn't know that. Well, I learned a ton. Because so what I will say is that the first act of
nine to five is perfect. The first act where you're like setting up the office and
david Coleman is so good in it. And they're all so funny in it. Everything is perfect. And I was
just loving it.
But I personally, and I might have liked it more as a kid,
I hated the fantasy sequences.
They're real lame,
where they're all fantasizing about killing him.
I don't like the,
I don't like the Snow White one.
It's a little too goofy.
Yeah.
I kind of like the Jane Fonda one.
Wait, what's the Fonda one?
That's the one where like the mob is chasing him, right?
Yeah, the angry mob.
At least that one's quick.
Then Dolly Parton rides a horse to the office.
And then she's just a cowl lady in the office.
I was like, it was stupid and I thought it derailed the movie.
And you felt the audience get restless
because the audience for movie in 1980 was going nuts
and then you felt the energy kind of drain.
Well, it is the scene where they're smoking weed
and it's supposed to be like,
they're laughing at ridiculous shit.
But then the movie definitely gets back on track.
It was very funny, I loved it.
And then I'm getting ready to leave.
I just thought I was a screening of nine to five.
Outcomes this late, who's 65, very not Hollywood,
like a big old Paramaham jeans and like a, you know,
almost like a Mumu type shirt comes out.
And she's the writer of nine to five.
Oh, wow.
And it was so cool.
And then I've been reading this letterman biography.
I'm loving this letterman biography.
It's fantastic.
The new one that just came out called Letterman.
And one of the key players in the book is
Merrill Marco, who was Letterman's girlfriend for 10, 15 years, and ran the show, like basically
wrote all these early bits for him in a very male dominated industry.
So they go, ladies and gentlemen, the writer of 9 -5, she comes out, and we're going to be
doing a Q &A moderated by Merrill Marco, this book I'm reading.
She comes out, she's funny, the lady's funny.
And the lady was critical of 9 -5 because she said, she goes, I did it, it was a male director,
and he said to me, you'll have no involvement.
I have your script, thank you.
I'm gonna do what I'm gonna do.
I'm rewriting it, I'll see you at the premiere
and Bander from the set, there might be more
to the story than what she's saying, right.
But yeah, it was kind of a bummer
and then she goes, and I saw the movie
and she goes, you guys all love the movie
and you've seen it a hundred times.
She goes, I see, I miss my original screenplay.
She goes, the heart of it is there.
I love that it brought so many people joy,
but it just goes to show you like you know there's a lot of stuff that goes on in
the making of movie and television that you know it can break people's hearts she
seemed still angry about it but yeah I would imagine because in her script the
three of them tried to kill Dabney Coleman and they replaced it and apparently Jane
Fonda was involved in this too she's like we can't try to kill him that's what led
to the fantasy sequences so I was like oh so the worst part of the movie was not
the writers idea in her script they were all planning on killing. Oh wait wait what oh the fantasy
sequences were there because they said they can't plan to kill in. Right they they'll be
unlikable or whatever. Oh okay. In her mind it was a very dark comedy about trying to kill Daniel.
But anyway they do that. Then how comes Callie Corey, Academy Award winning screenwriter. Right.
A film in Louise. Right. Talks about they have this three way discussion that was so great about
How they made these movies that
Were about what's going on right now right and they read from these reviews by major major critics criticizing
Thelma and Louise of being a man hating movie a man -bashing movie right male critics of course, right
And it was just really really interesting and then I stuck around and watch Thelma and Louise
Which I hadn't seen in 20 years and that movie's fucking great
You know, I've never seen Thelma and Louise it is so fucking good all right
Right, it's really, really great.
And it's funny, it's ran in a great,
and the men in a great.
Chris from McDonald, Brad Pitt, sort of big debut.
Brad Pitt, Harvey Kitell.
Is it funny or is it more of an action?
It's funny, but I mean, it kicks off
with the attempted rape of Gina Davis.
I mean, it's a serious movie, of course, but.
If you haven't seen Thelma and Louise,
make it a priority, everybody knows the ending,
but man, it's so good.
And I think it I got the impression like they really Scott loved reservoir dogs
Because like everyone from reservoir dogs is in it. It's got Madson and Kitelle and all these people. Oh, okay
It's a very cool movie very cool movie
Great you've only got Frazier right
Yeah, but we're we're making some good time here. All right. Do you have a lot more? No, I
Well, Heather and I, I did this bracket thing last night.
They had this bracket in entertainment weekly, which I still subscribe to, even though
it's become like us weekly essentially.
It used to be a great, you know, hard -hitting journalistic magazine, but they had a bracket
like you would do for sports, but with best picture winners.
Right.
What was the best ever, best picture winner?
And Heather and I did it and went through it, had a lot of fun.
And she was like, well, there's a lot of these I haven't even seen.
So, when you look through it, I was actually laughing out loud, looking back at like the five nominees for like 1998, let's say.
Right. They get it so fucking wrong.
When you look back at what movies were released in a given year, the ones that have gone on to become like all -time classics,
they're nowhere near the nominations list. And Heather's like, what is Shakespeare in love? I've never even seen this movie.
And I go, oh, it won best picture.
It beats saving private Ryan.
She goes, there's no fucking way.
I go, it did.
So she was, well, I want to see this thing now.
I saw it in the theater.
I go, I just remember it being kind of boring,
but let's watch it, sure.
We watched Shakespeare in love last night.
It is, Heather was, I've never seen her so angry.
She was so mad this thing won best picture.
It's stupid.
Yeah, of course it is.
I mean, there's a few like kind of cute little jokes
center or whatever, but Paltrow's boring in it. It's a boring movie. It's goofy.
Yeah. It plays like an SNL sketch sort of. And, you know, who got it best picture?
Harvey Weinstein. Wait, that was when people, when that beat shit, same prayer
Ryan, people were like, what's going on here? Because he bought it. That was when he started
getting into a lot of heat about that stuff. He would like really kind of elbow his way into
winning this stuff. But Shakespeare in love, for that movie to win best pick, like has
anyone mentioned that movie in 25 years? No. Nobody mentioned it that year. Nobody
mentioned it. 20 years, I guess, exactly 20 years. But nobody, I mean, nobody was walking
around going, have you seen Shakespeare in love? You got to see it. Nobody. Nobody cared.
And the other nominees that year were the thin red line, which is, I might rewatch, but it's
so insanely boring when I was, what I remember of it.
Yeah.
Elizabeth.
That's not it.
Like the folks, these are not the classics we're, we're still talking about.
They're, they're just all, the, we looked up our birth years, me and Heather, the year of
my birth, 1981, chariots of fire, one best picture.
Apparently, that's a very good movie.
I, I remember watching as a kid and hating it.
It's so slow.
Yeah.
And all the, you know, the only movie that's any good that anyone even remembers from
81 that got nominated was Raiders of the Lost Ark,
which did not win.
Thank God I made for best picture.
It did.
That's a, well luckily so.
It's in my top 10.
I'm not surprised.
I'm, yeah.
I'm surprised I got nominated.
Not that I don't think it's best picture.
I don't know.
It's generally they're dead wrong.
We watched another best picture,
which was Kramer versus Kramer.
I like Kramer versus Kramer.
That was a fantastic movie.
Yeah.
Amazingly well -acted by Dustin Hoffman.
I mean, that's the other thing.
I mean, like anything you watch now, you're like,
Oh, okay, I guess he probably did.
And that movie, Merrill Streep talks about now,
how to get her ready for a scene,
Dustin Hoffman slapped her as hard as he could
across the face.
And she was not prepared or asking for it.
Oh, he didn't, oh, she wasn't like hit, meesh.
He just did it.
She was like, I'm having trouble getting
into the headspace of the scene and he smacked her
as hard as he could and stuff.
I was like, all right.
But if you separated from that,
Kramer versus Kramer is a beautiful movie.
It drags a bit in the courtroom stuff at the end,
which I think was more novel at the time
because divorce was more rare.
But it's just a beautifully done movie
and Hoffman is great in it as is the kid, Justin.
Seeing where the kid falls is brutal.
And he's running running with him.
Hospital, it's brutal.
Yeah, I mean, it's a great movie.
All right, I'm done, I'm done.
Well, let's get into some crane shots.
Please, go for it.
I mean, what?
Look, I guess I could just kind of tell you
what some of my favorite episodes have been.
place but I'll just do one at a time so we can really juice this thing for a long time all right
uh but I would say that uh a recent episode I watched they enjoyed very much was a phrasier is
feuding with his upstairs neighbor cam Winston uh played by i don't know the actor's name
i've never seen him in anything except in this role but he's really funny in it and uh he gets some
of Cam Winston's mail by accident and which he opens and in the mail is an
invitation to the grand opening of some elite new something that's
happening in the city. Of course him and not here Niles are offended. We belong to
every elite club in the city. What would have we not been invited to? They go to
the place. They find out it's a day spa. They hustle their way in. It's the best
day -spot experience they've ever had, they're paying the bill, they're like, this is going
to be a standing appointment for us. My God, I feel rejuvenated. I haven't felt alive
in years, whatever. They see a senator. Frazier goes, oh, isn't that senator? So -and -so.
And the senator, he goes, I want to go say hi, and he goes to say hi. And the senator goes
in a gold door that Frazier is not allowed to go in. And he's like, why can't I go in this
store in the ladies like I'm sorry you're at the bronze level senators at the gold
level you're not allowed to go into the gold level but please enjoy the bronze level
as you have been and then of course immediately he's like I haven't been enjoying anything
this is trash he's disgusted yeah so they go to rods of course of course rods has slept
with the senator which by the time listen I'm this is not a gender commentary I'm about
I was noticing what you're about to say on my cell.
I'm sure.
By the time you get to like the 10th or 9th season of Frazier,
Rods' sexual exploits become disturbing almost.
It gets to a point where you're like,
something's wrong with this person
by trying to fill a hole.
Yeah.
More than what?
More than one, folks.
But anyway, they're telling Rods what happened.
She's like, I know that Senator.
I can call him, you know, when his marriage was breaking up,
we had a quiet affair or something.
And then so of course they get it and she's like, but you're going to get into the gold
door then there's going to be a diamond door and you're going to not be able to deal
with that.
And they're like, right.
Pitchposh.
Getting the gold door, it's the greatest thing they've ever experienced, they're on cloud
nine.
They're just loving it.
It's so much better than the bronze.
They were right.
Of course, Frazier spots the platinum door goes to open it.
Some guys like you're not allowed in there.
and a really well written sequence. They ignore the guy, the staffer, and when the staffer leaves
room, they kick the door open and they're in a thing called a serenity garden. Oh, that's right.
The staffer goes, you're not allowed through that door. You just have to enjoy your time here in
the serenity garden. And Fraser goes, enjoy your time here in the serenity garden. We're cruel
little words ever spoke. That's very funny. That's very funny.
They're this thing they've got like mud on their faces. They kick the door open.
Sunlight is beaming through and Frazier's like, behold, Niles, actual sunlight to replace
the chemical peel and they go out and then it's the back alley. They're in the, they're with
the dumpsters and the fucking back alley. So they upgraded their way outside basically.
That's a nice message.
Yeah, it is a nice message.
Frazier shirtless throughout these scenes.
I think you catch him a couple times.
Niles at one point is in a month full mummy rap.
Okay.
And I'll say this, after this being the second time
I've gone fully through the show
and not counting the ones I saw when it originally aired,
I think I fully believe at this point
that Niles Crane is the most endearing sitcom character.
Wow.
Well, of all time, but you have to watch the entire arc of it.
They all go through a nice transformation over the show, which is why I like it so much.
But his particular arc from going from being such like a nanny and a snot to like a guy
that actually has feelings and loves his dad and like becomes giving, and it's a fucking
beautiful.
He's so good on that show, man.
That guy is so fucking good.
He used to beat Jason Alexander every year, which is shocking to me, but he did.
I think, well, he brings an emotional side to it that is in the George character,
George is hilarious, but George is, you know, it's two speeds.
And it's great. That's true.
But, I mean, like, there's stuff with Niles where it's like,
there's an episode where he dresses up as his dad for Halloween and his, you know,
Marty's like flat or he loves it so much and then Niles drinks too many beers and
Then like goes on this speech about like how his kids are two major disappointment gets it gets so dark and emotional
I'm like, you know, you don't really see that on sign felt that's
They never allowed any emotional
But anyway, I love the show and I have made it the
It's become my barometer for all things quality in half -hour television.
Are you able to tell people like what episode that is, what season it is?
I believe it's season 10, and the episode is, I can't remember the name of it, I can't
remember the name of it.
But look, I'm going to be talking about Frazier on here for a long time.
All right.
We didn't even decide which one we're doing, we're recording two today, but I think we should do before I wake, correct?
No, no, no, no, no, we're in black mirror right now.
All right, well then you're getting a little preview.
Next week's episode will be the, I guess Netflix original movie it became before I wake.
You literally said before I hit record, what are we doing first?
I know.
I said, yeah, I know, I realize that now.
kids been drinking nothing but orange juice for a week yeah I will say during
that week like sometimes you'll start to say a word and it just won't be
there it's like I'm brain dead but we are talking about the back half of black
mirror season four we're talking about episodes four five and six number four is
It's called Hang the DJ.
Yes.
Great title.
Great episode.
Great song, which I was hoping would be used by the Smiths and it is used expertly
in the show as well.
Yes.
And also, then, to kind of step back and go, oh, hang the DJ because the DJ is playing what
they want you to hear, and the show is about making your own path in life, not letting
technology in this case, Tinder basically decide who your partner will be, decide for
yourself. I'm usually not quite bright enough to get those thematic connections.
I didn't catch that. I was like, I was like, hang the DJ. Why is that the title? Why is
that the song? And usually if you sit and think about it, you can get it. I think going to
film school kind of put those thoughts into my head. You start to analyze things. I had
a film teacher who used to say every character in every movie was gay. He thought Bruce
as well as a diehard was a coded gay.
It was hilarious.
He was a fascinating man,
but he made you look differently
at all kinds of movies and shit.
Well, and that was a particularly deep title for Black Mirror.
I mean, the first episode this year was called, like,
Space Jam, or whatever, you know what I mean?
Like, the title has been pretty on the nose.
That's true.
I don't know why that one was called Crocodile.
Like, I never figured that out.
Which one was Crocodile?
Crocodile was the one, it should have been called guinea pig.
It was the one with the woman who kills everybody.
I feel like that had something that was somehow a reference to the violence.
There was some sort of violent parallel between the woman's actions in a crocodile, like
how a crocodile will survive or something like that.
I mean, you know, this one though, I had no idea other than they were playing the song
at the end of it.
I didn't even put together the thing you just said.
We'll recap hang the DJ for our dear listeners.
It's fantastic.
It's everything.
It was probably favorite episode of the season.
Easily my favorite.
It's everything that Black Mirror does right, including keeping the episode under an
hour. You know, I love it. My favorite thing about Black Mirror is that, is that those, I
mean, I don't love the show, but I like when they do this. I love this one aspect. I like
the show very much, but I love this one aspect, which is, hey, they really give a nice fuck
you to people that want everything to be safe. Yes. And are trading off slowly but surely
their own decision -making abilities and their own abilities to be discerning, or whatever
However it is, so things are safe and done for them.
And I really like that black mirror gives you a real fuck you to that.
And that's what this episode does.
It shows that the dating apps have advanced to the point where not only will it get you
a match, but it'll tell you exactly how long you will be with the match, and then there
also, as it unfolds, you realize living in this sort of totalitarian society or compound
or something where you're not allowed to leave the relationship early.
It's telling you we know what's good for you, which is what these apps have
started doing. It was so well cast the lead couple who I had not seen before
had had such chemistry that like in a way I haven't done in a while watching
something that was supposed to be romantic. I was really rooting for them to get
together and I had no idea how it was going to end. I mean I watched this with my
girlfriend, and we were both just like, you know, on the edge of our seats, and it was
not a scary or necessarily suspenseful episode of the show. It was a very light episode
of the show, but I really wanted them to wind up together. They seemed so perfect for
each other. And the way it plays out, I just, I thought it was very interesting and very moving.
I got to say, I liked it a lot. It had great social commentary about what, at least I took
of this way, what our culture does to women, like the app basically forces her into being
very promiscuous with a lot of men, like just overly sexualizing herself, basically.
Because she just kept getting 36 -hour relationships one after the next, and it was just the app
basically being like, yeah, you're going to have a bunch of one -night stands now, like, and
she doesn't, inadvertently.
And I also really like to, so at the end of the episode, they decide we're going to make
a break for it.
We don't damn what the app says.
We're not breaking up.
We're going to make a run, leave this compound, climb the mysterious wall that nobody's ever
scaled over, and see what's on the other side and be free.
So they do, as they do it, everything sort of digitizes and disappears.
years, they end up in this weird, neutral space. There's a bunch of them. It's all identical
couples of them. They all digitize and go up into the air. And then a statistic forms
that says, you know, out of 100 matches, whatever of these two, there have been 99 rebellions
or whatever. Meaning 99 times that the simulation was run, these two decided I was meant for
you. And we need to be together. Fuck what the world has to say. And then it cuts and
you realize it's the algorithm behind a present day dating app that these two people are actually
using separately. And they're meeting for the first time in a day. And it is very hopeful
and it's very beautiful. And you're like, Oh, they found each other and they're allowed
to love each other in this world. But there still is that undercurrent of, yeah, but this,
This is this is where that one started. This you know that this will eventually get to that right just right now
It seems nice. Yeah, it was very well done. It's a very very well done episode
Favorite of the season by far and one of my favorite all -time black mirrors
On the flip side. Oh god, let's dig in the answer this one. What was this thing called this black and what metalhead?
I think it was called metalhead. It was called and I love black and white. So I will say
It was shot very well, because I'm going to say one positive thing, but and I liked
the way the little thing moved, the little thing that was chasing them, but yeah and
I liked that it was 40 minutes, I'm going to say three positive things about it, it was
the shortest of them all, but boy I didn't care about anyone in it or anything that happened.
I thought this was everything Black America could do wrong.
There was no, as far as I was concerned, there was no real social commentary here.
This is a story we've heard a million times.
It's just an elaborate chasing, you know, they break into a warehouse, they want to get something.
It's clearly post -apocalyptic, and I know we talk a lot about our least favorite genres
on this show.
I've never mentioned this.
My right behind remains of the day period pieces is post -apocalypse I can't fucking stand post -apocalypse
It's so boring and it always read Mad Max. I
Did like Mad Max a lot. You're right. Okay. Well, there's always exceptions. Mad Max is awesome
But yeah, I guess so there's exceptions, but
But I post -apocalypse most of the time to me wreaks of a producer saying we don't have a budget
it, let's drive to Arizona and pretend it's the end of the world.
And that's always how it feels to me.
There's a band of people looking for supplies or something.
They break into a warehouse.
They encounter a robotic guard dog in the warehouse.
And then it's the chase is on and it's, you know, it's fucking terminator.
It's just shit you've seen a million times.
The robots chasing the humans, the humans aren't any match for the robots.
They tack on this kind of lame twist at the end where you feel like we find out all they were trying to get was Teddy bears for her sister or something like that.
But again, no real commentary.
I think in theory their thinking was we'll just do one that's just like relentless pure action, but it wasn't exciting to me personally.
It doesn't work. It's like when it's like it's like when the Twilight Zone once in a while would go
We're gonna do a really heartfelt one. Yeah, don't yeah, the sinister element of this show is what makes it work, right?
So I just hated it and and and it was clocked in the shortest of the season at 41 minutes, which guys cut these things down
They don't need to be this long. We've already said it 41 minutes this fucking thing felt longer than any of the other episodes
I agree. I was so fucking bored, man, and coming on the heels of hanging the DJ, it really paled as well
I was just kind of like yeah, yeah, and then six I believe it's called black museum
Black museum. Yes, this one was nearly future length as well. It was an hour -tid. Yeah
Lot of cool stuff though. Yeah, this this felt extremely twilight zone e to me as well as many of them do of course, but
But since you watched them yesterday, you should recap,
because you'll do better than I did.
I watched them around New Year's.
Well, Black Museum is a story about a woman driving
through the desert.
Again, is it poked apocalypse or near -future, whatever?
She stops to recharge her car.
It's going to take three hours to recharge her car.
She notices there's a museum called the Black Museum.
She goes inside to kill some time to get a tour.
The tour guide.
I don't know who either actors name is,
but they were both really fucking good, man.
They were, and left these actors were really good.
Yeah, it's weird too, because there must be all these huge names
vying to be on Black Mirror, so it must be a conscious choice
or maybe a budget choice to just go with no names,
but sometimes it's very effective.
He gives you a tour of the Black Museum,
which, well, actually, I was surprised, but now that I'm talking about it, I'm like,
is a black mirror museum. It's all objects from previous shows, of previous episodes,
and like the guys like these objects were all used to commit criminal acts, and I have
them here, and I, you know, tell the stories of the objects to people. So can I, can I stop
you right there? Yeah.
I did not make the connection that these were artifacts from previous black
mirrors. That's a bummer because that's really that really hooked me in at the
top. I was like, Oh, like what? The lollipop from the space one is in there.
Remember the guy uses the lollipop to get the kids DNA. That lollipop and that
machine that creates the people in the space world is in there. The broken
iPad from the Jody Foster one is in there. So they were from this season even
and I still didn't make that connection.
I saw two or three from this season,
but then I'm guessing there were other ones
from other seasons that I didn't recognize.
I don't know how I feel dumb
after my victory on Hang the DJ, I feel like an idiot.
So anyway, this is a cool episode
because this is the only one they've ever done like this.
They go into an anthology style story or a show or episode
and the guy tells her three different stories
about three different objects
that last about 15 minutes each and you're like perfect.
And then this is the wrap around story.
It worked very well.
In the end you find out that this guy is much more evil
than I guess he initially reveals.
All the stories are connected to this medical association
or company, medical supply company he worked for,
that he was fired from when he figured out
how to capture the consciousness of serial killers.
And he wanted to do this museum of hologram serial killers,
and they told him to beat it.
So he actually did it in his museum with this guy who was,
you know, you get the feeling he was probably innocent,
but was sent to the electric chair anyway.
And this guy basically tortures this hologram
who has full consciousness over and over by electrocuting them every day for people
that come in to see the tours.
This kind of goes back to the episode one, the idea that you could create artificial
intelligence that actually can feel pain and all these things, but can't die.
And then you find out that the guy, the girl that's there that's her dad, and she's there
to avenge her father and poison this guy for what he's doing to him and set her father free,
from this hologram prison, you know,
and this is where it all stops making sense.
I don't really get what the hell happened,
somehow she puts the museum direct,
she uses all the devices from the whole episode,
which this has always been a criticism on a black mirror.
Everything doesn't need to be tied together like that,
and this one they really do it, she takes like a thing
that can put somebody's essence inside somebody else's head and she puts the
evil guy who has the museum his essence inside the essence of the hologram
dad which already you're like wait what yeah and then she puts the
electrocution thing on nonstop which for some reason will kill her dad who's a
but this guy will be electrocuted for the rest of time in his mind. I was like
what the fuck are you talking about and then there was another and then like
there was a teddy bear that a woman's conscious from one of the stories had
been put into and then she takes the teddy bear with her so she saves the woman
and then she gets into the car and looks into the rear view mirror and you see
that her mom is inside her head and you're like, well, how the fuck did her mom get in her head?
It lost me, too. It lost her. It goes wildly off the fucking rails at the end. It's too much.
I might actually watch that one again now that you're telling me all this stuff because I just
was sort of vaguely confused by it. Although I liked her getting the revenge at the end and I like
the stories. I like the stories and etc. But yeah, this one was kind of a question mark for me.
I guess because I didn't get it but not a favorite not a favorite and so it's called black
museum because it's a black mirror yeah because what threw me was I kept expecting a race element
to enter the story because the girl's black well there is a little bit of it the hologram the girl
is black right I think that's on purpose I think that they are trying to make you think like there's
definitely a commentary on race and crime and unfair persecution and whatever in there.
So I think that that's part of it, you know, I think, you know, so overall I'd say the
season was pretty good, you know, I love the first episode, I loved hang the DJ and I
loved, and I really liked this one until the end.
And I thought, as we already stated, the insurance episode and the black and white episode
were painfully boring, I didn't care for either, and I like the insurance episode.
The Jody Foster one was pretty good.
And the Star Trek one was great.
This was the first one I saw another name, other than Charlie Booker, the guy who writes the
show, our Brooker Booker.
And it was Penn Gillette, which I was not expecting, a Penn and Teller fan had the idea for it,
maybe.
I think as a visionary guy, obviously, as Charlie Booker or Booker is, it's time to open
it up and bring in even one other person to get kind of, there are so many people who
could just do a bang up job of coming up with like great shit for the show.
And the guy is a great, great writer, but I think if you're doing six a year, maybe
bring in another voice I think the shows it's about time for the show to open up a
little bit if they're gonna agree I agree you know Rod Sirling is is the man
behind Twilight's oh but he certainly had plenty of other fantastic writers in
there so I'm not pitching myself either I'm not smart enough to write a black
well Pat that's black mirror full season four we covered it you can find me at
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram and on Twitter though I don't really go on Twitter
much as you all know. I also think I think I'm plugging properly here. I will be at the Gotham
Comedy Club headlining five shows the 16th and 17th of February and I will then the following
week be performing at the Patrice O 'Neill Benefit with a slew of other wonderful comedians including
including Bill Burr, Robbie Kelly, Rich Voss,
and then many more, I look forward to that.
So I hope to see you out there.
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh,
and we are getting closer to the premiere of my show,
and also Joe's show, Living Biblically.
You will start to see promos.
I'd like to say in the most diplomatic way possible,
I do not have any say or approval
over the promos they are airing for the show but trust me it's a really funny
show and I hope you watch I also I also have no you know I'll say the most
diplomatic way possible I have no control over any of you tweeting
incessantly at CBS don't tell them to do that and saying where's Gary you know
what maybe they should but not a nice way I'm not saying I'm not saying it a
mean way. I know. But, you know, Les Munevez is not monitoring the CBS. Twitter account,
I assure you. I'm sure it's some nice person who doesn't want to answer all those. But I
ask myself each week, where's Gary? And I hope he returns. Thank you all. Check out that
merch page. As we said, check out that Patreon. Thank you to those of you who are supporting
us, sponsoring us on Patreon. And we'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.
That was a hitgun podcast.