I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, welcome to a very special edition of We'll See You In Hell.
Pat is dead.
It's just me, here by myself, to talk about stop motion.
The show must go on with or without him.
Without him.
He's not, he's gone.
What's more striking is I don't care.
I feel nothing, and that's freaking me out, so I'm going to just kind of keep talking
about movies right here, and I'm trying to help you sell this bit, Joe.
I can't talk.
You've set up a bit that I literally can't, yes and, with you.
You weren't jumping in on it, and it was making me nervous that people were going to actually
start to think that he had actually died.
I mean I'm sorry I wasn't jumping in on the bit where you said I'm dead and you're happy
about it.
I didn't say I was happy.
I wasn't volleying with you on that one.
All I said was I didn't feel nothing.
Well the joke's on you this week, Joe, because I only wish I was dead, thank you very much.
The show this week is brought to you by Lunchables, delicious Lunchables.
We start with six thinly sliced cuts of wet ham, wet floppy ham, and then we add water
to that compartment so there's even more wetness on the ham.
Do you remember when that was the original Lunchables slogan was, do you like it wet?
Do you like your meat wet?
They'd say that at the end of the commercial that a kid would wipe his mouth, and they
were like, this isn't going.
Man, that used to gross me out so much.
When you're a kid, there's not much better than a Lunchable.
Not a lot of families are affording a daily Lunchable, but when you bring one, you get
a little more respect at the lunch table, kind of like Leota walking into the Copa when
you're walking into that cafeteria with your Lunchable.
But they're gross.
They're real gross.
I just randomly popped into my head this morning and they've been on my brain all day.
I was like, God, that ham was gross.
Because in addition to the wetness, there would always be a gray spot, a black spot.
Maybe you see it on a piece of ham, you're fine.
I mean, obviously it's an animal, but there's something about if you're going to make me
a little circle of ham, it better look perfect.
And the fact that it looked like rhino skin or something was disturbing.
I felt like that was actually to their credit that it was real meat.
Well, it definitely was a real meat.
But I like that they tried to make it look like a piece of real meat.
In some way, they gave it some character.
I couldn't.
You like food with character.
I forgot about that.
Well, the turkey is more offensive because the turkey is just, it is uniform white discs.
It looks like what the alien and enemy mine would pull out of his fucking knapsack and
eat.
It looks so crazy.
It's literally as wet.
The fact that it's white makes it more disturbing.
But look, I liked Lunchables.
We talked about this once on Taste Buds.
What I liked about Lunchables as a kid, there's something about when you're a kid and you
have a meal and a food that gives you some kind of control.
It makes you feel like an adult, like you're put together.
There's compartments.
You ration it at your own pace.
It's not just something like a sandwich your mom made and you eat the whole thing and that's
it.
So that was what I thought.
It's like a candy cigarette or like the apple cider in the champagne bottle, let you pretend
a little bit.
Yes.
Now, I went to the Lunchable homepage hoping to see maybe one or two new options.
It's a whole new ball game over at Lunchables HQ, ladies and gentlemen.
We are starting things out with a chicken dunks meal kit with Capri Sun fruit punch drink
and nerds candy.
So we're like, no, we're just going to fatten you up.
Everything's got to have candy, Oreos, chicken dunks, I guess because they can't call them
nuggets, crispy grilled cheezies, which appears to just be a grilled cheese sandwich in a
pocket thing.
Chicken popper kebobbles meal.
I don't even know what some of these things are.
Earth cake snack pack with chocolate marshmallow frosting and gummy worms.
They're going Wonka style with the words.
They're just making up words for things.
But here's the thing, don't glaze over the crispy grilled cheezies.
Here's what pisses me off.
These are grilled cheese sandwiches that you have to microwave.
The whole fucking point.
The empire is built on the no heat factor that you pull off a lid or a cellophane, whatever
the hell that is, that plastic, whatever, and you're in business.
You're off to the races.
We're doing nachos.
Do you see these dunkable matzah sticks with breadcrumbs?
Oh, God.
Yeah, I ordered a skid of them.
It's coming to my house as we speak.
I'll tell you where Lunchables lost me when they, that's also how your college thesis
started.
That was the first sentence.
Yes.
Tried to start a kind of in media rest.
They called me into the dean's office and said, get out.
The this is where they lost me.
It was ballsy when they jumped to the pizza where it was like, it was just you poured
sauce and sprinkle cheese on a cracker and they called it pizza.
That was insane.
I love it.
But then I just was like, guys, that's a hot food.
Come on, what are we doing here?
It's not even close.
No, what I would do is I would take the Ritz cracker and throw it into the air.
You know, like I'm mixing the dough, throw each one up, keep doing that at the table.
I would eat the pizza one and then beat my wife.
Sorry, when did they lose you, Joe?
Post pizza, clearly.
Pizza was when I was like, guys, what are you doing?
And then when they followed that with the cold version of the nachos, I was like, all
right, guys, I'm out.
This is this is crazy.
But could you heat it if you wanted?
Yeah, of course, you could heat anything that you want.
But I mean, the point was that we weren't supposed to.
It was supposed to be like, no, you just put this salsa on and then you sprinkle this
cheese on.
I was like, this is bad shit.
Yeah, like it was it was just crazy to me.
Yeah, so they lost me there.
I wasn't too well, but they're sponsoring us this week.
So shout out to Lunchables TM.
What did you watch?
I haven't, unfortunately, but I saw the gladiator trailer was out.
Did you see it?
I did watch.
I watched it just before we hopped on.
I saw Denzel looking bad ass, looking younger than he's looked in 20 years.
I think they de -aged him or something.
He's really thin.
Like, I mean, he looks young.
Like, is that just going to be the norm now?
Because when you see him, he's getting a little paunchy, you know, like like any
65, 70 year old man, but like, you know, that third equalizer, I noticed he
wasn't wasn't necessarily chasing a lot on foot.
So like when I saw him in this new thing, I'm like, he looks like he's 40.
I don't, I don't know that he's ever looked this good.
He looked, he was like Malcolm X skinny.
Yeah.
And the hair looks great.
Um, or maybe he just got super and shy.
I don't know, but I never saw the original for, I don't know why.
I just, I just never saw it.
Because Russell Crowe wasn't performing exorcisms or riding a scooter around town.
Yeah.
It was out of character for Crowe for me.
I don't, I never got into a sword and sandal movie that doesn't also
have like dragons in it.
Like I always want like there to be a magic element.
So I get it, but I'll tell you, that's a testament to how cool gladiator is, is
that it's like two and a half hours, a true epic, and it doesn't matter at all.
Like you just, it's a great story.
Crowe is awesome.
Phoenix is awesome.
There's laughs.
It's good.
Well, I'll tell you, even having not seen the original, the trailer for this, I
was like, oh, this is cool.
If I had seen the original, this would really get me excited because it's about
the son grown up and then like taking up the father's mantle, which is kind of
cool, but two things that really stick out in the trailer, um, number one, they
play hip hop in the middle of it, which is really weird choice.
They play like a Jay Z song.
I was like, what are they doing?
And then, um, big pimpin it's it's like, no, it's a hard knock life.
Yeah.
Hard gladiators.
You know, like, yeah, like halfway through the trailer, it's like, it's like, my
name is ho it's time to fight blizzy.
You know, like, this is, it's just odd, but, um, then, uh, but then
somebody pointed this out on the YouTube in the comments.
They were like minute 53 or whatever.
Uh, my man gladiator, my man training day.
And I was like, what are they talking about?
And sure enough, like halfway through this trailer, it cuts to Denzel
at a table with somebody and he is full on doing the training day.
My man left.
Yeah.
I think they might be going a little meta in this one.
Like, well, he seems just from the little clip I saw, he seemed to be having fun
in a way he has not in a very long time.
Yeah.
I feel like I hadn't seen him smile since like the preacher's wife, you know?
Uh, and then I wasn't smiling, so it was a problem.
Uh, I love mescal.
I don't, I don't understand.
I never thought he'd go the gladiator route, but I'm sure he was like, you
know what, I'm not going to do Marvel and make that money.
So I'll make my money with Ridley Scott.
I guess I get it, but, um, he just strikes me as kind of a sensitive,
quiet man and not the gladiator was, is he jacked?
Yeah.
I mean, he's as the English would say proper fit, uh, he's, uh, yeah, he's
wait, is that the kid from ask kick where to kick ass?
No, who is from after son, which was one of my favorites
of the last couple of years.
And normal people, which I loved as well.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, yeah, he's cut, man.
I mean, he, he looks like a gladiator.
There's no part of it where it doesn't make sense.
Um, and who's he up against?
Keoghan?
I think he's avenging his father and he says at one point in the trailer,
Denzel says, whose head can I bring you?
That would satisfy your blood lust or something.
And he goes the entire Roman empire.
So I guess he wants to take down Rome.
But isn't Barry Kyo in it?
Oh, um, I'll tell you in a second.
And I thought, cause he looks like Phoenix, they both got hair lips
that maybe he was his son.
Pascal's in it.
No.
Oh yeah.
Kogan is in it.
Yeah.
I think, but this kid, Fred heckinger, heckinger, I think is the one in the
trailer or maybe it's Joseph Quinn.
Somebody plays like a really quirky character in the trailer.
Uh, I'm not sure who's who.
Uh, a FOP, a fancy lad.
Yeah.
It seems like it's taking the place of the, of the, um, Phoenix.
Uh, but, uh, but yeah, Pascal's in it.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, Hansu is in it.
Um, Connie Nelson, who's, what is she from?
She was in the OG, uh, gladiator, pretty blonde lady.
Yeah.
She usually plays a pretty blonde lady.
She's back.
Um, I mean, I don't know.
I don't really know much, but, uh, Oliver Reed is in the original.
Yeah.
I think he died during filming.
Oh, wow.
That's cool.
Check it out, man.
It's, it's very good movie.
All right.
One best picture.
I mean, used to mean something.
Uh, I've got a, uh, news psycho.
Did you see this?
DeGeneres just canceled her last four tour dates and said, this is it.
She was in Chicago.
She said, tonight is the last time you will see me, except for my Netflix special.
I'm done leaving show business.
And then she basically just said, I'm not mean by, and it's like this whole, you
put this whole tour together to go out and tell the world you're not mean, but
probably three days, four days into it, she's like, I'm too rich for this shit.
Fuck it.
Watch my special.
Who do you think's ghostwriting this special?
I actually know who's ghostwriting it.
The one who's ghostwritten all of her other specials.
Um, and I know her quite well.
Ellen doesn't write any of her own shit and really, I mean, I don't want to
say never has, but it's been decades.
And as far as her not being nice, and I of course will not name names, but I am
close with several people who worked at somewhat high levels at the Ellen show,
high down to low, let's say over the last 20 years to keep it as vague as possible.
And good Lord, the stories that is not a nice woman.
Ladies and gentlemen, don't listen to her.
Don't pull it.
She's gaslighting you.
You're being gaslighted by Ellen DeGeneres.
You want that?
Yeah.
I've heard some absolute horror stories.
She's a menace.
She's like, so there's a thing, um, at least I've experienced it every, I've been
in fewer writers rooms than Pat has, but I've experienced this in every writer's
room I've ever been in.
You've been in fewer writers than I have too.
What's day one is always like that lunch on day one is like, let me tell you what
it was like over at this place.
Everybody starts opening up.
And every time I've done it, one of my go -tos is like, I don't know if any of you
worked on that Warner Brothers a lot, but those Ellen stories sure are true.
Like, cause I worked at Pete's show and you were at Broke Girls.
That's when I met you and she, those stories would circle that lot man, her,
and the, and the rebel Wilson show stories would just woof.
Yeah.
Rebel Wilson, a legendary tyrant as well.
Like that show she had went maybe a season, maybe two.
And like, she is despised, despised, like the biggest monster on earth.
And now she's on this tour, going out, calling people out.
She called somebody else out today.
Oh, which who?
And I honestly don't mind your, your call outs, but you better have a pretty clean
slate, especially if you're going to call out people for rudeness.
I want to see who she, the people she called out today were producers on this
movie she made her directorial debut, which I know you're really excited about
you, but she's like, um, these producers in quotes, didn't contribute anything.
They didn't help.
And I'm reading this thing was on deadline or TMZ or some shit reading
her giant Instagram posts.
And I'm like, just cause everyone has sucked your dick for 20 years does not
mean that's how this business works.
Everyone, regardless of how far along you are, has worked on a project where there
are multiple producers who do nothing, who you never meet, you never see, maybe
they put up money, maybe they didn't, maybe they just know somebody, but
that's the business.
There have been jokes about producers who do nothing on movie sets, literally
since the beginning of movies, since like the silent era and she's taking
them publicly to task.
And I keep waiting in the comments for somebody to go, wait a minute.
You threw a cup of hot coffee in my face on the set of up all, whatever
the fuck that show was rebel yell.
It should have been called rebel yell.
What was it called?
Well, that's the title of my very scathing biography.
I'm writing about her actions on that show.
It wasn't called up all night.
Now that, now that was the one that was our net and my Rudolph.
So I don't know what hers was rebel.
Was it called like big gals?
Don't cry.
I think it was just called rebel.
Wasn't it?
Nah, that's right.
Well, rebel Wilson opens up about losing her virginity at 35.
Come on rebel.
Doesn't sound like much of a rebel to me.
Super fun night is the name of the show.
That's right.
She, this is what I love when, when, uh, when this kind of person starts
firing shots at everybody.
Number one, I love that they've always done the same stuff that they're
complaining about or worse.
Number two, notice how she's never given accolades to anybody.
Not a soul.
It's all just this person did me wrong.
Me, me, me, me, me.
She sucks.
And I, I've been ringing this bell a while now on this podcast, but these
things, you just ask yourself like, where are the rebel Wilson fans?
We get one to two, $25 million movies a year from her that don't make money.
You've never heard anyone say her name and conversation, even living here in
Hollywood, um, in bridesmaids where she had two quick scenes where she was like
the gross out character, she was kind of funny pitch perfect where she played a
character named fat Amy before she decided that body shaming is a problem
in Hollywood.
Um, I just don't get it.
What, where, why are people rooting for rebel Wilson?
Why, how did this fame start?
Was it bridesmaids?
Uh, it wasn't her movie at all.
It was the one after that.
It was the bridesmaids like carbon copy that, uh, that the, the, um, was it
just the pitch perfects that, that, well, it was pitch perfect and then she was
in the, what's it called the lady from the accolade, uh, uh, Harvey Weinstein's
assistant, didn't she?
Oh, the bachelorette.
That was a good movie.
Wasn't it just bridesmaids though?
Wasn't it just like a copy of, or not copy, but
bachelorette is, is I really love bridesmaids.
Bachelorette is a much meaner, uh, nastier movie.
It's not as good, but it's very like smart about the ways that women can be
mean and horrible to each other.
Okay.
Bridesmaids was kind of about to, but different.
Oh, it's the, so I think that was, cause I remember she was kind of like in the,
I don't mean this in a mean way.
She was kind of like in the Melissa McCarthy position.
And that is like the, the overweight person in the bridal thing,
party, whatever.
And, uh, and she was like the, the brash, like heavyset one.
Yeah.
So I think that's what I remembered her getting like, uh, notoriety from.
And, you know, maybe she's great.
I don't know.
I mean, I've seen her and stuff.
She's serviceable, like, but I've never seen her be like, Oh dear Lord, I
got to rewatch that rebel Wilson segment.
But Walter Hauser, uh, has been added to every major movie that's coming out in
the next like year and I was like, Paul Walter Hauser, the fat guy from.
A bunch of stuff.
Cruella, uh, I Tanya black Clint Eastwood, a fat guy.
Yeah.
Uh, or Dick Jewel.
And, um, he's, he's been added to everything and like huge movies and he's, you
know, he's a voice in this and he's doing a massive action movie.
And I'm like, again, I like the guy and he's a good actor and
he's been nominated for stuff.
He's a big deal.
I think he won for something or other, but I was just kind of surprised by it
until I thought you need a lot of movies, need a fat guy.
And we are in an age where we do not have fat guys.
We used to have lots of fat guys, but he's the fat actor.
If you want a fat, funny guy, he's it.
Yeah.
You know, if he's, you want guy younger than Jack Black.
We haven't had a good fat guy since Jack Black.
No.
I agree.
You know, some might say GAD.
I can't go with you on that.
Uh, I, I, I, I, I enjoy GAD.
I don't dislike him.
It's just annoying that anybody that's, anybody that's connected to
everything cool gets annoying.
That's just annoying after a while.
Look, I started to resent the Beastie Boys with it.
I started to really get tired of like, when that book came out and it's just
like every fucking, every cool person from every cool thing is like Beastie
Boys, Beastie, I'm like, all right already guys, like fuck off.
Like it just gets it.
And I love the Beastie Boys.
It just gets annoying though.
So like, that was my, always my thing with Josh GAD.
It was always like, well, I'll be, uh, I'll be writing my, the
reboot of Ghostbusters and then it's onto Garfield.
And then I decided I want to tackle Doonesbury.
Cause I was always a fan of that.
And it's just like these people are just going to do whatever they want.
It's gets a little annoying.
I hear you.
Those were terrible examples I gave, but you, you get the point.
I get the point.
When he was hosting during COVID, all those like, guys, I managed to get the
cast of It's a Living back together somehow, you know, and we're going to do
a Zoom, I was like, I don't understand who the fuck is this guy?
Right, right.
Um, but I saw a really funny headline today.
It might've been the funniest, uh, entertainment related headline I've ever seen.
I don't remember where I saw it, but it said Lou Diamond Phillips opens up about
who he thinks is blocking Young Guns 3.
Who, who, who does he think?
I assume a disinterested public is the answer to that question.
That's why I started laughing.
That was my thought.
But, uh, I w I would see Young Guns 3, but I'm like, Lou, it's
everybody, you got problems when Estevez is the most relevant name in the, you
know, yeah, yeah, that's just, you got Kiefer and so forth.
I mean, I guess Kiefer would still, is still around.
You'd have to go low budget.
By the way, folks, I sent just one to Joe the other night, just one out of a
dry, you know, a real, a true drop in the ocean.
You got to check out those Stephen Baldwin TikToks.
Uh, that needs to be a pretty high priority for you.
That's all I'm going to say.
Before he dies, which is days away.
I was surprised.
He looks pale.
He, he, he doesn't look great.
Ghost translucent.
Yeah.
Um, I was surprised too, because I thought the way Pat, it's not, I
should, let me rephrase that.
Not the, because of the way you described it, just as you were describing it, my
assumption was that he would say these things about his wife and then start crying.
That's not it at all.
It's just him staring for a full two minutes into camera crying and the
text in the, on the picture says like, my wife, my best friend.
I w I don't know what I would do without her.
I'm like, and it's playing a country song with the lyrics up and it's
like, I love my wife.
She made a happy place of my life.
And then he's sobbing.
It's very disturbing.
Um, speaking of disturbing, I'd like to give a quick RIP to the
boy from Alf, Benji Gregory.
Oh geez.
Passed away today at the age of 46.
From what?
Joe, you, you know, these things are never good, right?
Oh yeah.
This isn't, you know, just, we don't know details, but it says, uh, he
was found in his car in a Chase bank parking lot in Peoria, Arizona.
And his service dog, Hans was also found dead in the vehicle.
Jesus Christ, man.
Not what you want.
He had a career.
He did things other than Alf as, you know, that child star road is just
impossible, you know?
Yeah, that's dark.
It says he has bipolar, he had bipolar and a sleep disorder that often kept
him awake for days.
Oh Jesus, that's terrible.
I mean, we're talking about maybe an Alf curse.
Everybody associated with that show fell into deep depressions and acted out
and died young and well, two people.
And then the creator is Permanent Midnight.
That's right.
No, not creator.
He wrote for it.
Oh, okay.
Great book by the way.
Uh, let's, let's hit that movie corn, shall we?
Yeah, sure.
I only have, I've been because I'm, I'm back.
I'm not used to being back in the writer's room.
I only got one thing that I saw.
I feel bad.
I apologize.
Uh, I watched on Disney plus Jim Henson idea, man.
Um, this was directed by Ron Howard who has just been coasting for the last 20
years, uh, now he has entered into the true, uh, the coasting level of, uh, of
an older director's career documentaries.
You notice Scorsese quote directs for documentaries a year, in addition to
making four hour movies and he's 90 years old, they're probably not directing
these documentaries folks, they're watching cuts that an editor puts
together is usually the case.
Not always, but this movie it's, you love Jim Henson.
I love Jim Henson.
I have read two huge biographies on Jim Henson.
I feel like I know a lot about him.
I've been to his exhibits all across the country.
I went to an exhibit of his shit in New York, one out here in LA.
I'm a big fan.
The Muppets, particularly great Muppet caper, Sesame street,
Fraggle Rock, big part of my life.
And if you want truly the most generic look at a true artist's life, this is it.
I can't say I didn't like it.
It's one of those like, honestly, you like June Wilder more than I did, Joe,
but it's just like these documentaries where you're, you might as well have
looked at the Wikipedia page or starting to bother me, uh, you can go a lot deeper.
And I don't mean, I don't mean I needed all the warts and all of Jim Henson, but
like, there was a darkness there.
Do it, can we have one negative word about the man?
Can we know one fault that he had one negative relationship that he had?
No, it's an hour and 45 minutes.
It covers like a 30 to 40 year career.
And what it winds up being is like, then he had the Muppets on Saturday night live.
Then he did the Muppet show, then he did the Muppet movie.
They did a few more Muppet movies.
And you're like, guys, like it's just really, really frustrating in the exact
same way, uh, the beach boys documentary was on Disney plus.
And what's confusing about it is that they also do the overkill version of the
documentary, the eight hour get back Beatles, where you're watching them
literally order food.
Um, I don't know why Disney plus has pivoted this way, or if it's just they
happen to release a couple lame documentaries in a row, but, uh, two super
disappointing documentaries about two, like massive cultural figures in my, and
a lot of people's lives.
And I think it's a bummer because that means you're not going to get that great
documentary about Jim Henson unless it happens 20 years from now, because
they already made one.
It's a let down, Joe.
I want to shout out documentary filmmakers, the, the real ones, these
things, the, and I'll even include wild air.
These things don't deserve to be called documentaries.
They should just be called bios or biography.
Like some guy, like A &E biography used to do these, they'd be an hour.
There was a great one on John Candy, but that's what these are, you know, a
little tribute to a guy you like.
Imagine, imagine you, you know, you go to like Beirut and Hollywood and
blow the lid off of some child trafficking ring.
This guy's like also nominated Henson.
And you're like, why don't you go fuck yourselves?
Oh, did you put together Muppets clips?
Like that's a great point, Joe, is that these documentaries, it's not enough
for them to exist and for the director to get this acclaim that he didn't deserve.
But they're always nominated.
Always for like top, this will be nominated for an Oscar for best documentary.
I can almost guarantee it.
And why it's, it's honestly kind of maddening.
Like I don't even think the directors should say, boy, I really
killed it with that, you know?
And that's also not to say you can't make a killer documentary
about somebody's life.
Many of them exist.
Yeah.
You just got to dig a little deeper than literally like when I, when they'll
put written by on documentaries.
Sometimes the beach boys had written by on it and there was no narration.
So like, what the fuck is that?
You didn't write it.
And the outline for this movie in particular, the Jim Henson movie, um, you
could have looked along with Wikipedia.
Like there's an early years section that, you know, it goes through just
like any generic book report, uh, bummer.
Who, you know, come on, Ron, what were you doing?
This was probably a pandemic baby too.
So you had time.
Yeah.
You had time.
Then who do they interview?
Nobody I remember.
Frank Oz was kind of cool, you know, but that's about it.
Bummer.
Yeah.
Well, that sucks.
Um, well, the one movie I did watch, uh, is the highway men starring
Kevin Costner and Woody Harrelson.
I don't honestly don't know why I even watched it.
I just kept seeing it on Netflix and kept seeing, you know, when you, when
you're skimming on Netflix, it'll just autoplay a scene and it just kept
playing the scene of them in a diner and Woody, like Woody Harrelson's eating
like pie and he's like, how many bullets you got in you, you know?
And like, you know, uh, Kevin Costner was like, I don't know, 16.
And they're, they're doing like grizzled cop back and forth, ball breaking.
And I was like, I don't know.
I just, I'm intrigued.
I want to watch it.
I didn't even know what it was about.
Uh, it's about the hunt, the two men that hunted down.
It's a true story.
Hunted down, uh, Bonnie and Clyde.
Uh, I thought it was really interesting.
What I, what I liked about it was, you know, Bonnie and Clyde were, were
bonafide celebrities in their day when they were outlaws and they have been
fabulized ever since, uh, not without fault due to, uh, the, you know,
the, the Warren Beatty movie.
Yeah.
Um, but what this movie got into that I was unfamiliar with and I had never
seen depicted was, no, these were, they were like psychotic, like gruesome,
grisly killers, they were murderers.
Like, and they really got into like, they were on a killing spree of lawmen
and like, they got into like, no, they made this guy roll over so they
could shoot him in the face.
Like they were, they were really depraved.
Yeah.
You know, these guys come out of retirement as like the two, the two
grizzled old cops who were good enough to find them and, and catch them.
And that's the movie.
It's them on the, on the trail of Bonnie and Clyde.
It's not as riveting as you want it to be.
I thought it was going to be a little more like hell or high water, uh, or
even no country for old men.
Um, it's a little slow, but it's well directed by John Lee Hancock.
The performances are great.
Costner is awesome in it.
It's the most bad -ass I've ever seen Costner.
Like it's the coolest and toughest I've ever seen him.
And.
Harrelson's great, you know, but he's slowly slipping into like a
Kentucky moonshiner with, with each passing month.
Uh, he's deep.
He'll be wearing a barrel in about 10 years.
Yeah.
So he's pretty down that road in this.
Uh, Kathy Bates is great in it.
She plays, uh, the governor, Ma Ferguson.
Uh, well, I saw them recently on some maps, probably tick tock.
Who am I kidding?
But, uh, they looked ugly.
Like it was like, did they show you the real people or are they
played by actual ugly people?
Like it was Faye Dunaway and, and, uh, Warren Beatty in the movie, but
apparently they were like meth heads looking.
You never, um, you never really see them clearly, which I thought
was a really good choice.
You see them doing things, but it's always like a shot of their legs.
And you see the guy who's laying on the ground or you see them
from over the shoulder, you barely see them.
The first time you get a decent look at them is when they're dead.
And, and this is, this is equally as grisly they shot.
So, so the way they killed Bonnie and Clyde, they set up an ambush.
Uh, where all the, all the highway men, uh, were in the bushes and the weeds.
And, uh, the car came up and they were meeting like their contact that they
do whatever illegal business with in this town and they just come out and like.
I mean, it's wild.
They unload like 16 machine guns worth of bullets into the two of them.
And then they take the car, the bullet written car and the bullet written bodies
and they parade it through the town to be like, we got these fucking scumbags.
And people are crowding the car and crying.
Like it's the Beatles.
Like they're sad that they're dead.
So it was the depression and all that stuff.
And my buddy recommended that movie to me, uh, not too long ago.
And I'm like, well, how did these things happen?
There's no theatrical release for a Kevin Costner, Woody Harrelson action movie.
It wasn't made for Netflix.
It was a Netflix made for Netflix that I didn't know.
Okay.
Yeah.
The poster says Netflix original.
So it must've just been, but I enjoyed it.
I'd watch it again.
I don't know.
I wouldn't buy it, but I'd watch it again.
It's worth a watch the highway, man.
All right.
Uh, I watched.
What did I watch?
Pat, Pat, uh, did I talk about Geely last time?
I did.
Yeah.
We just re yeah.
Okay.
Um, okay.
Great.
I rewatched the worst person in the world, which I saw in theaters and I was like, I
liked this quite a bit.
And then I kept thinking about it.
And then I realized that I was thinking about it all the time.
And then I went back and saw it a second time in theaters, which I very rarely do.
And I was like, I think this movie is kind of amazing.
And then recently I watched it a third time at home.
Criterion just put it out and I think it's one of the best movies of recent times.
I think it's, uh, it's up there with the grip.
You know, we don't talk about a lot of romance movies on this show, uh, but I
think this is up there with like your before sunrise trilogy, um, in,
in movies that are kind of small, but wind up encompassing the entire human
experience.
Um, I love the fucking movie.
Um, I re next criteria and say, I'll pick it up.
You can't go wrong.
It reads like an excellent novel in that it goes back and forth in time and
relationships of this woman.
She goes in and out of people's lives.
They come in and out of hers.
It covers a four year period, sort of, uh, the, I believe the four years after
college of this woman, as she's trying to figure herself out and making huge
mistakes and fucking people over in the process and getting fucked over and
et cetera.
And it's that time when you're trying to figure out your life, your career, uh,
who do you want to be with?
Do you want to be with somebody?
What kind of person you want to be, et cetera?
And I've just, you know, I've really not seen many movies that capture
that better and I'll watch it again and I'll probably like it even more.
I think it's just one of those that's going to get better over time.
I highly recommend it.
Uh, it's like, it's, it's very small.
Like I said, it's, uh, from this guy, Joe, I guess you pronounce it,
Joachim Trier, who is Danish.
He is related to Lars von Trier, but not closely, not like his son or anything.
But, um, he's made several movies that I enjoyed.
I think this is like his masterpiece and he's making another one right now with
the lead actress who is incredible.
Her name is Renata Reinsve, but, um, highly recommend.
If you haven't seen it, check it out.
And I think not a lot of people have.
All right.
Um, okay.
One more.
Sorry.
If you're not going to, I'm sorry.
Um, one more that I didn't talk the greasy strangler.
No.
And if I mean, if I I've talked about, yeah, go ahead.
I was going to say if we want to do it, but I've talked about it.
Already on the corner, uh, the greasy strangler.
I actually had resisted watching because I had heard it described as exactly
what, how Joe reviewed it to me, which was that it was kind of hard to watch
and disgusting and, um, made him feel gross and et cetera.
And that's what most of the reviews say.
I mean, that's kind of what it's supposed to be.
Um, I really wasn't grossed out by anything.
There's certainly gross stuff in it.
I think people with like textural issues, which is a lot of people might like
it's one of those where like, if, if, if the gross stuff in it is specifically
your ick, then it will probably ruin your viewing experience, but it didn't bug me.
Uh, it's a father and son who are very strange.
The, the son is probably 50.
The dad is probably 75.
And you know, St.
Michael is the actor's name.
Michael St.
Michael's.
Yeah.
They live in, you know, essentially poverty, but it's one of those movies
where it's another it's America.
It's very recognizably like present day America, I believe filmed in LA, at
least it looked like it, but you're not in America.
You're in another world, uh, where everyone acts differently than normal people.
So the vibe is very much David Lynch.
The vibe is very much Tim and Eric, uh, especially the glory old great
days of Tim and Eric.
And the vibe is also, um, John waters for sure.
And you know, like a, a much darker, nastier, sicker Napoleon dynamite also,
all these influences I think are in there.
The director's name is Jim Hosking, who now that I've looked him up, looks a
lot like beloved listener, Will Potorf, who does a lot of the artwork for the
show and if will, by the way, if you're listening, well, if you told me you had
made a movie called the greasy strangler, uh, I would not bat an eye.
It seems like something you would do.
Um, this movie is weird as fuck.
I loved it.
I found myself stopping it and going away from it, not cause I was bothered,
but because I wanted to kind of live in the world a little longer.
The performances are insane.
Um, and when I asked Joe about it, you know, he said, I didn't love it,
but I'm happy it exists, which I think is kind of how you got to
feel about something like this.
Somebody with that specific and interesting a vision scrambled together a
couple thousand dollars to bring that vision to life.
And I thought it was awesome.
I mean, I was, it's one of those where your, your laughs are kind of caught in
your throat cause you're not sure what you're watching, but, uh, it's a wild
ride. I recommend it if you like the unusual.
Yeah.
And Joe tell us what he does next.
He followed it with an evening with Beverly love Lynn, which I tried to watch
and I found painfully boring, but
I heard it was bad with Aubrey Plaza, but I'll watch it.
But he stepped his game up.
I mean, his follow up to this movie had Aubrey Plaza, Germaine Clement
and, uh, uh, Craig Robinson.
So, um, all right.
Yeah.
Tell us about what the movie
stop motion.
Stop motion is a, uh, British horror film directed by a guy named Robert Morgan.
It's his first feature length, uh, film that he is a stop motion animator and has
won many awards, uh, for his shorts that have featured stop motion animation.
Uh, the basic premise of the movie is there is a young woman, uh, who, whose
mother is a stop motion animator, but her mother is suffering from crippling
arthritis and can no longer do the animation.
So, uh, also suffering from being a huge bitch.
Yeah.
And, uh, Aisling Franciosi, I believe it's her name, but that is her name.
I believe that's how it's pronounced, uh, plays the daughter.
She has to do the animation for the mother.
So the mother is puppeting the daughter basically.
Uh, and when the mother goes into the hospital because she has a
stroke and becomes comatose, the daughter takes over the movie and vows to finish it.
Uh, but then soon after meets a young girl who convinces her to make a different movie.
And slowly Suzanne Blake, uh, or sorry, Ella Blake is the character's
name slips into, uh, madness.
Things go from there.
Uh, the film is very well shot.
It's, uh, it looks very nice and it's very well performed and it has some
really upsetting moments in it, uh, visually and, uh, you know, things
that will make you cringe, but, uh, I gotta say, and the stop motion is the
animate their stop motion sequences throughout the movie that are brilliant.
Truly brilliant.
Um, but I gotta say, I was sitting there wandering the entire time.
Who, who, who is this movie for?
Uh, it's, it's, it's very well received, but it is, it is brooding.
It is joyless.
Yeah.
It is hopeless.
Um, it is heavy handed.
They lean so heavily into the metaphor of who is the puppet and who is being
puppeted, uh, to the point that characters even start to actually say it.
Um, folks take a seat also here, uh, cause this is going to blow your mind.
The movie is really a metaphor for trauma.
And I know you don't see that a lot in modern horror, but it's really a
metaphor for trauma and, and parental ship.
Uh, I texted this to you, Pat.
I didn't get a response.
I was actually kind of disappointed.
Yeah.
Cause I thought it was so funny.
That this movie creates a cutthroat community of stop motion artists.
Joe, check your phone because not only did I give it a ha ha,
I genuinely laughed out loud.
Oh, I didn't see the ha ha.
I might've fallen asleep by the time you respond.
All right.
Yeah.
It's there's like stop motion animators scene.
It's the cutthroat world of stop motion animators.
It made me laugh, but I, it's also like that was played as an amazing joke
in being John Malkovich that he was in a cutthroat world of puppeteers.
Like it is when you, when you're taking this seriously, it is a little goofy
for sure, and maybe that's why the movie is so solemn because they didn't want
it to turn into child's play or puppet master or something, and it's not.
There's a moment near the end where I was like, Ooh, is this going to
become kind of puppet master, but it doesn't.
And my issue with it is exactly what you're saying, Joe.
I think the reason it gets the good reviews is like, it's got a vision.
It looks cool.
Um, it kind of creates its own little, little world and its own little rules.
And you're not sure what's fact or fiction and blah, blah, blah.
But even these, I, I'm a huge fan of stop motion animation.
I love it.
I write up through Burton.
And then when I was a kid, I was genuinely obsessed with the
old like rank and bass stuff.
I used to just wait every year for that shit, loved it, lived for it,
loved how it looked, still do.
Um, I got to see a little bit of it when always sunny, I worked on their Christmas
episode and they did a little claymation sequence or stop motion sequence, but I
associate the format with unparalleled joy and happiness.
Yes.
And I see the title stop motion and I'm like, all right, it's horror.
It's stop motion.
I don't know what it's about.
And then I saw somebody compare it to puppet master.
And my mind just started going about all the fun I was about to have.
So maybe my expectations were a little tweaked, but it's just kind of a slog,
you know, and like when I saw the stop motion world and the characters, I was
like, they're ugly and weird and disturbing.
I didn't expect that.
I didn't expect like each creature to look like he was being choked to death
or something in the stop motion.
That was the only part I enjoyed outside of the animation itself.
I liked that it was like little creepy puppets.
It reminded me of the old tool videos.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, they, they were stop motion guys and then they also did the tool with
videos, but the, um, so I liked that and my hats off to Robert Morgan, whose
life's blood is clearly stop motion animation and has taken it as far as any
man since Rankin and Bass or whatever has been able to take it, but, uh, I
appreciate that and he's very good at it, but, um, I just didn't give a fuck.
I just, I started, I, when it started, I was like, this is interesting.
This is creepy.
The movie she's making with her mom is about a cyclops who sees her own death.
And so like right away you're like, Ooh, this is kind of a
creepy movie they're making.
And then she meets this little girl after her mom's hospitalized.
The little girl within 10 seconds, you're like, this girl's not there.
This is in her head.
Yeah.
And now the little girl is puppeting her and making her make the movie.
And the movie, the little girl wants her to make is about a little girl who is
haunted by a monster called the Ashman.
And, uh, you know, and she's like, the Ashman will visit on three nights.
And I'm like, this is, this is all the makings of a fun ghosty, scary, like
spooky kind of story you'd hear when you were a kid.
And then it just goes full fucking focus onto the artist herself
descending into madness.
And as Pat said, the, her own trauma and the metaphor for that.
And, and, you know, uh, by the way, as she's making her movie, each puppet
needs to be created with flesh.
Uh, and it becomes more extreme.
So the first one is created with raw steak.
And then the second one, the little girl makes her make it out of parts
from a dead Fox they find.
And you're, you're like, obviously she's going to now kill somebody.
And, and, and of course that does happen.
And then it's got this very ambiguous ending that almost makes you
wish for the cliched ending.
I was sitting there going, I swear to God, if at the end of this fucking
thing, it pulls out and this was all like a movie her mom was making and like
she's been dead and this was her mom's movie the whole time, you know, one of
those cheap shots, I was like, I'm going to be real pissed.
And then the end is so fucking dumb and poetic and ambiguous.
I was like, I would have preferred the goddamn cliched ending.
So at least I had some closure here.
I don't know what the fuck I'm even watching anymore.
Like it's just snapped at what's real.
What's not real.
There's a scene where, I mean, this is wild to me.
There's a scene where she goes to a party and asks, uh, her
boyfriend's sister for drugs.
I had to look on Wikipedia.
Cause I didn't know what was happening.
John is LSD I felt that too.
And I did the same thing at the same moment.
That's how bad of a storyteller are you?
If you don't understand a woman going to buy some drugs.
Because he makes the drug LSD.
Who is still buying LSD and going to a dealer to get it.
A dealer at a party.
And by the way, the dealer goes, are you sure?
Like she hadn't, nobody's had an LSD addict that then that's not a thing.
Yeah.
It's like, are you sure about what?
Like no question is answered.
Even the, even the relationship with her and the guy, when he gets her the flat
after her mom is sick, you're like, is this her boyfriend or are they living
together?
I don't even understand what this relationship is.
It's so vague.
All of it.
There's something happening and I'm, I can't go into anything on that, but
there's something happening with scripts.
I just read one the other day where the writing, I don't know if
it's a late Mamet influence coming back or what, but there's a real love of
like keeping you in the dark, not just on what's happening in a scene, but
even what's being said, like there's a new way of dialogue where everything
is like two words and you read it and you're like, what am I reading?
What are they talking about?
You're not David Mamet.
There's scenes now that happen.
So of course we've talked about the sound issues on this show, how you
watch anything on HBO.
You can't, you can't make out what people are saying without subtitles.
And it's kind of the same thing with movies.
We're getting scripts that are, you know, this isn't like a half baked script
where it's not like somebody put effort forth or something, but there are just
too many details where you're looking at Wikipedia to find out like basic plot
points, not confusing or esoteric or science fiction or like just what we're
talking about.
Where is she and who is she talking to?
Yeah, it bothered me.
I also have a problem with a lack of justification.
It's like you're showing a girl who is being completely
domineered by her mother.
And yet when she's freed of that, because her mother goes into the
hospital tragically, albeit, but she then says I have to finish the movie for her.
It's a guys show me one scene where we can see that she gives a fuck about her
mother to do this.
It's not enough to just say, well, you know, that's how it goes in an abusive
relationship.
Sometimes you just do this or whatever, or maybe they loved each other and now
the mother's abusive or whatever.
There's a lot of ways.
We don't always fuck off, man.
Tell a story.
You know, you mentioned David Mamet.
David Mamet will do vague dialogue, but David Mamet always has a beginning, a
middle and an end.
Not always.
Oh, I wasn't criticizing Mamet.
I was saying people can't do it.
I'm saying, though, it's like just now what you and I just did, that annoying
little exchange, that's like what you're starting to see in movies.
No, that's and then the other guy will go, but that's what I'm saying.
But that's and it's like, I know what you're doing, but you don't have the gift.
Yeah, so it's like, it's like, yeah, if you're going to have like the vague
mentions of, you know, Mitch and Murray and the when we were back when we were
selling Glengarry Highlands and, you know, and all these vague references to
these things and people you never see or meet or whatever, then you got to have
a twist at the end where where Jack Lemmon gets busted for robbing the office.
It's like have something to work towards here.
I don't fucking understand.
Yeah.
And even if even if the you don't love me anymore, you know, somebody could
explain to me exactly what happened at the end.
Fine.
Why do I care?
I don't care.
Why do I give a shit?
Right before we sat down here.
Yeah.
I Googled ending of stop motion explained.
I read one kind of like, okay, here's what it is.
And I read one kind of crackpot theory that involved abortion and all kinds of other shit.
And the truth is I didn't give a fuck.
If you can watch a full hour and a half movie and in the moment,
truly not even think I need to look up what just happened.
I was like, I don't get this, but I'm going to bed.
I only did it because I was about to do this podcast looked into like
what was happening at the ending.
You don't care.
And they give you nothing to care about.
Characters are paper thin, not saying the performances are bad, but
the relationships are not sketched out properly.
It's just it's like a sketch of a movie.
And if they had put as much or even half as much into the script as they did
into the stop motion might have been something amazing because there are elements here.
Of a very, very cool movie, but it's just not it.
Yeah, it's a bummer.
It's a bummer, but folks.
So we don't add an end on such a sad note.
Yeah.
I'm going to take us.
No, I'm going to take us to a little place where a man by the name of Rex lives.
Read to you.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
Oh, that reminds me of my review above.
I got to read.
Go ahead.
This mean old bitch.
His his his title for the Pullman review.
Yeah.
Chris Pine movie Pullman.
This could be the greatest.
Rex Reed's had some fantastic titles for reviews and we've read them.
This is probably this is it.
I don't think he's topping this one.
You ready?
Yeah.
Was Pullman written with crayons?
Oh, wow.
Chris Pine is a hunk, not a director.
Pine in a robe.
Coffee reading that at his table.
Oh, boy.
I'm just going to read some sentences that jumped out at me.
Pullman, a stinker that marks the hopeless directorial debut of Hollywood
heartthrob Chris Pine, who also wrote the idiotic screenplay.
It was shot in 22 days and it looks it.
He only does quips now, like he's just a quipster.
There's nothing there.
There's no substance.
Not only is it the worst movie I've seen this year, this dog is one of the worst movies ever made.
Uh, this is my favorite line.
He goes through the cast, uh, cause he's like shocked that all these people
agreed to do this movie.
Jennifer Jason Lee, Danny Vito.
Then he goes, and that Benning comma who doesn't need the money.
But the others do.
Interesting, Rex.
It's very funny.
Uh, zero out of four stars.
Zero out of four stars.
Uh, I can't believe they still let him sell, let him write these things.
Well, this movie is supposedly, this is one of the worst.
Yeah.
I can't, the two movies I'm most excited to see this year are pool man and uh, mega
lop, whatever the fuck it's called.
I can't wait to see these two movies.
Well, you know how near the end of the unfrosted press tour, a couple interviewers were kind of
like hinting.
So this wasn't super critically acclaimed or whatever.
From the very first interview I saw about pool man with Chris pine, everyone he talked
to was like, let's talk about the reviews.
Like, I mean, they, it's, it's bad.
It got like a zero point zero, I believe.
And I wanted to read to, to close, uh, this is from varieties review of the new Kevin
Costner film horizon, which is currently losing a tremendous amount of money at the
box office to the extent that they have now delayed part two.
The bummer, right?
That's the, this is the one that I thought actually looked good, but it's got the kid
in it.
That's like manicured with like the blonde bleach blonde hair.
Right.
I was rooting for it.
I I'll still see it, but here we go.
During the last hour of horizon, a man sitting several rows behind me descended the steps
in the dark theater, spilled his half full bucket of popcorn midway down, reached to
pick it up, but was interrupted when he let out an audible fart.
At this point, he abandoned the bucket and hustled to the door.
If only horizon matched that level of compact storytelling and wit,
featuring a memorable character facing challenging odds.
That's a very good review.
Very good, bad review.
That could be the best review I've ever heard.
Yeah.
It's up there with Ebert's classics.
Um, his, uh, his compilation of bad reviews is great.
I will say you start, uh, working in this business.
A bad review is harder and harder to get out of your mouth.
It's hard.
It's hard to criticize others because you know how hard it is.
And it's the only times I've ever thought I would love to stop doing this podcast or
that of me thinking, say somebody's going to hear it or B boy, I'm just putting out
more negativity into the world.
And this is such a hard business, but then I keep doing it.
So you're welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
Ditto, ditto Walsh, uh, folks.
And that's Reed's motto too.
He's going to keep doing it until he dies.
He's in it till he's 86.
He's still going.
Um, honestly, probably a one bedroom apartment on the upper East side that he's had since
1974.
And I bet it is.
It looks like Phyllis Diller threw up in it.
Like just like, you know, pillars and pink fucking flamingos and you know,
every surface smells like nicotine.
I think Reed's a smoker is my guess as well.
I don't know why I think that.
I just think it, um, we'll be back with, uh, long legs, I believe long legs and, uh, and
then probably, probably, uh, the fall guy, but, uh, that's it folks.
Yes.
I haven't been pumped about something like long legs in a long time.
I've just, I've been hearing nothing, but great things and silence of the lambs
comparisons.
All I needed to hear.
We will be back.
We are on, uh, Instagram at see you and help pod.
I am at the Patrick Walsh to miss Pat show.
Season four is available on BET plus.
And, uh, we got two more episodes coming this month.
As Joe said, the new, uh, solo movie corner is up as well.
See you next time.
And see you in hell.