Welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast reviewing the flicks you like to watch are
sci -fi all of that my name is Jota Rosa and my name is Patrick Walsh today we are
doing one of the most disturbing horror films of recent years talking about
big screen adaptation of Andrew Lloyd Webber's cats you sort of promised
this you know that we were gonna do it and it just never happened it's always on
our list and we just don't do it I thought oh shoot you know I saw this thing
eight months ago I'm gonna have to rewatch it and then I realized I remember
every single second and it's embedded in my brain it's it's a wild ride we'll
get to it soon enough because as you all know we don't we don't really you know
spend a heavy heavy amount of time on each episode talking about the movie
on hand but this is one where we're gonna really need to kind of sit back yeah
you know I actually would love to kick off with a fast news psycho before we get
into anything here please I'm curious I texted this to you the other night but
based on your response I wasn't sure how you what your opinion was on it I saw
that on HBO Max the movie blazing saddles is now being shown with a disclaimer
yeah I when I said sure I meant like yeah it's just a matter of time yeah there's
more to come I mean here's the thing we all say that you know this sort of
sensitivity culture whatever you want to call it I hate calling it PC culture
because that's such a trigger phrase anymore it's like saying snowflake or
something like that right but we all say the sensitivity culture isn't gonna get
out of hand and it's not it is it is and here's why I understand that racial harsh
racial language even if it's in the form of humor can be a triggering thing for
somebody and might be something you want to warn the viewer about I understand
that so just as you put a disclaimer up on the screen before an R -rated film
and under it it says this movie is rated R for nudity extreme violence whatever it
is I totally get if in there you also put strong racial language or whatever that
makes sense to me what they did here does not make sense to me and I think this is
crazy and I want to read you an excerpt from the disclaimer that was added to
this thing so a woman with the last name of Stuart comes out she is I think she
works a Turner classic movies she says about blazing saddles as the storyline
implies the issue of race is front and center in blazing saddles and racist
language and attitudes pervade the film but those attitudes are espoused by
characters who are portrayed here as explicitly small -minded ignorant bigots she
concludes by noting the real and much more enlightened perspective is provided
by the main characters played by Cleveland little and Gene Wilder so we're at a
point now we're we're explaining to the audience how to understand the film isn't
that kind of the point of a work of art isn't the point if if you watched for
instance my my my I was talking to my mom today about do the right thing she's
never seen it and I was telling her what a great movie I thought it was and how
she might enjoy but what I didn't do was go you know mom now here's the thing the
point of the movie is that because of these underlying racial tensions right
things come to a head on a hot summer day and at the end of it you're supposed to
feel conflicted about who you exactly agreed and disagreed with maybe you found
flaws and and positives in every what the fuck man you don't do that let people
what you you're they're saying in the disclaimer for blazing saddles both sides
are represented here let the viewer figure it out for themselves it's crazy to
me when I saw that they were putting that disclaimer on blazing saddles I was like
yeah fine they're gonna do this with a lot of movies but now that I hear what it
actually is that's nuts to me that's like standing next to a painting at an
argument being like you know this one's about his issue with his mom yeah
something like that it's that is crazy especially considering that even in
1975 when the blazing saddles come out so 74 I think Richard prior is credited
as a writer on this movie I mean they they went out this wasn't five white
guys sitting around writing about you know racial issues they brought in Richard
prior so it is very odd to just say like yeah things were different when this
was met because the movie in watching all of Mel Brooks movies recently there's
all kinds of issues with all of them but blazing saddles definitely the tar in the
right place and is telling an audience from almost 50 years ago how stupid racism
it's yeah and it's to say like hey I just don't know how they're deciding which
movies do it on and which movies not to do it on it makes no sense I think they're
picking flagship movies yeah and their fingers crossed people just don't notice
the other ones I mean if you watch for instance the golden girls yeah as
religiously as I do and have throughout most of my adult life yeah and I also grew
up on the show you know the the big topic of that you play Blanche's niece on the
show as well yes yes yeah yeah the Denise yeah was the character
Denise yeah yeah it didn't know it was just Denise it was spelled D .A. Space
yeah okay whoo why aren't we right a sitcom anyway the you know the the the story
regarding this stuff with that show is they pulled an episode there's an episode
where Dorothy's son is marrying an older woman the older woman is also black
Dorothy doesn't want her son to marry the woman because she's too old for her son
and she thinks it's a mistake black the black woman's family doesn't want her to
marry Dorothy son because she's not black right challenging issue they handle it
very well it's very funny and then there's a gag in it where Rose and Blanche do
mud masks and come out and they have brown stuff on their face and it's sort of
like a black face joke or whatever so anyway they pulled this episode because they
thought it was too offensive or who they the powers the mysterious powers to be I've
been rewatching the show throughout quarantine because it makes me happy and you
know whatever it's a nice relief release for me and and there was the one
yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean sexually there are so many other things in so many
other episodes yeah that are so much more offensive than this gag they do in this
episode and by the way there's no mention of when they pulled the episode of like
we also don't think it's appropriate that the black lady hates the white man
for just because he's white that never gets mentioned right so so and you're
watching this thing I mean I was watching it the other day I think I told you
this I've definitely told you this joke there's a joke on one episode where they're
doing meals on wheels and they're you know the the gag is everybody they're
delivering to is very old and out of step and they haven't been out of their
apartment in years and Sophia is bringing Dorothy into one of the apartment and
she goes you'll get along with this lady fine just remember two things something
something something and Jews run the world right that's a joke I mean if
they're not going to pull that up so my point is I'm watching the show and I'm
going you if you're going to play by this rule that you're playing by now with
this one episode you're going to have to pull this entire show yeah eventually
every single thing is going to come out as offensive or problematic or whatever
and it's going to have to be pulled and at the end of the day which is the nature of
the beast because times change you can't you know birth of a nation is a
disgusting movie you know celebrating the Cluclux plan it was also one of the
first movies ever made so it's like I don't know you can't expect people in
1919 to share the same beliefs as people in 2020 it doesn't make any sense and I
don't think people are stupid enough that they need the disclaimer when I watch
birth of a nation when I was 10 years old because I was obsessed with film
history I'm 10 years old watching this thing and I wasn't like oh wait a minute
the Cluclux plans good right watching watching this old silent movie with
somebody playing hype organ in the background of it I wasn't like okay I should
use this in my day -to -day life and you know put a sheet on and then write a
horse through town so I don't know how they don't trust adult human beings to know
the difference and to know that there are different more as and values in
different times it doesn't make any sense you we don't need you to tell us it's
wrong we know it's wrong and then we can choose to watch it or not be entertained
or not make our own decisions I think it's fucked up and it's going to be a
very slippery slope for quite some time well and that's the thing you you don't
erase history you learn from it you keep it around and you learn from it
Spike Lee shows birth of a nation as a tenured NYU professor to his classes in
filmmaking right because he feels that it's a film people need to know about
and I'm sure that is mostly a social commentary and you know know that this
is something that people thought was okay at one time and speaking to the
racism of it all and I wouldn't be surprised if he also was like that said this
is a marvel of filmmaking for 1919 you know what I mean like I don't know it's
also there's also the further discussion that grit DW Griffith followed birth of
a nation with a film called intolerance where he sunk all of the money of the
profits he made from birth of a nation into a massive movie that consisted of
inner I don't know if they were intertwining but it was four stories that about how
human intolerance leads to tragedy so then now this discussion is even bigger
and now you get into well what was he saying with birth of a nation is he racist
was that the point or was he putting a thing in front of you and saying this is
racist how does it make you think I don't know I'm not fucking DW Griffith the
point is is we should be allowed to discuss these things and discuss them from
what we take away from them and not putting them inside of this padding and
this this this flowery packaging that's letting you know if you interpret it
any other way aside from the way we're explaining it to you you're wrong and
possibly a fucked up human being yeah you know I a movie that had a movie that
had no warning was where's Papa which I talked about in the last episode you
know like and by the way I actually what I said was not as bad as what it was
Garrett Morse's character says they're like you guys are gonna gang rape this
woman and his line is it's in our heritage wow okay so there is no there's not
even room for interpretation on that yeah do you know Garrett I mean I know you
know Garrett you know well enough to like text him and say I saw this this is
wild like what what are your thoughts yeah Garrett is like in his early 90s so I
don't know if you would remember doing it he was very sharp when I last saw him
which was over five years ago but you know he's very vocal about having issues with
a lot of the stuff he's done in his life and he found the SNL crew to be very
racist and to like waste his talent and etc so I'm sure he knew during that
scene that something was amiss but he might have thought you know Carl Reiner is
this is this boundary pushing guy and whatever else and there's some spin on it
but watching it now the spin is not there are you sure yeah yeah I would
imagine I haven't seen it but the way he described it yes that's that's how it
sounds and this aired on Turner Classic movies at 7 p .m so I for HBO Max now to
have done this on two films blazing saddles and go with the wind it's like what
who's who's gonna be doing the evaluating going forward and also I think
that's a shame that that's the first way a kid is gonna see these movies you
know if you're 13 you're really in the comedy and your dad's like you got to
check out blazing saddles man which is what happened to me you know my my mine
was blown by the farting around the campfire scene you know I was like oh my
god I had never heard about any of it so to have your first taste of it be by
the way a very somber this film you're about to see you know it you know it's a
shame because however a movie is described to you before you watch it can't help
but impact the way you watch it and to have it viewed as something that is
shameful or wrong or bad and put that taste in your head especially at a time
when all these kids coming up are super woke which is cool don't give me wrong
no it's not it depends on the level of woe yeah yeah certainly I mean like you're
going in now with your arms folded to watch one of the most famous and beloved
comedies of all time and you're going in not in oh I can't wait to see this funny
thing you're going in with I can't wait to see how racist this piece of shit is
I just think it's a it's that it's that it's it's it's what George
Carlin once referred to as left -wing paternalism you know it's it's like
come on guys like if I if if you were talk if you were giving me that disclaimer to
protect me yeah as the person who may or may not get racially offended by this my
reaction to that would be like fuck you dude yeah exactly dare you talk down and
pamper to me and pamper me like this and and coddle me like fuck you so it becomes
that classic thing of now the solution to the problem is as bad as the problem
it it just did a completely different direction you know I don't know if you saw a
viral video my friends Ryan and Danny did it or it was like woke guy and racist
guy best friends or whatever and they're saying the same thing back and forth it
blew up on the internet it did really well it's hilarious but it's it's it's you
know or it's like that version of it's always sunny or that episode of it's
always sunny where they try to solve the bathroom crisis and they get to the
point with like the unisex bathrooms thing where they're like okay what if we
just had this bathroom for straight white men and then everybody else has to
use this one and we say this is for minorities and they're like no that's that's
racist and they're like how is it racist it's special we're treating them but it
becomes that absurdity where it's like guys what are we doing here what are we doing
here it's not fixing anything it's not helping anything anyway so we'll see how
it goes but yeah I agree with you to have somebody's first experience in
watching this film at the very least become a thing where they're saying oh I
guess something's wrong if I'm watching this like we're at a terrible terrible
terrible thing to to put into somebody said or you hope that humanity prevails
and and then people say you know what go fuck yourself you know it's like I told
you I bought the witches or sorry the devils and I bought the 120 days of
Sodom and yeah you know you read reviews of those and some of the reviews are
like it's the most revolting movie ever made and it's horrible this that's not
gonna make me go I'm judging it now through that lens that made me go well I
want to own it before they ban it you know sure I want to buy birth of a
nation not because I want to even watch birth of a nation I mean I want to just
for historical purposes it film purposes just to say yeah I saw this movie that
obviously has played a very significant role in cinema for several different
reasons yeah but I don't feel a need to own it the only reason I want to own it is
because they're going to fucking probably ban it at some point and I think
that's crazy yeah I mean a sort of a side screaming in that factors right into
this is deeply troubling I'll read you here from the digital bits where I used
to do some writing I used to write for DVD verdict, Cinematical and the
digital bits can I predict what this is gonna be yeah the kindergarten cop
getting pulled from the Portland no we can talk about that so we can talk about
that we talked about it at nauseam or without a country this week yeah I mean the
cop stuff and you know I I go on letterboxed and stuff too and somebody was
reviewing some movie were like I didn't even remember there being a cop
presence in it and it was like trigger warning there's cops in it that are
that are not treated like their animals or something and I was like okay like
I think there are people who want lethal weapon to have a disclaimer saying
there are police that you're supposed to like in this movie yeah I think people
want that now and yeah they do really hope it doesn't have whereas another way to
go would be the star of this movie is notably anti -Semitic you know are we
gonna start doing that I don't know I'm concerned but I don't know this
article says I'm really this this was some very trouble in news to me in
essence my sources said that the guy who wrote this was I'm sorry Bill Hunt the
editor in chief of the digital bits in essence my sources said beyond new
released theatrical titles animated fair from Disney and Pixar or Star Wars and
Marvel related projects there are no plans at Disney which also means Fox by
the way because Disney owns Fox oh and by the way if I can just interject quickly I'm
sorry I needed to rail you but if I can just I'm gonna give myself a nice pat on
the back for all the times on this show where I said Marvel movies are Trump a
hundred percent and now your precious fucking Disney has purchased Fox news so
let's see a boycott your precious fucking Marvel movies now everybody as you
tell everybody they can't watch anything that has anything to do at all with Fox
news or support anything Fox related there goes your nice fucking avenger films
everyone enjoy it they won't do it because they only want to ban things they
weren't gonna watch anyone yeah go ahead so yeah outside of Disney and Pixar
Star Wars and Marvel there are no plans at Disney or Fox 20th Century Fox one of
the oldest movie studios in America no plans going forward to release titles on
physical media meaning DVD Blu -ray 4k future releases for all Disney and Fox
projects will be 4k digital only now there are a lot of people there are
probably people listening to this who are like I only watched up streaming I
don't care for me and it's not just because I have this massive collection and
also I know for Joe who has a big collection as well collecting these things is a
big part of my life you know I love having a collection of physical media I
love I know you know it used to be you check the release date so when are we
getting that new abyss Blu -ray which isn't gonna happen now when the true
lies James Cameron was supposed to be working on something forever and it's never
been released on Blu -ray the abyss or true lies movies that have huge fans that
would look amazing in the format or were not available and now won't come out
because they're Fox properties and that to me is a real bummer that now if I want
to sit back and watch the abyss let's say or anything I'm going to have to
either watch it on my DVD which can't help but look antiquated at this point or I'm
going to have to pay 399 to stream and not own or owned in the cloud not even do
the cloud a movie and I just think that such a shame again it is Disney and Fox
deciding what we get to see what we get to watch and forcing us now to line
their pockets and keep this empire of streaming going and it's completely this
isn't like when VHS became DVD you know there's a new format I guess I guess it
is in a way and maybe I'm an old man but there's just something about not being
able to have something in your hand that feels like book burn to me it feels
gross and bad and now they're going to start using as an excuse like okay
we're never going to put that out on Blu -ray because it's got a good portrayal of
cops they know these other reasons now they can use to not release things and it's
it's a shame it's just a shame it's the end of an era it's this is the start of
it but it's just a matter of time I by the end of this year it'll be Warner
Brothers outside of DC and Batman is not going to release any more Blu -rays and
DVDs it's all coming and I think it sucks I think it really sucks and
absolutely sucks and you're you don't sound like an old man what you sound like
is somebody who is recognizing the no -ownership culture we are charging
towards I mean it's like anybody who reads the news even kind of and knows
anything about China for instance which is a very no -ownership society knows
that that's where we're headed towards every every single thing in your life is
moving towards a lease -based construct they tell you not to buy property now
because renting is easier renting is cheaper renting is more affordable rent
things less headaches every one of your entertainment services is a monthly charge
for streaming that can go away at any minute real quick they tell you that right
rent rent and now look at how most of the country is absolutely fucked now
they're at power now people are gonna be evicted people who thought they had
their shit together are gonna be homeless exactly because they don't know
anything exactly yeah you actually are in better shape now if you have a mortgage
than if you're renting because your mortgage can at least postpone payments your rent
can't you have a lease it ends so there's those two things every one of your
apps on your phone if you notice now you don't purchase an app anymore you rented
every month car car ownership is going out the window it's all leasing now with
vehicles they make the leasing packages so so so much more affordable than a
purchase package it's going away it's all look at your phone don't buy the phone
just pay a fee for it every month and then you can trade it in whenever you feel
like it this is where everything is going and everybody and my I've been guilty
this myself everything you just said be it the phone be it be it any of this
stuff leasing a car in the moment when you're sitting across that desk from the
guy at AT &T or the guy at the Prius dealership or whatever it may be
presents this to you like it's to your benefit and it took me becoming a
nearly 40 -year -old man to not be so naive and have my head up my ass and go
everything anyone does in this sort of exchange where somebody is trying to
sell me on something benefits them they are never doing something they might do
the best you can do is something that benefits you both equally but 99 % of the
time it is all to their benefit no matter how they how they put it to you and
this this announcement to me was kind of like we got a year left of owning my
favorite thing which is a movie collection I love that I've loved it since I was a
kid first first thing I spent my money was movie and music the music industry is
already done you know bands who are hugely successful can't make a time Joe you
know it from the stand -up industry you I saw Lori Kilmarton who's
extremely funny on Twitter talking about how she's a 20 plus year comedy veteran
who can't get a nibble on this special that she's reported you know I'm going
all over the place but it is just this culture where they have taken they have
taken away people's ability to monetize their life their career and it's all
across the arts certain people always will and always will be successful and
keep making money but for the people coming up they control everything in my
business this pandemic now the next thing I sell let's say I sell a script and
you know let's let's say they're gonna pay me let's say my normal rate would be
$10 ,000 for a script I'm obviously making up numbers then what they're
doing now is they're gonna say yeah we want to buy your script we'd like to pay
you $5 ,000 to do it and you go well wait a minute what are you talking about my
rate is 10 I have to at least make the 10 that is my job description and they're
gonna say you know the pandemic just wiped a sound yeah of course that's not
true that Disney is wiped out of cash because they had a bad three months but I
think you know what Trump is doing trickles all the way down and Disney and Fox
and everywhere else acts like oh Trump's the worst and he's a knight and what he is
doing they are using that business model to do it as well they are just gonna
say hey sorry we don't have any more money you're gonna say well shit do I want
that $5 ,000 or do I want nothing I guess I'll take the $5 ,000 then five years
now when knock on wood the pandemic is over and nobody even remembers that this
happened I'm gonna go in and try to sell a script and they're gonna go yeah we'll
give you $5 ,000 for that hundred percent but wait my rate is 10 I know we we made
the deal last time because you said the pandemic had you fucked up
pandemics over you're thriving now you're doing well right but we paid you five
last time we know you'll take five so you're gonna take five or else you're gonna
get nothing and I'll go well shit but I want to keep my house yeah I'll do it and it
all doesn't seem connected but it is and I'm becoming like Alex Jones now on
this podcast but when I am looking at at the way this world is going down
when I'm looking at the way politicians on down the line are using what this
horrible thing that is happening to our country right now to fuck us over now
and for the rest of our lives it is it gets hard to get out of bed you know it
really does know how fucked over we all are by the small amount of people who
own all the wealth in this country I'm not a desktop man there are people way worse
off than me and I'm well well aware of that and I'm thankful for what I do at but
they want to make sure that everyone is fucked except for this small group of
people and that goes for politics entertainment industry comedy industry music
industry etc etc one of my favorite little bands is the new pornographers this
guy Paul Newman who was a great guy one of the in my opinion one of the best living
songwriters certainly pop songwriters if you follow this guy on Twitter he
Nico Kase is another one who's in new pornographers and also a country singer
and a beautiful voice they talk all the time about how they are barely making ends
me yeah Nico Kase has a very I thought a very successful solo
career and she's in the new pornographers which I thought were a very successful
indie band they can't make ends meet they can have millions and millions of
streams on Spotify and they're not getting you know a hundred bucks each month it's
sick sick it is sick and it's very unfortunate because you get it from the
conservatives on the political side of things and you get it from the liberals on
the entertainment side of things nobody is your friend nobody is in your corner
nobody's looking out for you and I would say this if you can take their money and
you can use their money then do it if you have the opportunity to use somebody
else's money do it but everybody listening to this right now and I'm echoing
now the words of the great joe bob and so did this conversation about the
importance of owning physical media but if you are out there and you want to do
something for yourself go and do it you don't need their permission anymore they
don't give a shit about you they're not looking out for you you don't need
their permission it's why I stepped back from standup indefinitely because I
don't need anymore to go out and deal with these people that want to underpay me
to put myself quite frankly in harm's way not just talking about with the
pandemic and and the potential of getting sick from something also the fact that
we're living in a fucking pressure cooker and violence is on the rise
everywhere because people are going out of their minds because their lives are
falling apart and we're in the middle of the heatwave summer I don't want to be a
part of it I have no interest so what do I do I turn around I focus on podcasting
okay I am very lucky that I've had 20 years of standup comedy under my belt and
it's a little bit easier for me to launch a podcast then maybe it is for some
other people but I am not famous I am not a big celebrity I do not have millions
of followers and fans that I can rely on I have to get out there and pound the
payment like anybody else okay and I'm telling you I made a very conscious
decision to take a step back from this public thing from this being at the
mercy of this industry thing and most importantly getting wrapped up in all the
bullshit of the social media aspects up and all and said I'm gonna do it for
myself I'm not playing ball with these people anymore and of course every single
offer I've had come in that has come from one of the traditional avenues has been
terrible yeah terrible yeah insultingly terrible and when you say this isn't really
great and you try to be graceful about it or whatever you kind of get told
tough shit take it or leave it and you know what I'll leave it I don't I'd rather
not leave my house man I don't know what you know fuck it so I completely agree
I can't stress enough if you want to do something for yourself you can do it for
yourself right now there are ways patreon it's out there go fund me it's out
there Venmo there are all these ways and methods and things where you can
raise money and deliver whatever your product is directly to people who
want it directly to them you know when we were growing up Pat and I it was you know
you wanted to make a direct a low budget film it was a direct video film and then
that got put on the shelf in a blockbuster video or West Coast video next to all the
blockbusters that came out that year and it got buried and it was hard to find it
and it was in a sea of whatever now you have something like patreon that you
can literally go on or go fund me literally or Kickstarter literally go on and
say this is exactly what I am making here's exactly what it will cost are you
interested and people that are only interested in that specific thing will say
yes I am and and hopefully help you get to your goal it's it's it's we're back we're
back to the to the to the to the to the to the design of the 1980s with
record labels in the music industry now is your time to start your alternative
tentacles or your epitaph records or your discord records now is the time you
can be the independent punk label again and you can say fuck you to all the
silvery shiny bullshit that the industry is trying to tell you is the only way
and we are in the arts but you can apply this to whatever industry you are in
of course I mean people are always trying to fuck you over it's just something
it's important to remember at all times and another and this is this is not a
personal thing but NBC Universal yet another one of these big conglomerates has in
the past year offered two of my friends deals to write for their shows that
that they had to turn down even though their lives are bad right now and like
they need money because it would have so destroyed their quote in writing you
have a quote and each time you're supposed to maintain or go up on your quote it's
what keeps people in this business see you you move up and people are getting
offers well below their quote and not knowing what to do about it and in both
cases NBC Universal blamed in one case the pandemic in one case they were like
we just don't make those kind of deals anymore we just don't kind of have that
money in the budget anymore and a simple look online says that Mike
sure who is the guy who worked on the American office and also created and ran
the good place on NBC NBC Universal cut a deal for him right before we were told
by the writers guilt to fire our agents by the way and Mike sure is on Twitter all
the time to tell some people they got to fire their agents and taking these
big stands and whatever else Michael sure was given a deal right before this
happened for five years at $25 million a year that is beyond basketball player
numbers and the good place was not some huge hit you know he they are like we
don't have any money and they're giving it to somebody else so all it's and this
Mike sure is the most liberal guy in the world and it's stupid of me to even go
after him and I'm not but what I'm saying is they're furious about Trump right
please oh they're furious about how the government gets all the money and we get
nothing they're furious about how giant bailouts are given to corporations and
small businesses are given nothing and they're talking about it on Twitter all day
every day meanwhile this man is making $125 billion over the course of five
years and anyone else who tries to sell a show or has a great idea or anything
else is told we don't have any money the exact same thing that is going on in
America at large this guy either can't see it or refuses to look at it and it's
just the problem with the business and it's everybody shut Shonda Rhymes and all
these people Shonda Rhymes deserves it the greatest phrase anatomy and all this
shit she deserves everything she gets but you can't be online talking about how
unfair it is that people control all the wealth when you are making a billion
dollars and most other writers are being told we're out of money they're out of
money they're not out of money A but if they're out of money they're out of money
because it is all going to you so hopefully you're paying that forward if not you
know we're doomed we're doomed and I think we are doomed and it's too late but man
what a dark podcast let's turn that to me
well that's terrible time why don't we just beeline past the the other
segments today and just go right into cats let's lighten this up a little bit
get us chocolate cats we don't have to always do every segment I
saw cats my birthday this year was January 5th it's every year January 7th
wait was it you're one of those floating birthday no I don't not only leave
beer baby okay woke up Sunday morning went with my beer friend Ian up to the
Burbank movie theater one of the last movies I saw on theater and we saw cats at
10 am I had heard tell of all these screenings where people are going nuts
laughing they had like rocky horror style screenings of this thing and
everybody's gone nuts and laughing I had sort of the worst case scenario but it
wound up being wonderfully uncomfortable and that it was a sold -out house that
seemed very interested in watching cats and nobody was really laughing but
little by little people started turning to their grandma whoever they were there
with it going what the fuck is going on and you will say that at least once a
minute while watching cats I I really got one over when I saw cats because I was in
a hotel room I think the last time I was on the road I was in a hotel room in if I
remember correctly Michigan outside of what's it called falls in Michigan
something falls we're gilded the gilderradner festival happens I don't I don't
fucking remember anyway the point is no rapid falls okay I think it's called
rapid falls anyway I was there and it was my last night before I was coming home
and I got a bunch of burger king and went back to my room and said all right I'm
just gonna kind of sit here get a good night's sleep after I eat this tranquilizer
food and watch a movie in the room and there was something wrong with the I
remember what it was I was trying to do the thing where you can now hook your
Netflix up to the TV right your computer whatever and it didn't work yeah
yeah and they said well we can send somebody up to the room and I said I don't
want anybody to come up to the room it's midnight in bed yeah and they set
grand Rapids Michigan that's what I meant to say thank you Mike anyway and I
said look your thing doesn't work you should give me one of your paper
movie's for free and they said okay pick whatever you want we won't charge it okay and I
said I got a bag of burger king and I am put on cats yeah I got to see cats for free
uh that's the way to see it yeah and I immediately within two minutes had my phone out
taking down notes because I was like this is this goes beyond anything I could have
ever expected I mean I can't believe how that's how I think this thing was it is it is one of those
fiasco's where any movie with this this budget and this level of special effects they're doing tests
early on to see what everything's gonna look like when they see that first cat human hybrid
in this movie you're like this looks wrong to me it is bad it's making me feel uncomfortable
I'm sweating for some reason how the studio didn't go no no no this is all wrong let's let's start
again at that point because this this thing if you'll remember they were rushing to finish special
effect shots while the movie was in theaters they're the first week of release you can see the actual
hands of the actors and not pause like Judy Dench's hands human hands were visible and they had to
fix them so they basically they sent the movie to theaters on Christmas and said by the way in a
week we're gonna send you a new edit of the film the cost of something like that or or the sonic
deal or whatever is in the tens of millions of dollar range and people have no money exactly
and it's all for cats yeah I mean it's a musical I could have given less of a shit about ever yeah
and it's I saw cats I went to the Fox Theater which is Saint Louis's where they get the Broadway
shows and I went with my buddy Ryan and his grandma and we kept looking at each other like is this
for real we're 13 couldn't believe how terrible it was until then the cats in these stained suits that
have been like on a hanger that they wear every day and get sweaty every fucking day these these
furry suits they come out in the audience they smell like shit and they treat you like a cat they're
nuzzling your head they're licking their hands and rubbing it on your face and I you know if his
grandma hadn't taken us I would have ran out of the goddamn theater it's always been a horrifying show
and it makes no sense I will say the my first thing thought with this movie is this is the most
special effects laden film I've ever seen in my life I it's the fakest looking movie I've ever seen
in my life as far as I could tell none of these actors were even in the movie it looks like they cut
magazine faces off of things and put them on top of CGI cat bodies it looks fucking crazy
and what struck me is so odd about that was that it is literally the opposite of what a Broadway show is
a Broadway show is all practical effects everything is being done live on the stage with contraptions
and gadgets and they have to design sets that move and spin and whatever and this did none of that
this was the most green screened not real thing I have ever seen in my life I mean this made
the Star Wars movies look like a fucking three camera sitcom okay it's crazy it's crazy yeah crazy
and they all look crazy starting with Idris Elba was downright to fucking terrifying I mean he would
be frightened he was frightening looking Judy Dench I don't know if her teeth are always that bad
and yellow or if it just looked bad against the cat suit but her teeth shook me to my core they're
getting close on these old lady British yellow teeth yep everyone in the movie is terrifying
but what people were doing what's interesting is it wasn't like what usually happens with something
like this which is oh fuck they ruined this masterpiece cats what happened was people are going
this was cats this was the show that's been on Broadway for 30 years and it's beloved anyone who
hadn't seen it was like oh my god so basically it was a double discovery of not only is this thing like
this bizarre secret in American culture where people have gone to see cats for decades despite it
not making any sense of being criminally insane but they also did it in the most awful way possible
they made every choice incorrectly and at the end it becomes sort of this fascinate you're not
watching it for entertainment per se you're watching it as if to say how did this many people
all think this was fine and it's you just don't understand every celebrity in the movie every single
celebrity in this movie is somebody that I have wanted to with the exception of Dame Judy Dench
is somebody I have wanted desperately to see go away for quite some time all right I'm talking to
top of the ladder followed by rebel Wilson yeah I dress out I'm tired of him being in every single
thing that comes out I'm sick of it Taylor Swift I mean let's go on and on and on now I studied
theater in college and as a mild mannered theater kid I guess you could say of sorts this is one of those
things and I would see stuff like this once in a while this is one of those things where I was like I get
why people want to beat up theater kids like this is it's so self -indulgent it's so pretentious it's so
look at us look at what we're doing and it sucks also I about 90 seconds into this movie I turn my head
to bite my wopper or whatever the hell I did and I looked back about a minute later completely lost I
had no idea what the fuck was going on something about we have to get to a dance and then a cat's
gonna send up into the sky or something I didn't know what the fuck was happening a ball I mean yeah
they the ending of it is where it really goes off the rails and after an hour and a half of you not
knowing what's going on it is just cats introducing themselves then one of them is selected to fly
on a chandelier hot air balloon up to cat heaven yep but even the basic rules of what the cat world and
cat heaven are are never made clear so whatever you want to do if you want to create some crazy world
and and make up so you people at least have to know the basics and you're never given the basics it's like
it's like you feel like you're a doll and you're going into this movie cats and you're like I don't
understand anything about the world of cats and they don't help you out rebel wilson I didn't think I
could find her more irritating yeah she comes into this thing as some kind of like slut cat or
something I just she's rolling all around she keeps spreading eagle all over the screen she's there's a
eating cockroaches which is disgusting it's and it's 20 minutes into the movie you have to look
away it's a gross yeah and then cordon shows up and it's just oh my god and cordon shows up you want
them immediately ripped apart by dogs that was all I could think of I wanted to see dog people come
in and rip James cord into pieces yeah and and at this I mean my god there's musicals then there's
musicals this fucking thing is just top to bottom one shit song after the neck I was like does
Andrew Lloyd Webber suck I guess he sucks does he of course he sucks I mean I don't know the
operas got some bangers but yeah he he sucks he's always sucked every song and cats is bad it's
almost seems spoken word some of them seem made up memory you know the big song from cats is a
classic melody it you know it's a show too but you remember it everyone knows every other song in
this thing just sounds like they're making it up as it goes it sounds like they put the camera on
and they're like just sing a song about how you're the the dandy cat and the guys like all right I'm
the dandy cat and they're like yeah cut it printed we got it none of the proportions in the film
make sense now there'll be next to like a shoe and it's the size of like a battleship yeah and
then they'll use a human size spoon like to eat with it it makes no sense none none the the scaling
of everything it I don't understand how Hollywood could fuck something up this badly I just don't
get it I do think it was always fucked up but I you know it's a shitty property to begin with but
but the every choice is so wrong and what you're saying about the uh the sizes as well it's like
nobody even had the basic discussions of like okay are these gonna be person size cats they're gonna
be regular size cats they're gonna be smaller they never had that tall so what you're saying is
exactly right at some points you'll see James Corden next to like a giant teacup right then in the
next scene he's eye to eye with a human right nothing makes any sense they didn't decide on basic
rules for this world so you wind and I had so many friends who got high to go see it it's one of the
few movies where you just don't need to it seems like you know it's guaranteed it's seeing this on
nightmares going to see cats there's sites in this that I'll remember forever because they're so
wrong everything about them is just not done right it's hard to put a finger on but everything about
it is wrong and makes you feel weird I would like to know what Tom Hopper the hooporks excuse me the
director of the film what his take on this is I wonder if it was just a studio disaster and from day
one he knew it was gonna be a problem and there was a lot of fighting and whatever but my god almighty
he wrote directed and produced this this guy is he made the Danish girl he made lame as a rob he made
the king speech he made the John Adams many series for each field this is a guy that knows what he
is doing yeah he makes a quality product I don't now grant it he's written very little this was the
first thing he's written but the writing wasn't necessarily the problem it was the execution of
everything yeah so I just don't know how you go from these award -winning nominated projects to
something this disastrous it is because when you when you when you have you when you direct a movie
that wins best picture a lot of people's brains break and they think everything they do will be
considered that great till the end of time and I would think this guy has a lot to do with the
blame of it I think anytime they tried to interfere he was probably like you know I won the best director
right mate because this seems like a director's vision this doesn't seem like something where
a bunch of books ruined it this sounds like somebody said this is exactly the movie I want to make
and he was completely wrong in terms of what America wanted my I believe my most popular
tweet of all time I wrote it the second cats ended in the theater not sure why cats didn't work it
follows a classic three -act structure act one cats introduce themselves act two cats continue to
introduce themselves act three unclear um that is how I feel about cats because every song is a cat
going I'm this kind of cat and they sing about it then when you get to the ball cats keep coming
out and saying I'm this type of cat me I'm this cat I'm the cat that does this then they die
I guess they all want they all want to die because they want to go to heaven there's something called
gelical cats which I guess means angelical but that's not made clear yeah it's it's confusing man
it's really confusing they uh I mean Jesus Christ but by the way what director goes musical
we need ray windstone yeah it made no sense why ray windstone must have just been in his trailer like
I got it maybe I just killed my agent at this point
I don't get it at all man I don't get it at all uh ray windstone being in there he's not a singer
and quite frankly uh neither is Judy Dench I mean this movie ends with Judy Dench singing directly to
camera uh and Judy Dench is one of our finest finest actors uh of all time uh she's just tremendous
but that doesn't mean she's right right right right for a musical this film ends with Judy Dench singing
directly to camera which is extremely uncomfortable not just because of the teeth as Pat mentioned
but because she can't sing she's just it's just not good uh here's another confusing
as far as I could tell Ian McKellen who's also in this wasn't even wearing makeup
yeah that was another confusing thing like some people had like Taylor Swift is unrecognizable in this
movie she's got so much cat makeup on her face you don't know who it is I had to look up which
catch he was because I was confused and then Ian McKellen shows up with literally like it looks like he
went to Halloween adventure and got cat ears and then walked out onto the set I don't even think they
put whiskers on it so yeah it's it's it's it's just confusing from every angle man I don't get it
he's not wearing makeup and other people have like CGI faces yes you know
um do you recall the oh by the way Judy Dench says her character old Deuteronomy is trans
based on what just her interpretation of the character she there's nothing about that in the
no okay she she thinks her cat's character is trans I'm trying to find do you remember the
monologue she has right before her terrible performance of the song where she talks about the
difference between dogs and cats I mean I remember it happening I don't remember what the hell she said
that's where the audience finally started laughing and just was like fuck oh here we go
so first your memory I'll jog and say a cat is not a dog with cats some say one rule is true don't
speak till you're spoken to myself I do not hold with that I say you should address a cat but
always bear in mind that he presents familiarity I mean this thing goes on and on and on look at the
lyrics of this song it's terrible you ready for this yes cats grossed 27 million dollars on a
budget of what uh in the United States uh worldwide total of 74 million against a production budget of
95 million calculated net loss of the film to be 130 million oh yeah if they're if they're saying
that's what the budget is I would double it not to mention wait when you are paying
animators who all hated Tom Hooper and they also they were treated like slave labor by the way over
the Christmas holidays as they tried to erase hands and replace them with paws that paying those people
double time to work 24 hour shifts I don't not to mention holiday pay that movie I bet almost broke
universal and yeah the only thing that helped them out was that it started getting this kind of cult
following but it's not a cult following like Rocky Horror where people have fun with songs and stuff
it was just kind of this it's not even so bad it's good it's a cult following like the room where
it's like exactly it's not going to make you any money this cult following of yours no it's just
going to do an animal drive -towel screening where you know people would show up in a in a black
sweatsuit and cat ears or whatever else okay so here's the thing okay this is what these dipshits do
when will these dipshits learn universal hope that the film would appeal to young women as a
counter programming against Star Wars rise of Skywalker hey dipshits young women love Star Wars
stop making things because you think people will like them make things that are good and everybody
will like it in different demographics that's how it works they emphasize swift and marketing
but Taylor Swift didn't promote the film to our fans as she only appeared for one song so that's
what you get to for book in a fucking celebrity who's got an ego and an agenda in your movie thinking
it's going to make your shit movie good and then she goes shove it up your ass I don't need your
fucking movie and you bite the bullet on it there you go there you go I want to look up some just
before we wrap this up I want to look up while you're looking whatever this is up I recently watched
six degrees of separation which I had never seen a good movie it is a good movie it's based on
play it's a little talky but it's a very young Will Smith's doctor Channing and Donald so
in a supporting role is Ian McCallum and in the early scenes of this movie a running joke is
Stocker Channing, Donald Sutherland and Ian McCallum talking about how ridiculous it is that somebody
in this fictional movie is making a movie of cats and it blew my mind I can't maybe somebody's already
found this out and put it online but Ian McCallum is sitting there in a room while there's lots of
dialogue about how the worst decision that they could think of fictionally in this movie is to make a
movie of cats the worst musical ever made that's great top critics on rotten tomatoes gave this
is a 20 % of rotten tomatoes I like to read these little reviews Christy Lamir or Lamir from
film week says it's just baffling and yet it must be seen
Ruman Alam I believe it said from New Republic said or how it is said from New Republic said
you might still want to know if it's a good movie but that is the wrong question
Richard Roper from Chicago Sun Time says as the trailer suggested the enduring stage musical is a
bad fit for the big screen and let's say we can find one more Stephanie Zach Zacharek from Time
Magazine says cats is terrible but it's also kind of great I think all of those are accurate because
it is if you have to say something nice about it it is bad in a way that no other movie has ever
been bad before and let's close it out with your boy Peter Travers throwing fire over the plate
this is an all star all awful screen take on the smash Broadway musical that easily scores as the
worst movie of the year and arguably the decade cats shouldn't happen to a dog zero out of five stars
all right Travers if you haven't seen cats it is sort of a ride of passage I do recommend and I don't
but it's something that everyone should see if you should be able to talk about it and also see it
with somebody so that you can look at each other and be like is this happening you won't believe
you're on my other question is where was the Garfield cambia why was James Gordon that's
splitting a lasagna with Garfield out of the dots somewhere I heard that he actually did catch Gordon
splitting a lasagna with an actual cat and then reprimanded him because it was the cat's lasagna
yeah yeah anyway Gordon I mean Gordon I can't anymore I can't he's I fit a wall that's all I got
to say yeah that's our show folks thanks for joining us thank you for subscribing to the new tier
these were your two bonus episodes for that tier I hope you enjoyed them I already plugged on the
other one I don't need to do it on this one that's it that's all I got to say we really appreciate
your support thank you yes thank you so much for coming on board to the new patreon's
we just want to reassure you again I know Emily wanted us to reassure you as well because she
hears a lot of the complaints and thank you Emily for feeling that we know that patreon is a glitchy
site and that sometimes you guys lose access to stuff thanks for letting us know but rest assured
we're fixing it we're never trying to take stuff away from you or fuck you over there be no benefit
to us at all for doing that so if you lose access to something for a couple of weeks listen to some
from the archives and rest assured that it will be back we're figuring it out most of the stuff should
already be fixed I'm the Patrick Wall should put her on Instagram we will be back with four new
episodes next month since there are no real movies being released in theaters I think I can expect
a classic or two Joe and I are planning on doing the phantasm series at some point doesn't mean
it's next month but brush up on your phantasm as you've never seen them going all the way from the
original to gravity yeah um probably a one cut of the dead at some point one cut of the dead yes
my movie corners are still going going on the on the patreon site and people still don't know
we're on patreon so if they're not in the facebook page make sure you let people know because
your word of mouth is all that keeps us going we don't have advertising anymore so thank you very much
we will see you next time and we will see you in hell