Welcome to we'll see you at hell it's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear
about those films you like to hear other men discuss my name is Joe. Oh what happened
nothing I was just trying to put a little you know you get you how many times if I said this
intro it gets you know I mean could I could I do it one week do it I don't give a shit
I give the viewers some reprieve from this disenchanted mumble that you kick off the show with
you can do it whenever you want I'll start doing an on with the pat yeah it's uh you know it's your
favorite guys when you want to watch a drama or a documentary Joe we'll see you in hell
oh I mean what if you're a newcomer to the show you'd be like oh I guess this is the podcast where
two guys talk about their plans to kill themselves now now nobody's gonna think that it's that's
ridiculous don't you be ridiculous now folks yeah I know you're always wondering what what
goes on and the Hollywood scenes and in the in the board rooms the back rooms I'd like to tell you
that today I had a kickoff call they love to use these terms that you don't hear anywhere else but
we're gonna do a kickoff call yeah for a project I started working on in September yep
yeah kickoff call now now have I received a sent not one sent mm -hmm it's a nightmare so now I'm
gonna take this pitch out and if it sells I'll make money the pitch will go out probably in July
it's always two months three months later than you expect it to go out the pitch is ready
we have the kickoff call everyone's like yeah we pretty much agree the pitch is ready
and then it's like we'll probably take it out what do you think guys late July
what a waste then I got to just sweat that whole week with the anxiety of like
if I don't sell this not only do I have no money coming in but I have wasted a full year of my
life on something that's just not gonna happen yeah and by the way I love all the people involved with
this they've been it been wonderful it's just the nature of the bitch and it's getting worse by
the minute yeah I got an email from a somewhat reputable film company today telling me huh
vivid video vivid telling me that it was an email to my manager tell me they were gonna pass on my
script this is the second one I've gotten it took them both companies two of the companies we've
set reached out to it took them a full two months to respond yeah with hey love the script doubt
it's gonna cut through though at this point we're really bought you know the typical shit they always
say you're just like you know what I'll go get a hundred thousand dollars from some distant
ant I didn't know I had shoot the goddamn thing myself on video like I don't even feel like dealing
with it man it's the way to do it I mean a mackle honey if you'll remember we ran into him at that
always sunny party and he was screaming in your face like you do it yourself with your you make it
in a way he was talking about something completely different but like that's what those guys don't
get it's like they had they had that cockiness coming out the gate at like 23 and we're like throwing
their dick on the table nothing to lose and they've they've had complete creative freedom for like
20 years and that that just doesn't happen also too you make it yourself coming from a guy that
shot a seven minute pilot on video right and then managed to sell a TV show from it and then was
was taken out of the pilot as the director and replaced by somebody you know so it's easy it's always
easy I don't mean that to disrespect Rob I'm a big fan but like I think it's easy
when you when you're in the position of you know I've been at this a while and I've got millions and
you know right my thing caught fire you know it's very different from yeah I'm trying to get a feature film
made here this is you know but I don't know he is partly right I mean I I say it all the time why are
any of us putting ourselves at the mercy of Hollywood at this point but we are still to some extent
he's right I mean today they go in as funny as that little seven minute short was they don't sell
that show today I mean it's a lot of its luck a lot of it's been in the right place at the right time
and the people who've had success of course don't understand that things change and it's I mean
Charlie used to tell me on the on the Fox show Pat look him in the eye and say fuck you and then walk
away and I was like yeah Charlie you can do that you have a billion dollars and eight jobs
if I do it I will be immediately fired immediately fire you know yeah yeah no it's
a tough game out there you know what are you gonna do now Pat let me ask you a question are you
suffering from a lack of mask grief like so many Americans are right now since the CDC said you
could remove the masks outside people are are missing their mask now I haven't even seen that or
read that and I'm on Twitter what are you talking about is that a real deal yeah yeah it's a real
deal there's an article is it a real deal or is it something one nut job said and it gets reported
like this is happening now I read it well I didn't say it wasn't I don't know if it was written by
no no no it's a it's a thing it's like it's a thing that both conservative and liberal media are
commentating on liberal media I guess is referring to this as anti -science and conservative media is
referring to it as crazy liberals but yeah there apparently is a percentage of people out there
that want to keep the masks because it it feels to them that it keeps their anonymity up and
there and it makes them feel safe in public I mean people have lost their fucking minds I mean
guys you can't live inside your phone you have to interact with people it's a world and a society we
live in I mean Jesus God almighty man yeah no that that's nuts I what I would get is if somebody was
like I'm scared to take my mask off because now I've become incredibly scared and paranoid of
getting sick I get that but I don't get like you love the anonymity of the mask unless you're
Will Smith or something you know people said yeah it makes them feel safe from strangers it's
prevents people from interacting with them it prevents some women say it prevents men from
leering at them come on I mean it's just it's just a wild wild world we're living in these days man
it's it's just collapsing by the second but you know what can you do I mean
the leering is strange if a man's leering at you on the street odds are he's talking to you about
your body you know if a man is yelling at you from a window wiper uh cart hanging off a building
he's not seeing your lovely face and telling you how beautiful you are he's like nice ditch
sir nice ass and it's wrong I'm just saying take the mask off and get back honestly you gotta you
gotta get back yeah I mean I'm I'm out there I'm walking the streets I'm feeling fantastic I felt
yesterday I wouldn't got lunch with a friend and I felt not unlike when you're dating a girl for six
months and she's like let's drop the condom yeah you know if I I took it off and I was like oh yeah
this is great I love this in the Austin Powers voice though you did it you went yeah baby right yeah
that's right uh I think it's I think there are plenty of people out there that want to do terrible
things to other people and I think that's a terrible tragedy and I think it's a great shame
but I also think that this this thing we're talking about speaks to a self a self centeredness almost
that that everybody is so focused on you at all times it's it's crazy I hate an incident I hate
to call it an instinct because that sounds negative but the other night I'm coming home right it's fairly
late it's not crazy late but it's midnight I stop at my local deli get a sandwich I'm walking home
with my sandwich there are two women in front of me uh walking just by coincidence I am consciously
looking down at the ground because I notice one of them is kind of looking over her shoulder like
who's behind us yeah I get that I do that sometimes when I'm walking at night you want to make sure
there's no creep behind you and I'm looking down because I'm trying to accommodate and be like
I think that girl might be concerned that I might not be a sane person or a safe person so I'm
gonna look down so it's very obvious that I'm not in any way interested in this person for anything
anyway we get to the corner she stops and I keep walking and I look up and we're about to intersect
and I very gentlemanly go oh no it's okay after you and she goes now after you I don't feel
like I'm half up and I man I just walked and dude I had fucking steam coming out of my ears because
it's like look I get it that you have a concern I respect that concern there's a way to handle that
where you also don't have to unfairly make this accusatory thing about me you could have just said
no after you and I would have known oh it's I get it I'll keep walking right but to say this
condescending thing to me is if like I'm just supposed to be in front of you because it's people
are losing their shit man it's like they are they are and I you know I used to just anytime
somebody would go off in public or whatever it is or situation like you're describing I'd be like
what a fucking idiot what a fucking nut whatever and I think in the coming months it's gonna require
a lot more understanding on everyone's part just like people are not going to be right for a little
while it's like I'm I'm fully prepared to just be encountering madness at every turn once the
doors open I agree with that and but I I got to tell you but buddy I don't I got to tell you pal
okay ale mine this is how we talk on the what a heated crossfire debate and we'll see what I'll
now I'll tell you this though I don't blame the pandemic for that I think I said throughout the
toward the end of the pandemic I said we're all doing things as a result of the pandemic at first
there were things we did that were medicine for the ailment you know the pandemic was the ailment
and being locked in and all that stuff and the pain and the suffering and the depression that we
were all going through for varied reasons we had ways of treating that for ourselves and eventually the
medicine for that became the the focus yeah and the ailment became the excuse for the medicine so
everybody kind of became the guy that's still refilling the prosack I mean I'm sorry the percuss at
prescription a year and a half after the dental operation you know what I mean sure so I don't
blame the pandemic for this these these crazy behavior that's it's all social media this is what you
get when you build a society where the prominent means of communication is something where you can
literally ostracize and banish people from the conversation and only follow and be followed by
people that 100 % agree with you and build up your ego in that way this is what you get now you locked
everybody in for a year now you let these people went deeper into it now you're letting everybody out in
the street and now people really don't know how to I mean this was happening kind of before I remember
you getting to like a debate in a bar two three years ago and the person this this thing started
happening where the person who was losing would go okay I'm walking away and it's like why because you're
losing because you can't make a point you started an argument you started a debate and you now can't
make a logical point so now you're going to have a tantrum you're blocking me in real life this is
what it is yeah and it's just going to be worse now man who boy there's definitely you know some people
call it healthy boundaries whatever you know but it's like they're there does come a too far point
with the healthy boundaries if you are like you're saying only hearing what you want to hear
intentionally avoiding any discussion that might challenge you in any way not of course we're
excluding hate speech etc that's different but if somebody's just talking about their opinion of
world events and you have to walk away from it you know you might want to look at yourself and say like
I need to learn how to just engage in a in a simple debate I mean there's there's a reason debate is
a class in high school you know it's healthy it's healthy to open your mind and see other
points of view I do blend the pandemic and it sounds like you're blaming it a little bit too but I
think it just it is a combination yeah yeah it's a combination it's it's you're trapped inside
and now social media which used to be something you looked at while you took a shit or couldn't fall
asleep it now becomes something like and I believe me I was guilty of this where I started losing it
a little bit where I'm my eyes are cracking open in the morning and I'm reaching for my phone
and then I would start my day by looking at Twitter for two hours because I'm like what else am I
doing and then I'd get up and it's just bad for you like you I felt it inside of me that the voices
in my head that I that I and a lot of people try to keep it bay the voice that's like you're ugly
you're fat you're stupid you don't know how to write you don't know how to do this people hate you
texting you to be fair yeah I mean the voices that you hear at all times at some point
that became the sole voice I was hearing I was hearing that louder than like my wife and my friends
and it's like it's a mix of the pandemic and social media it can drive you insane yeah and I
started kind of normal there are people who went into the pandemic nuts and they're gonna come out
fucking oh yeah some of them are running these networks the no but I just like to say I'm about
to pitch and I think everyone at a network is sane and a track I blame I blame the pandemic mildly
in the way that like you know to me it's the same thing is like the difference between was was the
pandemic a hoax no but did certain institutions capitalize on it to create their own situations
that they wanted to cash in on yes so I think like everybody kind of did that to their own extent I think
the people the pandemic just gave certain people an opportunity for the excuse to go deeper and deeper
into these really really what I think are toxic behaviors and by the way for those of you listening at
home today's movie is American psycho and this all is relevant I think to the themes of not only the
themes of the film as we discussed today and the themes of the book but also fascinatingly enough
and I went through a rabbit hole last night on YouTube with this bread eastern Ellis author of the book
uh he has been on Twitter great I love him uh he has become very much a proponent of
why is everything so hypocritical now and why does why doesn't anybody have the ability to listen to
converse opinions anymore and why can't we discuss things and it's very interesting
because he's been a controversial artist his entire life or his career rather but I
I realized something today I was thinking about when American psycho came out and the controversy
surrounding it and I was reading about it last night and uh feminist groups really hated the book they
said it was sexist uh and and extremely cruel towards women of course conservative groups hated the
book because it was disgusting and violent and sexual and all these things and look it's the exact
kind of book that that certain liberal uh uh powers that be at the time would have banned in the way
that the PMRC was functioning at the time with explicit lyrics and all that sort of thing but I
realized something this thing that everybody's complaining about right now it's nothing new
it's not the first time in history in this country that we have battled extreme conservatives
and extreme conservative viewpoints it is not the first time in this country we have battled
extreme liberals and extreme liberal viewpoints it is not the first time in this country we have
battled extreme feminism and and uh uh uh uh uh uh uh social uh commentaries that have gone to pass the
cause and off the rails it is not the first time in history that we've battled racism in all fronts
and this good those things have always been something we've battled the one thing we lost was it used to be
the pool of artists where the place you could turn
that said fuck you to all of it.
Right.
And that's what Brett Easton Ellis was a part of
and still is, but that pool has shrunk
to such a point now that it's just very tragic to me.
Like there is no safe haven for people
to kind of rebel against all of it anymore.
You know, I don't think anybody in the 80s
or late 80s whenever that book came out was saying
that Brett Easton Ellis was a Nazi
and an alt -right Republican because he wrote a book
that pissed off certain liberals.
That was not the case.
It was, this group is mad at it.
I'm an artist, okay.
Yeah, that's where we're at.
Yeah.
And we really lost that.
We really lost this sort of gray area group
of people that are just supposed to be saying,
hey, man, it is what it is.
I don't know what to tell you.
We're going to agree to disagree here.
Well, we've really lost, and especially in the case
of American Psycho, which we'll talk about much more later,
is like, that's a satire.
So I remember people being crazy and upset about the book.
My mom actually read almost like a book a day
she was obsessive for my whole childhood
and it's the only book I ever saw her put down.
And I remember her telling me there was a scene
where they put a rat into a woman's,
and then she was like, well, a woman's, you know,
kind of thing, and I was like, god,
and to this day I've never read American Psycho
because I watched my mom get so, and now I should.
I should start reading it tomorrow,
but my mom was so troubled by it that it affected me.
And it's a disturbing book.
It's a disturbing book, but it's a satire.
Now, my mom is a Missouri mother, you know?
You would think that the people who are all upset about this
and they're upset about the movie as well.
I remember that big backlash, even though it was written
and directed by women, is that it's a satire.
And it happens every week on SNL.
I still watch SNL, I don't know why, but they,
the monologue rolls around and Michael Che,
we'll say a joke criticizing Harvey Weinstein
for raping women.
And the crowd will go, oh, it's like, what are you taught?
This used to be a prime tenant of comedy
was that you would go after monsters.
And sometimes you do it in a dark way
where you're exaggerating things.
Or that's my favorite kind of comedy.
And every week, you know, you see on his face,
he's pissed off, he's kind of disgusted with the audience.
Sometimes he just tells them like, you guys are fucking stupid.
But like, God, it's like, okay, do you really think
that this man on an NBC show is getting up there
being like, I love Harvey Weinstein or something?
Like, what is the intent of the joke?
It's not even that, it's bringing up the subject
of it in and of itself.
Just bringing up the subject.
They're trigger words, people hear words,
people it's selective hearing, people hear words,
and that's all they can hear.
That's all they can hear, certain words.
And then they form their own sentences out of it.
And their own opinions, you know,
they form what they think they're hearing
out of the choice words they're selecting.
It's ridiculous.
You know, I was reading about the movie,
American Cycle last night.
You know, Mary Harron, who's a great director.
She got a bunch of shit with this, you know,
for doing this thing.
And then she brought in, I forget the writer's name,
but the writer was basically a staunch feminist.
But a logical one.
Right.
That was like, we couldn't make this.
And if we do the scenes of the female murders
through the perspective of the female
and not through the perspective of Patrick Bateman,
we're making a statement.
And that's what they did.
And it said on the Wikipedia, like Mary Harron,
like once she brought this woman in and returned to production
because I guess they paused because the controversy
or whatever, she wasn't worried anymore
because she's like, now they can't say anything about us.
They can't say that we're being anti -feminist or anti -whatever.
And again, my point is is for all the controversy
that's surrounded this film, and I do remember it.
I remember when it was getting produced
and seeing the clips about it on the news
and entertainment news and whatever,
reading about it in Premiere magazine or whatever.
There was never a cry from fellow artists
as far as I can remember that Mary Harron should be canceled
or banned because she was doing something
that certain groups that other people
I might have identified with more than she did
or even maybe to the same amount that she did,
didn't agree with it.
And it's a terrible shame that we've lost that.
And now you're seeing a guy like Brett Easton Ellis.
In my opinion, one of the great modern authors
in American history, look, it's very lucrative.
I looked it up on Patreon, but he does a podcast
and it's Patreon only.
And it's like, this is what we've come to,
that like this guy is doing a Patreon only podcast
because like he, I mean, I'm assuming
doesn't want to deal with the bullshit anymore.
Like, yeah, I don't know, man, it's very strange.
Very strange.
I feel a lot less anxious about doing this podcast
when we went Patreon.
And as Joe can attest, I spend at least five minutes
after every podcast going,
ah, did I say this?
I shouldn't have said this, whatever.
I think, I honestly think cancel culture
is a little overstated.
I mean, as he's in Zari, he's doing another season
of master of none, you know?
But it is just a bad time, especially for comedy.
I had lunch with a friend yesterday who's in comedy
and he was like, you know, I was doing this thing
for a little bit of money, you know,
to try to like kind of just make some money
and keep my mind busy.
This little fun project.
And it was with college humor, which used to be,
I mean, I used to find some of their stuff offensive,
honestly, but.
Oh, yeah.
They're, they're, oh, I mean, I'm not saying,
oh, yeah, I was offended.
And I'm saying, oh, yeah, like, they put edgy stuff up, yeah.
Yeah, they, they were always sort of pushing the envelope
and he did this pretty innocuous, like animated script
and turned it in.
And he showed me the notes he got back.
And it was like, can you cut this, can you cut this,
can you change this, can you move?
And the jokes that they were pushing back on were,
I mean, as mild as can be.
And it's got me scared for my business.
And I'm not the kind of guy who's like,
no, I want to be able to make jokes about, you know,
Nazis or rape or anything.
I don't go that extreme generally,
but it's like, it's a concern, you know,
it's an ongoing concern.
Yeah. And that's the thing.
You know, we're not, we're not screaming fire
in the crowded theater.
We're not sitting here saying.
Cancel cultures out of control.
And I mean, I, you know, to some extent,
it is to some extent, everything is out of control.
It's, you know, you could look at anything
and go, it's out of control.
So nobody, nobody wants to pull the alarm on this thing,
but that said, I hope we can get back to a place
where at least the artists are pulling together,
at least in large enough a number,
that the artists that want to partake
in these exclusionary behaviors,
can do so on their own time,
but they're outnumbered by the artistic community
who is saying, hey guys, we don't believe in art censorship.
If you don't like it, turn the dial, turn the channel,
turn your eyes, whatever, but sorry.
Like this is, this is what expression is.
Well, generally, when you sit down
and talk to somebody in the arts,
it's they, everyone feels a little bit of concern
about where things are going.
You know, everyone's like, yeah, this,
this seems extreme or that's too much,
or that's crazy, whatever.
And I understand that progress is difficult, you know?
Like they, they, they thought everyone on set
thought Mickey Rooney with Buck Teath playing the Asian neighbor
in breakfast at Tiffany's was cool.
Every single person involved was like, yeah, this is great.
You know, I'd love to be 80 and not look back at movies now
and be like, oh my God, and cover your eyes,
but I do think what's getting lost is just the ability
to even do satire, the ability to tackle any subject,
the ability to even bring up things in a comedic setting.
And that's going to make life very, very boring, very boring.
Yeah, I think it's a shame that I've say this all the time
because you couldn't get him,
you couldn't get American psycho made now.
I mean, just the pitch alone, they'd be like,
are you out of your mind?
But I always thought it was a shame that
because even when it came out, it's, it's still considered,
it's become a cult classic, but it's considered
to be a very watered down version of the book,
which it is, I read the book, the book is insane.
But I always thought it was a shame that like, you know,
you take a guy like Tom Cruise, for instance,
and I know he's not really going to be our savior,
but you take a guy like Tom Cruise,
who's got more money than God and you go,
I don't understand why this guy doesn't buy the rights
to the book and make the version
that everybody says could never be made
because it could be made, you know,
there's a lot of movies that could be made
in the way they were supposed to be made.
It doesn't necessarily mean just violent films
or whatever, it just adaptations period
in the way they're supposed to be made, you know,
there are actors and several actors in Hollywood
that could have funded a proper adaptation of it,
for example, you know what I mean?
And it would have been no skin off their teeth, financially.
I think it's a shame that more,
it seems that when everybody gets to a certain level,
they just put their means right back into the system
and this thing just keeps churning and churning and churning.
It never really changes.
Yeah.
You know, they don't want to rock the boat,
they don't want to lose the check.
Yeah.
And who doesn't get that?
I mean, yeah, yeah, but still.
We were talking, who was, I don't know,
I was talking yesterday about Mark Wahlberg
and how he's like,
You know, I don't want to be away from my wife and kids
for six months every year, but I got to do it.
You know, I do it all for them.
And it's like, Mark, you have $500 million.
So at this point, you're not doing it for them.
You're not doing it like to provide for them
when you're gone or some, they're good.
You know, you might go off and do this movie
and then wind up with $520 million.
But like you're doing this for you.
A, you probably want to get away from your family
and go be a movie star and B,
you're doing it for yourself and your ego and et cetera.
Don't say that shit.
It's just gross to me.
I mean, this is even off topic.
But like, you know, I got to go do it for my family.
No, why did some of these people just not quit?
Well, that was a huge, huge part in the Bredistan Ellis interview.
I was watching last night was him talking about the hypocrisy
of Hollywood, how they try and pretend like it's not the most
capitalistic industry on the planet, you know, and it's capitalism.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's big banking.
It's, it's, it's not an, it's, they're, they're the people
at the top of that ladder all want to be William Randolph Hurst.
They want power.
They want to be able to live in a castle.
They want to leave a legacy behind.
They, it's all this stupid dumb fucking caveman shit.
I was at dinner or brunch, excuse me, for Mother's Day.
And my cousin Danielle was telling me that her son,
my nephew, wants to change his last name to DeRosa.
Her, her dad's name was not DeRosa.
Yeah.
And she said, why do you want to change your name to DeRosa?
He said, because aside from Uncle Joey, who else is around to keep the name going.
Yeah.
And Danny, my cousin goes, so I guess it's all on your shoulders.
And I go, I've got bad news for you.
It probably ends here, you know, it's like this stupid fucking shit of like,
I've got to leave my mark.
I've got to do this.
I've got, it's all male ego bullshit.
Are you the king of Windsor or something?
Who gives a stupid?
And as we all sit here and criticize the royal family for their bullshit,
everybody's doing it themselves.
Everybody's doing the same model.
It's so important that I leave my mark.
And you know, and it's not, it's everybody in Hollywood is the guy at the table
in Casino.
When, when, when DeNiro goes, he didn't see it as winning 10 ,000.
And he saw it as losing 30 ,000, a guy like that can't bet low.
It's just, you know, it's, it's just sad to me.
But anyway, well, Sam Jackson said once on Letterman, when I was probably 16.
And I remember it all these years later, but David Letterman was like,
now you're in a lot of movies lately, Sam.
You know, I remember Letterman gushing about Jackie Brown for almost like a week
on his show when I used to watch it every night.
And he clearly loved Samuel Jackson and who doesn't.
He brought him in and was like, this was around snakes on the plane days or something.
But he was like, I mean, he, in a very nice way, in a very letterman way,
he was kind of like, you're not exactly choosing with you projects.
Are you know, because Jackson was doing everything at that point,
deep blue sea and et cetera.
And Sam Jackson goes, now, let me ask your viewers at home something, Dave,
and like looks at the camera.
It was like, if somebody offered you $10 million to spend three months in Hawaii,
would you do it?
And the audience like laughs and applaud.
That is so much more refreshing to me than Mark Wahlberg saying,
I'm making this piece of shit action movie from my family.
Fuck off.
No, it's when I used to spoke at my college.
He said, he goes, I have six movies coming out this year.
They'll all be available to liquor store near you.
And and the crowd laughed and he goes, man, people give me shit
that I'm in a lot of bad movies.
He goes, let me tell you something.
If you're from the street like I was and you grew up with nothing,
when somebody comes to you and offers you a million dollars to be in a movie,
yeah, he goes, you'd have to be pretty fucking ignorant to turn it down.
And I was like, yeah, there you go.
Elliott percent.
Yeah, there you go.
You know, but Wahlberg's out there, you know, after his ninth
Transformers movie, he's the, he becomes a spokesperson for AT &T.
Mark Wahlberg, this is a fact and I've her rang about it nonstop, not nonstop.
But you know what I mean, plenty to people over the years.
And everybody's always kind of like, so what?
Mark Wahlberg was the highest paid actor on the planet when he took the AT &T
spokesperson gig for Christ Sanks.
I got it when Luke Wilson did it.
I got it.
This guy's doing these indie things.
Yes.
Like him and like David Keckner, you know, on these like shoestring budgets and whatever he's
not Owen.
You know what I mean?
He's like the, he's like the Alexis Arquette of that family.
You know, and like, I get, I got why he did it.
It's like, but Mark fucking Wahlberg, like come on, dude, give me a break.
They announced today and I'm a fan of the guy do not get me wrong.
But that Seth Rogen is doing a podcast.
And it's like, dude, you're you have five TV shows on television.
You're one of the top 10 stars in in Hollywood.
You're a writer, a director, an actor, a producer.
What do you need this for when I'm a time management standpoint?
I get it.
If you started it at the top of the pandemic, I want to make, I want to, you know, do something
creative.
I get that.
But to start it now, what are you doing when I go, when I go every week, once a week,
I'll check chartable to see how taste buds is doing in the ranks.
Yes.
You know, unfortunately, we're not a contender anymore because we're only on Patreon now.
But I go and check and we do very well.
Thank you to everybody listening.
I really appreciate it.
But every fucking week, when I see the number one podcast in the country is like Jason
Bateman, Will Arnett and whatever, you know, the number four is like deck, well, deck
shepherd, I get he's not like a huge, but the Bateman one, I'm like, bro, come on, dude.
Like come on, dude.
And like people go, well, there's enough to go around.
There is enough to go around in theory.
But this is the thing that podcast will always be number one.
Yeah.
Only so many people can pull off with Rogan or Burr, whoever did and get into that top 10.
Only so many people who weren't already there because of other things.
Well, and you listen to one, one, maybe two podcasts a week, even if you're a guy who likes
podcasts, so if Rogan's taken one of those slots, then it's kind of like, it's not going
to trickle down.
The people are going to be looking for new voices and et cetera.
And it's the same thing that celebrities, including Seth Rogan, including many others, speak
out about every day, which is capitalism, which is it like the same person will get on
and say, it's completely fucked up that some people have so much and some people have so
few and then turn around and add a podcast to their $500 billion empire.
And by the way, when you're operating at that level and podcasting, you're trust me when
I tell you, it's, you're, it's millions of dollars.
Yeah.
It's millions of dollars.
It is not a supplemental income.
It's not a little thing you're doing with your buddies for fun, where it is millions of
dollars.
Yeah.
And look, everybody's got the right to do what they got to do.
I think you're a fucking idiot.
If you were mad about Elon Musk hosting SNL because he's a billionaire or whatever else you
think about, I don't give a shit at all.
Go make your money.
Fine.
We live in a capitalistic society, but to, to, I don't know, I have nothing against capitalism.
I do think, though, I do have something against a person trying to make every single available
dime.
Yeah.
It's like, dude, go hang out with your, your family for a while or something, man.
I don't know.
Like, well, yeah, they're doing it for their family, of course.
How, how this stuff starts, I guarantee it is at these celebrity parties and, and there
are so many of them that go on and so many that went on during the pandemic and so many
that will continue to go on.
But you know, you want, it's just mass hypocrisy.
It's there, there are parties that went on over this pandemic, where celebrities who, who can
spend their whole day on Twitter criticizing people for doing the same thing would have
parties where it's like, we're all celebrities.
So, A, we're probably all rich enough that we're not sick and B, we'll all trust each
other not to tell anybody that we did this.
And, you know, I don't believe about the pedophile cabals, but I do believe that celebrities
like cover for each other and do this shit.
And they go to these parties and one of them says to Conan O 'Brien, and I hate to pick
on Conan and Seth Rogen, two people I actually like in Hollywood.
But they hear from somebody, maybe it's Jack Shepard, you know, maybe it's somebody else say,
you know, I just started doing this podcast like for fun to kind of kill, kill an hour
a week.
I'm making $3 million a year on this thing.
Then the celebrities all gather, what are you doing?
You're making $3 million.
Wow, that's easy.
I could do it and only have to work an hour a week.
That's amazing.
And they'll be more of these popping up, you know?
It's like the podcasting used to be kind of like hearing the voice of people and you look
for subjects you find interesting and et cetera.
That was the idea of it.
And now the top 10 every week is Conan.
It's going to be Seth Rogen.
It's going to be Joe Rogen.
It's going to be big stars at least with Conan.
I could say you're a talk show host, you're ending your talk show.
Now you're going to do a podcast, like at least with Conan, I could say that and it's, it
makes sense.
It's what you do.
You interview people.
That's what you do.
But yeah, there are, there are a lot of people out there where I'm just like, Jesus fucking
Christ, man.
Do you really need to?
Okay.
You know, I wouldn't.
And they all, they're all the same guests too.
It's like, okay, hey, guess who we've got Paul Sheer.
I like Paul Sheer, but this is not what the medium was for that we all listen to Paul Sheer
tell the same six stories on 12 different podcasts.
You know, it's like they never let anyone in.
It's not like they're never showcasing new voices they've heard and loved.
I'm, you know, some respect speaking about terms, but yeah, I respect the shit out of Kevin
James.
I really do.
And I know a lot of people think he's, you know, he's, he's broad and he's this and he's
that.
I respect the shit out of him.
Here's a guy that built a studio in Long Island where he's from where he lives.
So he could do his multi cam sitcom and any other project he wants to do from home.
Yeah.
Because he was like, life's too short.
I'm doing it the way I want to do it.
That's awesome.
And so few people do that.
So few people do that.
I love somebody that's like, no, I'm putting my life first.
And that's how I'm going to do it.
You can tell Sandler does that.
Yeah.
Sandler's like, hey man, I'm going to do these movies with my friends and, you know, they're
some of those Netflix Sandler movies.
I mean, they shoot him out while he's like sitting on the toilet in the morning.
You can tell they're like, they just green screen him into a volcano or something.
Yeah.
It's like, he's like one, you know, more or less one location, you know, go have some fun
for a little while.
And then I'm going home and I'm hanging out, you know, his wife's in every movie.
It's like, I think that's cool, man.
I really do.
You know, it's like, look, I think I know we've kind of knocked some of the more recent
Kevin Smith stuff because he's unfortunately high all the time and it sucks because of
it.
But I respect the hell out of Kevin Smith for being like, no, man, I'm going to have a podcast
network where I talk about, I have six shows about Batman because I can't shut the fuck
up about Batman.
I have a comic book store where I employ my friends in my hometown and that one of my friends
works at.
And then I'm, and then I'm going to make the exact one movie I want to make every
three years.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Like, like, and if it's about a podcast or who turns into a walrus, so be it, I'm a big
fan.
I know.
I know just we did on the show.
But anyway, we've, we've really, we're at the 40 minute mark, we don't know when the
American Psycho, I don't know when the show became meet the press, but yeah, let's quickly
do our thing, Joe, you know, I like to do the movie corner.
I like to have our segments.
People like a segment to turn to.
I look, I don't have an exponent, oh, here's my explanation, my, my sort of OCD issues as
I have said have been flaring out from time to time and I've found myself unable to pick
a movie at night, unless my wife says to me, gives me two letters, the first two letters
of a movie.
So she'll go like BA and I'll go thanks and then I can choose between 10 movies as opposed
to my collection.
Um, it's a weird little thing I do to help otherwise I, I would lose three hours staring at movies
and wind up watching nothing.
I've done that a lot over this break.
So the other night I, I bought Heather when we were early dating a bunch of the Disney classics
on Blu -ray.
This was before Disney plus.
And I watched Bambi for the first time since I was a kid ever so.
Um, the movie's like 60 minutes long like Dumbo, uh, it's really sort of beautiful.
I love the hand drawn animation.
It seems almost like you're looking at something from like hundreds of years ago at this point
compared to like Pixar and stuff.
There's a real handmade quality.
You can almost see the like pencil marks and stuff sometimes.
That's very cool.
Uh, what I, it's weird.
What I remembered from when I was a kid was Bambi's mom getting shot in the opening scene
and then Bambi's out on his own.
Bambi's mom doesn't die until the end.
So I completely messed that up.
I remember being traumatic for me.
But then they had, there's about four little songs in it, drip, drip, drop, little April,
showers.
I knew every word of these songs.
I saw Bambi once when I was five.
Hmm.
I could sing every word of these songs and yet I completely messed up the order of the plot
by like a hundred percent.
So I had sort of this weird look at memory and how, and, and it made me think about memory
and how slippery it is.
That's my review of Bambi.
It's a, you know, it's an entertaining movie, but it's for little kids.
It's a, it's a beautiful looking movie.
All right.
Uh, I, uh, where are we at here?
I'm going to do some old ones that I never covered.
Uh, watch vampires kiss with Nicholas Cage.
Joe, that's nuts.
And I hate to interrupt you, but that, that's nuts.
I was, uh, I, sometimes I'll search a, a title on Twitter to see old tweets about it from
people I follow.
And somebody, I don't even remember who pointed out that American psycho and vampires kiss
are almost the same movie.
And I was like, I'd have to watch them back to back to know, but I saw them both recently
and I thought about it and I was like, that seems right to me.
Uh, now that you say that, yeah, I could see the similarities between the two, you know,
it's, it's, it's a guy who is, you know, vampires kiss centers around Nicholas Cage, believing
he's a vampire, but you're not quite sure whether he actually is or if it's sort of just
in his head, uh, it's certainly a focus on women that he needs to pray on or feels the
need to pray on as a vampire.
Um, and, uh, it's strangely satirical and funny.
Uh, Nicholas Cage does, I don't know what the fuck kind of accent in this thing.
I mean, I mean, you think it's, he's off the reservation in this goddamn movie.
You know, like, I remember the kid from Big Bang Theory on Conan talk doing his Nicholas
Cage impression and saying, like, vampires kiss is the craziest Nicholas Cage movie ever.
There's a scene where he just recites the alphabet.
I, yeah, and he does it on Conan.
And then when I watched the movie, I was very funny.
And then when I watched the movie, I was like, holy shit, he's like just doing the scene.
Like it's, he's not even exaggerating it.
I know.
So it's wild stuff.
Uh, is it good?
I think American Psycho is a far superior film, but it's worth a watch.
It's a wild ride.
You know, I don't know if it's one I'd buy for the collection.
Yeah, but I'd say give it a watch if you, if you can on one of the streaming services.
I am a fan of that movie.
I thought it was very interesting.
And uh, all I remember about it when I was a kid is that Cage ate, they're like, he ate a
live cockroach.
This was a major news story for like a long period of time.
And I'm sure his team was like, oh, no, like, because Cage would do these movies and then
turn around and do honeymoon in Vegas, which is why I think he's a fucking great talent,
you know, who really has always just championed what he likes.
And I think that's great.
Now he's, you know, okay, a little different.
But uh, Vampire's Kiss was also one of the only successful films from the writer of
After Hours and they have a similar kind of energy to them.
Yes.
Uh, all right.
I saw a picture called my octopus teacher.
Um, this movie will be all the ad for that.
They didn't.
It's a documentary about octopuses being smart or something, which was also the plot of one of
the latest Jordan Peele Twilight songs.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh, um, a buddy of mine reminded me the other day that deep blue sea was about using
sharks to find a cure for Alzheimer's, which I had forgotten.
That's what the, the, the, the, the, the, the Peele Twilight song was.
Something along with the lines, something, uh, I had seen all the nominees for best documentary
at the Oscars.
And I remember watching the Oscars and I was like, octopus is going to win because it's the worst
of the five.
And it is.
And it won.
Um, a lot of people love this movie.
A lot of people were very moved by it.
I couldn't get past the dude.
It's this guy who like, he's very vague at the beginning, but he's like, my wife is
and I are having problems.
My son and I were having problems.
And I turned to the octopus in the sea.
It's basically a man turning his back on his wife and son to go have what at times feels
like a sexual relationship with the octopus.
I mean, the way he talks about this octopus and he keeps talking about it and
misting up and you're like, what happened under that sea?
What happened to keep referring to it as octopus -y?
Crashly, right?
My little octopus -y.
Um, look, here's my question, what got left on the cutting room floor?
What didn't we see when he turned off that underwater camera?
Because I found the whole thing vaguely creepy.
The underwater photography is the reason to watch it.
It's beautiful.
You see a lot of cool undersea creatures if that's your deal.
In general, I did not like the guy and I couldn't get past that.
But, you know, check it out if you want.
It's on Netflix at one best documentary.
All right, I watched, oh shit, I closed my thing by accident.
I watched a little picture called Viverium with a nihilistic little piece of fun.
I never saw it starring, um, what's his face?
Jesse Eisenberg.
Jesse Eisenberg, and what's her name?
Pam Greer.
Not Pam Greer.
The mom from happy days.
What's her name?
Marian.
Imogen Poots.
Poots.
Honestly, that was my guess.
Why didn't I say it?
Two names that sound like slang for gas.
Anyway, she, it's a movie where they're a couple.
They're looking to buy a home together.
You can tell in the beginning, they might be having some.
They're very much in love, but there might be a little bit of tension.
Uh, in the relationship and that this is sort of the next phase for them.
This is the next step we're going to move forward.
As so many people often do, instead of examining the relationship itself, they think,
if we just go to the next phase, it'll be fine.
If we just go to the next phase, it'll be fine.
And, and so many people's couplehood turns into this sort of pointless
course of just going through the motions and reproduction and, and for the sake of it all.
And, uh, that's basically what the movie is a big commentary on.
And, uh, they, uh, they are brought to this neighborhood that is cookie cutter.
Everything looks exactly, every house looks exactly the same.
The entire neighborhood is manicured perfectly in the exact same function.
Uh, the person, the, the realtor takes them into the house.
And within five minutes disappears and they're, they can't figure out how to get out of the
neighborhood and they just keep ending up back at this house.
And things unfold from there become more sinister from there until you eventually realize
what is going on and why they're being manipulated in this way and what's happening.
And, uh, it's a very, very interesting film.
I think it's a, I think it's probably a one that I would say you multi watch.
On first watch, I think your brain is going to take you to places where you think the movie is
going or, or, or give you certain expectations.
And, and if it doesn't go there, you'll feel disappointed.
But I think it's one of those flicks that with more distance and more watching becomes better
and better and better.
It's a very, very sharp commentary and reminds me quite a bit of like the sort of Richard Matheson,
Harlan Ellison style of short fiction.
Uh, so I, I, I, I recommend.
I'll check it out.
That's a cool premise.
I didn't know that's what it was about.
Yeah.
Uh, I saw Existens, which I had not seen since college, um, and I stand by what I thought then.
It's lesser Cronenberg.
It's, uh, it's sort of in that period that has a lot of fans these days.
But for me, he's got his 80s high point where he made just masterpiece after masterpiece.
And then in the 90s things kind of slipped.
And I, I'd include Existens in that.
It's an entertaining movie.
It's Jennifer Jason Lee and Jude Law as like game developers.
There's a lot of, you know, plugging things into open wounds and like, you know, a lot of sexual,
you know, type things going on sexual and the body and everything.
All Cronenberg's usual stuff is on display.
The acting is fun.
Although I don't know Jude, Jude Law really kind of botched his accent
and that's when he's trying to do the old American one.
But, um, you know, it's fun.
It moves.
But for me, this was during Cronenberg's kind of lost period with where he,
which he really turned around with, uh, history of violence.
Uh, what's the other one?
Eastern promises, you know, I thought he was really back on track.
What was the other one that was called like,
Cacquarium or something?
It was like Viverium.
What was it called?
Well, there was Cosmopolus, which started with Robert Pattinson.
And then Max to the stars, which is a highly disturbing film.
It is.
I believe he is now working on a new film.
And I know he's getting old and I had heard things about his,
his health, but I'm glad to hear he's working again.
This movie remake of of one of his original shorts.
And I've seen Cronenberg's the future, which is not something I felt
needed to be remade, but, but good for him.
It's Vigo Mortensen.
Um, it's sci -fi.
I'm eager to see it.
I love Cronenberg.
All right.
Last up for me.
Again, I closed the goddamn file.
Why do I keep doing that?
Last up for me is, uh,
Daniel isn't real.
Very cool film.
Very cool.
I agree on shutter.
Very, very cool film on shutter from the good people over its vector vision.
Elijah Woods Company.
I, you know, what, what is there to say?
A kid had a very, very sinister, it's like if drop dead Fred was a horror movie.
I thought it was awesome.
It's about a kid's very sinister best imaginary friend coming back
later in life and wreaking utter havoc and hell on his life.
Uh, it's a fun watch.
It's got some really creepy parts.
It's got some really cool camera work.
It's very well written.
It's a little away from itself in the finale.
But, uh, but, you know, it doesn't ruin the movie or anything.
I really liked it.
I say go check it out for yourself.
I especially if you like what spectra vision has been doing lately,
which Mandy and color from out of space.
I think it fits right in with all that stuff.
So check it out.
I agree.
And Patrick Schwarzenegger is great in it.
Oh, he's awesome, man.
Yeah, he's cool to see because I don't know if I'd ever seen him in anything
but I'm aware of.
Yeah, he's great.
Anyway, onto our feature.
It's American Psycho folks.
It is, uh, the, the, it is the only British and Ellis book I have not read.
I have it now sitting on my nightstand and intend to read it.
But, um, so I can't speak on the differences, et cetera.
But it, uh, this movie I had, I had seen it in theaters.
Maybe another time after that.
But seeing it now was the first time I felt like I get this.
I love this.
I'm on the same wavelength as this.
The other times I don't know.
It's, uh, it's something was lost on me that I just got now.
And it might be that my hatred of people has fully developed.
Uh, because, you know, he's, it's just a fascinating character.
Christian Bale is so good.
One of his best performances ever.
Uh, you know, I talked about Jude Law's accent being walkie.
Yeah, he's, he's amazing.
Bale, I had no idea he was British at all, you know.
He really is amazing in this.
You know, he transformed his body.
He looks incredible.
Uh, he's, he does that dead eyed stair thing just beautifully.
And this time for me, I think I went in and other times like with the controversy.
And I used to be kind of a coward when it came to horror and et cetera.
This is the first time I saw it for what it truly is, which is a comedy, I think.
I mean, this, this movie plays like a comedy, a very dark one.
But I, I laughed so much.
Some of the music choices in this are so perfect.
When he's basically like, there's no soul inside me.
I'm, I'm completely dead, lovable.
And then they cut to walking on sunshine.
Yeah, I laughed so hard.
And then the next one is he's basically calling Reese Witherspoon
the C word in a back of the cab.
Like he's just being awful to her.
Just terrible while they're going out in a date.
And they're playing simply irresistible in the back.
And I just was like, I love, I love the choices that are kind of commenting on the action.
Somehow I missed these clues the first time I saw it.
That's great.
I really love it on this viewing as a dark satirical comedy.
Yeah.
I love that scene.
I'm trying to listen to the new Robert Palmer album.
The music grants are great.
That's, that's straight Ellis.
I mean, I've read glamoramo, which is the sequel to American Psycho.
And I mean, those music grants are my favorite parts of the books.
And I'm so glad they, they realized how important it is to the movie.
Because that's the kind of thing.
A lesser writer director would have cut.
But it's, it's, hey, it's funny as shit.
But it's also like, yeah, this guy only cares about plastic things.
Pop music, looking great.
Business cars, you know, his, his, his, he focuses solely on the most commercial record being the
best record of the band.
In the book, he says invisible touch by Genesis is their masterpiece record, which is an insane
statement.
I mean, that records got great stuff on it.
But it's an insane statement.
He says in the book and in the movie that hip to be square is the peak of Huey Lewis.
He refers to Huey Lewis's early work as too new wave.
That's in the movie too.
My favorite thing, my favorite line is because I love Costello so much is that he was,
he's talking about their too new wave.
And then he's like, a lot of people compare Huey Lewis to Elvis Costello, which people don't really do.
And he says, I, I prefer Huey Lewis because he's so much more edgy and bitter.
Like, there is no more caustic bitter lyricists than Elvis Costello.
So I love that.
I thought that was great.
Interesting thing, you know, the debate about this movie is as he goes along on this killing
spree, all of his crimes are completely unnoticed.
And you start to realize as he confuses one person for somebody else and people confuse him
for somebody else and everybody dresses exactly the same and is competing with the same brands
of things and whatever it has the same exact job and they all eat in the same places
that his crimes could be unnoticed because other people in this scene that he exists in
or unnoticed or it could just be in his head, which is supported by the idea that the crimes
throughout the film get more and more outrageous and seem to be also any evidence of these murders
or being cleaned up miraculously and not by him, which could also speak to that he's so gone that
he's going and cleaning up these things and not remembering it.
It could also speak to that he is committing these crimes, but they're not quite as outlandish
as he thinks they are in his head.
He's seeing them as spectacular.
But in the end of the movie, the debate is always, was this real or was it not?
Most people say I think it was just in his head.
Very interesting.
Breddys Denellis and Mary Heron have both said it's not it's supposed to be ambiguous,
but it is certainly not definitively that he's not doing this, you know, that's not the intention.
You know, it's a very, very interesting film to explore.
It's there are every one of his most insane moments he's completely alone.
You have no idea if this is real or not.
And the film I thought does a very good job of capturing that.
There's a key scene in the movie or in the book that was shot for the movie and it's been,
I don't know why it's just a deleted scene, especially since they've released an unrated
version of this film and didn't put this scene back into it where I forget the character's name.
He goes, I'm leaving and they're in a nightclub and he goes, I'm leaving.
And he crawls up the fixture on the wall and runs into the air conditioning duct and never comes
back again throughout the entire book. And that happens early on in the book.
And it was shot for the film. It's on the DVD.
And that's such a key moment where you're like,
what the fuck just happened? Was that like, did he imagine that?
But you're also like, my uncle worked on Wall Street at this time period.
He would tell me stories like that. That were that crazy.
Like he would tell me stories of like a bar they would all go to where there was a sliding board.
And like they would all, you know, and like it was all these crazy.
What do you mean like he's like a slip and slide that's a board or what?
He said there was there was a two story bar and you'd get like shit faced and go up and take
a sliding board from the top floor down and like he would tell me stories about how he fell asleep
on the train and woke up and like Maryland because he missed his stop and then like just had to
turn around and go right back to work in New York again. You know, like it was a wild time and it was
a lot of excess and people were very eccentric. A lot of them doing tons of coke
because coke was considered almost like healthy back then.
My friend who worked on Will and Grace said they had a mountain in the middle of the
writer's room, no exaggeration on show nights. They would put a mountain in the middle.
They'd all talk while they got ready for the taping and do line after line on Will and Grace.
Yeah, that's late era too. That's way after. I'm well aware. I'm well aware.
But you know, so I think the movie does a really really good job in the book and the movie both
do a really really good job of exploiting the ambiguity of the scene that he lives in,
the anonymity of the scene he lives in and then tying that into a commentary on materialism
and and self -indulgence to a point of a guy that has no respect for other people, particularly women
and indulges in that to the fullest extents, you know. Yeah, pretty crazy.
Well, you know, there are really graphic sex scenes in it and I watched the unrated version
where I know one of the key differences that kept it from getting an NC17 is he goes,
don't just stand there, look at her, look at her asshole in the unrated version when there's the
two, the three semis having and I guess they had to make it ass instead of asshole was like the last
thing that kept it from getting an NC17. So the line is, the line is, you made him, you messed
the line it, the line is, don't just stare at it, eat it. That's the second line. Oh, okay, sorry,
sorry. And that was for some reason allowed, but the line before it, which is like I want you to look
at her ass in the original version is asshole and eat it, of course, becomes a little more graphic.
This was a time when ass eating was not on on every station, ladies and gentlemen. So
that those sex scenes are graphic. He's looking in the mirror, you know, clearly a big influence on
the on the Dennis Reynolds character on always sunny, the American psycho. And it's like,
yeah, okay, did that sex happen? Or is he masturbating this fantasy, you know, that, to me,
that's kind of the least successful aspect of it. That third act and is this real, is this not,
that tends to be a kind of thing where I feel cheated. But, you know, I prefer the first and second acts.
I really, really like the movie. I like how just it nails this world. It nails the world better
than almost anything. A perfect triple feature would be after hours vampire's kiss and American
psycho. It's just three men losing their shit in 80s New York and a lot of cocaine and a lot of
crazy characters. I loved Lido in the movie. I love Savigney. I love Witherspoon. I love all
the great, great Lido is really good. It's good. Yeah, he's great. Justin Thoreau is awesome.
Yeah, when he jumps over that bathroom stall to scream and that guy's face when he's doing coke,
like they're all amped up and yelling and nuts and I think the key to this movie working and the reason
it was not even more controversial is is the fact that it was written and directed by women. Because
what they are doing is, you know, I think a man directing this would almost seem like he was
approving of the of the behavior or thought it was funny when in every step of the way from from
at least his writing, you know, I read all his other books. Why just completely lost my
trying to thought, but what I'm saying is, yeah, the women give it an appropriate perspective.
They give it a perspective. They give, you know, the term female gaze and male gaze is a very new
term going around lately. But like the shots of Patrick Bateman admiring his body, like when he's
showering and you see his ass and all this stuff, you're not going to get that from a male director
and it makes the movie work so much better because all he's thinking about it all times is his body.
You know, it lets you see him as a sexual being, which is how he sees himself. It just works really well.
And what people miss with Ellis and miss with the movie as well is that it is satire and he's
disgusted by these people. He's been around them. He hears what they say. People saying like, oh,
you know, putting this misogyny on screen or whatever. I have been in conversations with guys talking
about women, guys I liked guys I was friends with where I was like, holy shit. Like if that is your
view of women, my God. And that's what it puts on screen. That doesn't mean the writer is misogynistic.
It means the people, the behavior is misogynistic. They know that they're above that and they're trying
to expose that this horrible behavior goes on for people to be offended and say, no, you, the writer
or misogynistic is so stupid. It really is. It's just like being unwilling to do any work to read a
movie or a book and look behind the lines and just accepting everything in phase value. That's what we
started talking about at the beginning of this podcast. And American Psycho is a perfect example of it.
Do a little work. If two women made this movie, do you think maybe they're trying to say something
other than misogynists are awesome? That's probably not their goal, you know? Right, right, right.
Well, it's interesting to another thing that Brady Stone said in the
interview I was watching last night was he said that he thinks American Psycho is a very gay
film because he was like, he's like, Patrick Bateman is so fucking gay. I made him so gay.
Really, really like hung on that. So it's interesting. It's interesting. You know,
Brady Snellitz himself, a man that even though he won't identify his gay or straight or whatever,
he, you know, he was in a very long relationship with a man. So I always thought he was totally gay.
I never heard anything to the contrary. He said he prefers, he said he, I think he said something
on the lines of like, I don't care if you call me gay or straight or whatever. And I'm not picking one,
but I'm going to, you know, I'm just going to kind of do what I do. So anyway, two hogs way up
for American Psycho, it's a fantastic film and you should check it out if you've never seen it.
The unrated, I think, is the only version that's out now. You're not getting a ton more than you
are in the R rated, but, but, you know, why not do the R unrated if you can? Yeah, the bluer is one of
those where it's, it's always five bucks. You know, you can always get the unrated copy of five
bucks. I'm sure it's streaming on somewhere, but a lot of people have seen this movie. A lot of people
have requested it. To me, the only competition in terms of the best Brett Easton Ellis adaptation is
rules of attraction, which I think is a very underrated and fantastic movie. Yeah, but Ellis is hard
to get right. People do miss what he's going for and miss his tone. And I, I feel like this movie just
nails it beautifully. And I will read the book. I'm excited to see him put a rat into a woman.
Well, you won't see it. You read its words, but I'll, I'll say it in my mind. Yeah, yeah. Anyway,
all right, folks, that's our show. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell. And by the way,
I'm going to kick off the next episode, which will be a movie called, what is this thing called?
Boys of county hell. Boys of county hell. I keep wanting to say boys of summer.
All right, we will see you next time in hell, right gang?