I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's, oh boy, did you hear my voice crack right there?
Little, little RFK, folks, I saw a video today, Joe, before the podcast starts said, hey, let's keep politics out of it today, 12 seconds in, I sound like RFK, well, I'm not going to get into politics, but no, I saw a video on Instagram today, it was a, it was so funny,
it was a guy doing RFK eating Taco Bell, yeah, and it's just showing the food, you don't see the guy, and the voiceover is RFK, and he's like, he's like, I snuck out and got Taco Bell, my Uncle John used to take me to get Taco Bell, I used to say, why doesn't the cheese on top ever melt, it's very disappointing, it was really funny, man, yeah.
What happened to his voice? I know he had the brain worm, but what happened to his voice specifically?
I believe it is a direct result of cunnilingual throat cancer caused by his wife, Cheryl David.
Alec, was it, who, who originally, oh, it was Michael Douglas, they tried to say that he got throat cancer from going down on too many ladies.
No, no, on his wife, he just, he just put it on his wife.
Oh, he said he got it from his wife.
Yeah, and then he came back out and said, I shouldn't have said that, I spoke too soon, I'm sorry.
Turns out old Catherine wasn't happy that I said that I got cancer from her pussy.
Yeah, she's on set saying, can you send out a memo then to tell everybody to stop calling me stink crotch?
Yeah, I heard, you know, of course, the joke at that time, a lot of guys were like, oops, guess we don't have to do that.
Can I just say, I love it, ladies?
I love it too.
I love going down on a lady.
One finger up.
One finger's all it takes.
You know, some ladies might demand more, maybe they've been around a time or two, but one.
Welcome to.
Two in, you press up.
We'll see you in hell.
Because your hell is listening to Pat and I tell you.
We do what we do to a lady's vajayjay.
That's somebody's hell.
Press down on that lower tum -tum to get a little more pressure.
That would be somebody's hell, us having them cornered.
Just be like, wait, no, no, no.
It's kind of my hell, to be honest with you.
I like her to lift her butt up and then lower both cheeks into my waiting hands.
So I'm holding a cheek in each hand and then I can just sort of bring it to my mouth.
Like a big watermelon.
As Billy Ocean plays loudly on the stereo.
Get out of my dreams.
Get into my car.
It's.
The idea that it's upbeat, Billy Ocean.
Yeah.
Well, you think I was going to pick one of the sad Billy Ocean songs?
Caribbean queen.
Johnny Cash.
It's.
Lover of Caribbean queen.
What's the song he did?
What's the song he did for Jewel of the Nile?
Jewel of the Nile is.
Who's that lady?
Got a straight number nine.
Hold on.
I'll be your love.
Shining on you.
Have me your shine.
Bad and dab it out too.
I'll be your nice time.
Get him out of there.
It's when the going gets tough.
That's the song I'm thinking of.
That's his worst song.
Are we ranking?
I was just, I was just singing.
Get out of my dreams.
Get into my car again.
I was just singing the verse.
Uh, are we ranking Billy Ocean songs?
I guess.
I mean, that seems to be, seems to be what's happening right now.
Uh, yeah.
When the going gets tough, the tough gets going.
That's not a good song.
Let's be real.
I loved it.
I loved it as a kid.
And I loved that in the video, it was the cast.
It was Michael Douglas, Kathleen Turner, and Danny DeVito as the backup, uh, singers and
dancers.
Pussy cancer survivor, Mike Douglas, Kathleen Turner.
Now Kathleen Turner might've got Dick cancer with the way her voice sounds.
Yeah.
She's got a little RFK going.
I like they, you know, now obviously she doesn't look like she used to.
And I will say.
People are usually pretty nice about it aside from casting her in dumb and dumber too, as
a, you know, as a grotesque, um, cause she's still really sharp and funny.
And I don't, I don't feel like she cares, which is very appealing to me.
I love Kathleen Turner.
I agree.
Uh, I'm a big fan.
I I'm, I'm very pleased with seeing her, uh, resurgence that's been happening.
Yeah.
Um, I think that that's, that's really cool.
I think it's really cool.
That she's, you know, she was in that last season of, um, Jesus Christ.
I almost said Schrodinger's cat.
The fuck was the movie to show with Michael Douglas?
What was it called?
Back Douglas show.
The TV.
We did one where he was Benjamin Franklin.
That looked like the worst show I've ever seen.
Kaminsky's method.
Is that what it was called?
Oh yeah.
The Kaminsky method.
Yeah.
She, she played in the last season.
She played his ex wife.
And I thought that was a very fun.
Uh, throwback.
Throwback to all their past, uh, you know, co -starring vehicles.
I loved them together.
Few people did that.
I hate you.
I love you chemistry better, but, um, man, war of the roses to me is an all timer.
It's great.
That movie is so fucking much.
And DeVito directed the fuck out of it.
DeVito was a good director, man.
I don't know why he stopped.
He was excellent.
I mean, it seems to me like he, he just put so much into it.
It probably wore him out.
In addition to everything else.
He does like, I mean, he, he does some amazing shit in his movies.
He's a really talented technical director.
I remember I was at a party in Williamsburg when I first moved to New York and I had a
friend that lived in Williamsburg that was, you know, telling me at the time how great
Brooklyn was.
It was before Brooklyn was universally known as the, as the cool place to live.
And I was at a party in Williamsburg and, and, you know, a girl.
A girl dressed like, uh, you know, like she was going to start doing crystal ball readings
or something, you know, just super hipster or whatever.
Um, said to me, uh, Hey, Madam Ruby, could you grab me a Jack and Coke while you're over
there?
There you go.
If I could have thought of one, you know, genie lady, it would have been a funnier.
Anyway, Madam Ruby is the peewee woman.
Um, she, uh, she, we were talking about movies or whatever.
And she goes, who's your favorite director?
And I said, uh, said, I believe it or not, I really like Danny DeVito a lot.
Cause I was watching like a bunch of his movies at the time.
And she laughed at me and it was the most welcome to Brooklyn.
Fuck face, uh, moments that has ever existed being mocked for not saying the right director
to a woman shrouded in linen, you know, on a fucking warehouse bedroom party in Williamsburg.
I think I then said, you want to get out of here?
And she said, no, I want to go watch a Danny DeVito movie.
I'm gonna watch Matilda at my place.
Um, how I used to handle women like that.
I was, I was fresh from Missouri and in New York.
So I was kind of rough and tumble, you know, a little rough around the edges before she
even got that comment out.
I would have punched her sharply right in the baby maker, right in the tummy.
Okay.
And you do, you put one, you put your left hand on the shoulder.
Like you're going to say something kind of flirty.
And then just right in the stomach, you walk off into the party.
She doesn't even know what hit her and you're in a cab going home.
Yeah.
That's how you deal with these film types for the future.
These film times.
I will do that when I approach women, but I'll do the fake one.
Yeah.
Anytime I approach one for the first time, I do a fake punch in the stomach and then
I go, I gotcha.
And then she laughs and then I give her a noogie.
Yeah.
And we're off to the races.
I go.
You should meet, uh, um, my favorite director, Roman Polanski.
And I punch her.
You do an actual punch.
Yeah, I do.
We also come over and I'm like, what, what I was, I was just saying, I like
Roman Polanski.
I, uh, man, I'll walk up and gently pat their heads and kiss them on the lips.
Sure.
It's a very, I try that at a me, but the next time they're trying to correct me
over something, just passionately kiss them.
Not a passionate kiss, more like a, like an inappropriate father to, to son kiss.
Like just a, when I think father to son kiss, I think passionate.
So, I mean, that's just me maybe, but maybe how I was raised.
So that's how it is in their family.
It's a wild joke.
Uh, especially knowing what we now know about the deliverer of said joke, Jeffrey Jones.
Yes.
That he would dare be offended.
Yeah.
Um, folks on today's show, we are doing a very special, uh, tribute to a hero, a personal
hero of mine.
Um, perhaps Joe's, he can speak for himself, but certainly when, when, uh, obnoxious woman
at a Williamsburg house party asks me my favorite director.
Um,
very early in that conversation, I will be mentioning Mr.
David Lynch.
Yes.
RIP a legend, a hero, a man who did more to bring surrealism, weirdness, craziness to
the mainstream than really anyone else.
Yeah.
Uh, certainly in the film world.
Um, I was talking to Joe.
I was like, he had the tag of Lynchian, meaning like somebody says your last name plus Ian
and everyone knows what.
You mean by that.
And he had that tag by like his forties, just a fucking baller, a legend.
Uh, and we will be talking about what many consider his masterpiece new on 4k to the
criterion collection, blue belt.
And we will get there.
Yeah.
I'm excited to do this and, uh, rest in peace, David Lynch, rest in peace, DL, a guy like,
uh, you know, an artist like the Ramones or something, you kind of just assume they're
always going to be out there.
And then, uh, and it, I can't, I can still in disbelief.
He's gone.
It's, uh, well, all the more reason to hate these fires.
Um, I had heard that he had basically retired because of his asthma.
He was also a very heavy smoker.
So let that be a warning to you, but he had really bad asthma and then he died because
of the fires and the smoke.
You know, there was a day or two where the S the smoke and the difficulty breathing actually
got past the windows of your house and got inside.
And a lot of people skipped town for that, but I guess he couldn't because of his illness.
So it did essentially kill him or help him, but he had emphysema though.
He had very advanced emphysema.
Yeah.
I said asthma, but he had asthma and emphysema and yeah.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Variety of things.
Um, trouble breathing.
But then Ted Sarandos, the head of Netflix said,
said that David Lynch had privately been working on a limited series for Netflix.
That would be his final project.
And I don't know if that was something he was maybe, uh, directing from bed via satellite,
or if he was directing something within his home or if he had been directing it, but then
got sicker than he expected.
Maybe we'll get details at some point, but, um, I very recently listened to his audio
book room to dream.
And I talked about it on the show and I highly recommend it just because it's this very funny
push and pull between this woman who wrote his autobiography, trying to tell his story.
And then David Lynch interrupting her and talking like 40 minutes, not reading the book
that they're supposed to be reading, just telling you stories about his life.
Uh, it's a special experience.
If you have audible room to dream by David Lynch, you get the biography of him.
You learn about him, but you also get a whole lot about his creative process and meditation
and his life and his women and his money and all that kind of stuff.
Uh,
I, uh, I'm very happy that these clips of Lynch are, are resurfacing.
Um, they're all over Instagram now, but these just wonderful, you know, little 32nd to a
minute long clips of David Lynch, his take on things, his reaction to things, his philosophy
on things.
And nine out of 10 are him getting furious at some sort of thing.
Uh,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
It's the great one where they ask him about product placement.
What do you think of that new trend?
And he just takes the long pause and he goes fucking bullshit.
Absolute fucking bullshit.
Um, then there's the, the best one.
Everybody's favorite is, is the lady as he's shooting going, David, I think the scene's
too long, but what the fuck is this shit?
Who gives a fuck?
fuck how long a scene is i'm serious he's just he was a tried and true he was a tried and true
a true artist true artist in a world where every film set i've been on 95 of the people
despite how good they may be at their job but they spend all day slumped in a director's chair
like legs spread wide scrolling through their phone and tarantino banned phones on his set
christopher nolan banned phones on his set and you get the feeling if david lynch is trying to
give you an acting note and you pulled your phone out he would probably slap it to the floor
and there's something to be said for that these are our best directors and they remove the evil
distraction box from their sets something to think about um
i think uh yeah i agree and speaking of of artists and you know a director whose last
movie i did not enjoy but i do respect the man as an artist uh osgood perkins yes uh the trailer
for his adaptation of the monkey by stephen king the full trailer has now been released
uh it looks great and the reviews early are like are really praising it saying um
um
it's uh it's a new they said it's a very far cry from long legs they said it's basically a horror
comedy that all the deaths in it are like insane and it looks super fun man it looks goofy and fun
and and freaky and i'm excited for that movie that's that's that's what i'm excited for
osgood perkins has such a great style and if you look at his movies black coat's daughter i liked
a lot
uh long legs i liked a lot no you didn't we talked about it on here i liked it a lot i had
major issues with it i had major issues with him compelling a nun to do his bidding but
for by and large i really enjoyed the movie i think i my hog was up all right i know my hog was
up but all right i gave it four out of five probably three and a half closer three and a
half all right but um he's i love the i love the movie i love the movie i love the movie
i love the way he makes a movie i love the way it feels soundtrack vibes a picture you know
everything about it is working he's he's got the shamalan thing he struggles with story when
shamalan is on he's on don't get me wrong but he's yet to just master a screenplay so i'm hoping that
adapting a stephen king book is perfect for him um because i always wish shamalan would do more
adaptations because he's he's kind of lost his his gift but is the monkey a great story and which
book is it in
the monkey is in skeleton crew oh so i read it might have been the first stephen king story i
ever read i got a copy of skeleton crew when i was in the eighth grade i believe i was uh it was the
first stephen king book i ever got and uh i think i read the monkey uh first because it was one of
the shorter stories um but uh monkeys and i love a monkey uh but it's a good it's a good little
story it's fun
um but you know they're obviously expanding it quite a bit for for the movie the the story
itself is not yeah terribly long um and i might be misremembering but i feel like it's one of those
stephen king stories that sort of has you know the end just sort of trails off mysteriously it
doesn't have like a definitive like and then this happens yeah kind of ending i don't think uh but
i might be misremembering but yeah it's a good story
and uh certainly spooky and and we'll make for a good uh flick so i'm i'm excited about it
i have already forgotten it and we did it on this show i used to have a photographic memory by the
way um what was the movie that was an adaptation of a stephen king short story came out a year
maybe a year and a half ago we didn't like it it was about trauma man there it is
oh terrible
and a great story but a terrible oh god that movie sucked it really did it really did i'll
forget i forget most of the movies we've done at this point like i don't have a good
i i've never been good at cataloging things in my head but uh i'll i'll see a thing
for a move some shitbag movie that and i'll be like oh my god wait a minute i've seen this we
reviewed this and i've seen this and i've seen this and i've seen this and i've seen this and
when that came out man that movie sucked yeah that that can happen it's for me it's it's how
generic these titles have gotten and what we've discussed already on this show the fact they'll
reuse the title five times like they'll call a movie the boogeyman once a year for five years
in a row they just don't care anymore no no they really don't speaking of lynch folks i wanted to
say uh joe and i were originally going to do wild at heart on this show because joe had never seen
and it is kind of an under seen under appreciated an insane david lynch movie
um i owned a copy i opened it i watched it with my lady friend and then i looked online and it
was going for like 200 used um there will be a 4k of wild at heart coming out any day now i'm sure
they'll announce it because of david lynch's passing but like it was just more proof that like
when a great film director
dies you cannot find a very notable film of his starring nicholas cage laura dern and willem
defoe three actors who are still just as relevant you cannot find it on streaming again we've had
so many instances of this and then you go okay well i really want to watch it you go to amazon
you got to pay 200 to get a used blu -ray so i feel more and more happy with my physical media
collection every day i popped it open i was able to watch wild at heart i bought it for 7 .99 like
10 years ago i'm seeing oh jesus that's a laser disc i'm seeing a blu -ray for available at walmart
for 40 bucks yeah from shout from shout select
you
i have the shout one maybe that look maybe they upped the stock or maybe shout was like quick we
got to manufacture a bunch of them or something i'm just saying anytime you go to at the amazon
movers and shakers page meaning the movies that are like suddenly had a jump in sales
there's always it's always 20 movies of the guy who just died yeah and it's because you're like
oh i'll have a little streaming marathon of his best movies and you realize very quickly you can't
find them
even even the criterion channel who has put out every one pretty much of david lynch's movies and
i'm sure they'll do wild at heart at some point but they don't have it must be a rights issue or
something but anyway let's get to that movie corner joe what do you got today wait real quick
i have one more thing because we're talking about physical media uh people we are
huge proponents of physical media here at the we'll see you in hell show
but you got to be careful who you buy from and uh i actually have a post coming sometime soon on
instagram about this but i for for as much as we praise a lot of these outlets we buy from i want
to give you all a warning of who not to buy from do not do not do not do not purchase anything from
merch bar um merch bar is
a seemingly good service they will inundate your mailbox with all sorts of wonderful offers
and prices that can't be beat for things that you seemingly can't find a lot of the time anywhere
else um you will place an order your order will remain in the processing phase for months i
ordered things from them last october and as of
uh late january they were still processing i then emailed them and i had emailed a couple
times throughout that period and said what what is going on here guys like it's not even
the order isn't even processed it still says processing and they would say well you know
we're we're having a processing issue we're working it out we can't really give you an
estimated time for delivery now to their credit they did say you are welcome to do a refund if
you want and i said no i guess i'll just wait i already filled my coffee what was the
company merch bar merch bar okay i see them all the time and they seem too good to be true
yeah so i said there's a lot of these now on on especially on instagram being advertised and i
said okay so i waited finally january i said this is ridiculous i said just give me a refund
then got the uh we're we're overwhelmed uh with customer inquiries at the moment uh we sure you
are do our best to get back to you as soon as possible
i was furious because i was like well that's how this rub is going to go now that i've asked for
the refund they're going to say they can't process it because they can't get to it right i then waited
a couple more days and then emailed them again and in all caps just said refund my money and
then they immediately responded to that and said it's been all refunded which is a common tactic
used in customer service a lot of customer service things they'll they'll say wait until
they've complained x amount of times before oh yeah actually whatever
so um the point is is don't order from these people from this company i i then googled them
and there is reddit thread after reddit thread and and you know review boards saying merch bar
is a complete scam basically you know either they my theory is is they they promise you product they
don't have you buy it and then they do this we're having processing issues thing in the hopes that
you will just forget about it
yeah or ask for a credit you know we you know and then they have your money like i ran into that
problem with a t -shirt company recently on instagram it's it's a shame people we live in an
internet age but my god almighty you you can't just buy anything online you got it you know and
people i i get it i understand why people chastise amazon i get the problem but it is for the most
of us in the sense that you are getting what you are paying for and if there is a problem you are
able to quickly get that problem rectified yeah uh and and it is an affordable and but i get why
it's part of the problem i'm not saying it's not but you know uh these the the scam is on man
everybody is and now the scammers are in on collectible merch i never thought i'd see the day
that i'd see the day that i'd see the day that i'd see the day that i'd see the day that i'd see the
there was a massive amount of scammers running around in in you know in the in the world of
collecting media but there is and here we are so you got to be careful people i've i've heard
grove is the same way gruv is another uh blu -ray site that does the same kind of shit and i sell
lately 25 items a week on amazon and i gotta tell you
the amount of people who are just like i didn't get it full refund and then amazon just immediately
gives them a full refund that's happening in spades i mean everybody just realized it's like
the people walking right out of walgreens with their arms full of shit at some point people are
like wait there's no consequences to stealing and eventually that will be the end of society
the downfall of of the world yeah but for right now it's just like and i and i used to get so
angry i you know i'd be like it's very clear to me that you are stealing this stuff and i'm not
you know you you you filed two complaints with two different reasons that you want to refund like
it looks like you were drunk when you wrote your reason like there's a thousand misspellings in
three sentences and you still have to pay them so that sucks it really blows there's just scammers
everywhere i had you got to be careful with the atms now uh go to your bank's atm do not try to
pay with a debit card at a bank and you're not going to get a debit card at a bank and you're
a gas station because they have false fronts on them often put on there by the owner of the 7 -eleven
or the grocery store so i my bank of america told me i had a 500 charge at a sushi restaurant two
hours from my home that i've obviously never been to of 500 and even though i have had a bank of
america account for 43 years which my parents set up for me when i was born they refused it
and they said because we know you made this
transaction because you used your card i said but i didn't my cards in my wallet like i look at all
the business i've done with you please help me they finally said file a police report then we'll
know you're serious because nobody would file a police report against themselves because then
you'd know that they're going to investigate and i was like great i filed a police report can i have
my 500 back no i call it false fronts i i didn't i didn't quite understand what you meant by that
let's say you're at 7 -eleven and you buy a slurpee and a protein bar and and you scan your card
there is a plastic false front to the card machine that just grabs all your info your
expiration date your number and and keeps it um so it's doing both it lets you pay but it also
skims your info so that they can rip you off in the future jesus christ and when i i said to bank
of america like surely you've got a card that's a false front and you're at 7 -eleven and you buy a
you've heard of this there's like tons of this scam going on they're like yeah that's why we
don't pay stuff off as easily anymore and as quickly it's like okay but then why are you
accusing me of doing so i still didn't get the money back and i said all right after 43 years
i'm switching banks i have bank accounts with you savings everything i'm moving and then sure
enough they called my bluff i didn't i didn't have the time and energy to switch my bank account of
four decades so i just stayed there even though they robbed me bank of america i'll
i had an opposite experience maybe just uh luckily but um i had an issue with you know they had this
thing where you had to file for the f eidl or whatever the hell it was sure you know and i
filed through a site and site looked looked like a government site i thought it was on the government
site and and then at the end it was 350 and i paid it stupidly yeah and i was like i can't believe the
government is making us file this quickly and and and and and and and and and and and and and and
and they're charging it's such a scam yeah and it was a scam it wasn't the government it was free
to file and when i found out weeks later like you shouldn't have gotten charged i called bank of
america and immediately they were like here's we're putting the money back in your account
temporarily and then we will investigate and i haven't heard anything since now they the day
might come where they go we're taking the money back right but it hasn't yet so anyway folks um
let's get to that by the way they will do that they they gave me my money back and then eventually
took it back they do great that's fun let's go to the corn let's go to that old movie corn i saw
here did you see wolfman by the way no no let's let's save it for the show i i'm not gonna do it
i'm asking you a question no all right i'm just no i did not see it yet did you see it
i did not see it i did not see it i did not see it i did not see it i did not see it i did not see it
i did end of end of thought we will discuss it when it's on the show all right um folks i
watched all four parts of the new snl 50 documentary um i am not ashamed to say that
i unless i'm forgetting something i don't think i have not watched an snl since i was a little boy
um i still watch it if i if i'm out of town and i miss a couple of movies i still watch it
a couple months i come back and i catch up i'm not sitting in a chair two feet from the tv
watching it carefully taking notes it's a sunday morning show for tidying up the house
or this sketch looks funny i'll sit and pay attention to this one but we all know the
shows hit and miss we all know the shows had terrible periods um i think this is a surprisingly
strong period and i think the chapelle episode on saturday night was the best in several years
he did a 20 -minute monologue that was so much better
than his endless trans rants that have been the last three specials he doesn't mention that issue
at all he's just as shocking just as button pushing he did he goes now obviously you'd
have to be insane to joke about a a tragedy as as horrible and and and and destructive as the
los angeles fires you'd have to be just a maniac to make jokes about it and then he looks into the
camera and goes and then proceeded to make 10 great
jokes about the fires that like it showed his mastery you know they were shocking but but it's
they're so shocking that a laugh explodes out of you before you have time to think about whether
it's fucked up or not that's i heard uh i heard that monologue was amazing i haven't watched it
it's the best it's the funniest he's been in at least five years he was excellent and the sketches
were great too he i would assume he brought a few of his writers along because uh certainly in the
first half he had some great sketches
but um it is the 50th anniversary of snl i worked at snl i got to have that experience for like six
months and be behind the scenes and i idolized all these people when i was a kid and i was an snl nerd
for my whole life so i was pumped about this like four hour doc and i will say it was both great and
a bit of a letdown the first part is basically about the audition process and you have a lot
of big stars talking about the audition process and you have a lot of big stars talking about the
auditions and how they did and you see all these great old clips you see the people who didn't make
it you know jim carrey and uh henry zabrowski who i do not know but people always compare our
our podcast because they do a horror podcast last podcast on the left i think um they showed a clip
of henry zabrowski's audition and i my guess is he did not want this on the show but i don't know
he came out completely naked he's a big fat guy and he walks out naked and they're talking to the
producers and they were like nobody laughed nobody smiled he didn't get the job it was disturbing and
unpleasant and so so it's great you know it's like um you get to see the process of like how
you get to see jim carrey audition steven colbert audition people who didn't even get the gig
um loved it there's a whole episode devoted to the writing process that of course as a comedy
writer i ate right up i loved it um tina fey talks about the show and she talks about the
how like the pettiness and the competitiveness and the vindictiveness she thinks is what drives
good comedy and i i love that tina fey often says things that are very just according to today's
standards wrong and controversial but she's like no i think there should be a lot more of like i'm
gonna fucking ruin that woman and write a way funnier sketch than that fucking bitch or whatever
and um yeah in my 20s i liked that aspect of comedy now it makes me want to kill myself
the competition but um but then about halfway through and it is a four -hour documentary
in four parts they do the final episode is about the the worst year of the show the year where they
had anthony michael hall and robert downey jr and and and uh julie louis dreyfus and all these
and they couldn't quite figure out what the show was and that gets a full hour of this documentary
about the legend this legendary comedy institution
like this should have been five minutes we had a we had an off year like why why is the last hour
of this documentary focusing on the negative i found it very weird and then the third part
focuses only on the cowbell sketch and they have interviews with josh ham one of my favorite people
on earth they interviewed dave grohl they interviewed some rock musicians and comedians
and why is the cowbell sketch so famous and why does it hold on and great but you run out of steam
20 minutes in you're talking about a four minute sketch for an hour and 10 this should have been
in my opinion 10 10 minute short clips about the 10 best sketches in snl history there's been a
million do a vote on peacock .com for the 10 best sketches and then do a doc a little mini doc about
each one but um to me it felt like a little bit of a missed opportunity half the parts were great
half the parts i felt like boy this time could have been used better
but if you're a fan of snl you got to watch it it's on peacock it's a lot of fun
little trip down memory lane joseph um i just excuse me i have two uh
uh two quick ones first of which these are just rewatches because today technically is a rewatch
review uh with blue velvet uh but i rewatched uh anchorman my uh girlfriend had never seen it
and i said you got to see it and she said i want to i would love to and we watched it and uh my god
almighty the movie is still so goddamn funny and it gets weirdly more relevant as time passes like
the the commentary of the film uh the perspective and and and uh the take and the story all of that
stuff it's all more relevant by the minute in in the addressing of the story and the story of the
not just addressing you know toxic masculinity versus gender acceptance and gender equality and
all those things but also to the commentary on the unspoken commentary on being able to joke about
things that are extreme in an extreme fashion there there's so much of this movie that
you know theoretically in this
day and age would not skate by and i know people keep saying oh give me a break with the
you can't say anything i see a lot of people saying shit and it's like yeah but the people
that are saying that are all operating independently outside of a system yeah i'm talking within the
actual system of hollywood itself you you would not be allowed to make anchorman still to this
day you just wouldn't um maybe that'll change i don't know uh two even less anchorman two brings
yeah that actually is uncomfortable in spots but you know the point is is if you're making fun of an
extreme and horrid thing you need to exaggerate that thing that's how jokes work jokes are
exaggeration so the movie is just excellent excellently done i honestly think it's a comedy
that deserves like a criterion or something stamp on it i think it is a much higher level
uh sharper piece of material than most people give it credit for you know most people love the
movie but they love it because it's hilarious but i think there's a lot more to it than just that
and um excellently acted it's just great it's a great movie uh treat yourself watch it again if
you haven't seen it in a while or watch it for the first time if you've never seen it you're
gonna have a great time the reason anchorman should be in the criterion collection
is the same reason i think a movie like wet hot american summer should be in the collection
because comedy gets no respect nobody cares nobody goes oh that that's a comedy that changed
the landscape the way they do with dramas they don't care they think they're all stupid joke
machines so who cares what an american summer and anchorman essentially invented new kinds of comedy
and invent by the way invented and perfected in the same breath
mm -hmm like they just
it's not it's not the same to make a great like tootsie's a great comedy don't get me wrong
but it had precedence a movie like anchorman or wet hot american summer really doesn't
airplane maybe but where's airplanes criterion by the way you want to talk about a fucking
influential movie yeah i could talk about how comedy gets the short shaft for days and i won't
um i saw a movie that fucking blew me away and i knew it would the
second i saw the trailer it is called hard truths um it is an amazing director mike lee you can watch
everything he's ever done including like his early british tv work on the criterion channel
um i've seen many many of his movies his most famous is like naked with david thules is amazing
topsy turvy uh secrets and lies was a big oscar movie the year of fargo and this reunites him with
the star of that movie uh marion jean baptiste
she plays one of the least likable people i have ever seen in a film
and it is because of how sadly relatable she is uh i know joe and and myself have people a lot
like this woman this woman in their lives you have a person like this woman in your life and
you cannot stand to be around her but it's just it's that thing it's if somebody's in your family
and you've been around her for a long time and you've been around her for a long time and you've
been around them for years and years and decades and decades there's sort of nothing you can do
they're terrible but you're gonna have to keep seeing them and being around them
um so this is a movie about a lady who is ruled by her own anger depression ocd
uh at first it's kind of an as good as it gets type vibe where she's like at the grocery store
and starts snapping at the cashier and the people behind her in line and she's funny she's cutting
and her insults make you laugh and she's like i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know
and unlike as good as it gets this movie sticks with the realism of being that person and being
around that person because jack nicholson is so charming that by the end of as good as it gets not
only do you love him but you're rooting for him to fall in love with ellen hunt in this movie you
you you can't do much except hope that this woman dies or that the people around her get away from
her she's married to these these two actors it's a movie about a lady who's been around her for a
i had never seen either actor before but it's a man and her son is very overweight he's in his
teens he's very lazy and has no self -esteem her husband is a cuck he's a shell of a man he's empty
and then you learn very quickly why these men have no souls because this woman terrorizes them
everything they do in their own home is wrong and bad and they're they're all fat and dumb and lazy
and she lashes out
at everyone and this might not seem fun it is sort of a dark comedy at first
until it's not and that's the way with these mike lee these mike lee movies is
he lives with the actors for years and lives with them as the characters but also has fun
and writes in character with them so every movie is like a multi -year process so when you see these
films that the characters have so much more depth than certainly in your average movie
piece of junk that you watch but you just keep watching as this woman fucks up her life and is
mean to everyone around her and you don't know what to feel really you don't know what you are
feeling it starts to get claustrophobic and then it hits you with one of those endings like about
schmidt um that just sort of takes the wind out of you like it ended and there's only 20 people in
the theater maybe but nobody got up and it's not like we were waiting for samuel jackson to pop up
and uh give her her next
instructions for the next mission everyone just kind of sat there like
you know and if you like that sort of experience i do a movie that just you kind of can't get out
of your head for days i recommend hard truce it's a difficult but very rewarding movie i loved it
joe um my second and last film in the corner another rewatch a movie that in the past i have
defended
and over time i just realized i can't any longer unfortunately uh but uh again my girlfriend had
never seen any of the uh indiana jones pictures we watched all of them and had a wonderful
experience joe's girlfriend is six by the way he's not saying six years old uh
uh she so we watched all of them had a great time she loved them it was great
but i ended up skipping crystal skull we watched about the first movie and i was like oh my god i'm
the first 30 minutes and i was like look we're having a wonderful time here i'm loving watching
you fall in love with indiana jones and the last movie i really think is one of the best
and it's so emotional and it's such a beautiful end for the character i was like i don't want to
ruin this by making you sit through the second half of crystal skull because this is going to
get real goofy yeah kept having haunting visions of shia labeouf swinging over the screen and i
was like you saw all you need to know she's he gets back with marion and shia labeouf is his son
that's all you need to know and we can move on that's that's the only significant information
in this and um and we did and it was the right move and uh i liked that movie when it came out
i think maybe because i felt like i don't know i maybe i felt like there was never going to be any
more indiana jones and um i also was a staunch and am george lucas defender everybody was just so
mean to him and shitty to him now they're all screaming for him to you know it for about his
absence and how he needs to come back um but i you know i don't know i liked the movie enough
when it came out that i had you know i enjoyed it and i saw it many times in the theater and
i was excited when it was released on on home media
but my it's just especially after the last one that made such sense to me in the canon of those
films um that movie just doesn't make any sense to me anymore it's just it's got its moments
um but it's just it looks different it feels different it's just a misstep in many directions
and uh it just doesn't work um and you know that
that's that's really all i have to say it's sad bums me out but but what are you gonna do
i think it's a very strong franchise outside of that entry and for four out of the five to be
awesome you know you can't really ask for much more than that what's interesting what i found
with with my ex and different people i've dated and stuff is if you didn't grow up with it
whether it's because you're younger or you just didn't get to see him or whatever
you don't care as much about the huge drops in quality you don't feel them as much
because you're watching the movies with a 10 minute separation as opposed to a 15 year separation
yeah so i don't know i mean it's very possible your girlfriend would have watched crystal skull
and said oh this one's way way worse but sometimes it's like if you just watch them all today you
don't notice the dips which is crazy to me well she said as soon as we turned on dial of destiny
she immediately goes oh my god this already looks 10 000 times better yeah like that opening scene
where he they pull him out of the car and he's like oh my god this already looks 10 000 times better
out of the van he's got the hood on his head and they're walking past berlin buildings getting
bombed and what she was like yeah this looks like the other three yeah yeah it was like crystal skull
like you could tell it was like a lot of cgi and it looked weird and i was like yeah they tried to
make it like this 50s b movie it was just a misstep although i like the beginning of crystal skull
to some extent yeah the beginning's fine but i'll tell you the greatest misstep in crystal skull
is that they stray from the
formula not just aesthetically but they stray from the formula of every indiana jones movie is
supposed to begin with him at the tail end of another thing with another artifact and then
that experience somehow launches him into or ties into the main story and the main artifact
they don't do it in that one it starts immediately with the russians being like
we need this crate with the alien inside of it and it's like
that's it you're just it's just it's way too linear right it's it's it just doesn't have the
pace you know the fact that it opens with a fucking car drag race yeah yeah yeah you know
you're like you know which is sort of like temple of doom opening with the musical number but that's
just then it then he walks in and it becomes immediately awesome you know so i don't know
anyway i've been writing on spec
uh a movie where a 90 year old indiana jones is in like the cruising world the the william
friedkin al pacino cruising world uh he so he's got the whip and everything and you know he's like
i dress this way anyway how bad could it be and then we do a star wipe to him you know some guy
kind of lubing up his prick watching him across the bar you know in a pair of assless chaps and
it's like oh boy
i didn't sign up for this that's the teaser all right that kind of i'd watch it i've been
buttfucked before on adventures but not like this winks to the camera
wow getting buttfucked in the back fourth wall breaking in this new indie movie
there's this this uh guy comes up to him you hear a zipper sound effect
and he looks down and he goes snakes
usually i hate snakes and he just takes it in his mouth
folks i'd like to talk to you about uh a movie much like hard truths like i just talked about
that that movie was like each day that i get further away from having seen it
i find myself thinking about it more and more the sign of like a movie that's gonna last you know
i gotta say i watched this movie between the temples
on netflix which was this little very very indie romantic comedy
and it kind of worked the same magic on me i thought well that was cute that was entertaining
that kind of felt like an old like a hal ashby like a 70s movie and then with each passing day
i keep thinking about it and i find myself with a big smile on my face
um so
it's two different things hard truths is a movie that was kind of so dark and and true to life
that it hurt and it keeps making me think about harmful hurtful things sad things and this movie
just keeps making me smile and uh that's very important these days as well as we all know
highly recommend it it's directed by a guy named nathan silver um it is a movie starring jason
schwartzman who
you know i feel like i've kind of grown up with when i saw rushmore i was basically his age and
now you know he's a middle -aged dude it's like it's weird you know it's weird when you see your
little cousin and she's suddenly 10 years older time and life is weird but it's jason schwartzman
he's uh you know 40 year old dude his wife has passed away and he teaches gets you know prepares
people for the bar mitzvah he's very active in his life and he's a very active person and he's a
church or i'm sorry excuse me his synagogue um robert smigel one of my favorite comedy people
of all time of course one of the head writers of conan he was the voice of triumph the insult comic
dog he plays a fellow um you know uh person at the church he's very good he's very funny
but the movie really belongs to jason schwartzman and carol kane carol kane i've always loved you
know she always plays a coup
whether it's scrooged or whatever she's always like kind of an unhinged woman in this movie she
plays about as normal a person as i've ever seen her play she wants to get her bar mitzvah or bat
mitzvah um at her age she never got it so she goes to jason schwartzman to teach her and kind
of be her guide her sponsor through getting her bat mitzvah and she used to be his teacher in
school she was his music teacher they have this great chemistry
the two people and also schwartzman and kane have an amazing chemistry together
and you watch it's very harold and maude you watch these two people who are
you know at least 30 years apart slowly fall in love with each other and build respect for
each other and feel safe around each other and it's a very realistic rom -com it's a true indie
it looks like this thing cost you know maybe half a mil i don't know that for sure but it's a very
but it looks and feels like a true independent movie and it's very very charming and funny
it's on netflix um and it's a very sweet pro -jewish movie at a time where it must be
fairly horrifying to be a jewish person i highly recommend between the temples joe
all right that's our oh sorry that's our corner let's get to the movie at hand
david lynch's blue velvet uh
many consider it to be the quintessential david lynch film i think it is the film
where david lynch fully becomes david lynch i was talking to my buddy adam egott uh of the
norm mcdonald podcast and the norm mcdonald book and now the uh booker and entertainment director
over at the mothership here in austin texas uh great guy his favorite director of all time is
david lynch his favorite movie of all time is mahalan drive and we were talking about blue
velvet and the blue velvet and the blue velvet and the blue velvet and the blue velvet and the
blue velvet last night i was telling him we were doing it on the show and i said that sentence to
him and he said well i think lynch was was already lynched before that and i said well what i mean is
uh you know eraser head obviously is as lynch as you can get but but that's also
it's the first thing out of the gate it's the it's the art house movie that he made it's it's
very much a director's first effort um where they're able to just kind of let their
freak flag fly and then they get noticed um then he did two major studio movies he did elephant man
then he did dune yeah and after dune he said i'm done i'm going back and doing the shit i want to
do and he made blue velvet and and to me that's the movie where in the mainstream he's already
known he's he's got that to a certain extent the the studio system behind him
he says this is the kind of thing you're going to get out of me from now until the day i die
and um i think blue velvet very much represents that and i also think it's interesting because
it is a perfect sort of fence straddling movie for david lynch in the sense that the first half
of the movie plays it's it's it's got its aesthetic and everything obviously but but it
is very straightforward sort of representing where he had been over the last years that had
the recent years that had led up to him making this movie and then the second half of the moments
pop out like you know the chicken walk and then he does a chicken walk you're like what what did
i just say moments pop out yeah little things you're not watching a procedural but yeah for
sure yes i know what you mean and then the second half which kind of starts when dennis hopper
enters the picture
is when ladies and gentlemen it becomes you know i was saying to to jamie when we were watching i
was like i go this is i go this is the moment where you you you're you it becomes a david
lynch movie like this is where it starts like yeah hopper comes in that insane scene with him
and isabel rossolini and then you know all the you know when every everything from there on out
that's where he starts doing the lynch camera tricks and yeah and and you know it just feels
very very you know twin peaks at that point on so weirdly though in this rewatch blue velvet
i think throughout is a much more straightforward movie than i remembered it being because of how
insane it seemed when i was a kid well holland drive which i rewatched last night feels way
more experimental and bizarre than blue velvet um but
yeah it's like it's it's all the more effective because dennis hopper even though he's inhaling
nitrous oxide he's not really played for laughs he's played as one of the most horrifying people
alive well uh like you know he's he's amazing in that movie and of course then he got nominated
for hoosiers and not blue velvet kudos to dennis mill dennis mill dennis hopper's uh
performance in this movie because um he you know actors i've heard a lot of actors say over the
years you know um well it's easy to play crazy anybody can play crazy because you can just do
whatever and it's like well i don't agree with that i don't think it's easy to play crazy i
think it's easy to to play crazy and and have it be hammy and stupid uh it's real hard to
play crazy and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and
and play crazy convincingly and the fact that he goes as big as he goes in this thing and takes
the swings he takes and they land and you aren't going this is an insane performance what is he
doing you're watching it going i'm terrified of this person yeah uh that is a huge testament to
what an actor dennis hopper truly was um you know and he famously went to david lynch and said i
have to play frank booth because i am
frank booth david lynch was like then i don't know if i really want to work with this guy but
um yeah he he embodies it i mean when when in in the most famous scene in my favorite scene when
dean stockwell is performing in dreams the orbison song and he's doing that thing where
he keeps closing his eyes like he can't stand the power of the music but it's also like this
is just a guy who can't handle life you know like he's always clenching his eyes and like
oh i'm gonna explode you know um it's unlike it's unlike any other performance it's one of the great
villains you're you're so scared for rossellini then you're so scared for mclaughlin i watched it
alone i've seen blue velvet 10 times and every time after kyle mclaughlin fucks isabella rossellini
and he's walking out of her apartment and it cuts to dennis hopper then walking in my heart just
sinks this time out loud i went oh
no and i knew it was coming yeah but the dread in these david lynch movies that that's
maybe the top emotion he he gets is dread and it's such a hard thing to pin down but he understands
it so well just this feeling of like oh no and that's blue velvet i i had so like so many nights
out in missouri with like a bunch of drunk dudes where at a certain point you look around and
you're like this night has gone bad
and i need to get out of here that's the whole feeling of like the back half of blue velvet
and it is very funny it's got a dark humor to it it's doing that thing you know very explicitly of
look what you know american beauty did it years later but like look what's under the surface of
suburbia but that opening like short film which by the way looks amazing in 4k uh but the roses
and the white picket fence and everything and then the guy has the heart attack and then
the dog's
yapping at his hose or whatever that's a masterpiece of a short film before the movie
even starts it sets up the theme that it's not just a little theme piece because that guy winds
up being kyle mclaughlin's dad um but it's just perfection you realize unlike dune which was not
exactly uh david lynch at his most confident you just feel like you're in the hands of a master
from the opening seconds of blue velvet and he doesn't let it up it's so good i always talk about
the three movies in the 80s that i set my alarm for the middle of the night snuck them downstairs
and watched like with my ear up to the speaker do the right thing which is where you know in my
12 year old self basically learned about race since i had never really met a black person before
in missouri um good fellas which is where i was like okay i want to be a writer i want to make
films i've never seen anything like this this is the best i love this and then blue velvet
which was where i basically learned about a whole nother alternative lifestyle like even the sex
they are into in this movie i was unaware of when i saw this movie so i mean this movie introduced
major things to me major ways like i basically was like oh there's a whole nother way to live
there's a whole nother way to be um you know i grew up
very much like laura dern or kyle mclaughlin very straight -laced religious you know had to dress up
to go anywhere and it was almost like in real time learning like you don't have to live your
life in this boring fucking 50s pleasantville way there's a crazier more fun more experimental
more dangerous world out there for you um so i mean the the movie now i watch it and i'm like
where does it rank amongst david lynch's greatest stuff but
this is the first thing i saw of his and this this changed my life in a very big way no question
when i saw blue velvet it's uh it's a it's it's a great movie uh the basic premise is is kyle mclaughlin
uh is home from college finds an ear in a field that he walks through every day to get to the
hospital where his dad is um and he brings the ear to the police the police say thank you very much
and we need you to back out of this now let it go forget about it we'll handle it from here
he doesn't believe well it's not that he doesn't believe his curiosity
which the detective even says to him it's the reason i'm in detective work is curiosity
uh he lets it get the better of him and he decides to investigate
uh in that investigation he is led to a lounge singer named isabella rossolini
he finds out that uh her husband and child
have been kidnapped by a gangster named frank booth excuse me played by dennis hopper
it is her husband's ear that he had found and uh there's basically a drug ring happening in
this small town uh of of beautiful uh peaceful americana that nobody knows about and uh he gets
wrapped up in it and eventually things come to a head obviously uh you can you can watch the movie
yourself and you can watch the movie and you can watch the movie and you can watch the movie
yourself for all the the finer details of the story but that's basically the gist of it um
it's uh the ending i'd like to talk about because
it's you know things come to quite a violent end in this movie um and in the epilogue you see that
kyle mclaughlin and laura dern who is the detective's daughter um are now together
boyfriend and girlfriend uh they've they sort of court each other throughout the movie but she's
got this kind of psychotic uh preppy boy boyfriend um that she eventually gets rid of and falls in
love with kyle mclaughlin kyle mclaughlin had gets sexually involved with isabella rossolini
in the movie but ends up with the woman he loves played by laura dern uh they're at a barbecue at
laura dern's father's house
the detective he and his wife are there kyle mclaughlin's parents are there his dad is now
out of the hospital and and better uh after some horrific accident where he needed a tracheotomy
um and you see laura i'm sorry you see isabella rossolini in a in a park and her son is there
and her son is playing and they embrace and it's beautiful whatever i think that the end
is not real i think it is a very
realistic you know wouldn't it be nice if things all ended up like this uh in life but but
in reality her son is probably dead or severely damaged kyle mclaughlin's probably got ptsd
and is is a manic paranoid mess because of what he's experienced violent wise in this
yeah uh laura it's it's so smart to not take us into the room in that in dream scene
you just you just you just you just you just you just you just you just you just you just you just
hear the son's voice say like one like mommy yeah immediately you're like i don't need to know
what is going on in that fucking room and that's lynch you know he can go he goes so extreme with
shit you know like you're seeing some of the most extreme jaw -dropping visuals you've ever seen
but he also knows that a little boy saying mommy in the distance as a door shuts is going to be
a hundred times more effective than showing you something fucked up in that room he just
he's a master um yeah and you know it's it's it's and he that's interesting you think you think
that's a fantasy hundred percent from which point i think it's i think it's i think the beginning
indicates the end and it does bookend at the beginning you see this beautiful serene street
in suburban america it's shot so
rockwellian that it's absurd there's a fire truck going down the street with a man waving
directly into camera at you yes um and then that is met with a guy watering his plants having a
massive coronary yeah and the camera pushing in pushing in pushing in on the grass until underneath
the grass you see all of the disgusting bugs and the insect ecosystem and everything like that
and it's telling you
right there it all looks like it's okay but it's not there's a there's something happening under
the surface here at the end of the movie when all is resolved and frank is killed um they show that
sequence with the fire truck they show i think they go back to it if i'm not mistaken and it's
got this perfect little suburban american life end where the boy gets the girl the the the sick
man is all better the mother is reunited with the son
of allah and the uh and allah in the film and then they just have a gunshot and they shoot the
boy at the end of the movie this is like no the this is what we would like to think happens at the
end of this yeah but these people just went through a horrid emotionally devastating experience this
is not all perfect like that there's i i think you could very well be right um and i've seen the
movie a bunch but that i don't know that that ever really occurred to me certainly not in the same
way it does in mulholland drive where i very actively try to decide what is fake and what is
real and what is dream and what is reality when i watch that movie but to me at the end when when
rossellini hugs her kid in the park and you're like okay happy ending but then it stays on her
and her expression changes and it goes but i still can see blue velvet and that's how it ends
so i took that as as real but um she's going to be haunted and tormented by this experience for
the rest of her life so i think you know we basically just disagree on on whether or not
lynch is showing us that as a fantasy or not i thought that final moment was basically like
yeah things look okay but they're not um either way we're kind of saying the same thing but also
there is that animatronic bird outside of kyle mcclaughlin's window that certainly would lend
credence to your theory that it's a fantasy sequence yeah um but then it could have just
been 80s or just
being weird or something but this movie does not take the same flights of fancy that like a
mulholland drive does where it's like bobbing in and out of of reality and consciousness and all
that kind of stuff it's weirdly very much in the real world which is what makes it so disturbing
um i read on my letterbox this week i follow paul schrader who actually writes great reviews on
movies even new movies so if you're on letterbox follow paul schrader especially if you're a
a fan but when lynch died he said uh dino dilorentis the famous producer gave him the
script of blue velvet and was like there's clearly something here but you know it's not a it's not a
real movie i need you to do a pass and he was going to pay paul schrader like a million dollars
to do it because he recognized that there was potential for a successful film and schrader
sent the script back to dino dilorentis and said the script is perfect there is not a single thing
i could do to improve upon it i would love to take your money but i cannot and then on only then
dilorentis said all right here's your money david lynch i guess i'll trust paul schrader
and a beautiful moment from paul schrader because screenwriters are very backstabby people who
generally aren't that kind but it's true i mean a master of like difficult screenplays paul schrader
read this and was like i can't improve upon it and it is it's sort of
for what it is you know american beauty would would explore this same territory a lot of movies
explore the same territory uh desperate housewives is probably the most commercial
um but nobody did it better nobody did it better he says exactly what he wants to say in that
opening five minute brilliant scene and then proceeds to just flesh it out for you in the most
beautiful way um everybody in the movie is excellent i just saw this clip
of david lynch at a film festival it must be a big one because they're all in tuxedos
and roger ebert is complimenting him on mulholland drive and he says you know
david i gave it three and a half stars i really you know which is also just kind of ebert being
a dick like it wasn't perfect but you know and lynch has given him kind of the cold shoulder
he seems like he wants to punch ebert in the face even though ebert is telling him how much
he loved mulholland drive and then i remembered that ebert
brashed blue velvet and it's one of the great reviews to go back and watch because it's one
also one of the only reviews that ebert ever apologized for and said he was wrong
but he was so pissed at david lynch for exploiting isabella rossellini she's asked to walk full
frontally naked uh in a yard and there's no narrative purpose for it and it's done it's
only there to titillate and it's like boy you really missed the boat there especially for a
who's been a champion of nudity his whole life it's like so you don't mind if a woman's like
naked fucking a guy for a 20 -minute sex scene but when lynch uses it for an actual artistic
and disturbing purpose it bothers you so much that you need to lash out at the filmmaker
instead of like analyzing this complicated emotion that comes up and that's what lynch does for a lot
of people he brings up shit in you that you're like wait a minute do i like this am i like this
um
it's great i i love the man i don't think blue velvet is his best after watching mulholland
drive last night that is the masterpiece for me and the embodiment of david lynch but blue velvet
is certainly his best like straddle of a straight movie and a lynch movie it walks the line
perfectly better than twin peaks even it just it's got such control of tone in this movie
yeah it's a great flick there's a reason
it's the one that people go to uh it's the reason there's a reason why it's the the real breakthrough
for him people would say that's the elephant man but it but it's not because that is not the style
of movie he continued to make the style of movie he continued to make was blue velvet
yeah this is where in my opinion again david lynch is born uh you need to see it if you're
a fan of the man you should see it even if you're not uh might turn you into one um and rest in
peace david lynch
you will be missed terribly um we'll be back next episode with conclave a movie about the pope
uh you know there's not much more to say than that uh we'll also uh since they just came out
i gotta gotta do a hot hot off the press news alert but since they just came out we'll also
be discussing the oscar nominations they just dropped uh on the next episode as well and for
those of you who listen to the solo movie corner this month's we'll be back next week with a new
will be a special tribute to david lynch and i will be discussing all the non -blue velvet movies
in his filmography uh i am at what am i at the patrick walsh at instagram we are at see you in
hell pod on instagram uh thank you so much everybody for your patreon support and we will
be back to discuss conclave joe uh jodorosa .com for all tour dates please come out and see me
whenever you can uh sadly some dates are going to have to be moved and canceled uh due to some
family stuff i'm dealing with i will alert all of you on that as soon as i know exactly what's
happening um and uh in the meantime uh you know just keep your eye out come out to the stuff that
is happening and and i apologize to the stuff that needs to be rescheduled um if you're in
new york go to joey roses joey roses .com and uh that's it
folks we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell