Hey folks, welcome to We'll See You in Hell, it's the podcast about movies.
My name's Joe and my name's Pat Walsh.
That is today.
We're going to be discussing Jacob's wife.
Yes.
Uh, Jacob is a friend of mine.
Joe's we, you know, we, we gave him subtle hints when they were dating.
Jake, this girl is a mess and now they're married and we need to discuss it.
I agree.
I, um, by the way, regret greatly, immensely regret not making the joke on
the green night episode, that it was the sequel to Martin Lawrence's black night.
You did.
I don't think I did.
Did I then, then I made it to you in person over text from the theater.
Whoever does the minutes, uh, of our show, please let us know.
Yeah, we might've just discussed it.
I saw black night theatrically that I, that's why I know it wasn't on the show.
I remember that text coming back.
I saw it in the theaters.
Yeah.
So, and, and I may have seen it alone.
You, you, I think you were the one person that saw it.
Well, this was coming on the heels of nothing to lose and, uh, blue streak.
And, and Lawrence was, was a viable comedic star, but, uh, you just
named two horrific films.
I thought you loved nothing to lose.
Nothing to, I've never even seen it.
Tim Robbins, Marty Lawrence.
I've watched, I've seen clips.
It's up there to me with, uh, what's the Chris Tucker, Charlie Sheen, one
double trouble or something like that.
Uh, no, that's money talks.
Yeah.
That they're up there with Mo money by Damon Waynes.
Like there's a lot of these like sort of half thriller, half comedy.
I didn't see money talks.
I know I did, I didn't see Mo money.
I did see money talks also theatrically.
And that movie was horrible.
Um, but nothing to lose is a very funny comedy.
And I think you'd agree if you'd just sit down and watch it and, and
open up your mind a little bit for watching goddamn life.
What's the one with Lawrence and DeVito?
That's what's the worst that could happen.
Just random cliche phrases.
They just throw it on the script.
Almost anytime a movie is a question, it's bad.
Like that, what, like what's that?
Uh, Sarah Disco Parker went like whatever happened to the
Millers or something.
It's like, Oh God, disagree on this.
Who's next?
No, that was your next.
Okay.
Nevermind.
Uh, it's not, it's yeah, it's not your next, it's your next.
It's not top of the muffin to you.
No, it is.
Yeah, I, I agree.
I agree.
Uh, Pat, how are you doing in life on a personal level?
Uh, subpar.
Subpar, but, um, I had been not even showing up to the damn golf course.
So subpar is an improvement, you know, I, uh, I feel slightly better.
I feel like I'm coming out of the dark into the, the extremely dark gray.
So I'm not like, you know, dancing into the end of the sunlight, but I do feel
when I wake up, like, I want to continue with the day to some degree,
which is a step up.
Yeah.
You're not doing a Phil Collins dance into the light.
No, what is dancing to the light?
Is that a solo Phil?
It was one of the solo albums.
It's when he started to take a more positive approach to the records instead
of just being his like grizzled face, you know, and the album opening with like a
six minute homeless epic on housed, but yes.
Oh, is that the, that's the new term on how everybody's just doing things
that, uh, George Carlin pointed out 30 to 40 years ago, which was what he was
like, it's, it's, it's homelessness.
Isn't it's not homelessness.
It's houselessness.
A home is a state of mind.
It's right.
It's a sense of something that house is a physical, tangible structure.
These people need houses.
Uh, is that why they go with unhoused?
I just, I just thought it was like, Hey, it's, it's been 50 years that we have
to change the word like that's sometimes what it seems like.
No, it's more fucking pussy bullshit about, you know, homeless is, I assume
homeless is now offensive in some way.
So now they're going to say unhoused, which somehow sounds houselessness
sounds right to me.
Unhoused sounds vague and blurry and convoluted to me.
Unhoused sounds like the label they'd put on the rabid German shepherd that
they're trying to sell at the, you know, it's like, it sounds like it's an animal.
And I think that it sounds way worse than homeless.
Then again, it might just be what I'm used to, but I also haven't heard anyone
say unhoused except, you know, politicians.
So who knows how much it's catching on.
Language is changing by the minute.
The other day I saw an unhoused sex worker and I went up to they.
It's a lot.
I feel like I'm staying on Twitter just so I know the terms because it's, you
know, like the old, the old nightmare of walking up to perform and you don't
know your lines and your dicks out or whatever.
I have that with like walking up to a group of people and being like, you
know, hello, my Latin X friends.
And then they're all like, are you fucking kid?
Like Latin X was two years ago, you know, and I do try to keep up and I, uh,
I do my best and I don't think it's silly.
I think that, you know, you should call people what they want to be called.
However, I don't disagree with that.
I think the it's relentless.
You know, I think the social mandating part of it is silly.
I think taking it too seriously is silly.
I think, I think I will call you whatever you want me to call you.
Absolutely.
I a hundred percent respect that.
But, um, I think, you know, the people look, it's never the
position.
The homeless guy is never going to go unhoused.
Thank you.
It's always the white guy with a lot of money.
That's going to be like, excuse me.
Did you just call him?
It's like, no, the guy needs a hot dog.
He doesn't give a shit right now.
You know, that's the truth.
I, in trying to cut down on, on internet shit, I started looking at next door.
Like maybe I'll, I'll learn about my community or whatever.
And man, that's where I saw the Bruce.
The lunch post this, uh, I mean, there was a guy and he's like, Hey, there's
a man on my street who threatened me or whatever, uh, six one, blah, blah,
blah, Latin X.
And it goes into the comments.
And I see there's a hundred and 116 comments and I'm like, Oh no, sure
enough, the guy who posted it had a, had a very Hispanic name.
He says Latin X and then who's in the comments.
But tons of white people, tons of Hispanic people arguing.
And by and large, the Latin X community is saying, stop calling us Latin X, at
least in an informal poll of people in my neighborhood, and then there's white
people saying, well, that's what it should be called now.
It's not about race.
It's about gender to a next person.
And then he's like, excuse me.
Rightly so.
Yeah.
And I'm reading down and I'm like, Oh no, this is Twitter.
I might as well just stayed on.
Yeah.
It's all just Latin X to me sounds like some kind, it always makes me think of
that David, uh, David, uh, uh, not Lynch.
Who's the other day?
The Cronenberg movie, extinctions, the weird Z's in it.
Existence.
Yeah.
I didn't like it back then.
And I watched it recently.
I don't like it now.
Existence.
That's like, he's doing an abbreviation of existential.
Yeah.
It's like a game.
It's like a VR game at look, the movies, it was ahead of its time.
It just doesn't mean it's, it's very entertaining.
Gotcha.
Um, I went to bed last night at 8 p .m.
Okay.
After a Chinese food for lunch and dinner yesterday from two
different restaurants, same order.
What'd you get?
Give me an idea where I'm at.
Spare ribs and egg rolls.
Uh, I enjoyed it so much at lunch.
I went back for seconds at dinner at a different place.
The lunch serving was better.
Got the lunch serving from wo hop classic, uh, Chinese food, like
an Americanized Chinese food joint here in New York and Chinatown though.
Uh, you know, a staple, one of the old, one of the old staples here.
It's amazing, uh, food, but, uh, uh, and then, uh, you know, I ate it.
I watched, what did I watch?
Well, I'll talk about it in the movie corner, maybe.
Uh, and then I went to bed at 8 p .m.
and, and laid in my bed and, and, uh, fell asleep.
Okay.
Woke up around 1 30 a .m.
With rousing anxiety about the bar I'm about to open.
Sure.
Uh, and the fact that I said to a tile person earlier that day, thanks
man, and God forbid she doesn't identify that way, you know, you're, you know,
you're in a store full of pipes and tiles and it's a, for all intents
and purposes, a guy behind the counter.
You, you, you think, Hey, thanks pal.
Right.
But who knows?
Yeah.
So I'm scared I'm going to get canceled for buying tile inappropriately.
Um, it's just a, it's just a whole thing anymore.
It's just, yeah, I think it's all in our heads, but as we were talking
about the changing times, there's just more opportunities to, to mess up.
You know, that I hope you get that we're trying to do good in the world, but
I hope you get that, uh, you know, spare ribs and egg rolls was the, uh, first
draft of the Frazier theme, toss salads and scrambled eggs, and, uh, Kelsey
just couldn't wrap his, wrap his lips around it.
I was going to say it was, uh, it was a discarded, uh, Austin powers joke.
She went, she grabbed me spare ribs and egg rolls.
Uh -huh.
Okay.
Uh, I think, um, there's still talk of a new one.
And then I also am dying to see what's going on with this sketch show.
It's the kind of thing with Myers.
Wait, what's your show?
He's doing a full sketch show.
Myers for Netflix.
Really?
He's playing like 10 characters.
Then they, they all interact with each other and so forth.
It sounds like I, you know, something I'd be excited about, but something
that could be a huge, huge disaster.
That's, that's where he's at.
Everything's either an F or an A at this point.
Which speaking of one guy playing many characters, interacting with one
another folks, we decided last night, we in the near future, maybe even
in the next round of EPS, we will be reviewing Norbit officially on the show.
I rewatched it the other night.
Pat said, I'm going to give it another go.
I said, I think the fans would enjoy an official review of this.
Let's really get into this picture.
We're going to do it.
I saw it in the theater when I first moved to LA, uh, and I remember
pretty much only Eddie Murphy playing the Chinese man and my mouth being
on the floor, the audience laughing hysterically, and I'm excited
to see how it holds up.
I tweeted about it last night and I was shocked at the wave of love.
Really?
People writing to me like, anytime I'm down, I put Norbit on it picks me right up.
So anyway, what'd you tweet about it?
I don't want to say, well, I guess you could see it.
If I don't want to spoil it, let's say for the episode.
Anyway, we're talking about Norbit by the way, because a Joe was watching it,
but be the director of Norbit, who also was one of the leads of head of the
class, one of the students on the original head, the bad kid, not the bad
kid, but like the, you know, like the, the Fonzie type kid, right.
Uh, he is now the head of Paramount pictures, which is like, man, I was
talking with Joe, I'm like, you know, yeah, you know, you try to make your
way in the world and you're worried about something you said 15 years ago,
coming back to buy you.
And the man who directed Norbit is direct is, uh, in charge of Paramount pictures.
They also announced for a little, uh, screaming in that Paramount has basically
decided we're stepping away from the film game, we're going to focus on
to bolster the Paramount plus app.
And that's going to be most that in their announcement, they say it's going
to be mostly reboots, sequels, um, going into our rich history or rich Paramount
library, they're done, uh, Paramount was one of the three, you know, you'd go
to a movie when you're a kid, you'd see Paramount, you go to a movie, Raiders of
the Lost Ark, all the Indiana Jones movies would dissolve from the Paramount
to an actual mountain.
Exactly right.
I'd be, I'd be homesick.
I always put on Ferris Bueller and Raiders of the Lost Ark.
That was my go -to Paramount back to back.
They did comedy, they did action.
And now it's just going to be, you know, a three picture deal with
TikToker Madison Gabu.
Yeah.
I mean, it's, it's, it's just crazy and the shit they're rebooting that
not just Paramount, everybody.
It's like, what other awful UPN series are you going to reboot that people
barely cared about the first time?
It's like, it's like, they're doing, they're, they're like doing like
serious, hard edged, Xena reboots now and shit like that.
It's like, guys, this was supposed to be absurd.
Like this was like dumb fun.
I turned on HBO Max the other day.
They got a Walker Reap, Texas Ranger reboot on there.
I'm like, this can't be based on the Chuck Norris TV show.
And then you click on it.
It's like based on the never award winning Chuck Norris TV show.
I mean, based on the mocked for decades, Walker, Texas range.
It was the whole segment on Conan making fun of Walker, Texas range.
But that I get, there's a lot of old guys who love Walker, who like,
Hey, they got the new Walker on.
I get it.
But like Eraser was the one I pointed out to Joe yesterday.
Arnold's, anyone listing off their top 20 Arnold movies is never getting to Eraser.
It's no, it's not a good movie.
The whole trailer.
This was in his quip days.
He shoots an alligator and he goes, your luggage.
Yeah.
Which is like the most average below average quip, especially for Arnold
only topped by the six day as for bad Arne Arnie movies.
That's that's at the tip, like that, that, that tail end before he became
governor, those three or four movies are worse than the ones he did when he
returned and not all the ones he did when he returned were bad, but there's
certainly were not what he used to do.
Um, I stopped seeing them.
I know people liked like Maggie, you know, the zombie one and he's been in stuff
that people kind of enjoyed, but I never heard of one that was great.
So I dropped out a while back.
Same with Willis.
Yeah, I was literally in, in to be originals.
Now they take movies that he made five years ago and they're like a premiering
on to be like, that's where he's at.
We'll do it to himself.
New movie.
I Bruce Willis's new movie is called midnight in the switchgrass is the name
of the movie up there with hotel for dogs, as far as worst titles I've ever heard of
a movie that's really bad.
Um, it stars him and Megan Fox as FBI partners.
This is the movie that machine gun Kelly and Megan Fox started their affair on
all right, the two most despicable people on planet earth, in my opinion.
I assume he saw the photo last night of her basically in a pair of panties
sucking on his tongue.
Yeah.
It was just so fucking.
And then the kind of thing where I age 20 years, just looking at the
photo, I became like a guy in a porch, like, you know, in my day, a woman would
put on a Lacey frock and go to the box social and everybody respected her.
It's literally to the point where you're going in my day, she'd wear a leather
mini skirt that barely covered her hooch.
And we loved it.
That was enough for us.
Now she's naked.
Bullet straps over our nipples.
We were happy with it.
The, um, yeah, this movie also stars.
This is heartbreaking.
This movie also stars a meal Hirsch who no relation to judge Hirsch, but let me
stop you beat a woman in a restaurant.
He strangled a woman.
No, no, no.
Let me, let me finish what I was going to say.
I think this is what he has now been reduced to because of that incident.
And it's like to see an actor of that caliber in a movie like this is, is so sad.
I'm not saying he didn't do anything wrong or, or didn't do this.
I'm not saying anything like that.
I'm just saying like, it's that guy, that guy, you know, that guy was into the
wild, like this is like, he should, you know, it's like, Jesus Christ, man.
Like, yeah, he's, he's one of the few where you hear the reason and you're
like, no, I get why his career would have taken us a slip after drag wasn't an
executive, I think.
Yeah.
Strangled an executive.
He's only now in these, like, he was in like the follow -up from the director of
the greasy strangler, which I like that movie, but like, it's, it's like, dude,
that is a huge get for that director.
Obviously you're talking like grindhouse stuff, you know?
Anyway, I got a movie.
Oh, I've got a few movie psychos.
Um, I guess Marvel, I think I'm getting this right, just announced that they're
only going to release their movies theatrically.
Really?
Yeah.
So does that mean they'll never make it to streaming?
Then maybe Disney announced that?
No, they're just going to do exclusive.
It might've been Disney announcing it.
They're going to do exclusive theatrical releases again, which is clearly a
result of the Scarlett Johansson thing with black widow.
And, and I think Shang -Chi was theaters only and did well, you know, that might
be part of it, but this is what bothers.
I actually want to see Shang -Chi.
I'm not a Marvel fan, but I actually think that one looks pretty cool.
Um, the, uh, this is what bothers me about it.
So, so they throw Johansson, both sides of this make me pissed.
They, they throw Johansson under the bus, right?
Make her look like the bad guy from their end.
Yes.
And then immediately go, we fucked up and we got to make it right.
And then on the other hand, she is now demanding $100 million as compensation
for her move for black widow going to streaming as well as theaters.
I'm not sure black widow has a whole feature cost a hundred million dollars.
That's it's just, it's just the, the level.
It's just gross to me.
I don't know.
It's gross.
I'm a fan.
I like her a lot, but it's just got, when is it enough?
My God almighty.
But also too, you go, well, fuck it.
I'm sticking it to a big corporation.
So maybe that's it too.
I don't know.
You know, it's, I think the, the right answer is neither, neither party
here is, is a real gym, you know, I get people demanding what they're, they
feel they're worth, but Scar Joe, you're not worth, if you weren't in a Marvel
movie, nobody goes to see it, you know, that's, that's what it is.
So Marvel is the star now.
Like you could, you could like Shang Chi is a perfect example.
Nobody really knows who this guy is.
Um, right.
They're not, they like Aquafina fine, but they can see her for free on comedy
central and they're not watching that.
It's like the, the, the brand is Marvel.
So like they, I do think it's, it's dumb that they say, Hey, we're going to
release this theatrically and they don't, and you might be entitled to some
compensation as they say in the commercials, but a hundred million dollars is absurd.
It's just absurd.
Um,
I also read that.
So, so HBO max is streaming the original evil dead from 1981.
Why is that?
No, is that like a special cut?
That's not, no, that's not the, that's not the story.
The story is the original poster features, uh, if it's a very iconic poster,
it's a woman like being pulled down into the ground by like a zombie hand.
Right.
And HBO max soup took the zombie hand out of the picture, uh, because they
it suggested violence towards women.
This is ridiculous.
This is w what is, what are we doing here?
What are we doing?
This is a horror movie.
It shows a zombie hand grabbing a woman.
It's what the movie shows women being killed.
What would it, their, their top movie right now, their, their
homepage is malignant with a knife going into a woman's eyeball.
Yeah.
So what is the, I don't know.
So there's that, is this something you noticed or something they announced?
No, no, it was an article I read on movie web.
Yeah.
I don't know if they came out and said why they did it.
It's obvious why they did it because they've done it.
This is, this is par for the course with HBO max now.
Yeah.
This is what they do.
Um, and then also PETA has demanded a criminal probe investigation into
Jackass for, for animal cruelty.
Can you imagine the level of fucking privilege you need to live at that?
This is where your focus is with all the shit happening in this world.
You want to do an animal probe into Jackass for cause Johnny Knoxville
let himself get rammed by a fucking bull or whatever it is, a snake bites
somebody on the nose or whatever.
Like there, there's no way PETA has seen this movie that everyone's
trying to see and can't get their hands on.
So they're just looking at the trailer and saying, so, so what are you
going to do an investigation into the rodeo circuit like that?
I'm sure they have, I'm sure they have, but it still happens.
I mean, Jesus Christ, man.
I'm on, I'm on the internet today.
Looking at dogs.
Yeah.
Cause I'm thinking about adopting a dog and, and, and, and, you
know, it's heartbreaking.
Thus, uh, kind of, I don't really speak anymore.
Uh, it's heartbreaking.
You go on these, these adoption sites and you see dogs with one eye and stuff
like that, it's horrible.
Like, cause people fought the dog or, or tortured it or something awful
happened to it just out and about, you know, in the world or a cat with one
ear or no tail or whatever it is.
And it's horrible.
And it's like, and then you see PETA and it's like, I know PETA obviously
tries to help with that stuff too.
But it's like PETA, why not give every animal adoption agency I've ever
encountered is struggling to stay afloat.
Yeah.
So maybe try to raise money to save those organizations instead of
demanding God knows how much money be spent for a criminal probe investigation
to try to get Johnny Knoxville and Steve -O sent to jail or whatever it is.
Because, you know, they let a ferret scratch their asshole or something, you
know, it's like, it's so stupid, man.
These guys have risked their lives to make people smile at horrible times.
They, I just read that they have suffered $24 million worth of hospital bills,
damaged their bodies from doing these jackass pictures.
Um, and I hate that it got moved.
It was just something I was really, really looking forward to watching.
But PETA, as far as I know, especially if a film of this size has to
have a representative on set, that's why they say at the end, we assure
you there's been no harm done.
That is there a chance that somebody saw something on set and said, you know,
we need to maybe, but like those guys, they're not cruel.
Wouldn't we have heard sooner too, when that thing happened with the dog in the
wave pool for the Dennis Quaid movie or whatever the hell it was that that was
out before the movie even came out, like we wouldn't, we're, we're just
hearing about this now when the movie's in the can.
I think if something had happened, we'd know about it.
I think somebody had PETA saw the trailer and was like, this is
outrageous and it's supposed to be supposed to be, we're just going to,
we're going to get the most boring entertainment of all time.
I think that's what the next 10 years is looking like.
It's over.
You got it.
But here's the beauty of it.
You're going to get tons of people doing awesome low -budge because that's
that's the, that's the flip side of this.
Now you can now do your own thing affordably, you know, for, and look
thousands of dollars is thousands of dollars.
But the point is, is you can now do your own thing for thousands of dollars
and actually make it look pretty good.
Uh, and if you want to go that, you know, that eighties low budget, all on video
crazy route, it's even cheaper and easier to do now than ever.
Uh, so we're going to get, I hope a lot of independently released stuff, uh, under
the, under the noses of these, these big distributors and production companies
and studios and whatever else.
And that'll be the entertainment you want.
I hope, you know, I hope, I hope the Lloyd Kaufman's keep coming.
Yeah.
So, um, you know, they don't have to be that bad, better than Lord
Kaufman's movies or either that, or everybody will just watch TikTok videos.
And that's the end of that.
Honestly, I think that is definitely happening.
When I, when my dad was visiting and was watching full volume TikTok videos for
hours at a time out on the deck, I was like, it's we're doomed.
I mean, he's, he's been doomed from the jump, but it's like, I, you, you're,
you always think of this stuff.
Like even when I was on vine, I was like, this is a kid's, this is a kid's app.
And I, I'm getting off and, uh, I never signed up.
It's a dangerous sense.
You know what I'm getting off the app.
And I think, you know, never even signed up for TikTok.
I'm like, ah, this is something for kids, whatever.
And then when you hear your parents talk about TikToks, you're like, oh no,
everyone's just getting dumber and their attention span is getting smaller.
And they are just discovering these social media stuff.
And like, even your parents don't watch movies anymore.
It's sad.
Huh?
There you go.
Folks, the usual bright energy coming from this.
Yeah.
My mom called me the other day.
I'm like, what do you, what have you been watching?
She's like, I love this growing up mafia show.
It's on MTV.
It's about all the kids of the mobs.
I'm like, this is like something like 14 year olds are supposed to be watching.
Joe, let's go to the movie corner because I still watch them.
You know, I still watch them.
I saw Lula rich, which is a four part documentary on Amazon prime chronicling
the unraveling of Lula row, the billion dollar clothing empire accused of
misleading thousands of women with their multi -level marketing platform.
So this was the trailer for this.
I didn't watch it though.
It's great.
It's, it's three hours for 45 minute parts.
It goes by.
I mean, I watched the entire thing and it felt like five minutes.
Um, you know, it's the characters aren't at a level of like a tiger
king or something, but you got some really funny people, a lot of hypocrisy,
which is always fun to watch in these things.
It's the same kind of stuff as like Amway or whatever, where these people
are basically setting up, we'll send you these leggings that you sell.
You give us some money and everything will be great.
And then if you can maybe add in some people, some friends of yours to
sell it to then, so it's women, mostly women, um, you know, on unknowingly
in some cases, knowingly in some cases, signing their friends up for this
system that is going to fail them and wipe them out financially, and then
the leggings start showing up and they, they stink and they're wet and they're
supposed to sell them and they're like, Hey, I can't, I can't move these leggings.
They're wet and they stink.
Right.
And they're like, nah, I figure it out.
You know, figure out how to sell them and just the customer service and
everything gets worse and worse and worse.
And now, you know, they still exist.
These people aren't in jail.
They're, they agree to be on camera being interviewed for some reason.
And, um, it's kind of the new, the new way people get away with things is just
by looking you in the face and kind of telling you what they're doing and
everybody goes, well, okay.
So it's again, depressing.
It's, it's watching these people, uh, who are extremely rich.
They did have to pay some big settlement.
Doesn't change the fact that they're extremely rich and they fucked over and
continue to fuck over thousands of people.
It's pretty entertaining, you know, they bring in, there's people talking about
how they can't get any money, uh, out of them, but they'll, they'll spend
$5 million to have Katy Perry or Kelly Clarkson play their big events because
they do these recruiting events at the recruiting events.
Also, the guy starts trying to subtly convert the women who are there to
sell leggings into Mormonism.
So it's also kind of a front for Mormonism.
Um, it's great.
My, the funniest clip is this man going, you know, when I heard about this
Kelly Clarkson thing and that they gave her all this money that could have gone
to us, I decided then and there, I was never going to listen to Kelly Clarkson
and he's like, his voice is shaking and he's like, and I love Kelly Clarkson.
She does a duet with Jason Aldean.
That was one of my favorite songs of all time.
And you realize he's serious, you know, um, there's laughs in it, but it's
the kind of laugh where you're like, I hate laughing at somebody
whose life has been destroyed.
It's a very depressing, but also entertaining documentary.
All right.
Same goes for Bob Ross.
Happy accidents, betrayal and greed on Netflix.
I haven't seen it yet.
I believe it's produced by Melissa McCarthy.
I think her husband is the director and, uh, you know, off camera
host or whatever, um, luck, man.
You know, when I first saw the trailer for this, I was like, God damn it.
Stop with these things.
Like why is everything I think is nice and pure or have to get
ruined with some dark backstory.
But I couldn't resist.
So I watched it and right off the bat, the sun is like, I've been
one trying to tell the story for years.
And when I see you're like, all right, the son wanted the story told.
Like, let's see what it is.
And sure enough, it's a, it's a slightly inspiring story because it's
Bob Ross and you know, and all the qualities of Bob Ross are in there.
Yeah.
It's also pretty cool to see how, how large a star he was.
I didn't know he was a global like celebrity.
I, you know, everybody, you know, in the nineties, when like you saw
like the Bob Ross, like MTV promos and stuff late nineties, you know,
everybody kind of thought we, you know, we, we, we, everybody thought,
Oh, I just rediscovered that thing from my childhood that nobody knows about.
And it's like, no, no, everybody apparently knows about this.
Um, he was also adored by women, which is funny.
Uh, well, PBS was a thing, you know, like I would watch it.
But it would be on, you know, we'd go to 5 PM mass on Saturday sometimes.
And I'd watch it like at three 30 before I went to mass.
Yeah.
And it's like, well, I, this many people were watching this guy paint.
It's crazy, but everyone I, and everyone I know knows who he is.
At that time, three 30 TV on a Saturday was not, you know, you tuned
in to things, you know, right.
But, um, but spoiler alert, you know, it was kind of bummed to hear
he had an affair with this horrible woman who eventually
stole everything from him.
You don't want to hear Bob Ross had an affair.
You just don't want to hear it.
You don't want to think of Bob Ross having sex or anything.
No, um, but the, this couple stole all his money and
touch my happy little penis.
Yeah.
Not stole his money.
Touch that happy little penis.
Touch those happy little balls.
Stole, uh, basically it's a long story and it's worth watching,
but basically they have retained, they managed to retain the rights
to his name and likeness and anything you see now that has
the name Bob Ross on it.
His family is getting none of that.
And the people that swindled him are, and it's really gross
and, uh, it's very upsetting.
But at the end of the day, his son finally got to tell the story
he wanted to tell about his dad.
And that's really sweet.
So,
all right.
I started it and fell asleep.
I planned to watch it.
Uh, I saw in theaters only the card counter Paul Schrader's film.
It looks like arguably the most boring movie ever made.
I mean, Schrader just keeps getting more and more.
It was like that last one was Ethan Hawke as a priest alone in a room.
If I, I loved first reformed and I didn't see it, but, and many did,
but it's a tough, tough sit.
Uh, yeah, it was a critically acclaimed movie.
I mean, the guy still makes shit that people talk about.
And he's getting up there.
Do you see that Facebook post about how it used to be in a, on during
the, during the pandemic, he was in a video poker group with Paul Dano.
And eventually he got thrown out of the group and he was like, I thought,
you know, men sitting around talking could kind of like say what they wanted.
But very quickly I learned that wasn't the case.
And I was thrown out of the greater was thrown out.
Yeah.
What would he say?
He didn't specify, but I mean, the man they were like, you're
not PC enough or whatever.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay.
He, you know, he's, uh, I follow on Twitter, Paul Schrader's Facebook
posts because they, this Twitter account just posts his Facebook posts up on
Twitter and I don't have Facebook.
So you get to read them and see the comments.
I mean, he, he courts controversy.
He talks about the issues that interest him.
And that is a, is a problem often these days, but, uh, the card
counter is Oscar Isaacs.
I don't know how the man sleeps.
He's obnoxious at this point.
It's obnoxious.
Well, right now, you know, in a three week period, he's coming out in
Dune, this huge action movie card counter, a small indie movie, and then
a five part HBO mini series, a reboot of scenes from a marriage.
So what do you do?
And then every time you go to the movies, you see trailers for Oscar Isaacs
movies.
It's him driver or the two of them together.
It's enough.
Who's driver, Adam driver.
Oh yeah.
Now it's obnoxious with driver Isaac's or Isaac.
Brolin.
Uh, of course.
Yeah.
Brolin.
Uh, of course.
Chad, not Chastain, uh, Paula.
What's your name?
Not, not, uh, Sarah Paulson.
She's whoa.
I just banged the table.
She's got like another thing coming out now.
It's like, Jesus Christ, guys.
Can you please, it's a lot.
I mean, luckily Oscar Isaac is a good actor.
Uh, the movie he plays a character named William Tell, which right off the bat,
sometimes people choose a character name and you're immediately at odds with the
move.
It's like, I don't know the story.
It was William Tell.
He got an apple shot off his head or I know the William Tell overture, but I'm
sure it has some sort of thematic meaning.
Anyway, I'm a huge gambling fan as we all know, Vegas fan.
Uh, so I'm inclined to like this movie.
Paul Schrader starts this thing off by explaining card counting with, uh, with
football style chalk lines on the screen.
Uh, and he does it.
Card counting is very complicated.
Once, once you learn, it's like blackjack.
If you sit down and spend an hour learning it, you got it, but it's just not
something that comes across in a one minute explanation.
And he explains it in such a way that I had no idea what he was talking about.
And I know how to count cards.
It was like, Paul, that was a terrible way to explain it.
You just want to like break into the editing room.
But, uh, anyway, he is a card counter.
He goes from casino to casino.
These early scenes of the film kind of play like that, um, that great
Philip Seymour Hoffman movie, Love Lies, or Owning Mahoney, the gambling movie.
Just a depressing, they really capture that world of like third tier casinos,
you know, like not, not big names at all.
That the sports bar, it's very sad.
I liked it.
They had great opening credit sequence, believe it or not.
Scorsese produced the movie.
So for a half hour, I'm very into it.
Then you realize this guy's got a past and his past is that he was one of
these Abu Graib torturers.
So now you're in the like out late Oliver Stone or late diploma territory where
they have this ax to grind about Abu Graib that suddenly comes bursting into
this movie that you're enjoying about a card counter.
So there is a five minute sequence of just like, you know, shaky cam, steady
cam, you know, doing laps around this torture facility where like, you know,
men covered in their own shit are getting beaten and tripping and falling.
And, you know, Jesus Christ, I can barely stay awake through this description.
I mean, this is brutal.
They're, they're dicks and balls being slapped around and everything.
And, and you're like, wait a minute, like Paul, I'm watching a movie
about a card kind of, why are you showing me war torture?
And that's kind of how it feels.
It goes back and forth between these two stories.
You realize that Oscar Isaacs and this young guy want to get revenge on a
military Colonel who basically trained these guys to be torturers killers.
That man is of course played by Willem Dafoe, who is contractually obligated
to be in all Paul Schrader movies.
So yeah, it's like, they kind of abandoned the cards and then it becomes
this movie about going to kill this military Colonel and will you ever get
the blood off your hands and does killing another man, you know, excuse
the crimes of the past and blah, blah, all very familiar Paul Schrader themes.
It does get pretty boring.
And the big issue is, is, uh, Tiffany Haddish, she was getting a claim and
in half the scenes of this movie, she's great and natural in the other half.
She's awful.
And I think it might just be Paul Schrader not knowing what takes to use,
but basically in the first half of this movie, she's really bad.
Isaacs is bad.
And some of the same bad, how though, like acting class, like somebody who'd
just be in your acting class, like really unnatural, then Isaac does this
monologue that's supposed to be really intense, but Schrader keeps zooming
in on his face, you know, there's just, it's, it's what you get into with
late period directors, what Tarantino talks about, why he wants to get out
because they kind of lose it.
De Palma has lost it.
Other people have lost it.
And, and Schrader is just not really up to the task of making this as exciting
and good as he wants, as wants it to be because either it was too low budget.
They had too little time or something, but like, there's a lot of scenes
in this that just don't work.
And there's a lot of scenes that are great.
I'm giving it an average review.
Oh my God.
I thought that would never end.
If speaking of ending, I watched the, uh, Burt Reynolds film, the end.
Not a fan.
Uh, it's not good.
It starts funny.
It's okay.
It's, I mean, I love Burt Reynolds.
He directed this thing.
He probably shouldn't have.
Uh, I love Dom de Louise.
He's in it.
Sally field.
I love she's in it.
It's that classic, you know, Burt Reynolds crew type of movie.
The guy that plays Roscoe and Dukes of Hazard is in it.
Uh, you know, his, his, his players are in it and, uh, it's fun to see them all together.
Uh, the movie is about a man who's diagnosed with cancer and has about a year
to live and the gag is, is that he, he, he overblows everything in his head.
So within 10 minutes of the movie starting and him getting the news by like scene six,
he's like, I've only got a week to live.
Damn it.
He keeps reducing the time.
Uh huh.
Uh, so he wants to kill himself because he doesn't want to die sick in a hospital.
And the, the, the gag is, is that he, he cannot succeed at killing himself.
There are some very, very funny moments.
There's a part where like on his fifth attempt, he just lays back on his couch
and starts laughing, doing that Burt Reynolds laugh for like five minutes.
And it's, that really makes me laugh.
Uh huh.
Uh, well, he finally gets checked into an insane asylum, uh, because they, they
catch him half dead and, and they know he's trying to commit suicide.
Dom DeLuise comes in in a tour de force.
Yeah.
His performance as a, as a mental patient in this place, those scenes are worth it
for the watch, but overall, it's just not a great move.
It's kind of like cannonball run in that sense.
It's got its moments, but you know, by no stretch is it a good movie.
Yeah.
I remember, uh, Burt Reynolds swimming in the ocean at the end for
what feels like 20 minutes.
Yeah.
The, that was like the, I clearly, they had no idea how to end this movie.
I was not a fan, not a fan.
I saw bitching the life and times of Rick James.
I heard that's good.
I'm sorry.
The sound and fury of Rick James.
It was very good.
It, uh, it does what 50 % of documentaries do now, which is have large animated
sequences, which is odd.
Um, it kind of uses that to detail the sexual exploits of Rick James, but.
You know, it starts, it's really odd tonally.
It starts with his daughter who has grown going to this storage
facility and seeing all of Rick James's old, you know, costumes and, and
memorabilia and stuff and getting emotional.
And then by the end of this thing, you're learning about Rick James and a
woman tying some lady they picked up to a chair naked and burning her with a
crack pipe.
So like, it's clear everyone has a lot of affection for Rick James.
Uh, Chappelle's show brought him to a new generation and he, you know, kind
of owned that and loved that, but he was a bad boy till the end.
And, uh, you know, a lot of times bad boys get glorified and everybody loves
them.
But when you actually hear the, and the documentary doesn't shy away from it.
When you hear the specifics of what he was doing near the end of his life, uh,
it's very dark.
He was a, he was addicted to crack, which makes people do dark things.
But, um, yeah, they talk about how he'd have these orgies and just like walk
around staring at people.
And they were like, Rick didn't always want to get involved, but you'd be having
sex and you'd look over and he'd just be looking you right in the eyes while
you had sex.
Sounds like a disturbed guy, but the music is undeniable.
I have, uh, several Rick James records that I listened to all the time.
I think he's a great songwriter.
I just wish he didn't, uh, burn so many ladies with crack pipes.
Isn't it all of our greatest regret?
Yeah.
I know looking back on my life, that's a regret.
Sure.
Uh, I, last but not least, I watched, um, uh, independent movie that I thought was
going to be bad, but I actually really enjoyed it.
It was called city of lies starring Johnny Depp and Forrest Whitaker.
It is about the investigation into the murder of Christopher Wallace, notorious
BIG and the corruption of the LAPD that gets exposed and its ties to death row
records.
Um, based on a true story, uh, Mrs.
Wallace, Biggie's mom plays herself in the movie in one scene, which I thought
was a really beautiful piece of closure potentially for her.
Um, and, uh, look, it starts, it starts pretty cliche and I was like, Oh boy,
where are we going with this?
And then I got to tell you the twist turns the story.
I was like, this is a pretty riveting case.
Like I'm, I'm very intrigued.
And Depp and Whitaker, it's like, forget it.
It's it's grand slam acting.
Like, you know, they're, they're, they're no joke.
They know what they're doing.
And Toby Huss comes into this thing.
Who you might know it from a carnival.
Love them.
Big fan of Toby has met him, did a show with him once at the meltdown.
And he was very nice.
And we talked about his various projects.
He comes into this thing on fucking fire.
He's awesome.
He's in that new movie coming out too, with, uh, Gerard Butler about
like the, the assassins, like stuck in the jail together.
Ash dash cam or body cam or something.
It's like the two guys are the Gerard Butler's trying to kill the other guy.
And okay.
I know it's into the prison to kill him.
And then Toby Huss comes in as the other contract killer and he's all over the
trailer and I'm like, this guy might be stepping into his day in the sun.
Finally, you know, he's an amazing actor.
Um, anyway, I thought the story again was very intriguing, very riveting.
Uh, and it, it, I went and read up on it after I watched the movie and I was
like, this really kind of stuck to the script.
Like they didn't, there was one particular scene in it where I was like,
they clearly merged these events for dramatic effects.
And then I went online.
I was like, they didn't, Jesus Christ.
Like that's how it happened.
Was this like a big, like would have been in theaters?
I know my mom saw it at the theater, but without really knowing who big even was,
which I thought was funny, but like, was this a movie that was going to get a big
release, but then the depth should happen.
So it became a low budget or I think start with budge.
I think it was clearly an indie.
And I think depth depth was already in that weird period of like when he did the
Kevin Smith movies, that was all pre his, and look, maybe he was making weird
choices because of what was going on in his personal life.
But, um, but you know, this was after like, it was like, was that movie
Mordecai or whatever, where he was like the art thief or it was kind of the,
at the end, I feel like when that was like, all right, we're not promoting
this guy's movies anymore, but he's really, really great in this.
And so as far as where everybody's great in it, everybody's really great in it.
Uh, I thought it was, you know, it's an interesting little watch.
I wanted to show it to my dad because I thought my dad would like it,
but it time jumps a lot.
Look, it does, it does what it does.
The time jumping.
I love when a movie does this, when a time jumps without saying three months ago,
or I hate when they do that.
Well, it's necessary.
It's never necessary.
You have a character say that was three months ago or whatever, but, um, it's
almost never necessary, but, but they just time jump around and you kind of have to
figure, oh shit, wait, this is before that happened and my dad will be completely
lost.
I mean, yeah, I believe during the star wars prequel viewings we had, he thought
you and McGregor was Luke Skywalker the entire time.
So this is before star.
It's a prequel death.
You know what I find helps with, uh, with the over 60 crowd is, and it helps me
too sometimes is, is the subtitles.
It helps keep you grounded to the movie.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm getting to a point where I don't know what's happening.
You sent me that article today to read.
I went, I went blank halfway through the goddamn thing.
I was like, I don't even know what I'm reading right now.
I can't even look, it's, it's the, I told Joe it's the worst written article I've
ever seen published on a, on a big level.
It's, it's in variety.
It's about dear Evan Hansen.
You can't tell what the guy's point of view is.
It seems like it was written for like a school paper.
It's grammatically incorrect.
It makes, I just feel like everything is slipping.
And in this goddamn country.
All right.
Let's get to our movie.
That we've got a review to do.
It's called Jacob's wife.
Uh, you know, this marks like the 10th movie I've watched on shutter where I've
gone to the Wikipedia page and they don't have one, they finally did put up a
Wikipedia page for Jacob's wife with like a two sentence plot description.
Yeah.
But shutter like it's not hard, man.
Hire a social media person or something.
Meanwhile, tweet every six minutes about creep show season three coming out.
It's like, I don't know.
I know one person who watches this besides me and that's pink stone.
Even you won't continue to watch it.
No, I'm done.
Yeah.
Who the hell is anyway, this was a big movie for Barbara Crampton because this
was the first foray into producing.
She's starting to like apparently produce her own projects, which I think is
really cool.
You know, Barbara Crampton is a horror, uh, um, uh, she, I guess she started as
an ingenue, you'd say, but she's an icon of horror.
And so is Larry.
Those as a last name up there with the X existance.
Fessenden.
Yeah.
Um, but these are icons of horror.
And it's one of the things I like about shutter is shutter will put out an
original film and, you know, for the shutter crowd.
These are amazing gets.
And I don't say that to discredit them at all.
I say that to say they are cult figures.
And it's very cool that they can lead these movies.
I mean, God bless horror, man.
Still given lead roles without batting an eye to actors of all genders and
races in their sixties, seventies.
Yeah.
I completely agree.
He's like, you know, and you, and they get no praise or respect for it.
It just, they just keep doing it.
Yeah.
Uh, cramped it in this thing.
She, she takes her boobs out, you know, as it, as if it's reanimated days.
And I was like, this is fucking awesome.
Crampton's at least 60.
She looks fantastic.
Uh, it's, uh,
bubby like,
Bobby, like her, her age is not actually not listed on her, uh, on her thing.
And, and good, but, um, she's fantastic in the movie.
And, uh, as is Fessenden, they play a married couple and.
You know, I'm glad they got a place to go.
I really am.
I'm glad that, yeah, that horror keeps these people alive and still making movies too.
He makes a lot of his, mostly his own stuff, but he's appears in stuff too.
I'm sure they just look at like the response when these people go to these,
uh, screenings of their movies or when they go to a, you know, a signing event
or whatever it may be, they, I'm sure people see, okay, these guys have a real
legitimate fan base and they get made.
This is a, it's a small budget movie.
It doesn't really look or feel like it, you know, it's, it's really well done.
Joe, tell us what the plot is, if you would.
Uh, it's about a very religious couple.
Clearly the wife is unhappy in their marriage.
Um, the, I don't think it's due to anything like adultery or anything like that.
It's just because of the staunch religious pursuits of this couple, you
know, like in most religions, the woman is sort of condescended to and, and, and
not treated on equal footing, right.
Uh, or kept if you will, by the husband, even though the, you start to see that
it's unintentional by the husband.
Um, it doesn't change the fact that it's what's happening.
Yeah.
Uh, you also find out that she used to kind of be a bad girl and, you know, you
see that a lot, I thought that was interesting.
I saw that a lot when I was growing up, I saw like some really wild women that I
went to high school with settled down with some in college, also settled down
with some real like straight laced dorky dudes that, that physically were under
their league or whatever, because they were like, this guy takes care of me.
And like, you know, and I, I, you know what I mean?
Like I don't want to be a wild whatever anyone.
So I thought that was a really, really cool thing to see in a movie.
I'd never really seen it yet.
Um, and not to knock Fezenden's looks, but it's, you know, it's, it's that
that's obviously part of the plot is that he's got this like very attractive
wife and he's kind of out of shape and he's kind of boring and right.
And he's not a lot of fun and whatever.
And, um, she gets attacked by a vampire who was played by the woman who plays
the nun in, um, the conjurverse and she slowly starts to descend into vampirism.
And it becomes a metaphor for women's lib basically, like the liberation of
a woman, like her taking her life in control and being who she wants to be
whatever, and not looking at vampirism as being a slave to something, but
looking at it as a means to liberate yourself, uh, from, be it your marriage
or the social constraints or whatever it is, and it goes from there.
Uh, and it, it sort of turns into a story about a husband and wife who are basically
emotionally estranged, starting to work together and rediscovering why they love
each other.
Yeah.
Um, so as it goes, it becomes more comedic, which was one of my criticisms,
not that it became comedic.
I actually liked some of the humor in it.
I didn't think they put enough humor into the beginning of this.
So I thought it was weird when it started to get funny, cause I was confused
at first and I was like, Oh, I see what they're doing here.
This should have been funny from the beginning and it wasn't.
Yeah.
It's actually pretty grim from the beginning.
And then it kind of does the reverse.
Most horror comedies like start funny and get worse.
You know, this is what Krampus did.
Um, but this did, this sort of did the opposite, but you know, Barbara
Krampton, you know, really they, they, they're both great, but she really shines
in this, she pulls off, there's a scene in this and she pulls off a thing where
I'm like, that is so, that is such an embarrassing thing to have to do and to,
to stick the landing on it and look cool doing it.
I was so impressed.
There's that scene where she, right after she gets bit and she's realizing
like she has like strength, like super strength and she starts moving the
furniture around her own house by herself.
Like she likes the couch up over her head and stuff.
She puts on like that sexy, like sort of EDM song or whatever it is and
starts dancing while she smokes.
Yes.
And like, she looks cool.
You're like, could you imagine?
I mean, like my mom at 60 could never have done that.
Like, I'm like, this is amazing that, that she's able to
channel this and do this.
Like, I just found it impressive, man.
That's that scene.
If that scene went two ticks to the left, it would have been absurd.
Yeah.
And she just channels his character.
If they filmed me smoking a cigarette, moving my furniture around, it would be
one of the least cool things you've ever seen.
Right.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
And I'm very cool.
So, yeah, no, I, she, she makes the movie what it is she's, uh, and that,
that she could get the movie made and get it kind of a nice horror audience
and get it on shutter is, is, is the, the story of the movie to me, these
two, her and fast Ben and are great.
They're clearly having a lot of fun.
Um, I'd watch a sequel to the movie, even while I felt it was a little,
a little, a little too flat, I guess I would say the gore was like really gory.
And that was kind of cool.
But the story just kind of, you know, I was waiting for a surprise.
My cat's crawling around on me.
That just didn't really come.
I was waiting for it to kick up a notch.
It didn't really happen.
I liked the vampire.
I liked all the performances quite a bit.
Uh, I liked that it had this kind of weird sexual energy in a story
about senior citizens.
Basically.
I love that.
I think that's awesome.
Um, at the end of the day, it's a, it's a pretty average movie.
You know, the, the gore effects are cool.
Uh, it's horror, scary looking vampire, scary looking vampire, which is
great, very, uh, it's clearly based a hundred percent on the original
Nosferatu, but, but more so I would say on the Salem's lot.
Yeah.
TV movie, the original sounds lot, mini series vampire.
Also, I think based a little bit on, uh, Jackie Earl Haley, the man, just the
vampire looked a little bit like Jackie Earl Haley, but, uh, I, I thought
it was, it was a solid movie.
I w what you're saying, Joe, uh, I thought it was a good blend of comedy
and horror, but that's such a tricky blend.
I'm trying to write something that kind of blends genres now.
And it's like, I mean, it's, it's so hard to calibrate, you know, where
you're going off the deep end and becoming like the end of it too, where
they're all like making wisecracks while a clown's trying to kill them.
You know, it's, it's tricky, but, um, I thought this did a nice balance.
And it's a nice movie.
You know, it's a, it's a slightly above average horror.
It looks better than a lot of the shutter fair that you get the
original shutter pictures.
It looks, looks better.
And, um, I would also like to shout out my friend, Aaron Crozier, who co -edited
this movie and did a fantastic job.
He does a lot of these horror movies and, um, yeah, uh, I liked it.
Great.
My, my hog is slightly up.
My hog is slightly up too.
I didn't love it, but it is something I would revisit.
Uh, and after a second watch potentially purchase, yeah.
Which, uh, you know, that we're moving in the right direction here.
I am excited to see what else Barbara Crampton does as a producer and, or
actor, uh, and I'm excited to see what Larry does next as well.
Uh, everybody, uh, did a nice job with this picture, you know, and it's
nice to see that shutter is doing, you know, we've talked about it.
They essentially are doing direct to video horror movies.
And, you know, a lot of these are a lot better than what the
direct to video fair was in the, in the, in late, you know, it's well, definitely
better than what a lot of it was in the eighties and, and better than what, and
it'll get better as it goes, you know?
I mean, I thought, I always thought the best, I don't believe it was direct
video, I always thought the best direct to video horror movie ever made was wax
work because it doesn't feel, you know, it's, it's really well done and, you
know, the effects are great and whatever.
And, you know, I remember when, in, in, when that came out in the early nineties,
like being like, wow, these like direct to video movies are starting to get
better, you know, like, uh, you know, pit in the pendulum with, um, uh, uh,
what's his face, Mike, um, for Christ sakes, Lance Hendrickson, uh, was one.
Yeah.
You know, um, so I think that shutter is basically making those types of movies
and, uh, for us now, which is great.
For sure.
Yeah.
I mean, uh, ice cream man and, and uncle Sam and Jack Frost and all those would
have been shutter originals now.
And I think that's great.
I love it.
All right, folks, we will be back, uh, shortly since we're releasing two at the
same time, the next one will be, uh, candy man, the new remake of candy man.
We'll also in coming months be doing malignant, which you can see on HBO
max or in theaters.
And I'm not sure what else we'll do.
Probably dune or something of that nature, but
dune possibly.
Definitely.
Norbit.
Malignant.
Definitely.
But Halloween kills.
Yes, definitely.
Halloween kills, uh, which is going to be dropping on peacock.
I just read.
Also, I mean, look, I'll probably see it in the theater, but matrix going right to
right to the max.
I'm going to go to the fucking theater and say, yeah, I'll see it.
Yeah.
There's rumors that it's ignoring the two sequels.
The description is like picks up right where the original left.
What?
That's crazy.
I watched this.
I watched the sequel like two nights ago and I was like, this is way better than
I remembered.
I was hoping that they kept it.
But the guy from candy man is playing young Morpheus and I'm like, if Morpheus
can just make like there's the, the speculation is Morpheus isn't in it
because they kill Morpheus in one of the video games, but I'm like, yeah, but.
But you clearly can do whatever you want with time.
Just bring back Laurence Fishburne.
Or is this just a ploy?
Because now it's like, well, if we make six more, we need a younger
guy in here playing Morpheus.
It's probably what it is.
Cause Fishburne got fat.
I think that's all it is because they, they, why would they care about
what happened at a video game, but not in parts two and three, which
costs $300 million each doesn't make any sense.
They also couldn't pause production long enough for the original agent
Smith to finish whatever TV show he's doing to shoot this thing.
So we'll see what happens.
It's also only one of the Wachowskis right now.
So I'm, I'm curious if this is going to be like the recharge, the
matrix franchise needed, or if it's going to be like, Oh, this is why.
It's only one of the sisters and half of the original cats and why it's on HBO
max and et cetera, et cetera.
There's a lot of question marks.
All right, folks, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.