Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hey, everyone. Welcome to the We'll See You In Hell podcast. Now a part of the Fangoria
podcast network. For more information about the network, including other programs, how
to follow the show and find past episodes of We'll See You In Hell, please visit Fangoria .com.
Now on with the show and on with the Joe. Hi, Pat. How are you? People like or like him
they do you know the numbers have spoken I actually heard more people like that
than like to pay in manning when he won the Super Bowl really yeah that's
amazing we that means we were trending my Trump impression oh really you hear
that no what did you say about painting manning no they asked him how he thought he
did at the CIA they were like why are you talking about your crowd size this is a
meeting your first meeting with the CIA. And he goes, uh, you know, uh, the fake news,
they're trying to, I'm going to a little impression work. Right. The fake news, yeah,
they're trying to pretend I didn't do good in that, uh, in that speech. I did so well. Uh,
I, I was told many people told me that I had the biggest standing ovation since Peyton
Manning won the Super Bowl. You know, in a room of 100 people, it's, it's one of the craziest
things I've ever heard. Many people, many people told him, no one's had a standing
ovation that long since Peyton Manning. And that's how you answer a question, day two,
as a president of the United States. I, it's, I don't know what's going on. I don't
know if he's out of his mind. He is. You do now. Or if, or if they're saying, here's how
we smoke screen them. You go out there, you say this crazy shit. Yeah. I know Bannon's
playing them. We'll be doing all this bad here. I don't know what the hell is going on like a
two -bit piccolo folks. That's our politics chat. I did want to say and I know we've already had
people tell us they don't want to talk politics. We'll get right past it, but it's a terrible time.
It's a terrible time. The old Muslim band kicked in yesterday to give you an idea time -wise of where
we're at. But Joe, the previous time we talked politics, but I thought it was a great conversation.
Yeah, you would said, you know, and of course we all know things got way worse than we expected way quicker, but you were like
You know, it's gonna be like it always was you know like we've had bush and everybody said the sky was falling
We had a bomb everybody said the sky was falling. I
Mean you were like I bet my life's not gonna change that much
I almost got into that deeper with you
But I was like what I know Joe doesn't mean by that and would probably like to clarify in case anybody
Let's us to the old ones and you do because we get your comments is that I don't think and correct me if I'm wrong
Joe sure I don't think that you meant
It doesn't affect me so I don't care because now you can see that while it might not affect you and I a couple of
Reasonably successful white males in our thirties. I'm not technically white
At least have to point that out all right. I just feel like you must care about the everyone else who's of course I do
That's not what I mean at all, but it got terrible real fast and I knew you'd want to clarify what I meant was
Would I by the way Pat didn't set me up for that at all? I didn't say hey, let's go on and pretend like I need to clarify something
No, not at all. I didn't even know you're gonna say that but now that you said like I look I learned from David Frost
You know the star of frost next and I ain't I interned under him. He said patty
Wait, well, he's not the star of frost mixture Michael Sheen is the star of frost next to David Frost to it's about
David Cross, the comedian, the star of Cross Nixon, and also Cross Odenkirk.
Right. He told me he was like, Pat, if you've got a political discussion, don't talk
about it two minutes before the podcast, put it on the podcast, because that's going to
be the electric gold. Now, now some call it gotcha journalism. I don't.
Oddly enough, that's what Frank Langella told me, who was also in Cross Nixon.
Yeah, yeah. Now, uh, did you see what I asked for us next?
And which was the talking snowman against Nixon in a battle of wits.
I saw the sequel where the, uh, the snowman is, uh, accused of breaking into a hotel.
Oh, okay. Uh, which I like is a little bit better.
And then the beauty is they get away with it.
They get away with the caper because the snowman melts at the end.
Right. And then it turns to watergate.
There you go. Folks. That's why they, what is this,
It's a live taping of Ad Midnight.
What does this say?
A comedy bang, bang, podcast?
No, these are just two guys having fun.
Just to speak back to what you were saying earlier.
No, that's not what I meant.
It's not affecting me, so I don't care.
That's not what I meant at all.
What I meant was, I don't think anything's going to change and then I was really wrong.
Yeah.
I mean, there's a little bit of stuff changed during Bush, but it was more like, it seemed
more like panic craze and then, like, nothing would happen.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, Bush was almost like a like a Y2K president where you were like it's
got it all in and then it didn't end and somehow turned out okay, you felt like his
people diabolical folks though they may have been were intelligent and reasonable enough
to guide him into making granted some some catastrophes decisions for our nation.
Katastifus? Katastifus.
Folks, I'm not gonna lie to you. Pat and I smoked a little bit of...
Folks, you gotta get through the goddamn day.
Funny stuff, they call it.
You know, wacky to back.
Smoked a little of that God's green, but I'm feeling fine.
I just wanted to open up to you for a minute, folks.
Things aren't good. Things aren't good.
You know it, I know it. Don't be into Nile about it.
Joe knows it.
And I'll tell you, here's a little frustration of mine.
Don't tweet 50 things about folks. We must take action. We must do that. We must. When I can see you out my fucking back window
Sitting on your couch doing jack shit
Yeah, you know that that's it so you're looking at people's windows now
I purchased a telescope
I'm looking around the silver like area and I'm seeing all these tweets now
I'm not saying I'm on the fucking front lines either people and I'll take shots at Trump and I'll talk on Twitter about how
helpless and scared I feel and try to make an amusing if I can't that's what I do
I try to bring joy here's a time of evil here's what I keep saying yeah ready ready
the revolution will not be televised unfortunately it'll be tweeted instead
oh that's good I'm gonna get that should have been the title of your special that
entire the bill you're not even on the billboard just those words who was the
I was an Avril Levine Fiona Apple like that second album that title wave hits the pawn into the
Revee just just immediately goes to her head second album. I'm gonna I'm gonna name it a paragraph. Yeah, I do love Fiona though
She's great, but I'm just saying that's that's a real that's a real dick on the table kind of move
Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna give it a paragraph title. I went to see her years ago at the Greek theater by myself
I bought a ticket. I was out on a run
I was like yeah, that sounds like fun
I go into this thing hundreds and hundreds of women sobbing all around me, and I'm just sitting there alone, and I felt guilty. I felt responsible. Did you say, hey, I thought I was out of the house this evening.
Yeah, I mean, it was sort of freeing to know that many women were crying all around me, and I was not responsible.
Sure, I'm sure that's nice the second time I ever once the second time I ever appeared on television was on the Carson daily show
I was about four years into comedy. I was scared as hell this was after you were the the bookie who beat and eventually killed Sam
Malone on the series finale of cheers. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, you were not popular. You couldn't get work after that
Nobody loves Sammy so much they love Sam. I would say interviews people. It's make believe it's a show
And they said they didn't want to hear it the graphic violence of it to see like on the set of just you know
A familiar multi -cam sitcom how how graphic it went and then this flesh chipping away from the skull and pet
I got to be honest and this might be the weed talking. I don't know what the fuck you're talking about right now
What are you talking about? I'm trying to riff but you're you're you're you're made up a thing about cheers
that wasn't a thing. So I just got stuck on there's nothing even remotely close to that in
cheers. You think you go for like a more folks we are still listening to the comedy section right?
Can I show you the route? I thought I was working with a scene partner with a laurel to my heart.
Can I show you the route? I would have went. Yeah. I would have made it a little more
way out of you. So I said like Pat, after you did that gig on that movie, happiness. Now folks,
You didn't see Pat in the film, Pat's job was to stand and jerk off and shoot his jizz against the wall
So they could get that shot
Yeah, they cut it in to make it look like Philip. See where Hoffman's just I was the first the first guy in the
Sags green actress guild to be given the credit of
Stunt come see then you go and after that the guy can't get work anymore. Yeah
You you painted this whole thing. I didn't aware that how you were going
I think I think time will tell when this drops that our listeners really enjoyed that riff that I was going on
All right
I think we're like what will Joe say to continue this fun riff and you immediately dismantled it going against all rules of
Improv and comedy. I didn't not enjoy it. It was just freaking me out. It was honestly freaking me out man
Hey, listen
Here's what I was looking
Look, here's what I was going to say.
Well, you know, I don't remember what we were talking about.
Let's get on to the show.
Let's talk about movies.
We were talking about Trump, but we shouldn't be.
Let's get us back on track.
It's going to be a real meandering one, folks, both because we're
high and we're under a great deal of stress and things are bad.
But here we go with Pat's movie Roundup.
Pat's movie Roundup.
New wise, I saw a monster calls where a boy's mom is dying.
So he creates a fantasy world with Liam Neeson as a talking
tree, and the talking tree tells him a lot of stories that have little to nothing to do
with his life.
I always thought that that movie was going to be about a kid first discovering masturbation.
A monster calls?
Boy, that did turn out to be a monster, didn't it?
I can't, I couldn't even count on.
Why did you see this movie?
Couldn't count on a thousand hands how many times I was, I pledged myself folks, but let's
move past that.
Why did you do that to a monster calls?
Actually, that'd be a good term for I got to take a shit.
excuse me fellas a monster calls I'm using that go answer doing that real life
I watched it because it was sent to us by the Academy and if I'm gonna be voting in these important
Elections like our writers guild awards. I want to have seen the films sure and somebody thought it was worthy of being for my
Consideration sure I've also seen close friends of mine talk and tweet about how much they loved it folks
It's it's not a good movie
good movie. It's stupid. It's like okay a story about a boy and his mom's dying. How
about we throw a talking tree into the mix? And then the tree tells these stories that
are like poorly animated. And you watch like a 10 minute almost like you know that early
cartoon Lord of the Rings quality. I like that. And you're just watching these stories unfold
and you're like how what does this have to do with the kid and then you find out at the
But you don't give half of the shit. I thought it was stupid
I honestly thought what it was about was this kid is like an outcast and he gets the monster to like help him
No, the monster is there to help him get over his mom's death. So what you I don't know
He created the monster in his mind or his emotions. Oh, Christ. All right. Well now a similar
and similar
our, uh, film is, uh, demolition, which Joe has talked about on this podcast, Jake
Jellin Hall, Jake Jellin Hall Naomi Watts in a, in a indescribable role, what the fuck
was she even doing in the movie? Her role was so stupid. She's a woman he meets on the
bus. She's married and she like takes him under her wing in a platonic way after his wife
dies because she understands that he's damaged because she's damaged. And then he burns with
the kid and the kid starts to teach him humanity. This this movie just hit HBO folks it's so bad
and Joe loved it and said it made him cry. So yesterday we're texting and as I'm watching it
and I was talking about how schmaltcy and like him honestly embarrassing the movie was and Joe's
like I love that I love that and I must have said three times admit that you were drunk while you
watched it and he never denied it. He was like of course I'd have to be drunk right I couldn't just
just enjoy it.
I wasn't drunk.
I was watching it in the airplane.
You didn't have a couple cocktails.
No.
I don't drink when I fly.
I don't do that.
I mean, I don't not do it.
I'm just saying I don't usually do that.
The Joe, I know, could not love demolition.
I don't understand it.
I think you're always just trying to throw a monkey in the wrench here.
I'm going to read the text.
Go ahead.
This is how it starts.
Last text of the day up to this point was at 1210 p .m.
12, 10 p .m., 7 .30 p .m., over seven hours later, walking my dog mind in my own business,
I get a text from Pat, this demolition movie you recommended is just absolute shit.
As if I made it and said you have to see this.
I write back, you're in a lousy mood, it's a wonderful film.
Pat, you must have been on something, it's very bad.
Now, I try to give him a chance here.
I stand by everything.
I try to give them a chance. I go first off how far into it are you? Secondly, how is it bad?
I could understand you not being into it, but it's not a bad movie.
Pat responds,
15 minutes remain. Now, it's hard for me to think that you got no joy out of this movie
until the final 15 minutes. I don't, I, I, I, it's very hard. No, I hated the final 15 too. Please don't get me wrong there.
I didn't think any of it was good. I'm saying there wasn't one moment of enjoyment. There wasn't one. I was extremely bored.
You didn't find it funny when he like
Feel so little when his wife dies that he's almost like confused by it. No, I mean it seemed like
It was written in like the Sundance lab or something, you know all right in 1999 and
the guy is so unlikable and
You just you hate him you don't care about him, but everybody hates him
He's boring. Well everybody in it is kind of an asshole as well
Everybody hates him in the movie.
It's not like he's walking around waiting him at the end of the movie.
But that's what were you dawned because then Joe was like, why can't you have a movie
with bad character?
No, he wrote, this is what you wrote.
Get back into it.
This is what he writes.
I've never given less of a shit about a lead in a movie.
True.
That's not true.
That's, that is not, you, this isn't the worst lead character you've ever seen ever in
your life in a movie.
That's not true.
That's an absurd say this year, this year.
Rich unbelievably handsome guy can't feel so he breaks his expensive things yeah what a tragic
Yeah, that's not all it is he also starts working he destroys like a three million dollar home
And you're sitting there watching this rich handsome white dude destroy a three million dollar home
And then you're supposed to give a shit about him today today in 2017. I don't think it's supposed to be that you're supposed to give a shit
You're going to lay it in by the end at the end he's running down a pier and slow motion with children
You're supposed to come her he's he's at one point is laughing with a child with Down syndrome on a
Mary go round that he built to honor his dead wife who that's the movie we're talking who he was completely
The guy destroys his life. He throws it all away. He has no money
He spends the last of what he has in the in the tail and the climax of the movie to put this
It's a miracle.
and then he buys a fucking merry -go -round for his fucking dead wife that's what
that would be if you didn't like the mother. I wrote Pat your criticism is
exactly the point of the film you're supposed to think he's an asshole and
questioned the way he chooses to feel and then it all ties up in the end which it
does. Pat writes okay then I better pay attention didn't realize it all be tying
up in the end I'll probably love it yeah because you know how fucking great man
I'm going to ask all some and we're going to talk about it today
You'll stick through a goddamn channel on movie till that twist comes won't you? I sure especially the one we're going to talk about
And I go the lead characters in the bad lieutenant movies weren't good people. I guess those movies suck too
Now pat renegs now. He starts back paddling. No, not at all
My issue is not that he's a bad person. He's boring. Yeah. Yeah, that's a whole new argument
Well, no, it's not I mean, I you know, I love movies about bad people
and terrible people doing terrible things,
but they're not boring.
That was my issue.
I never care that a lead character is a bad character.
I just, why are we supposed to give a shit about this guy?
We care about bad Santa,
that first one, the pops to mind,
because he's clearly a severely damaged alcoholic,
you know, who like never had a father,
never had a connection, et cetera.
This is like on the surface,
the most privileged guy I've ever seen in my life.
But he didn't earn any of it. That's the point. The point is is that he married this girl
Well, he earned that reason down syndrome Marigold round, didn't they?
Marigold down. I write back then when he called it a Marigold downs. I almost turned this thing on. Come on. I wrote back
I almost turned this thing off. The movie is no tremors or give you that. That was a cheap shot as I was typing
But what do I know? I like aliens. So we both had a similar job. Yeah. By the way James Cameron who
to just an interview that said,
I don't think we need another alien movie.
They've kind of gone off base
as he plans to reboot the Terminator again next year.
You're not gonna be first in line?
For what?
You're not gonna go see the new Terminator.
Yeah, of course I'll go see it.
All right.
This guy's sitting there going,
you know, I don't think we need a new alien movie.
The franchise is going to bit off track.
This is what he says in the interview.
Then he tries to do a save -all by going,
don't get me wrong, I'd watch any Ridley Scott movie.
Yeah, but like you don't think that these other terminators movies have been bad you love three and I think four and five point is is the thing
That everybody yells about James Cameron being so great for oh he made the good two movies and when that he comes out
And he shits on a different a competing franchise and says it's going off the rails as if the whole world doesn't think his franchise
It's going off the rails and he's rebooting it again next year. It was just a snotty thing all right, that's all all right
Well, I tell you what anyone who's making Avatar 4 right now, doesn't really need to flap his mouth
That's what I'm saying unwanted sequels. That's what I'm saying this goes on and on
I'll just read a while I caught 20 minutes of true lies the other night. I was pumping my goddamn fist
I was I was standing up pumping my fists hate the film true lies is a great movie. It's not a great movie pet
It's not a good. This is why I can nobody can trust you in your demolition opinion. So you say demolition is a better move
I'm not talking 100 % I'm not talking demolition man Joe. I'm talking demolition a hundred percent you think demolition is a better movie than true
I'm a demolition man over true lies a demolition man's a shitty movie, but at least it's got a cool
Statement to it you make your own arguments. At least it's got an interesting state. I don't I don't have to make them you you make my
Arguments for me. All right. I'm just gonna I'm gonna just jump to some of the
highlights, remaining highlights. This movie packs all the power of a jewelry
commercial. That was from Penn. Yeah, I said that. Man, I'm funny. You know what I
mean? I said, my Keenan learned it palette for the cinema is never wrong.
You're wrong. He didn't reply. And that was the end of that. Yeah. And then I said
that I'm gonna eat weed by myself.
I never did that before.
Any pointers, and he sent me a bunch of mocking memes.
They all were Samuel Jackson saying,
hold on to your butt.
No house now.
Now here's the end part to the story
because I know a lot of you were sitting there going,
ooh, Walsh had the last laugh.
All of us.
Walsh had the last laugh in that one.
No, your old buddy Joe did.
Because later that night, I went over
to my friend Vince's house.
Now, what the fuck's going on now?
Pat wouldn't join us because you're sitting in,
you were staying in yesterday, right?
Yeah, I wanted to stay in and watch movies,
which I did.
And you were a little stressed, right?
Yeah, a little stressed about some work related stuff.
Projects on the pipeline?
Yeah, but you were stressed.
No, the cats on the cradle.
And you made it very clear that the stress was,
you didn't feel like doing anything.
You wanted to stay home because you were feeling great.
Right, I go over to Vince's April's dear friend. I don't know about 10 o 'clock at night. We're
Listen into a Spotify. He follows you on spat of Spotify. Yeah, uh, I didn't know this he was apparently tracking you
Uh, I'm sitting in Vince's house. Let's go. All of a sudden. He's up there putting a song on all of a sudden this is the song that comes on
That's right.
That comes on.
I go Vince.
What the fuck man?
And he goes.
He goes, uh, that may I just put this on.
It goes patty.
Walsh is listening to it.
Our boy patty.
Walsh is listening to me.
This is what he's listening to to cheer up cheer up on a little
Mace. This is his depression music.
And I was this I would decided to cheer myself up and put on some fucking
Mace Vince Avril turned and with with all the with all the concern of a parent
that finds hypodermic needles and their son's software goes he's listening
to this to get himself through. He's right on the money. He's right on the
money and we both I think we're a little afraid for for your well -being. No
no no. I mean I I'm afraid for the world. I got a big heart when I see what's
going on, folks. It bums me out. I had a bad day. All right. Look. Well, here we are today.
Right? Is that all right? Does that feel good that you're here with me? Feels good, Joe. I also
watched the accused yesterday to talk a little more about my mood. Why would you watch that when you
felt the way you did? Because I didn't know if I had ever seen it. I know, you know, it's like a very
off -color joke and wedding crashers about, I knew Jody Foster got raped on a pinball machine. That's
all I really knew. But then it started and I was like, I've never seen this. So I watched
it. I thought it was fantastic. It was made 30 years ago. And it's like, it's about
like, was she asking for it? Like it's a very timely thing. Of course she was not asking
for it, folks. Now I'm not going to hit you with that twist. And then there's the actual
trial is about all these guys cheering on the gang rape. So the trial that she goes to is
not to put her rapist away. It's to put away the guys who cheered it on and
enabled it and didn't stop it. And they do it the rapist. The rapist go away
for like three years. They get it like a plea bargain and they're already in
jail. But I was like, this is like such a more complex movie than I was expecting.
And guys, I mean, it's a tough watch, but if you haven't seen the accused, it's an
amazing fucking movie that I read that you maybe you think you've seen much
you haven't. Jody Foster, yet pre -science of the land, Jody Foster, Kelly McGillis,
post -top gun Kelly McGillis, two women who would later become Lasbans. Maybe they found
love on the side of the film. I don't know. I don't want to tell you how to school.
Lovers, they became? No, but they're currently both Lasbans in good form. Oh, that is right.
Kelly McGillis did marry a woman, I believe. But, man, it was just such a fucking great movie
that I found myself like watching the extras, you know, I was just like very interested in everything about it's based on a true story.
But then again, I remembered it as opening with the rape and it being kind of graphic but shown very briefly and tastefully.
But sure enough, you watch like an hour 40 of this movie and they just show you the entire 10 minute gang rape sequence, like in the middle of this courtroom drama.
how it happened and it's very, very, very traumatic and yeah, it sounds like a
horrible thing to watch. I mean, I mean, awareness, it seems like a good
thing. Yeah. I knew it was depressing. I was not aware that I was gonna watch
like this like intense and graphic of the same. And then I on these extra
features, he was taught this guy who did unlawful entry in a couple other great
thrillers of the 80s and 90s. But he was just saying that they showed a cut.
But the special feature is you buy the DVD I had accused it was on a like a four pack
of the hand very courtroom dramas or something.
So the guys like it was the the four pack was the accused deliverance.
Yeah, exactly I searched that word.
But yeah, he was talking about how they showed a cut to like paramount or whatever.
And it got the lowest scores in the history of it.
and most of the people on their comment cards said that she deserved to be right.
Jesus, really?
So like, because she dances pretty provocatively in this bar for about three minutes
and her, her tank top things are kind of falling off and showing a little
brass, perhaps. That was right when that whole argument
started. Yeah. Where people were like, it doesn't matter whatever the woman was doing.
You're not allowed to just have sex with her. Right, of course.
And like, that almost seemed to be the argument of the people in the movie.
but I tell you, the most chilling thing about it was that it showed absolutely no forward movement
to now from 1988. There was like no, this movie would have been made today,
it would have had to update a single thing about it, and that was 30 years ago, which is disturbing.
But it was a, I gotta say, it's a very fascinating movie, if you can put up with that 10 minutes.
They haven't made a movie like that recently because it's surely I mean a very very talked about issue in the media and whatnot
And yeah, you'd think you'd think that something and then I wonder are these studios so fucking
So fucking wipe red that they won't let a movie like that get made because it's too graphic probably I mean that
Everything I've been hearing is that any movie 20 million dollars and under can get made if it's an independent type movie and
Anything like 75 and over can get made
But that sweet spot of between 20 and 75
is where all of your favorite movies
from the 80s and 90s come from.
They just don't make them anymore
because they don't feel they're worth the risk
to spend $50 million on like an adult drama
and make $52 million.
It's not worth it to them.
And they don't do anything overseas
because there's no monsters in shittin' them.
So that's what happened.
That's how you were end up with office Christmas party.
Didn't see it.
I'm not gonna speak out against it.
I didn't see it either, I don't want to see it.
I was rooting for it, I like an R -rated comedy, they're rare.
It's the laziest title, next to Hotel for Dogs, it's the laziest title I've ever
heard of movie ever have.
A lot Titanic.
No, that's fine, you know, if it's a historical thing, biographical thing, Malcolm X, fine,
Titanic, fine, Selma, fine, named after a person or a location or something, you know what
I mean, that's fine, if it's some kind of,
even look, Fargo, great name, sure, great name.
But if the office Christmas party people had named it,
it would have been called Lady Cop on the Hunt.
You told me you wouldn't go see Lady Cop on the Hunt?
I would, but that's besides the point.
All right, let's move on to Joe's scary stuff.
What do you earn about?
I support your little fucking things you do every week.
It was the way you delivered that intro
That's why I did it though.
No, I loved it. It's a marker. I want to hear it again, but I laughed at it. It brought me to school.
Is the part that upset me. It was gross and then I loved it.
Okay, all right. The Joe's scared this week.
I would like to send a shout out and these are not, these people are not sponsoring us by the way.
This is, this is not a sponsored product segment or at least it's not yet.
And we're not doing it for that reason. We're just doing a segment where we can talk about some stuff
that is hard -related that is not a film because there are a lot of cool
products out there for horror fans and the product I want to talk about this
week is HorrorPack. If you haven't heard of this go to HorrorPack .com. They have
two subscriptions, one is $20 a month, one is $25 a month, $20 a month subscription is
DVD, $25 is Blu -ray and here's what you get every single month. They send you
for brand new movies of the horror genre on whichever media you've chosen your plan to be for
and you keep them forever that's it that's it and it's a big surprise grab bag every month
gotten some great stuff you get a couple real indie flicks but everything in there is something they
clearly uh stand by. Are we getting paid for this? Huh? Are we getting paid for this? No.
I said I wanted to talk about a horror related product that people should check out.
All right. I mean it's basically uh it just sounds like I'm gonna add.
Well, remember last time I talked about Resonity before. Yeah, not.
I just think people should do this thing. I don't want it to go away. Right, right. Look, we can
Ask them to sponsor us. Yeah, we should that's sort of I guess what we could use this part for yeah
But that's not why I'm doing it. All right. Well, look how committed we are to you now. You call for some goddamn
Point is you like hard movies. You powered you cowards
Well, don't insult them
My you like hard movies. You got to do this thing. I've gotten some really cool flicks
Yeah, any big titles or you just get an old chip you get both
I got the collector's edition of Hannibal and the tin case the other day. I got the fog or the carpenter version, which is the one you want.
You open it, fog comes out of the box. That was a cool nature. I've gotten a bunch of really cool stuff, man.
A house one and house two, the dual pack. One time, one time one of the movies was a box set of old like 70s
exploitation harm movies and that was seven things in like a metal coffin and
that only counted as one of the movies because it was a it was a package deal.
So you get a lot of those kinds of things too. Really really cool man.
Folks it sounds like a great deal. It's an amazing deal.
Joe and I are dear friends. Didn't never told me about it.
I've definitely told you about this. I've talked about it on the podcast.
I've told you about this and you and you met it with the same pig fucking
who knows disgusting ignorance that you met the movie demolition with so you've missed out folks
we've already gotten some comments about how bad demolition is like on previous episode
when Joe raved about it but please watch the movie on HBO and send in your comments one more
scary one more thing for Joe scary stuff I just want to point this out because I got it today
Made it ten times better with a howl if we had discussed that I would have thrown in the howl earlier do the howl every week from now on I went to
France's howl high school is where I went to high school really howl the uh I want I once I once had sex with a Mrs. Howl and then
She felt the face of the earth. It's like she went to some remote island or something never heard from her ever again
Holy cow
Well, there's a time where Joe said yes and maybe you should have said no but folks.
I went to an antique store today to buy a lamp, I needed another lamp for my living
room and while I was there, I just looked on the wall and they got a French version of
the Texas chainsaw massacre two poster.
It's the large official, you know, like movie theater poster, the giant one.
It's an actual print from one of the original prints from the 80s when the movie came out and it's in French
And I bought it and now it's hanging next to my TV looks great. I'm very excited about it
That's all I got Pat you want to get into this movie? Well, let me do mine real quick
Beware the slender man branded documentary on HBO movie Pat
But it's not it's not a horror movie. It's a documentary and you might not think about it in that way
But it's all right. I mean, I think you know, I thought you I thought it was non -horror was the theme. It was like a no
It's like a horror related product. We're not reviewing a movie. You're saying like hey, there's this new
book out
That's a collection of anthology your palms greased on the side by horror DVD pack dot com
Doesn't mean I can't recommend a fine film. We're the slender man watch it. Let's get on to our
for a task at hand, which is the new M -Night shawmall, let me just say something.
Had you said the Slenderman, meaning you were going to talk about maybe befriending
the actual Slenderman, that would have counted, but not a movie about it.
Sorry, I just don't understand what your shitty theme segment is.
It's a product that's horror -related, that's not a movie, it's not that hard to understand.
Hey, I bought an action figure a Freddy Krueger by this toy maker. It's pretty cool. Check it out. There you go
about I got an electric bill last week. That was pretty scary. Yeah, that's better than what you did
All right, this week's movie split split by Amnit Shyamalan
Split which I earlier called switch by Amnit Shyamalan and
And Joe and I went to see it this week a rare a two rare if I may say my dear friend Joe
Together movie that we saw
We went we had a drink over at the old cheesecake factory. Oh, yeah
And then Americana and then we sideled on Joe actually took a couple of apps with him to go and brought him into the theater
Which was surely a violation of their policy right right and then we watched
Switch split Josie and like wings dipping them in blue cheese next to me in the dark. It's very sensual
But uh, no this is kind of into the movie and Joe synopsis. We'll hold on a second. Give this synopsis to the movie
Listen, the synopsis is there's three girls leaving a birthday party. They're about 15 16 years old
And they're with their father and this maniac
kills their father, kidnaps the three girls and takes them to his underground
layer. There they realize he has 23 and perhaps 24 or personalities and it's
kind of a serial killer type movie after that where they're held his
prisoner. Yes and I was enjoying it if not like in love with it and I'm kind of
going along with it. Joe turns me and he's like this is a piece of shit right? Isn't
this fucking terrible. And I was like, I wouldn't go that far. And it kind of kept growing
on me. I had big problems with it. And yet I liked it quite a bit.
I love the beginning. I was super invested. Yeah. I came back around to it at the end
for reasons that we can talk about later, but with a huge boiler alert. We'll set that
aside if we're going to talk serious spoilers about. The end brought me back to it and made
me like it as a whole, but the middle when I didn't know where it was going and kind
of just had an idea of where it was going, I thought it was overstuffed, overdrawn.
It took way too long.
I didn't need flashback, the flashback of, all right, now we're getting into spoiler territory,
so if you don't want to know, you should switch the dial.
Are we going to talk about her as a young girl and the lots in story?
Yeah, it's like this, there's this dumb hunting story thing with the flashbacks of the girl and then it's that her uncle
molested her and did molester and which which was
Disturbing and like okay fine. It's it's a reality and like I I can deal with a disturbing reality like that
It but it had no real place in the movie. I didn't see it like why it had to do with any these women were in a horrifying
situation already and then they're on top of it
They're like oh and then this girl's backstory is also horrible and you're like okay
Well, what's the point of that and then you realize at the end of the movie
It's to do that god damn thing that Shyamalan does in every movie which is in the flashback she pulled a gun a shotgun
On her uncle
To finally get him to back away from her and stop molesting her and then in the end of the movie when she's in this climactic
situation with this maniac, he just so happens to have the same type of shotgun
that she has to then use to defend herself. And it's like, it doesn't have to
all be that need of a bow, man. Like, yeah, I mean, I honestly until you were saying
it just now, because this was the one I asked for the movie I really hated for a
variety of reasons. But her grabbing that shotgun was, of course, supposed to be
like her taking a second chance at killing it on a sexual abuser, correct?
Sure.
Yeah.
You know, I guess that was supposed to take from it.
I think that's exactly what it's supposed to be.
But sometimes she didn't shoot him the first time she lived with him.
And now when she goes back, so like, is it worth it there?
Like when she rounded that 10 and he's, you know, it's this big gross dude and he's, and
is underwear like he's gonna be play play barn animals with her or whatever. Like is it worth
that imagery and conjuring up this adorable girl who like was like such a great actress?
Really like that young actress and her as an adult I liked as well. I thought they were both
really good. That's a girl from the witch by the way. Yeah, but uh just to to put her through that
like why why is that necessary in your movie to make her grabbing a gun at the end more satisfying
Because it did what that made it all feel gross. That's my point is that Shyamalan does this thing where everything has to be connected
And sometimes it's stupid you could have easily just like swing away and then son exactly swing way in signs
The fucking kid doing the football charge at the end of the visit right. It's every goddamn thing now
Here's the thing the kid wrapping on the fucking visit was a goddamn tragedy, even though I love the business
You could have he could have easily achieved the same type of
you know, commentary or sentiment, whatever you want to call it, if he, without it being
exact, they could have insinuated that she had a checkered past and that her uncle was
probably abusive to her whatever. And then she could have still stood up to the bad guy
in this and at the end of the movie. And you would have been like, oh, that's cool. Yeah,
like she's, I mean, let me, let me throw it off the top of my head. Let's make it identical,
though, and it's stupid. Yeah. Let's say the whole molestation sub story doesn't happen. He picks
her up at the end, this uncle who we met earlier in the movie, like a breakfast club type deal,
he comes to pick her up, and he's like, where the fuck were you? You scared me and raises hand to
hand up, hand up to her, and then she gets out of the car, and she's like, no, I have to deal with one
of you as I'm not going to do this anymore, or something. It's not the top of my head. That probably
would have felt stupid too. I'm saying I don't think we need to see a not
graphic in terms of we're seeing anything but just pretty graphic depiction of
molestation that the movie doesn't support. It's using it as like a little side
story. Then at the end of the movie she's in she's in the custody of the
authorities now because you know she's escaped and they're they're waiting to
hand her off to her guardian and she's in the backseat of this like cop car
are completely traumatized for obvious reasons.
And then the door opens, and this female cop goes,
hey, your uncle's here, it's time to go home sweetie.
And then you're like, for Christ's sake, man,
like, I've seen her go through enough.
Now, it's like, oh, she's definitely not 18.
Yeah.
And she definitely has to go,
because they never really say their age.
Oh, but I see I actually thought in that moment,
she locked eyes with that place officer
and she was gonna tell her about her.
Oh, okay, then maybe that is what will happen.
But it was maybe too subtle, but that place officer was like looking at her like,
you know, you don't want to get back together with your uncle.
And then they shared this look like she was going to tell the whole.
All right.
Then I'll let that go.
That's fine.
So it's an odd thing to use.
It's like, you know, how every TV series for the past 20 years,
when ratings are getting low we'll have a main character get raped. It starts to feel a little
unnecessary and strange to me and if you're using it for shock value that feels a little weird.
I will say. It's so so okay so then my other thing was but again these are the the book ends of
this film I thought were great. So the middle of the movie is predominantly James McAvoy who plays the
Yeah, it's the best friend from edge of 17, which I loved is one of the girls. I did not recognize the third girl, but they're all really great in the moment. So the bulk of the middle of this movie is James
is Maga Boy going to therapy, yeah.
And that's what I turned you when I was like,
all right, this sucks.
There were like five fucking scenes of him in therapy
and they were long and it's like,
hey guys, I didn't come here to listen to people
talk about multiple personality disorder.
This is fucking boring, we get it, we get it.
And I don't need, again, I don't need all these things
so spelled out for me.
You're telling me that some of the personalities
could actually manifest things that others
weren't capable of.
Yeah, it's almost like it says in the script in bold make sure you really put some stink on this because this is the big
This is going to foreshadow a plot twist. Yeah
I mean, well when that finale comes around. I was kind of like
If this was like a truly surprising thing and it was hinted at throughout
It would have been much cooler than
Everyone just almost looking you in the camera and saying this will happen later
Yeah, so you're watching it's so you're watching it's Gary Shanling show and he's just turning the camera
and telling you everything what's happening.
So that was the part where I turned to Pat.
I was like, this, this is getting annoying.
I'm not enjoying this.
And then right at the very end,
and this is where it started to come around again for me,
I turned to you, I don't remember me saying this,
they keep hinting through the whole movie,
the 24th personality is coming, the beast, the beast.
I turned to you, I go,
a fucking werewolf or something better show up
at the end of this goddamn thing.
Because I was like, there's no way
this is gonna get supernatural on us.
And then, again, spoiler alert, here we go.
It gets supernatural.
Yeah, he does, and that was all pretty cool.
Yeah, he's able to like, he becomes this personality,
he's able to climb walls, he's able to deflect shotgun bullets
when she shoots him.
And he ends up escaping.
And it's a bit of a head scratcher,
but you're like, okay, that was pretty wild.
And I haven't seen a shamble on twist that wild
in a long time.
Yeah.
I'm paying attention. I'm paying attention. Now, here's the big spoiler. And this is this is where I was like I'm 100 % in
I actually grabbed Joe's knee like a young girl. A young beautiful girl. The last scene is a news report on a TV set in a diner. The reporter is saying
You know this this suspect is escaped. We don't know where he is, but because of all of his personalities
they're being 24 in total. He's been nicknamed the Horde. And I go and I'm sitting there to myself
going this is this is getting dumb like what is happening right now. And then the camera goes into
the diner pan or pans down the the countertop area where people are sitting. A lady goes the Horde
that's crazy. That's kind of like that guy that was nuts in the wheelchair that they put away. What
What did they call him?
And then I was like, holy shit, holy shit.
And then the reveal Bruce Willis.
I just got chills saying it right now.
The reveal Bruce Willis sitting there and he goes, they called him Mr. Glass and then he
does that Bruce Willis face for a good 30 seconds that he makes a John Travolta in a pulp
fiction.
I just got bolded up on my seat.
I hadn't been that excited about anything in a long time.
We told this spoiler alert twice because I would have hated to have that ruined.
I didn't know what was coming at the end of it and I fucking loved it if you're an unbreakable fan in that one
I'm looking around at the 12 -year -old kids in the audience to even know what that meant maybe not well
Here's the thing
Tell me in that one moment. That's when I went. This is a great movie. Yeah, because everything I questioned
Again, you know, I had my little you know problems. I don't put such a stink on this line and I
Don't need this tight into that or whatever, but aside from that stuff
That moment was when I was like, I really liked this movie a lot because I was not expecting
that surprise.
Fans of Unbreakable, Wayne for Unbreakable 2 forever, and then I would have loved it
10 years ago.
All you had to do was see Bruce Willis' face and then everything that was kind of crazy
in the movie, like, wait, he deflected bullets, like all of a sudden you were like, holy shit,
this is the Unbreakable Universe, he's a fucking another supervillain that Bruce Willis is going
to have to fight. And then suddenly it was like, oh, this is so fucking cool. Yeah. And
then I read, it was probably Buzzfeed or some, I hate to give them traffic for all the
bad that they do, including just outright stealing some of my jokes and posting them as their
own, which I've been called out about in the past by myself. But anyway, it was some sort
of article about interviewing Shyamalan about the twist and about what it means for unbreakable
to and all that. And he had the best answers for it. He was like, I had that version and
I was like, right down to the last minute, not going to use the Bruce Willis thing. He was
like, I just kind of wanted to do it. And I thought it would be a cool thing to let the
audience know, like the whole time you've been watching a movie that's in a franchise that
you didn't even realize it was in, which is kind of amazing that he pulled it off and amazing
that no one ever thought to do it before. I think that twist made it a great movie. And
cool to me. And it sets up a great thing for Unbreakable 2. Also, as I told Joe, the
Horde was in the original Unbreakable script. And I think producers very wisely said you
should just focus on one, Mr. Glass, because I don't think you can't introduce the whole
superhero thing and do a twist and have him fight a bunch of people. It's not going to
work. Right. It makes me very excited about Unbreakable 2. I hope he gets some money though,
because his last two movies have cost $5 million bucks. I don't really want to see a $5
my dollar unbreakable too. Well you know look man I just want to see it unbreakable too
and I felt like this movie felt like the visit was shaman on inching closer back to his
territory I felt like this movie he really jumped back in the saddle. It's a it's a great flick
despite my criticisms in the big picture of the film they're small and I love that the guy had
the balls to just he basically did him just like he did with unbreakable where at the end he's like
I got you I just made you watch a comic book and you didn't even know it right
I love that he wrote a sequel to the comic book and just did it and
The fact that people you're right. There would be people going what the fuck are they are they talking about yeah
He was like he kind of wisely put it after the first credit like
That maybe you just be like oh, I guess that was a weird Bruce Willis cameo and not a part of the movie, but I
Loved it. I loved it. Yeah, I
Yeah, I look for lurching like he really does like sometimes you're like what the fuck is this?
What are you doing? Why am I following this when I should be following this and I think that's when I look back at his movies
It's always what I like about them is that they are kind of all over the place
It's kind of makes you a little more uneasy, I guess, which I like yeah
So that that sounds like it that sounds like a two approval pet. We agree. Yes
Go see split you'll enjoy it first niche in fact well if you listen to this much you haven't seen it yet
It's real and don't see it, but
We want you for the tail end of the show folks
Let's do deep cuts
I've already forgotten this one Pat because I do all the work. You talking about an old favorite
No deep cuts is when I read the short insulting thing off around
It was about a movie that's shitty. Oh, because it cuts deep now. I get it. I didn't I wouldn't have thought that that
Sigma was called that. It's what it's called. It's a weird time. I've told you that that's
Deep cuts
Uh, this is for the movie sleepless
What's oh with Jamie Foxx? The new Jamie Foxx vehicle. Yeah, you know, I've never seen a plot like this before
Guy doesn't want to get his hands dirty daughter gets kidnapped
He kills everybody.
This is a new very fresh.
Yes.
This comes from David Erlich at IndieWire.
I like David Erlich.
The listless, shotty sort of a remake where it feels like
all of the characters have already seen the movie they're in.
Sleepless reduces one of the best action films of the 21st century
into one of the most benign.
And I'd like to read one as well, folks.
What is it a remake of, by the way?
I don't know. I don't know anything about that movie at all.
There's your, there's your deep cut.
I want to read one from Dustin on film file.
It says demolition would be so tweey it hurts if it weren't equally spiteful and disingenuous.
I don't. Sounds like he's describing you. Oh, jeez. Folks, here are the plugs. I'm rubber
your glue. That's what that's what we're coming back with. That's what we're coming
back with. That wasn't no, because the demolition movie didn't say that. I said it. You weren't
insulting me. Listen, here's the thing. Don't watch demolition. But you should watch demolition.
Man, it's got a brilliant commentary. It's about as you watch as dead ringers. I watched that
last night. That bring us this fucking great. Very unsettling. Yeah, Jeremy Iron,
Cronenberg, very unsettling. I mean, to me, that, you know, the biggest creep show in
cinematic history is Jeremy Iron, I mean, it was that Cronenberg teaming up with Goldbloom.
I mean, you couldn't, you couldn't get too creepier guys in a room together. You almost can't
shower those 80s period Cronenberg's off your stamp after you watch them. They're rough.
And he follows it with Peter Weller with that naked lunch thing that's bad shit doesn't follow the book
But yeah, I don't know what the fuck is going on in that man. I'm a fan though. Anyway
My
It it it's out now go watch my hour special for comedy central you let me down
Yeah, well, we don't know this will this will not drop before your show airs
Well my show airs
uh yeah in air February oh no this might yeah February third oh shit I forgot okay
February 3rd at midnight my special premieres you let me down on Comedy Central it's an hour
I wrote it I directed it I do the stand -up please go watch it uh and if you don't watch it you'll
let us down yes uh February 5th is the replay 1 a .m. playing off the tongue February 7th that it's the
Internet for download. So check it out, follow me, Joe DeRose to comedy on Twitter, and Instagram,
and that's where you can see where I'm planning live stuff. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the
Patrick Walsh, in addition to that, a show that I helped write and produce, and Joe wrote for as well,
is our friend Pete Holmes' new show, Crashing, which starts airing on HBO in a couple weeks, I believe
early February after the season premiere of Girls. Check it out. Support, support, good
shit. It's a funny show. You've been listening to We'll See You In Hell, which is a presentation
of the Fangoria Podcast Network. It was produced by Thomas DeFaye on executive produced by
the great Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment. For press opportunities, advertising inquiries
and information about, we'll see you in hell, contact Ken at Fengoria .com, you can reach
me at the Patrick Walsh, Joe at Joderosa Comedy, we read and see and love all of your comments,
tweets, et cetera, about the show. We also have a new Facebook page, let me very quickly shout
the scroll out who set it up, and we will probably get our own official one going shortly, but I
wanted to direct you to this and I almost forgot. Her name is Emily Florence. She has set
up a Facebook group for fans of we'll see you in hell. I check that out the other day.
It is awesome. I'm going to start spending some more time in there. Thanks, Emily. Thank
you very much, Emily. And go check out that group. Guys, we love you. Appreciate it. Talk