Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Hello everybody and welcome back or welcome for the first time I don't know your situation
I don't know what's brought you here tonight, but
You know what I'm trying to say is welcome to we'll see you in hell. It's a podcast. We're each week. We discuss
a horror sci -fi a fantasy movie and we veer off into a variety of tangents
We're on the head gum network
What am I forgetting? I guess I guess we can just go
on with the show and, and help while we're at it, on, with a chill, I, that one hurt a little
bit.
It hurt me.
I feel like a neighbor might have, you know, might get a broom on the, on the ceiling
over here.
I look forward to, I can't go any, any much higher than that, it's going to have to get
varied up.
Well, I was going to say we're going to go we're going to get to a point with the with the die hard fans
Are they going to go you know? I liked the first few on with the Joe's when they were it was simple
They they got they got too carried away with themselves. I don't like it anymore either on those later albums
Pat good to see you. Welcome back to my apartment. Welcome back Joe
Listeners welcome first time listeners. Helian's I've been calling them. I don't know if that's catching on or not
But it seems like the right thing to call your podcast listeners. I think it's very clever
I've never heard anyone but you say it or seen anyone online say it nobody's ever said it
But every podcast has that my favorite murder. They say murderinos right WTF. He says what the fuckers what the fuckets
Pete's thing you made it weird weirdos. Yeah, you got to do it. You got to have a thing. You do
You know
I remember back when I listened to Ricky Jervais
he would say, where are all my Ricky Jervaisa,
Gino's at, and I was like, what, doesn't even make any sense.
I was a, I was a pylconator myself, it's not a, yeah, I, uh, I'm here.
We're here to talk about, uh, Predator and Predator 2,
Colin to catch a Predator, which is appropriate because it's,
there's a lot of talk right now in the movie news about the Shane
in black, fourth installment of the Predator films,
which is called The Predator.
And is that treating all the other ones with respect?
And like, yeah, okay.
I believe so.
I think pretty much everybody doesn't count
Alien versus Predator, those two.
But I think, I think I've seen them both.
I mean, Alien versus Predator one and two,
or two of the worst movies ever made.
I just cheap shitty video game piles of crap.
I remember seeing Alien versus Predator
in the theater. And it was before predators came out. And I remember I liked it in the
theater because there was a big nostalgia predator factor for me. But then I bought it on
DVD and I was like, why did I like this? This is terrible. And then I saw the second one
with my dad in the theater and I was like, this is fucking awful. Yeah, like it was just
it was just a yeah, really, really bad. But I just were doing these movies. Again, it's
time appropriate, they just push back the release of the predator. Unfortunately, but like
I said, to hear that, I thought it was you, but I have some new stools in my house and
they seem to be deflating or something. Do you think that's just because they're new?
I thought you were making a new stool in your pants. But the reason we're discussing this
is because we, Pat, as you all know, has been very busy with the ins and outs of his pilot
over at CBS there. Oh, yeah. I've been a little nuts with traveling and I had to leave town
this week early to do dates and actually in Dallas. Well, you're not even going to hear this
before then. It doesn't matter. I was just in Dallas. Thanks, everybody. I hope it was a good time.
But the, he said, what do you want to do? And I just so happened to be in the best by
in my neighborhood. And I said, you know what? I want predator on Blu -ray. I don't know
on it on Blu -ray on the DVD.
And I went to buy on Blu -ray.
There it was, $10.
We're the trilogy for 14.
Yeah.
So that's a no -brainer.
I've never seen Predator 2.
I want to rewatch Predator 2.
Predator 2.
You saw Alienverse Predator 2 with your dad.
With my dad, okay.
So I bought it.
And I watched it.
And we get into it and just jumping right in.
No, I'm just telling the people why we're doing a throwback.
It's probably like an odd throwback right now.
I think they're good to do.
I mean, yeah, what Joe is saying is true.
We've been so busy and he was like we got to do one. I'm going out of town and I was like what like I mean
We're just I speaking for myself and who I'm completely brain dead and
When he said predator I was like thank God because I watched predator in 3d
Several weeks ago, which I don't even recall buying but I owned it
And then I also had that predator trilogy which I got for 799 on Amazon
Blu -ray.
I'm gonna tell you, it's a real nice way to kind of lose yourself in an evening.
You definitely can't look at your phone during it.
It's really an immersive experience.
And what I really love is when they do these older movies in 3D.
So I have Predator.
I have the Wizard of Oz in 3D, which is really cool.
Well, that's trippy.
It's really neat.
We should do that.
I mean, let's get even more cliche here.
Let's get high and do the 3D dark side of the moon to the wizard.
I would do that in two seconds.
A DONE.
Yeah.
Um.
But yeah, it's really fun.
And then not to mention, uh, watching like Mad Max in 3D, like the new one.
I mean, you are guarded with the Galaxy.
It just, it adds a nice element.
Thinking about buying that Mad Max Black and Chrome version.
I checked that out.
But pisses me off that it's a separate thing though.
It's not just a bonus feature.
Yeah.
That should be part of the set.
Come on.
They're doing that with Logan too.
You can buy black and white Logan.
But it's not a feature.
It's your own thing.
I won't be buying either Logan.
No, I know you won't.
You all know, dear listeners, let's do a quick catch up before, you know,
we get into anything to movie related here. Pat, I joined a, I did another DNA test
because I'm trying to find out what my medical history is as an adopted man.
I don't know. What do you mean medical? What illnesses
around your family? You think you need that added pressure? Well, I go to the doctor
and he goes, you know, you fill out a questionnaire. Anybody, any history in your
family of heart disease? I'm like, I don't know. I'm adopted.
it. I don't know. Yeah. I feel like I should know. I'm terrified of getting the results, but I feel
like I should know. Right. So I did this thing for 23 in me. It's actually been a running segment
or whatever you want to call it on the emotional hangs podcast. That's why I did it because about my
lineage and my adoption and maybe finding my parents. But I get that they send me today on the profile
on the thing, you get a list of diseases.
I don't have any of the results.
So it's 80 diseases, next to all of them,
it just says pending.
Oh boy.
And you go down this thing.
I didn't know there was 80 goddamn diseases out there.
Let me hit you with this one.
They're out there.
Maple syrup urine disease.
What is that?
Your piss smells like urine.
Your piss smells like maple syrup right before you eat it.
You have metabolic crisis in your body,
Which means your blood is blood is toxic and you start vomiting and shitting and
Demet being demented. Well, you don't have that. How is that one of the 80 big ones?
It tells you if you have a predisposition for it. Did you live in New York when
The city smelled like maple syrup for like three days. It was it would have been about two thousand four
I think I did I don't remember though. It was so baffling
And I remember going into work, like, am I having a stroke?
What's going on?
And everybody's like, no, the whole city.
And it was a lorry side up to, well, the upper east side,
Joe.
What I'm trying to say is the whole city
smells like maple syrup.
Why didn't it smell like maple syrup?
We never got an answer.
It was some sort of weird probably.
I would assume New Jersey played a hand,
like a New Jersey factory wreaked or something.
I have a good New Jersey story.
when I was when I was starting out in comedy Caroline's comedy club you
Caroline Ray Caroline Ray an old friend in this business for me I matter
she was very funny and nice I don't know why I wasn't shitting on her oh wait
Caroline Ray the comedian yeah yes she's a friend too she's cool I was thinking
of Caroline that runs Caroline's I got confused you're thinking of Caroline in
the city they're yes yeah they're both they're both Caroline no sweet Caroline
That's who I'm trying to talk about.
Yes, they're all nice.
But anyway, they used to do these things where you'd go to,
they'd send comics out to a high school they perform.
Like the high school would bring it in as I could activity.
And, you know, I would do it because I was fucking broke.
They'd give you like a hundred bucks to go play
two high schools in an afternoon.
Right.
And keep it clean.
You were supposed to, but it was sort of loose.
I mean we're going into some statin island schools, you know, it wasn't we weren't going into you know kids weren't in blue shorts and ties, you know
But Kurt Metzger was on stage and he goes I'm from Jersey and the we're in statin island and the high school audience booze Jersey
Sure and he goes you can boom me all you want you live on the island where we dump our fucking garbage to a to a
To a group of high school children
Now I'm baffled by a high school having stand -up comics from New York come in. I was baffled. What a confusing
thing
Yeah, it was baffling. I think the one rule he might have not said fuck
I think he did though, and I think it was okay. Yeah, I think they were kind of like trying not to say fuck
Yeah, school, I mean I think said that right anyway
I'm gonna warn you folks I
I was really sort of panicked today.
I was telling Joe before the podcast,
but when I was in maybe a sixth, seventh, eighth kind of grade,
I would have a stutter that came and went
and it's not like the, I'm not gonna do it and insult people.
It's not quite what you're thinking,
but it's a really kind of stuck on a word thing
and gets really embarrassing.
Well, can you give me some of it?
I know you're not doing it.
It's not I'm probably going to do it on the course of this, but I so I
Is it one of the face ones does your face lock up and stuff? Or is it just like?
It really now ends with me being so real super embarrassed and going like I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry and like cutting myself off. Okay. I know how to cut it off before it gets into like a real
spitty violent place
But anyway, I had not had this
experience in
in ages, unless I remember when I thought I was never going to get a job when I lived
in New York, it started coming back and it really freaked me out.
But now I'm meeting with 20 writers a day to potentially work on my show, which we still
don't know.
I will know by the time you hear this, which will make this either a real sweet podcast before
Before he knew how his life was going to change for the better, or you know, you can just
imagine me just bottoming out of society with the no, but I will know this weekend.
So the meetings are going smoothly at first.
The meetings are going great and I love meeting right.
The phone rings the guy says, Pat, it's Mike, it's back.
That's an it joke.
Yes, okay.
Stutter.
Yeah, Joe referenced that it was like it which ties it into Horan and it really was.
I mean, I was shocked today by how many meetings and these are writers who are there technically to impress me
I mean, I'm trying to hire them and I met a lot of great funny people tons of great funny people
But I tell you it happened on about three different occasions
Where I got locked into the stutter and would just stop talking and in a one -on -one meeting
It was mortifying and I'm imagining it will probably happen tonight during the podcast, which is why I'm saying it because now that I'm
hyper aware of it and
Frightened of it much like it. I am worried it will elbow its way back into my conversation
You know what I say you say next time in one of those meetings when that happens you say hey
Sorry, I had a stutter when I was a kid and you could imagine this has been a stressful way. I said it on each one
Oh, you did I did and people were very understanding. Well good
My old boss, Mr. Michael Patrick King of Sex and the City fame.
He talked about the stress before the pilot of a two broke girl.
This is a man who's got a lot of money, folks.
Very successful.
And he said, he refers with his stigmata.
He was like his nose, which had never blood before, was just dumping blood.
And whenever he would get a new bit of information like, this isn't looking good, we don't know
We don't know if we can get this right or we don't know if we can get this actor or whatever his nose would start pouring blood
Oh, I mean stress when you're not dealing with it properly as I never have
It manifests itself in very crazy ways. It's all I can sign. All right
So anyway, it's just a warning if you hear me suddenly
Spass out. You're not gonna spaz out. Spaz is a one. That's not a correct word correct. That's now a derogatory term
I fist spas below or worse than the dreaded R word can you just say retar it's no
I can't you're not saying it to make fun. You're just saying a word that exists
I'm asking just cuz I want I think retard is worse than spas
That seems right. I think you could get away with spas in the right company
I didn't feel good about it. I think if I was describing myself. I think if you said retard you'd be
You wouldn't be directing the Oscars anymore and you have to be right, you know
That's right. One of those situations.
Pat, the only movies I watched this week for our little movie run down,
were the Predator films. Yeah, so I can't really talk about one and two, but I can't talk about
Predators, because I didn't know we would be we would be doing these, but we are doing them now. So I'm, but I
Predator is the third installment. I folks. I saw this in the theater. The date I was on at the time got so
Aggravated with the film. She walked out of it and you stayed. No, I ended up leaving. Oh, and it was like a 2010
10, so I don't know if I ever saw Predators, I own it.
I don't know if I ever saw it.
I left with her, not to just patch up the day,
but pardon me, was also like,
you know how this movie sucks, who cares?
And I thought it was a Robert Rodriguez joint,
but he didn't produce it.
He didn't produce it.
No, he produced it.
Then I caught glimpses of it on cable, never cared, whatever.
I gotta tell you people, I rewatched this thing
from start to finish finally, properly the other day.
Yeah.
Fucking fantastic.
I loved every minute of it.
The twists were great.
What a fucking cast in this thing.
Adrian Brody.
Now do you like Adrian Brody?
I love Adrian Brody.
Your boy, Walt Goggins is in it.
Toe for Grace.
Right.
Now one of my favorite, Larry Fishburn.
Yes.
I forget the lady's name, but she's great.
It's only one lady, of course,
because it's the only, only the actresses.
Cause they only ever let one lady in the damn thing.
I can't remember.
Oh, Danny Trejo's in it.
Yeah.
I, uh, now Rob Delaney, who was just unquestionably a master
of Twitter and always has been.
I met him a couple of times.
He's a very nice guy as well.
He is one of my favorite tweets of all time.
And I'm not going to get it right.
But it was basically when the Darjeeling limited came out.
And it was, uh, wow.
Adrian Brody, Owen Wilson, Jason Schwartzman,
is this thing called the Darjeeling limited or no strain?
And I laughed, and then immediately was like,
I hope they're not all Jewish,
and this isn't a horrifically racist Jewish.
Owen Wilson is not Jewish.
He's not, I knew that much.
But recently, I guarantee Delaney sat before tweeting it.
It was like, I better make sure Owen Wilson's not all so Jewish.
It's a great chair.
It made me laugh hysterically.
And I never liked the jeeling limited and I never really I don't think I like Brody frankly. I mean, he's never done anything for me
I like Brody. He's in the son of Sam. He's great and so sure summer or summer of Sam summer of Sam
Summer of Sam's a great fuck. He's great in the jacket
That's a great hard thriller kind of thing you take you like summer of Sam or you like 25 hour better to me
20 hours one of the best movies of that decade. I like both films
But I remember liking summer of San and a bit better because it was a little more
Uh, par -oriented because it was about a serial killer.
I guess so.
Um, 24 -hour though, I don't think so.
The 25 -hour I would say is probably technically a better film.
I just...
Norton, Seymour Hoffman, Pepper.
Yeah, it's a great fucking flick.
I mean, it really is great.
Uh...
A very old Dawson and her hottest.
Summer's...
I mean, 25 -hours a lot of fun in the same way that, uh, like a pop -a -granage village is
a, you know, it's that kind of thing.
Well, I watch all the Spike Lee joints.
All the joints.
and I mean, I'm talking the sweet blood of Jesus.
I haven't seen that one, how is it?
Man, it's, I mean, he is a guy who has really
kind of lost his way, but I was really excited
about when he got into like commercial shit,
like, I mean, even like inside man.
Yeah, he's just a guy who never got lazy,
you know, he was always doing like really awesome camera shit.
Spike Lee, for the acclaim he's gotten,
I think because of his politics
is one of the most underrated directors of all time.
Do the right thing is a masterpiece,
25 -hour masterpiece, summer and a Sam masterpiece,
Malcolm X, masterpiece.
What more do you want?
But he's not held up in that high regard at all.
The number 10 slot on my top 10 list
is it's a tie between Fatso and Malcolm X.
I'm not joking, let's do it.
You gotta loan me Fatso, I've never seen it.
I don't own it because the fucking DVD is $80
because it's out of print.
And I saw it on Amazon years ago for five dollars
Because I had the fucking VHS. I don't know the I don't want to talk about an idiot. They're two beautiful films
I mean two very entirely different ways, but Malcolm X is the reason I bring it up
It's I mean it's a tour to force. It's a fucking astounding film. Yeah, I love the guy the guy's amazing and he's always
Even his movies like an inside now, which is the highest movie. He's always packing them full of like really interesting
shit and social commentary and etc. And you got to just call it racism that he's
not talked about amongst the greats. I mean he is to me one of the absolute
greats. He's a master film. I haven't heard Spike Lee's name in ten years.
That is true. You know I think it's I do think it's because his last four or five
movies have been a little like sideways where you're like yeah you wonder if
there's maybe a drug issue.
I mean, old boys sucked in a weird,
unconventionally bad way.
He did that military movie that was supposed to be great,
but nobody saw it.
What was that?
Chirac?
No, Chirac, I didn't see Chirac.
I liked Chirac except for it was a modern take
on a Greek tragedy.
And about like 15 minutes into the movie,
you realize, is everybody rhyming when they talk?
And then you realize, wait, they are.
And then that kind of fucked it up, yeah, but he did it. It was cool the way he did it in certain
place like Samuel Jackson is like the Greek chorus and he's like this very like boisterous guy
So when he's doing it, it's cool, and it's fun, and it's weird and different, but then like in like dramatic scenes
When the when the actors are rhyming, you're like it's just taking me out of it, man
It's two. It's too all the nose. I hated it going back to Shakespeare. I don't need to see it or is it a Shakespeare thing?
I thought it was a Greek is it shakes I might be wrong well the Greek chorus thing is essentially a Shakespeare thing
I mean the witches and Macbeth and all that that is considered a Greek chorus. All right
Well, whatever the hell it is it rhymed. Yeah, no, I mean I just he also got a lot of heat for that movie
People said that he was exploiting the violence in Chicago. It's a which I didn't understand
I thought he was actually doing a very he got a lot of heat about a lot of commentary and when he well
Well, you know, as Donald Trump says, Chicago is garbage, is what?
Cardage.
You know what's happening on the streets?
Listen, don't even, don't even, don't even, people on the way to the store to buy a loaf
of bread are getting gunned down.
Now I'm, I'm veering into Jiminy Glick, but yeah, I, uh, I'm so, this is the only political
thing I'll say on this podcast and it's very non -partisan what I'm about to say.
Okay.
I'm very spun around right now. Last week, last week, the headlines read Hillary Clinton calling
out Comey saying he's bad at what he does, saying he cost her the election. Yep. And everybody
was going, good for her. Now Trump fires him yesterday. Everybody's going this monster. It's
I don't know which I don't know what to believe anymore. My head is this. I don't know what
The truth is, you can't believe shit.
I mean, I, I feel, I don't, I don't, I don't,
I'm like, what am I supposed to, who am I?
Who's side of me?
I don't know what's happening.
It truly is.
And, you know, it was discussed
in this White House Correspondence Center,
you're watching a house of cohorts
to feel better about politics.
The show that was supposed to be like the darkest
extreme of politics has become quaint.
As, as we said on that dinner,
because for Trump to fire the man who is investigating him,
how he does not have his people say to him,
do you realize how terrible this makes you look?
They're saying, no, it's a mob hit.
They're saying to him,
you better get rid of this fucking guy
because he's just gonna sing like a babe.
Well, if he fires him, he's gonna have more incentive.
That's what I don't get.
Yeah, but he can't testify against him if he fires him.
I think, right?
Yeah, because the new the new guy is going to speak at his place like the temporary head of the FU
It's a mob. It's like a mob thing
But last week everybody was saying go Hillary. We're glad you're calling out this set of a bitch
Now he's getting fired up and we're going this is a disgrace. He should still have his job
Who says who on anymore? What's going on? Let me tell you Joe
You're not on Trump's side. You're fine. I'm not on Trump's side, but I'm also not on Hillary's side
I don't know who the hell is trying to move them.
You know, so confusing, this is no longer true.
The enemy of my enemy is my enemy.
That's not true anymore.
So now, I just want to go into a hole
as we've talked about many times on this show.
I want to live in a fucking, I don't know.
I always talk about going to my cool ranch
and I'd call it my cool ranch.
I'd be stocked with cool ranch Doritos,
but it would be a, just a ranch where I have my money
and I can, till the earth, if I sow desire,
I can watch movies, I can get stone, drink,
I'll have a pool.
That's really my goal.
And everybody's like, I you'd get bored.
And maybe that's true.
But that has truly become my goal.
All right.
To buy a cool ranch and live there.
Fair enough.
Well, let's move on to the scary stuff segment, Pat.
This is a quick one.
Oh, have you seen movies?
Have I seen movies?
The answer is and it's been more than a week and I have not seen a single movie. That's correct. Well then let's move on all right
Real quick this week folks from our friends at scream factory
Who don't sponsor us god damn it. We got to get some sponsors
Nothing we got nothing. Anyway, I never saw a check from that other thing we did I never saw it either
Who the hell knows I got debts, baby
I don't know how new or old this release is, but I got this when I was in Australia, per
the recommendation of a nice man that worked at the Minotaur collectible shop.
If you're ever in Melbourne, Australia, go to that place.
It's video's comic books, you know.
Oh, it's not like just Minotaur collectibles.
No, it's just called Minotaur.
guy. Anyway, screen factory released this thing. It's called my minute are collectibles at
minute target. Huh? I go to minute target to get all my minute are stuff. Who doesn't
anymore? He's good. Clothes, you know, washing stuff. This is why the mom at our pop stores
of our clothes. Oh boy, people guys, we're not doing well. Carry on, Joe. They released this
This thing, the four movie all night, horror marathon, it's four flicks, what's the matter
with Helen starring Debbie Reynolds and Shelley Winters, the godsend, the outing, which was
originally called the lamp, and the vagrant starring, you're in my favorite Bill Paxton.
Love them.
Four really fun movies, four very different films than one another, they're very goofy.
the, uh, some in a good way, some in a just straight up 80s harway, the vagrant is, it's,
whoa, I just dropped it.
Hello.
The vagrant is almost a horror comedy, I'd say, um, Paxton's great.
He's playing a nerd in it, which is a role you don't go off and see him in.
Uh, it's just a really fun pack.
It's like, I think 11 bucks or something, uh, pick it up.
It's worth grabbing and it's also the first time many of these films have ever been released
anywhere.
all right so check that out I enjoyed it quite a bit all right and now the main event yeah I
have a shit ton of questions that just came in on Facebook that we can get to but I
I guess, you know, what do we do?
Do we do predator and then into tune?
Do we give an overall?
Well, here's what I'm wondering.
I think everybody has seen predator one and two.
I saw predator two for the first time last night.
And I had always thought I had seen it
or wanted to see it and never saw it.
Let's do a re, let's, okay, so then let's,
I guess let's just do a quick recap of not plot -wise
of both, but just a quick review of both.
And then I think we can just move into these questions because I think these questions are going to all right instead of us going to the questions after and then going hey
Are we already talked about this? I'm gonna give my take on one two you give your take on one two
Briefly predator one Arnold Schwarzenegger Carl Weathers
I recommend the 3d version of you can see it because the way they shoot him
You know the predator with the the kind of hologram graphics it looks really awesome on 3d
I love Arnold and Predator.
There's something weirdly like more likable
than his other action movies of the day
before he became like Mr. Comedy and everything else.
He's really likable in it in a weird way.
The movie is pretty much airtight.
It's got the best action sci -fi movie ever.
Predator?
No shit.
It is my number one action.
It's definitely my number one action movie ever.
It might be my number one sci -fi movie ever.
I wouldn't put it anywhere near either of those lists.
You're going to put it above like die hard, you're saying.
110%.
It's like without argument.
I know you're putting it above aliens because you don't like it.
120%.
All right, I wouldn't do either.
And to me, predator is not, I don't know if it's hitting my top 50 for either, but I liked
predator a great deal.
And when I rewashed it, I appreciated it even more.
or I thought it was a good, about as good a B movie as you can do, but to me it is kind
of a B movie.
Predator 2, which I watched for the first time last night, I struggled to stay awake.
I liked Danny Glover, he's not a lead to me, and I did not at all think he should have
had this role.
Gary Bucy makes no impression, he didn't, it wasn't even crazy, he had no character at
all. Bill Paxton was a nice surprise, but I think it immediately becomes Bill Paxton's
worst. Like I was like, they didn't even use him well. I don't think, you know, I heard
Arnold didn't come back. He didn't like the script, but he also really thought the
predator should never come to Los Angeles. He should be in the jungle. That to me was
like, no, I like the predator in LA idea. And when it opens and says, set in Los Angeles,
I was rubbing my hands together. But I just thought it was a complete waste and a real
a piece of shit of a movie.
Well, Pat, much to my surprise,
we're gonna have a lot to disagree about tonight.
Okay.
Predator is the best action movie of all time.
It is better than diehard.
Do you like diehard?
We never even diehard.
I do like diehard.
All right.
I like all the diehards except that last one.
Oh, of course.
Well, the last two, I mean, live free or is it?
I like live free or diehard.
I mean, say this, diehard one, two and vengeance.
are better than predator. You're out of your fucking mind. Sorry. You think die hard, too. Die harder.
Is better than predator. How can you even compare? How can you compare?
The machismo. I'm going to go. It's always sunny on this. You got Bruce Willis in one movie.
You've got Arnie, Carl Weathers, Jesse The Body, Shane Black, who is directing and writing the
new predator. You've got, I mean, you've got the Indian guy. You've got Bill Duke.
Bill Duke, who I have met is a very cool guy. Here's the thing. You've got a monster. I don't
respond to machismo. I don't like it. I never have. It's never been my thing. Part of that's
growing up in Missouri where that's the only currency. And I grew up with a lack of it perhaps.
but to me Bruce Willis is about as machismo as I as I like and that movie he's he is a cop
he's not jacked up to the point of ridiculousness predator is a way better movie than a
commando certainly than than a lot of shorts and it doesn't touch the top 50 you said 50 not for
action movies know and maybe for sci -fi because I'm not a big sci -fi fan it's not on my top 50 action
movies now. I don't I don't think right now you could name eight action movies better than
Predator. You couldn't do it. I'm gonna say Raiders in Temple of Doom. They're not action movies,
they're fantasy movies. Oh, that's ridiculous. Okay, fine. They're action movies. I put Raiders in
Temple of Doom, but I didn't want to try true lies. I know you're gonna get mad about true lies. That's
because I just watched them bull. Okay, my head last crusade. I might my head is not tainted by my
my childhood anymore, I recently watched Predator
and True Lies and True Lies is better.
Always watch Predator.
Yeah, and I got to see it before I knew what the twist was.
I didn't even know that there was an alien coming.
I just rented it because it was an Arnie movie.
Well, that's, and when you go 40 minutes in
and you're like, this is an awesome Arnie movie
where they're saving POWs.
And then all of a sudden a goddamn alien comes in
you're like, what the fuck?
That's like a dust toldon twist.
Yeah, that's fucking awesome.
Can I tell you this?
I think I put it from dust to dawn over better. That's a horror movie. Come on. Now here's the thing
What I never like or what I never really give much of a shit about is one guy
Fighting one thing
An alien an alien versus Arnold whatever
To me it gets boring and it got real boring in predator two when it's standing lever fighting, but
But at the end, when all his very colorful crew
was gone and you're left with Arnold going,
come on, come at me.
Awesome.
I'm like, Arnold is going to be fine.
You don't know he's gonna be fine.
The goddamn thing sets off a self -destruct mechanism
that levels three miles of rain forest
if you weren't listening in Predator 2,
which I also liked quite a bit, and here's what.
I thought Predator 2 and it really, really phenomenal new elements to the mythology of the Predator.
Did you like the voodoo subplot? You always complain about the voodoo subplot?
No, the voodoo subplot I didn't care about.
I like it.
It really is more than a subplot, it kind of is the plot.
I like that there was a red herring and they thought that this badass Jamaican gangster was actually killing everybody
and the fact that he was into voodoo was the reason these people were being decapitated.
I thought that was actually very smart.
Okay, but the details they added in Predator 2 now the the curse of Predator 2 is the same thing as the curse of the fly to it came out
Too close to the original had that movie come out 10 years later, which is where it actually takes place it takes place 10 years
Predator 2 actually takes place in 1990 about three years later, which is the reasonable time for us
It came out it takes place in 1997 it came out in 93 I believe and
or it takes place in 97 came out in 90 excuse me yeah had it actually come out in 97
we would have appreciated it a bit more I think but that being said whatever that is
probably true I like the fact that they add the detail why is this thing here because it's attracted
to heat and conflict I thought that was awesome I thought it was awesome that they
went into further explaining like the oh the uh it has a it's it's suit can deflect light
and it appears invisible it's not actually fucking invisible they just added these really cool details
I like that in the if you watch the special features Gary Busey is woo I don't know if he's
fucking around or not or what but he is going off the fucking rails in these interviews and he is
is it modern day interviews no it's from the set and he is he's given a backstory I don't know if he
He just made it up, but he's like,
he's in here because he died nine weeks after the first film.
I was in charge of that mission in the first film.
Now they sent me in and the second,
like he's going deep.
I didn't watch those.
I mean, a big part of it last night
is that when I walk into my home now,
I am falling asleep from the moment my door opens.
So I was, I was never out,
but I was, definitely my eyes were dimming here and there
and it was a very loud movie.
And I just realized I didn't give a shit.
what are your thoughts of Gary of Danny Glover as an actor? I've always thought he's a solid actor
but he's got that raspy and tense thing and that is it. I like Danny Glover. I think his go -to bag
of tricks is I'm going to look confused and sweaty right now. I'm going to look a little frightened
and I'm going to mumble a lot. I mean of course I love a lethal weapon. Of course I love a royal
that's the, that's the, I don't, he's not a lead to me.
Listen, he's a lead, he's not a lead in this movie.
Sure.
So I agree with you there.
All right.
The reason Danny Glover works so well in lethal weapon
is because he's the guy saying, I'm too old for this shit
and I'm clearly a bewildered man
and I want to retire and be with my family
and I'm a wreck emotionally because I don't want
to do this shit anymore.
Yet my partner's fucking crazy
and he keeps dragging me into these situations.
So I have to go in with my hands shaking
and I'm really on edge because I don't want to,
then it really works.
It doesn't work when he's alone in this movie.
Yeah.
I would have liked to have seen him in packs,
I was mad when Paxton died in the middle of the movie
because I liked the Paxton character
and I thought what was really going to happen was
Paxton was going to earn a salt in the final moments
or Bucy was going to.
Yeah.
And they did for a second bring back Bucy after he thought
he was dead and I was like,
Oh, this is great. They're going to show you the busies like a real deal guy here.
And then he gets killed immediately. So they did make bad decisions in the film.
I love that he goes on to the ship. I love that there's the Easter egg of the alien skull,
and that's what started the entire alien versus predator thing in comic books and everything
that went to unfortunately bad films. But I thought that was really cool. And it wasn't the mess I
I expected I like the aspects of it and I always like anything like a 90 like speed for example
Speed feels like a period piece about LA to me in a weird way
You're gonna say speed's better than predator cuz I'll throw this speed is better than press you're a
Speed is better than for those you know my head is down on the
Joe Joe just looked away from me for the first time he turned his swivel stool away from me
Listen to me, you fans, you motherfuckers.
I swear to God, if he does not get the same amount of shit
I got for my Jurassic Park comments,
for saying speed is better than predator.
If he does not get the same amount of shit,
I think it's shit for two weeks
about fucking Jurassic Park three.
If I had left it as die hard
is better than predator.
No, everyone would have agreed with me.
I am pushing it, but I mean it.
I think Predator is a B plus A minus, and I can give you a lot better movies that I liked more.
Speed is a better movie.
It's not a better movie.
That's an insane statement.
And I think a big issue is we're dealing with an unformed Arnold.
We're still dealing with an Arnold who is not in control of his powers.
What are you talking about?
And if I'm saying Keanu Reeves is more effective than than Arnold he's not he isn't speed Keanu Reeves
And if I'm going speed predator Keanu gets that win if I'm going
True lies speed Arnold gets that way true. Oh, but Arnold had to find it. Come on. He doesn't have an impredator
He does have an impredator. He's certainly stick around solid. He's already saying that stuff. Yeah. No, I know he is
He throws a knife into the guy's chest and he goes stick around
I think Predator is super entertaining and yet, so what did you think of the Rambo franchise?
I love first blood in ways I can't explain, but again, I don't consider first blood
action movie.
I consider that a drama.
It's a drama with action elements.
I think the Rambo reboot is better than everyone except first blood.
I would say it's better than the second two, but I bought that along with first blood on
Blu -ray, and I watched the back -to -back, and I turned off the fourth installment, because
it didn't have any of the depth or heart that first blood had.
It was gone.
I'll take Predator over all the rambos.
I mean, I'll take Predator over a lot, but not over Keanu Reeves and Sandra Bullock and
Speed.
Keanu Reeves is terrible in that movie.
That's one of the movies that made everybody go Keanu Reeves can't act.
Keanu Reeves is bad at speed.
You're talking about a guy who's worse than devil's advocate because he's going up against
Puccina.
But speed to me is a genius prem, a true genius prem is where if somebody told you that
in the bar, you'd be like, I'm going to kill this guy and make this movie and it's executed
beautifully and it never stops and it has the three, three acts set and it's got the elevator
Schitt at the beginning, which is really intense, the bus stuff, which is pure gold throughout.
And then it goes on to that crazy subway, shit at the end.
And Hopper is a great villain, and Daniels is a great actor, and Reeves does his best.
And him and Bob are great.
Bobper is a great villain.
Yeah.
Everybody else I'm fine with too.
Reeves is the main guy in it, and he's fucking bad in it.
Those, here's why I'll take him in.
Kans, it's just Kans.
Here's where I'll take him in Devil's Advocate
any day of the week over a counter -reason speed
because he doesn't have to do fucking monologues
in Devil's Advocate.
But, you know what he is doing?
An accent.
I love Devil's Advocate.
And by the way,
Devil's Advocate is great.
But Chino, and dare I say it
because the man was arrested
for child pornography, unfortunately.
Jeffrey Jones' performance in Devil's Advocate
is over the fucking mode.
Crag Teen Nelson, Grand Slam, they're, you're talking, you're talking fucking
Bahimuth performances. The, to overshadow, I tell you, they're on his phenomenal.
I, when I, I thought that I was going to maybe start stalking Charlize there when I saw that movie.
And they got her at a time when it was like, you need me to be naked, three -fourths of the movie?
Fine, I'm 21, I'll do it.
I mean, Devil's Advocate is fantastic.
And I love that they cast Reeves,
because Pacino is able to slap him around
and be like, just make him look even worse.
But he's just dancing all over Kiana Reeves
in that movie, who was doing, I suppose,
a surfer Boston accent.
Yeah, and the movie ends with,
the movie ends with one of the greatest
monologues of all time.
Yeah.
Pacino.
He's an absentee land.
Yeah.
But Chino has two of possibly the 10 greatest film monologues ever of all time.
The one is devil's advocate.
The other one, of course, is set of a woman when he goes in, I just got chills talking
about it.
When he goes into save Chris O'Donnell, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's shatters
the screen.
It's beautiful versus the climax of speed.
What would you do?
It literally sounds like Bill and Ted are chasing a criminal.
I love it.
I love it now.
I mean, I saw speed when I was 14 it was like the third already movie I ever seen it since then. Yeah, and I loved it again
I think it's fantastic
Let's go to the phones wash
Let's go to the phones. I mean, by the way the nudity in Predator 2 which is
brief but particularly memorable and I looked it up and it was Terry Weigel who was the first porn star I ever saw
Because I was like how do I know this nudity full frontal naked for about five minutes porn star Terry Weigel
That's what you used to get when you would go to an R -rated movie in the 80s and 90s, and that is what you never get now.
And it's infuriating.
In fact, Pat text me the way he said, he said,
I know those tits anywhere.
I didn't tell you, and there's a screenshot of it.
I didn't text you, I know those tits anywhere.
I didn't screenshot you.
So, okay, Facebook.
Let's go one for one.
I'll do Twitter and Facebook.
Facebook, and please go to, we'll see you in Hell Page.
Joe said he couldn't find it.
I didn't even know Joe had a Facebook account, but really you just had the time and we'll
see you in hell on it.
It's right there.
I couldn't find it.
Also, too, while we're on this, we'll see when hell is now live on Twitter at WSI, what
are the letters?
WSIYHPOD, at WSIYHPOD, all in caps on Twitter, follow us, please, we already have 55 followers
the things been alive for I don't know 24 hours or something. I mean I haven't even gotten the
check -in with it so I should and will and I'll be in there soon. Anyway we're on there and the
patreon is almost up. Okay very soon. All right beautiful. Right off the bat and I can answer this
because I watched them both in the last two weeks. What's better predator 2 or kindergarten cop?
up. My answer. And I'll say it's closer than this person might like to believe, but my
answer is predator to. Okay. Thank you for that. You still have some sanity. Uh, Lino,
Erica Branding. I'm sorry. Hi, Erica. Lino forced all at four stall 21 tweets us. You think
predator couldn't see Dutch. Dutch is Schwarzenegger covered in mud because it's because the
mother lowered his body temp, or do you think there's something different about the clay?
No, well, in Predator's the third film, they confirmed that it was just the mother lowered
his body temp.
Also, at the end of Predator 2, there's another detail.
Wait, they are referencing the events of Predator 1 and Predator's 3.
Yes.
That's weird.
Yeah.
They referenced it very briefly.
I always assume that people on military missions don't research previous military questions.
once they once they realize they're fighting a monster sure they bring it up we
should check the the notes that Arnold wrote down in his journal right right after he got back
uh they also in predator two sort of reference it um because the sprinklers keep them
keep them uh invisible uh at the end so anyway um what's this heath keen hello Keith
What's the scariest alien you've seen in a movie? And how does the predator rank against it?
I will say I am rarely scared of an alien. I
Am scared more by real things, but if I'm gonna think about
What the scariest alien I've seen in a movie is
What do you think, Joe the scary aliens I've ever seen in a movie without question without question
are the are the aliens in communion and fire in the sky fire in the sky is a
good answer yeah fire in the sky not a great flick where you you want with me
that night where I hung out with DB Swini that's a night you should have been
there I wish I could have been now you were texting me actually this man is a
trip I mean he I loved him I love he's a good friend of Johnny Galecki who I'm
doing this pilot with and he was a treat yeah you were saying that he's a real
character like a nut. Yeah, he fired in the sky. Those any any time the aliens are
waddling around like little nuns, you know, and cloaks that freaks me out. That's so
in both those movies they were sort of nun -ish. I hear you. All right. Here's another mud
one. Just let me do these two back -to -back really quick because this is a quick one.
and grumpasaurus at grumpasaurus on Twitter.
Mud, how does that mask heat signature anyway?
Well, I'm just assuming because it was cool, mud.
Yeah, and that was it.
And this is another one from grumpasaurus.
I think a better P2 discussion would be
colors or RoboCop, inner city post,
Reagan, black, gang, panic movies.
Well, a P2 discussion wouldn't really involve movies
outside of P2.
Well, we should do RoboCop.
I do RoboCop.
Colors doesn't fall.
a helicopter in 20 years. Colors is a great movie, but certainly doesn't factor into this podcast.
I love colors. It doesn't fit the genres that we do, but Dennis Hopper did direct it in the
great iced tea. Yeah. The title's track, which I love. So there you go, grumpasaurus. Oh, there's
a third one from grumpasaurus. He writes, can we start with the fact that P2 is terrible and shouldn't
be cannon, but P1 is one of the greatest bad movies of all time. Oh, no, I don't agree
with either of these things. He's saying, I think Predator is a B movie, but it's certainly
not a bad movie. And he's saying P2 is terrible. I don't think it's terrible. I think it's an
interesting slice of the story. And again, I think it expands the mythology in great ways.
I think it's necessary. Okay. Yeah, I mean, I have some joke questions here that I'll all
skip, but favorite quote from each film and would you watch it? Come on. Come on. Hurley
SkyNet. What? What happened? Would you watch a predator remake with an all -dwarf cast
which included Peter Dinklage as the lead? Of course I would. I mean, these aren't serious
questions. That's not a serious question, but I would watch it. Favorite quote from each
film? I mean, I ain't got time to bleed. Predator is full of great lines. Yeah. Pussy jokes are great.
Yeah, um from Shane Black and also like learning about the backstory like Shane Black basically
He didn't get a writer credit on it, but he was like I'd love to come in and punch it up
If you give me a role in the movie and he was making so much money and doing these huge deals that they let him do it
But he's like all Shane Black contributed was those two pussy jokes and he's thought of as being like a guiding voice in the predator
They're funny jokes for those you don't remember
I was going out of my girlfriend yesterday. I said, hey, you got a gigantic pussy. You got a gigantic pussy
She said, why do you say it twice? I said I didn't. Yeah
That's a good down Rikkel's style vagina joke. I also learned from the predator blu -ray that
They shot everything in predator. They're like it's in base. It's in three acts as a good movie
we generally is.
And they were like, the third act stuff
where the predator comes in and we had this giant guy
in a suit, we were waiting on the suit to be created.
Yeah.
So it's this amazing story of their ready to shoot.
The third act, the suit shows up and they said it looked
like a particularly bad lobster costume.
It's supposed to be Van Dam too,
was supposed to be playing the predator.
Yeah.
It was a big red, ridiculous costume
and they started to shoot it and the director,
who did die hard, better movie, sent in.
He also did last action hero, by the way.
I mean, he didn't hunt for red October too, it's great, man.
But I like last action hero.
I'm just mad at you.
I don't know why you needed to shit on it.
I didn't, well, the predator was just,
you push me, you push me to this.
The predator was his rehearsal for the master class of die hard.
But he sent back footage of this guy running around
in this lobster costume and was like,
you guys want me to proceed or what do you want to do?
And they said let's shut it down and the predator production was shut down for nine months while they created the amazing predator costume
Well, yeah, that was really interesting because the costume is
The mandible thing
It's it's it's it's it's pretty legendary. Yes. It's an amazing costume. I've never seen something that is
Obviously fake because that creature doesn't exist that looks so fucking real. Yep, and it's all animatronic
Mass work whatever not not a bit of it is CGI that fucking thing looks real. Yeah, it looks like a real god damn alien with it's it's awesome agree
Hold on. Okay. This is from at LP 6188
With the predator have been able to see Arnold if he covered himself in peanut butter instead of come on guys
I mean you got to read him before you read him on the air. Oh
Oh, gotta do a little vetting.
Does a good one.
Patrick Baxter at Pat Man Power.
Thoughts on the legendary handshake
between Arnold and Carl.
I absolutely have thoughts on that.
Okay. That shot, I would describe it as gratuitous.
It is a gratuitous muscle shot
when they, when they clasp hands mid -air
at the beginning of the film.
Somebody asked here about it.
I mean, gratuitous?
I don't feel it is.
It, it is literally a cut of 80s in one moment.
Yeah, I love it. Yeah, I love it. And my friend Robert Davis from Austin, Texas, and I used to always mimic that scene to each other
What's the matter dealing see I got you pushing too many pain souls?
We said that all the time. We yeah my buddy Ryan Hotsle who I grew up with a great man
he was obsessed with both predators and
It took me it was one of those amazing moments where it took me
25 years to get a joke
He used to always go once some candy once some candy from Predator 2
Whenever he had candy he'd go once some candy right and I never was like, why are you saying it like that?
I would just be like yes
I would like a a chewy sweet tart or whatever it might be and then last night. I'm watching it
I started the text him and then remembered in Missouri would have been 3 a .m. Right, but I was like once some candy
Well, there you go. There you go. It was a nice moment. There you go. In a bad movie
This is from hay fight and tiger at hay fight and tiger
Thought you'd like to see the original script for Predator then called hunter
Written in 1986. Well, thank you, demon. Sure
We we can't read it right now, but that's very cool of you that if you descend that to us
I will like to to read that
You got anymore over there. I'm coming to the end of mine. That's my usable ones. I mean, I think we're ready to pack it in
And folks, we're going to be able to put a lot more focus back on this show.
But I think we pulled together a nice couple episodes.
We are at a busy season.
The busy season out here in Los Angeles.
Thanks for coming out.
We're going to see more movies.
We're going to have more discuss.
Joe, do you have anything, anything pressing and you're going to Dallas?
I don't.
Well, I want to apologize to the people we didn't get to,
Cole, Rathaker, Gibbon, Wizard, Abby, Manuel, sorry, guys,
you were, we're sorry, we just didn't get to you.
Mike Holinger says he recommends the dark horse comics,
if you want to dig deeper, I don't know about those.
Abby, Matt, you know what?
The predator do it.
Sorry.
Abby, Manuel asks, what's the scariest monsters?
Scared you most as kids, predator was her number one.
We already kind of answered that for ourselves
with the communion aliens. Your top five Schwarzenegger movies, given Wizard, we don't have time
to get into that because that will be an all -out shit show in here. Top five Schwarzeneggers, I could
do that with ease. I could do it with ease too. We don't have time to yell about the stupid fucking
order that you put yours in. I mean Arnold is a very bad actor. He's not a very bad actor.
he's not a very bad actor that's not fair he's a limited I think he's a better
actor than I think he's more capable than Stallone is and I like Stallone a
lot but I think if Stallone is not playing a punch drunk boxer or a beaten down
cop that's the thing though he's not that good I think Arnold though I buy Arnold
in twins I think he's great in twins I buy him in junior yeah I know I like my
I'm very sensitive. I like Arnold in a comedy. I do. But I'll tell you, Arnold has never had anywhere near his
Copland. And Copland is a perfect movie. And Salon is a big part of it.
Salon is out off the reservation of the movie. I don't know why he doesn't always play that part.
Arnold has never had and will never have his performance where he hits the the heights that's
Salon hits in Copeland. Salon is the better actor. Let's close that with Cole Rothaker I believe it
is. Rothaker at Cole Rothaker. They've done the jungle. They did Los Angeles and they did the
predator planet. Where else would you like to see the new predator movie take place? There are rumors
circulating that it's going to take place like in the desert which I think is a perfect thing
because, again, heat, conflict, Middle East, right?
Sand, desert.
I think that would be great.
I'll tell you two things I wanna see in the new predator film
that I can't believe we haven't seen yet.
I wanna see the predator use those fucking mandibles
on somebody.
Sure.
I wanna see him bite somebody's face off or something.
And I wanna see the final blow to the head predator
in the film.
I wanna see him die by them ripping the predator's skull out.
Okay.
Because the predator always rips everybody's skull out.
That would be fucking awesome and they should do that. Let me ask you an interesting and uncomfortable question real quick before you wrap it up
I don't know why I'm ending on something that could be a bum note. I think it was ebert
But I was reading some reviews of Predator 2 last night and they felt that the new design of the Predator and Predator 2
was racist and that it was meant to conjure up thoughts of like
Los Angeles gang member type situation, right with the dreads and etc
Well, the problem is he has the dreads in the first one too. He does hit him against a goddamn Jamaican drug lord in the first one
That's true. Once you do that
It starts being like and then you start being like I think this Jamaican guys cut in people's heads off
Yeah, I think it's where the problem came really kind of had my radar up and he would always raises like to me
The best most interesting questions about everything which is why I loved him, but um, I
Want you know, I want like chappy?
Maybe Chappy was a rapper alien, essentially, and it was a disgracefully racist movie, in
my opinion.
I thought Chappy was one of the worst movies of my lifetime.
I didn't even see it.
It just looked so bad.
I think Predator's, Predator's, I don't think they were trying for it.
I think it's hard in the right place.
I think we can all agree that Predator is good.
Joe thinks it's the best action sci -fi movie ever made.
I completely disagree.
And I think that we all agree that Predator 2 is worth a look.
Well, I can't listen. Here's the problem. I can't say it's the best sci -fi action movie ever made because I like Star Wars better
Yeah, I like Empire Strikes Back better, but as far as I'm gonna say action movie. Yeah, yes, it's the best
I would put it as the best action movie because I consider it more an action movie than anything else better in the fugitive
Fucking thousand times
He's not being chased by an alien. I mean I could really keep going
I have so many that I just find all right. Listen, I'll be a cluster fest in San Francisco. Yeah, June 3rd and 4th
Performing it's very fun shows actually. I'll be doing some showcases with other comedians
I'll be opening for Bill Burr at one show, which will be fun and I am hosting. This is really cool
trivia at patty's pub
At cluster fest they are gonna have a they're going to have a
You know a fucking what do you call it? I'm a rent. They're gonna have a patty's pub
thing there they're always sunny yeah they're gonna make like a patty's pub on the grounds
of the festival it seems very strange why is that strange it's comedy is it sanctioned
by all yes it's comedy central as long as they have something no that's fx Joe I know
the comedy central syndicate i'm sure comedy central is allowed to be doing this pet all right
let me be excited about a thing i'm doing it seems weird it's like the castanzas for Christ's
What are you doing this fast?
June 3rd and 4th.
Boy, I tell you, I mean, depending on how,
to what extent my life is about to fall apart,
I would go up there for that.
Well, hey, come on up and then question everybody
about the validity and legitimacy of all of it.
You know, I used to write for the show.
Anyway, yeah, I'll be hosting a trivia day or game
at the Patties pub model.
I don't know what you call that, the set.
It's gonna be like a Disney World thing.
They're gonna make a Patties pub.
All right, fine.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
So I'll be there and check out emo hangs
things on federal audio, Kurt Brano, or myself, follow us,
Joe DeRos' comedy on Twitter.
Also, that we'll see you in help on Twitter.
I can't remember the letters, you'll find it.
Joe recently tweeted about it, so find it.
I am on, well, Jesus Christ.
Now I'm gonna start settling with 30 seconds left.
I am all at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
And that's all we really got, folks.
The Facebook page is really awesome and I love checking it. You guys are really funny and
Thanks, we'll see you next time and we'll let you know what's coming up soon