I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's We'll See You In Hell.
We're back again today to deliver to you our review of The Deliverance.
A great title, a unique title.
I've never heard this title before.
Well, you know what, Joe?
This is what I came at you about when I watched the movie a couple of weeks ago.
You can't call a movie Deliverance.
There's already a very successful film called Deliverance.
It was nominated for best picture.
It was one of the biggest hits of its year.
We still talk about it 50 years later.
Martin Short has a great joke that he still does on his current tour where he says,
you know, hanging with Steve Martin is a lot like Deliverance.
It's all fun and games till the banjo comes out.
Which is honestly one of my favorite jokes of all time.
That's a tremendous joke.
I really love it and I don't care that it's 50 years old.
You know, that's something that always bothers me.
It's like, you'll have a million jokes in a project or a show or a movie and
somebody would be like, really?
Like a joke about Kramer from Seinfeld.
Like, what is this?
And that, yeah, you can have references from all, every reference
doesn't have to be current.
We don't have to be making references about Addison Rae.
I like an old classic reference.
I don't even know who Addison Rae is.
She's a TikTok person.
I couldn't pick her out of a lineup, but, you know, it's like the,
Oh, there's, there's a, there's a relevant reference or whatever.
Who said every single comedic reference has to be current?
In fact, I love an old fashioned reference.
I hate all these comedy rules.
Everything has to be grounded.
Everything has to be realistic.
Everything has to be boring.
And now everything has to be dramatic.
Another great joke.
The other night, the only one minute I saw from the Emmy Awards was Eugene
Levy saying, I know a lot of you are wondering if we're going to make jokes
about how the bear should not be nominated for best comedy.
Well, I got to tell you much like the bear itself, we are not going
to be making any jokes tonight.
Very funny.
Did it right to their faces.
They looked very annoyed by it, but they're committing fraud.
You know, in a world where this is like something that people actually give a
fuck about award shows, you're committing fraud.
The bear has, I would say the bear has attempted five jokes in
three years and 30 episodes.
Five.
The guy, Jeremy Allen White, who won best actor has never smiled either
on the show or in real life.
A man that manages to look even more somber than actual Gene Wilder.
Exactly.
He looks miserable.
And I got to tell you the person who I saw really throwing his head back and
laughing at that Eugene Levy joke was the rightful winner of the award, Matt
Barry, who should have won the award 20 years in a row for Toast of London and
all this other shit, but everything just is unfair.
Like letting a show submit in the category they think it should be in is nuts.
Yeah, I know.
It's just because all you're doing is, is, is placing yourself in the category
where you have the best chance.
And I'm sure the people behind this would go, well, yeah, that's
cause we're smart, whatever else.
It's like, but it's not fair.
You're not actually winning best.
Well, then this year the hacks won best comedy and that's just people pushing
back and being like, no, we're going to award a very well -written show that is
funny because that's what this is.
I'm glad they fucking lost.
And I bet next year they nominate themselves for best drama.
It's, yeah, it's similar to like when it'll be like, and the nominees for best
supporting actor go to Tom Cruise in Mission Impossible and you're like, he's
the lead and it's like, oh, I see.
You shoved him to supporting because the lead comp was too thick.
Correct.
So in a technicality, you could say he was a supporting person because he had
one less line than a, than a lead normally has or something like that.
Should not be allowed by the way.
And this is not a shot.
I'm a fan of the man.
Did you ever think we'd see a reality where in 2024 Eugene Levy is
hosting a major award show?
Joe, this life is so insane.
Eugene Levy, when I was growing up, when I was in high school, was the fifth lead
in a variety of kind of low rent comedies.
You know, American pie became a smash, but it was essentially a tit flick.
He was in, you know, the man with Samuel.
He'd said yes to any and everything.
He was the villain, much like Martin Mull, the villain in an
Olsen twins movie at one point.
And then he gets it back.
A hit show.
Hold on.
Don't leave out.
He's the only cast member of the American pie franchise to do all of
the direct to video sequels where we, and we were happy for him.
I was always happy to see the guy and you know, John Candy, we don't
know where he would have wound up.
He might've wound up doing roughly the same thing.
Fun cameos.
Same with Phil Hartman, but yeah, it's just like odd to me that he has now, I
mean, they asked three people publicly.
They asked Mulaney, they asked Kimmel.
I mean, many people turn this down, but like Dan Levy is a, trying to be
a serious actor at this point.
And his dad, Gene Levy was the, what was a wash up from SCTV when I was 19.
It's just crazy.
I mean, I guess it's sort of inspiring that this career can have so
many high highs and low lows.
Like, yeah, it was wild.
Well, it's clearly, it's a result of Schitt's Creek.
It's also tangential to Dan's success.
Maybe Dan Levy said, look, I'll do it if my dad can do it with me.
I don't know, but it would make, if it was, if it was Katherine O 'Hara, it
would have made sense to me because I'm like, yeah, she's like in some big
box office movies currently, she is a constant, you know, Katherine O 'Hara
has always been there and not that Eugene Levy hasn't, but it's just, it's
a little, it's a little different.
Um, great.
I didn't see it.
I heard they did a nice job.
I definitely liked that, that one joke.
Um, well, what do you think, Joe?
Do you think, obviously we have so much content now that shows and movies
are going to be doubling up on titles.
Oh yeah.
But don't you think if you, if your movie hits a certain dollar amount, that
it should lock in that title permanently?
Yeah, I never understood, you know, I'm in the midst of trying to put together
a solo new solo podcast and like every idea I have with a title, I immediately
Google, yeah, is there another show with this name and whatever?
Yeah.
I know taste buds.
There were probably some other things out there, you know, and certainly things
that came along after we did ours, we're doing ours that were called that.
And I just kind of chalked it up to look, this is, this is a common phrase and it
applies to what it is we're doing, but, and it applies to what some other people
are doing, but, but aside from that, it's, um, it's very, it is strange to me.
Tarantino and I agreed a hundred percent.
He talked about, um, I think it was walking on sunshine or something.
Like he talked about, I remember when American psycho used that song and I
like American psycho a lot, but I was like, this is the song from secret of my
success.
Like this was the big song in that movie.
Like you, you can't use this song.
And they did.
And I remember Tarantino talking about that with his soundtracks.
He was saying like, I start with the soundtrack and I write based on that or
whatever.
I don't know if he still does that, but he was saying like, somebody will be
like, you should use this song.
And I was like, you can't use that song.
That song was in platoon, you know, like, and I was like, yeah, I agree.
Like it's like, it's been done and don't, you know, whatever, but it is weird.
This was my next point.
I mean, this is where I wanted the conversation to go.
We're clearly aligned this morning, Joseph, but that's where I wanted to steer.
It was movies using songs that are iconic from other movies.
Uh, you know, so like just take those old records off the ship.
That's one of the most famous scenes of all time.
And it introduced one of our biggest stars to the world and risky business.
Tom Cruise.
You don't really hear that song in anything else, nor should you commercials.
I get it.
Commercials are just trying to sell your product, but movies,
it always does feel weird.
Now I'll point out though, that Tarantino used fucking Mrs.
Robinson in once upon a time in Hollywood.
I have the soundtrack and every time it pops up, I'm like, why would
Tarantino use this?
Well, now, so, so that we are on the same page today, because that brings
me to my next point, which is there's also a difference if you're clearly
making a nod to something now, since that was this once upon a time in
Hollywood, this Hollywood fairy tale or fable, whatever you want to call it.
I took that as he's clearly making a nod to the graduate for
whatever his reason is.
I don't know.
Tarantino also, by the way, for a guy that is such a stickler about
originality, I mean, he uses, he recreates shots from famous movies,
Pulp Fiction, the famous shot of when Ving Rhames crosses the street and
sees Bruce Willis in the car and goes, motherfucker, that shot is psycho.
It's the, it's, it's when the boss walks across and sees Jan Lee in the car and
it starts her paranoia about like, cause she's fleeing town.
And Tarantino quote hates Hitchcock.
That's why I sometimes don't believe what he said.
Yeah.
Well, well, he also says that psycho too is better than psycho one.
I love psycho too, but come on, come on.
Sometimes he's just being inflammatory, but like I own every Tarantino soundtrack.
They are some of my most listened to records because you get such a wide
variety of music.
I liked that.
He includes the dialogue snippets.
It's like having, it's like going on a little journey
that's separate from the movie.
I love his soundtracks.
However, I could point out several of these instances, like he used the
song from cat people in inglorious bastards.
It's literally the song from cat people written by David Bowie, putting out
fire with gasoline.
It's the theme song of cat people.
So what is that Tarantino?
What is your explanation for that?
Does he think that maybe nobody's seen cat people, so it doesn't matter?
I don't know.
It's a walking contradiction.
I didn't like, I thought it worked very well in Django Unchained, but I
remember being disappointed when I saw Jackie Brown and he had a Foxy
Brown song in the movie.
Now I think he probably did that because Pam Greer, Foxy Brown,
rappers named Foxy Brown, he needed a modern song to play in the record
store sequence when Robert Forster goes into the Sam Goody to buy the cassette.
Yeah.
Delphonic.
But I remember being disappointed because I was like, man, this guy always dug up
these weird sort of esoteric pop songs and whatnot, and this sort of genre
music, and now he's just putting in a modern song.
And I remember at the time being disappointed, but then when he did it in
Django with Tupac, it was fucking awesome.
So, you know, maybe I'm wrong.
He also uses bits of other people's score.
I mean, Kill Bill uses a lot of famous snippets from other scores.
And so it's, it's an odd stance for him to take, but well, I definitely feel that
way, like even, you know, when Sopranos famously used, uh, don't stop believing
it's about as memorable as a, as a quote, needle drop can get.
But at the time, I remember being like, see, I thought this song kind of belonged
to monster the Charlize Theron, Christina Ricci movie, it's like the song they
fall in love to now the Sopranos I think kind of wiped it out, but there's a lot
of fucking music in the world, you know, maybe look a little harder.
I, I, I definitely like hearing new shit.
Well, I think at least stuff I haven't heard before in the movie.
It's also, I'm sure that the, the budget, the budget bullshit, you know, a
thing that happens now a lot is, and Homecoming did this, the entire score
for Homecoming, the TV show with Julia Roberts, that was all scores taken
from movies from like the seventies.
Like the Andromeda strain was one of the big ones they use music from.
And I'm like, I don't think, I think that was an interesting thing to do.
I don't think they did that necessarily as an artistic choice.
I think that was, we don't have money or we're not at least going to give you
guys money to score this the way you need to.
So we've got this catalog of our stuff that we've produced already, and we
have the rights to use this music.
So go ahead, have at it.
And that's becoming like the new version of licensed music, you know?
I mean, maybe they probably would have still had to pay for, to use that score.
And I don't know that it would have been that much more, but I could be wrong.
The, when I, I did a cool kids where they were going to a Fleetwood Mac concert
and, uh, wanted to use, go your own way for this montage at the end of the
episode, they wanted like $140 ,000.
Yeah.
Well, as they read the script and they were like, Oh, they need this song.
So we'll charge them that.
I mean, that, that makes it almost impossible to, to score your movie with
anything.
Well, also too, there are different costs, like with sampling and stuff.
There's a, there's a cost.
The highest cost is if you sample the actual record, but then if you do a
recreation, it's a little bit cheaper.
If you do this, it's a little bit cheaper than that.
Bad monkey is a great example.
Bad monkey has a lot of Tom Petty music in it, but it's all covers of Tom Petty.
And they're true to form covers.
They're not like these weird interpretations.
And I'm like, this seems to me, they want it to do Tom Petty.
It was too expensive.
And the Tom Petty estate said, well, if you just do recreations, it will only
cost this much.
And they were like, fuck it.
Just do the recreations, man.
It'll be cheaper.
You know, so I don't know.
Yeah.
TV shows are definitely not getting that music budget they used to.
And it shows, I mean, music can make a huge difference.
Um, your love of a show.
I got a new psycho.
Um, did you see the trailer?
Did I talk about this before the trailer for a Salem's lot?
Finally, I haven't seen the trailer.
You didn't talk about it.
And I'm just about to read the book for the first time.
So I'm pumped.
When does it come out?
Comes out in October on Max.
Uh, it was shelved for so long.
The, I just read an interview with some of the cast and they were like, you
know, we'd given up hope.
We thought this was never going to come out.
Yeah.
There was a lot and has been a lot of speculation that because of the shelving,
because of it being sent over to Max directly and not theatrical, theatrically
released, that it's probably disastrous or terrible.
I got to say, man, they released a scene.
The scene was great.
Yeah.
The trailer is awesome.
The trailer is really spooky.
It's getting us back to scary vampires.
Is it, pick up your mind, decide to walk with me.
I don't know what that is.
What is that?
It's possum kingdom by the toadies, which is a song about a vampire
turning a young woman.
Um, no, that does not play.
Uh, in fact, I don't, I don't think they slow a song down.
I think that might have, I don't remember, but the, I think that was one of the
things in the trailer that struck me was that it just, no, no, definitely not.
Uh, it, um, other trailers.
Good.
It's, it's, it, and it takes place when the book takes place.
They didn't update it.
It's, it takes place in the seventies.
Like it, it looks fucking cool.
And it looks like there are sequences in the trailer that I remember, you know,
I remember the scenes from the Toby Hooper version and in the trailer, it's
not like they're just recreating or copying it, but in the trailer, some of
sequences that I recognize, I was like, wow, that looks like, uh, a scary R
rated version of the Toby Hooper scene that I love so much or whatever.
So I don't know.
It looks like they're going for it.
It looks like they're, they're, they're making a true whatever.
Speaking of which true adaptations, true remakes, the original director
writer of speak, no evil has now publicly slammed the remake.
Oh, so he just was like, because the entire third act in this is a major
spoiler, but at the entire third act of the movie, which I just read what it was,
I don't want to say it is completely different.
The mother rallies, the family and they fight back and they escape and they
kid that's, that's been abducted by the freaky family and blah, blah, blah.
I figured something was amiss when they revealed the, the big tongue
thing in the trailer.
I was like, Oh, okay.
They've done something different with us.
So, yeah, the director was in an interview when he was like, you know,
American audiences just can't handle tragedy.
Everything has to end on a hopeful note.
Everything has to end with like some uplifting, whatever.
And he's like, that's not what my movie was about.
Yeah.
But you know, I guess have at it.
Have fun.
Yeah.
I don't disagree.
I mean, I disagree too.
I think people don't disagree with him.
I mean, Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I mean, I think as people grow more and more depressed, they, they can
handle more depressing content, but maybe I'm wrong.
I do know, you know, and maybe it's why my mom has remained relatively
happy for her entire life, but like it definitely bothers her when a movie
is sad or depressing and she just, it, I just wish I hadn't seen that.
It's just, you know, I get it.
Especially once you hit a certain age, it's probably just like, I
can't take any more sadness in.
Well, look, I'm guilty of it.
I've said on the show, in fact, I think I said it about speaking to
me, but I was like, you know, it's just, it's a hopeless movie.
I'm like, I don't understand what I'm rooting for.
I don't understand what I'm like.
Yeah.
And now I read a very interesting analysis of that original movie, which
I think it probably resonated differently in its country of origin than it did
here, but they, the analysis said the original film is about polite society.
And when you adhere to the standards set by polite society,
it can destroy you, which is why at the end, the family is not fighting back.
And they're being, they're allowing themselves to be stoned to death
because it's just, it's a, it's a, it's a commentary on polite society.
Yeah.
And I was like, ah, it's interesting.
I never thought of it that way.
So, um, you know, sometimes a movie is just a commentary.
It's not about getting behind the character and rooting
for the good fight or whatever.
So I don't know.
That made me look at it a little differently, but you know, when we
did devil's bath, I said this, I was like, I mean, it was a well -made movie,
but I don't understand what I'm supposed to be taking away from this.
Right.
Like, yeah, it was horrible.
It's a horrible period of time.
Yeah.
I always talk with a coworker of mine about this, but it's like, like that's
a really interesting take on the movie that it's about, you can just sort
of polite your way into, you know, abandoning yourself and, and, and death,
you know, but I wonder, like, there's so many movies where the director maybe
has some, some intent in mind, but no one ever gets it.
And there's also so many movies where a critic will be like, this movie is
clearly a searing indictment of late stage capitalism.
And I'm like, no, I know that nobody involved with this movie intended that.
Like they'll just give them credit for things.
It's interesting.
But, and of course a movie should be open to interpretation as should a piece
of music or anything else, but I do think sometimes critics are just absolutely
making shit up and telling you that's what the movie's about.
Yeah.
It was kind of like when I was talking about that, that Wolfman thing, the
Lon Chaney Jr one, where the, the, the critic or whoever was saying, now the
more astute viewer has realized that the original Wolfman is a metaphor for
trans and I'm like, well, it's, I see how you could make that parallel, but
I highly doubt that that's what the motivation was at that time in this
society and gay sure puberty.
Sure.
You know, trans was not as a, you know, a common discussion.
Yeah.
So sometimes I think it's spot on.
Sometimes I think it's sort of retroactively put, put into, to it, you
know, and it, it's kind of like the, the, the dark side of the moon,
wizard of Oz thing.
It's like, yeah, yeah, it works and it does make sense and it is very
interesting, but I don't think that it was done on purpose.
I don't think for two seconds, Pink Floyd did that secretly years later, we could
all sort of discover it.
I think it's just one of those things that interestingly has developed and,
and, and aged well, or, or, or become, it's taken on a new application with
age, which is great.
That's good art.
Good art can be timeless in its own way, even meaning it meant this at this time
and it means this now, because that's how broad and, and, and, and comprehensive
the commentary in and of itself was.
So, you know, like, like a face in the crowd, the, the excellent, uh,
Elia Kazan movie, you know, now is basically seen as the Trump story,
you know, like, but the movie was made in the 1950s.
So of course it wasn't, it's a brilliant movie about that type of person, that
type of Huckster who can seduce a nation, you know, but, um, yeah, that's
kind of what I love about movies.
That's what I was talking about on the solo corner about heat is how this was
an awesome heist movie when I was 15 and now it's a very somber movie about
marriage and relationships and divorce.
Now that I'm 43, you know, like I, I love that about movies actually.
Yeah, but I do think sometimes people are given credit for things they did not
intend and, and, you know, critics have to write about something.
I get that too.
A lot of times you're trying to discern meaning from something and you make
shit up, but.
Well, also too, a sharp commentary again, will be encompassing on either side, on
either side of the timeline from, you know, within the, you know, in the point
that it's created and exists initially, a good, if it's a good commentary, it'll
encompass the past and it'll eventually encompass the future, but it's not a
prediction, you know, like, yeah, I just read a great interview with Rakim the
rapper and they were like, you predicted 9 -11 in your song, Casualties of War,
uh, in 1993.
And it's like, I don't think he, he's cause the song's about a soldier coming
back from Iraq and having PTSD and saying like, there's a line in it about like
being in New York and looking up, looking up to the sky and wondering when the
attack is going to happen.
And I'm like, right.
Well, he's, he's making a comment.
He's, he lives in New York and he's talking from the perspective of a
soldier coming back to New York and having PTSD and like everything, you
know, he's, he's, he's in fear.
I don't think that's the same thing as a prediction.
Right.
It's just a great commentary that happens to again, be applicable as it, as
it grows.
So the one that about the Simpsons all the time, I mean, every couple of
months, there's a new, can you believe the Simpsons predicted this way back
and it's like, no, they just have 5 ,000 episodes and they've always been a
brilliant ahead of their time satire.
So sometimes they're going to get it right, but like, no, they didn't predict
Kamala Harris or whatever else, you know,
the one that bothers me, and this isn't about predictions, it's just about
people reading into it.
The analysis of the shining has always irked me, you know, there's that
movie room, two, two, three, whatever the hell it's called.
I did not like that at all.
Well, it's, it's, there's 18 fucking people all talking about the
brilliance of Kubrick and, and he did this and he did that.
And this can sitting in the kitchen is clearly indicative of what, and it just
gets to a point, it's like, guys, yeah, we could read into any, all of, this is
very easy to do, this is very, this is why there are hundreds of people on
YouTube making their living off of Will Smith slapping Chris Rock was staged
because Will Smith is heavily involved with, with, with Pfizer and Pfizer
needed a boost in their exposure to push their vaccine for COVID.
So they had Will Smith go up and slap him because that brought, it's like,
guys, Jesus Christ, let's all take a fucking breath here.
You know, you stare at something long enough, you're going to see a lot of
things within it.
So, you know, I think the shiny is a brilliant movie.
I think Kubrick's a brilliant director.
I think he probably did do a lot of very cool stuff that was meant to be a
reference or, or a commentary or little details that were supposed to resonate
with you on a subconscious level.
I do not think it has the depths that, that people have, have claimed it has
in, in, in, in the later years, but yeah, you know, I don't know.
Uh, let's get to that movie corn.
I would like to start if I may with a film I rewatched because it came out on
4k, having completely skipped Blu ray altogether, a Martin Scorsese movie that
was never released on Blu ray, um, bringing out the dead starring Nicholas cage.
This movie came out in 1999, often considered one of the best film years of
all time.
I read a book about 1999.
It's a, it's a really great book.
And there's a lot of truth to how great that movie year was.
It's the year I graduated high school.
There was all kinds of great shit coming out, but bringing out the dead kind of
doesn't get mentioned as one of them.
It kind of doesn't get mentioned as even a notable film in the
Scorsese filmography.
No.
And as much as I enjoy it, I kind of see why it's a very detached, cold movie.
Uh, it's written by Paul Schrader.
It's it's Schrader and Scorsese reunited and dealing with loners late at
night in New York.
Um, so yeah, you kind of can't help but compare it to taxi driver.
It's not on that level.
It's weirdly sort of a dark comedy about a very difficult job being a EMT,
being an ambulance worker.
Nicholas cage is excellent in it.
He really is.
He always is kind of, um, he's was married to Patricia Arquette at the time.
She plays, they would divorce a couple of years later.
She plays a woman whose father passes away.
Nicholas cage is there to resuscitate him, try to help him and kind of falls for
her, sees our cat as sort of his redemption.
And that's kind of the problem.
Patty Arquette, I like a lot.
I call her Patty sometimes she's not great in this.
Uh, weirdly, John Goodman's not great in this.
The movie almost has a Scrooge approach of pairing, partnering Nicholas cage
with three, you know, increasingly nuts partners.
You got John Goodman.
It's one of the only Goodman performances I've seen where he's not quite on the
mark, which is odd to me, especially because him and cage were amazing together
in raising Arizona.
Then you have, uh, Tom Sizemore, who's excellent, come in as the, you
know, truly bat shit guy.
He has a very funny scene where Nicholas cage just calmly strolls past him while
he's beating an ambulance with a baseball bat, uh, which was in the trailer.
And then the third partner that he has is Ving Rhames, who is awesome.
Ving Rhames is not used enough as a comedy actor.
He should have won the Oscar for baby boy.
I think he is so funny and great in John Singleton's baby boy.
And I love him in this too.
He's got the thing where he does the big sort of preacher thing.
Um, basically trying, he's, you know, he's basically trying to preach his way
into bringing somebody back to life.
Um, there's laughs.
I like this tone.
I like the style.
It's dark comedy.
That score says he's kind of specialty.
Um, but this is a movie that just kind of keeps me outside the glass.
It has since the first time I saw it, I like it.
The 4k looks great.
Um, it's, it's middle of the road.
Score says he for me would have been, would be anybody else's masterwork.
But when you hold it up against Scorsese, it falls somewhere in the middle to me.
Yeah.
That was the sort of dip period with Scorsese.
Yes.
I was kind of like, Oh, does he not have it anymore?
This movie was okay.
This was pretty good.
And then he came back swinging hard.
Yeah.
Um, well, I, uh, I should, I'll, I won't bury the lead.
The new Frasier has begun season two.
Uh, the first two episodes are out as of this recording.
Um, I watched them, uh, it's, it's certainly an improvement from last season.
Um, it suffers, it's much more apparent to me this time around.
It's not the writing.
The writing is there.
I think I just think the supporting cast is not as capable.
And I don't think that that's their fault.
I don't think they're bad.
I just think there was an art form to sitcom acting that is not really a thing anymore.
Yeah, that's very true.
There, you know, a lot of sitcom actors, there's a reason why a lot of sitcom
actors from the eighties and nineties became big movie stars.
And there's a reason why a lot of sitcom actors from the eighties
and nineties were, were stage trained.
And they, these people knew how to bring this material to life and to find a lot
in seemingly not much on the page.
Um, and unfortunately the supporting cast just is not, they don't nail, they
just don't nail and you can kind of start to see they're giving them less to do.
At least in, to me in these first two episodes, there's a much greater focus
on Kelsey Grammer and the English guy who's great.
I forget his name.
Um,
the guy with the stroke, the guy that was in the original Frasier?
No, you're thinking of the guy that played Gil who eventually comes back in
this season, but not, not yet.
I don't think, no, not, maybe I didn't finish the second episode.
I thought I did anyway.
Um, but the first episode, I will say Kelsey Grammer brings his A game and
he has, I would say three or four like hackle out loud moments as Frasier,
like where he, I was like, this is this, he, this is the old stuff right here.
This is great.
Yeah.
I hope they go further down that road with him.
My fear is, is that they keep adding people to this cast and they just keep,
it's, it seems like it's getting bigger and bigger and it doesn't need to get
bigger and bigger.
It needs to get smaller.
It needs to focus on Frasier and just Frasier.
Um, but I think they're trying to find those counterparts to, to the great
cast, you know, apparently Ross is back this season, like full supporting character.
Now she's not just coming in for cameos.
Um, they wrote into the story that her daughter is going to college in like
Rhode Island or something, so she's now in that Boston area a lot.
Um, I know that he goes back to Seattle at some point this season and does the
radio show, which is why you see Bulldog again and Gill.
Yeah.
Um, you know, I'm sure, I'm sure Lilith will be back and they said a couple
cheers characters are going to show up.
So they're doing, they're just, they're adding a lot, but I don't know.
I, I have hope it's, it's just good enough that I'm like, okay,
I'm going to stick with this.
Hopefully it gets better, but I am very grateful to have, you know, it's kind
of like, even when star wars sucks, you get a couple of good lightsaber fights.
You're like, all right, I had fun watching that, I guess, you know, so, um,
we'll see what happens, but, but, but it has begun and I'm happy.
It is weird though.
The first episode or sorry, the second episode is Valentine's day.
Okay.
It's weird, right?
It's weird.
I mean, well, that's what we were talking about with the difference
between cable and streaming.
I mean, when you're, when you're working on a 22 episode show and Halloween
comes up, you're like, oh great.
Now we don't have to come up, you'd have to still come up with a story, but
you're like, we know it's going to be a Halloween episode.
There's definitely no reason to do that in the world of streaming.
It's also like you miss out on Christmas apps and stuff like that, which I was
always my favorite part of a sitcom.
Well, they did the finale of season one of the Frasier reboot was a Christmas
episode and it landed right around Christmas.
So it made sense.
Yeah.
I'm like, why would you do a Valentine's day episode when
you're dropping in September?
There's no way they didn't know.
Probably not.
Yeah.
I don't know.
But it's odd.
Anyway, we'll see what happens.
Uh, I rewatched for the first time in ages to the point that I basically
was a fresh watch for me, uh, naked.
Directed by Mike Lee.
I really love the movies of Mike Lee.
He comes about them in a very unorthodox way that has, you know, has become used
definitely by other filmmakers like David O Russell and Appatao and people like
that, but, um, basically he comes up with characters, scenarios, uh,
Fleshes them out with the actors, you know, they bring their own life experiences,
but he's got a story he wants to tell.
Curb also does this obviously, and he creates these two hour movies
like from the ground up, you know, he doesn't sit down with a script.
And so you're left with, you know, 30, 40 years worth of really excellent, rich,
deep character studies that maybe don't have any plots.
Sometimes they, you know, they kind of are just basically watching a
person from point A to point B.
Sometimes there's no change in that person at all.
Sometimes there's a tiny change.
I love movies like this about Schmidt, uh, is in my top 10.
And it's about a guy who basically goes not from A to B, but from A to like
point one.
And it makes me weep that this guy had made this tiny change in his life.
I really love stories like that.
That is what, uh, a lot of Mike Lee's stuff is about.
One of my favorites of his is happy go lucky, which is he it's,
they're always tiny topics.
Happy go lucky is a movie about how difficult it is to just make the
decision to be happy.
And it's about a woman who is, has done that.
And like the problems she faces in just trying to be a happy person.
So they're small stories.
Naked is one of his darkest, uh, it's super British.
It's all this pulp I'm listening to.
I'm getting back into this period of like nineties British shit.
I just love it.
I like that vibe, that world.
And naked is just a real scummy movie.
It's David Thulis.
He's incredible in this movie.
It's often called one of the great performances ever.
Um, I like Thulis a lot.
I think he's great.
This is probably his best work and he just plays a monster.
He plays a guy who is so angry at everything and just is
always spouting and ranting.
And he basically ruins the life of everyone he encounters.
The movie opens, uh, in a back alley.
The camera is like saving private Ryan style flying down this alley.
You don't even know what's going on.
And then finally it lands on David Thulis having very rough sex
with this woman in an alley.
And she's into it.
This is the first thing we see in the movie.
She's into it for 10 seconds, kind of.
And then she starts going, stop, you're hurting me.
Get off of me.
What's wrong with you?
Thulis stops assaulting her after too much time.
Uh, he runs away, steals a woman's car and just drives out of town
to get away from this situation.
He lands at an ex -girlfriend's house.
He's like, I got nowhere to go.
Can I hang out with you?
So it's very hard after that opening one minute to be on
this character's side at all.
Later on in the movie, he brings in a landlord character
who's like Thulis, but worse.
He's rich, he's more monstrous and he commits actual rape on screen
in a couple of occasions.
And that's where the movie gets really weird because it's like they
added this character to make you like Thulis more it's like, yeah, he
does a lot of horrible things, but at least he's not this guy.
Um, it's dark as hell.
It's super depressing.
It's that's a great movie, you know, it's, it's definitely not
one that tells you what to think or what to feel.
It's definitely one that stretches your ability to like an unlikable character.
And it's just a fascinating picture.
Like a lot of Mike Lee's stuff.
I know they had most of his movies on Criterion collection when our criteria
and channel, when I used to be a member, I don't know if they still do, but
you can still find a lot of his stuff.
Joe.
That's what they do in a Henry portrait of a serial killer.
Right.
Henry's this terrible guy.
And then he links up with a worst guy.
Hey,
yeah.
So you find yourself by the end being like, Oh, I hope Henry survives this.
Like as he's dragging a woman by her hair across the floor or whatever.
Um, I watched a speaking of great sitcom actors.
Uh, I watched a cartoon anthology, well, not anthology, it's a series, but
it was on adult swim.
It's called over the garden wall.
Uh, saw it on a list of recommended, great fall viewing, uh, on YouTube.
Uh, it's a fun, really fun show.
Really took me back to the kind of thing that I loved as a kid.
If I had seen this when I was like eight, I would have, it
would have defined my life.
Um, it's about two brothers.
The lead brothers, the older brothers played by Elijah wood or voiced by Elijah
would the younger brothers voiced by a guy named Colin Dean.
Um, they're lost in this enchanted wood.
They don't know quite how they got there.
They, they need to get home.
And in every episode, they encounter another group of characters in an odd
situation in this forest, uh, and the situations are often dark and creepy
and sinister while also having a bit of a humorous tone, uh, but Christopher
Lloyd plays a woodsman who initially seems like a threat and turns out to be
an ally, uh, the first for Lloyd is always a threat that turns out to be
an ally, isn't it?
Yeah.
Uh, John Cleese pops up in a role or two.
Uh, BB Newworth is in it.
Um, the very funny Fred Stoller plays a horse named Fred, the horse,
Thomas Lennon, um, and Tim Curry.
Oh, nice.
Tim Curry post.
That is a stacked fucking cast.
These are all voices.
Yeah.
Also to Chris Isaac, Shirley Jones.
There's a lot of people in this thing, but, um, Tim Curry post stroke, which
it's great to see that he's working again.
This is an older show, but I mean, it was, you know, it's not that old, but
I think Tim Curry was my favorite character.
He plays a woman named Auntie Whispers who seems to have, seems to be, I don't
know if you'd say kidnapped, but she's, he, she's got a niece and it's, and it
seems like the niece is being held captive, um, and that the, at the, that
the aunt has sinister motives, but then it's revealed that the thing the aunt
is claiming to protect her, her niece from is her niece herself, who is a
monster and, and, uh, that's why the aunt is not letting the niece leave
the house or anything.
It's stories like that.
It's really interesting.
It's really fun.
And they just announced that they're going to do a claymation special.
Uh, I guess they're doing it with the Wallace and Gromit team.
So it's a fun watch.
Is it a comedy?
It's, it's funny.
It's yeah, there's some very funny stuff in it.
Um, but it's also creepy.
It's, it's, you know, it's a kid's cartoon.
It really walks that great line that like labyrinth walks where it's funny and
it's quirky and it's silly, but it's also very dark and very spooky.
Yeah.
So, um, I'd check it out.
I think it, you know, and it's, it's, I think it's 10 episodes and they're each
like 10 minutes long or something.
So I, I enjoyed it and it was perfect to get you in the mood for becoming,
uh, events of Halloween and the fall and all that stuff.
Love it.
Um, I.
Sore.
Let me get my last one here.
What did I just watch?
Think, Pat, think, uh, slap shot.
Slap shot, uh, is one of my dad's favorite movies and that can go either way.
I mean, if he was obsessed with something when I was a kid, a lot of times that
led to me just blindly, passionately loving it like blues brothers.
Um, but sometimes we just didn't quite see eye to eye slap shot.
I liked as a kid, I think I liked that it was so profane and that my dad
was allowing me to watch it, watching it.
Hey, it doesn't seem near as profane.
I mean, this is considered like one of the most cussing movies ever.
You read the reviews at the time, including a review from Rex Reed, Joe,
still bitching about the movie that came out in 1977.
Um, but slap shot took a lot of heat when it came out as being gross,
uh, too violent, too misogynistic, too much cussing.
And I, it really just goes to show, uh, how far society has fallen that nothing
in this movie would even raise an eyebrow anymore.
It basically plays like a little more, uh, R rated bad news bears
or something of that nature.
But slap shot's fun.
You know, I wish there was more like hard laughs in it.
I think Paul Newman is so excellent in this movie.
I was reading some shit and like Pauline Cale said it was the best he's ever been.
And he really is.
He's great, but I don't know.
I, in a, in a world where we have Kenny powers, you know, that it's just
hard to really get behind something like this because the, the movie's point
was to shock and it's lost all of that power, I think.
Um, so what you're left with is basically a pretty good sports movie
where it just kind of feels dated.
I mean, Jesus, the amount of gay jokes in this thing is astounding.
It really is astounding.
And the amount of times you hear that F slur, I forgot how much that was
like a part of the vernacular.
You know, you could hear that in a PG movie, but, um, let me find
what Rex Reed says here.
Gene Siskel, interestingly gave it two and a half stars then said, um,
he saw it again two weeks later, and then he knew it was a terrific film.
I appreciate when critics do that.
Ebert did that on a couple of occasions as well.
It's like who amongst us hasn't been in a bad mood and hated a good movie,
you know, to think a critic would never have that happen is kind of dumb, but,
um, Rex Reed's review, I don't recall it being as funny as his current ones,
but it says, uh, it's violent, bloody, and thoroughly revolting.
Revolting like the man likes, he's never liked anything to my knowledge.
Um, but if you want to see slap shot, it is considered like a sports classic.
It is considered a cult movie.
Um, goon with Sean Williams.
Scott has also become a cult movie.
That's kind of like the grandson of slap shot.
I'm just, I never care much about these, these sports pictures outside
of the major league, bad news bears and a few others.
They just never get me as much as they might get your average person
because I don't give a fuck.
Uh, it's, it's impossible for me to care about hockey.
So, but good movie, good Paul Newman performance, just a little overrated.
I have a dream remake.
I want to do a bad news bears, not the Billy Bob Thorne one.
No, I want to do another.
I like that one.
I really like it too.
For, for what it was, it really stuck to the original stuff.
Uh, you know, when Billy Bob is leading the kids at the pizza place in a sing
along of cocaine by Eric Clapton, that is truly hilarious to me.
I always want to do a remake with Mike Epps as the coach.
Yeah.
Instead of a booze hound, he smokes way too much weed, uh, and, and
ice cube as the, the other coach.
I was like, I love those two together.
I think that'd be awesome.
Um, you know, but, uh, I, I saw Slapshot in college.
I didn't like it because I was misinformed that it was the
Zucker brothers and it wasn't.
Um, but somebody said to me, if you, you know, if you like this naked gun
and whatever, you're going to love Slapshot.
So I watched it thinking it was going to be like airplane, except hockey.
Did they think it was baseball?
No, I don't know.
I just, my friends in college were hockey players and they loved Slapshot.
They were on the hockey team.
So, I mean, I get that.
I just don't, it's such a different style of comedy.
I would say there's almost nothing like that in the movie.
I think they were just wrong.
I think they just thought it was the Zucker brothers.
Um, you know, we all drank quite a bit, uh, so so I, um, I did not
like it because I went in thinking it was going to be something different.
But I, I, I want, want to revisit Slapshot.
It was written by Nancy Dowd, who she read about her, man.
She's got an awesome story and she, she basically rewrote for no credit,
some amazing fucking movies in the seventies and eighties, including
ordinary people, ordinary people, straight time, North Dallas, 40
straight time is an eight plus and then, and then she's the
thing she credited for all of them, except for Slapshot.
Yeah.
She has a pseudonym of a male name, probably because she
wanted to get the script bought.
She, she fully admits to that.
She's like, and they, they accused Slapshot of being misogynistic and
woman hating, and she's like, no, I, I'm a feminist.
I wrote it.
Yeah.
It's interesting.
I mean, what a, what a, what a cool career she had.
Um, interesting lady.
Um, I'm ready to move on.
Let's do it.
But did I ever tell you, it's a, it's a 32nd story, but did I ever tell
you my Mike Epps, Uncle Buck story?
You have, but I don't recall.
Please tell me, uh, to, to, to friends of mine that I've worked with a
couple of times, they ran the, uh, CBS multicam version of Uncle Buck.
There was one with Kevin Meany, which I remember watching.
Kevin Meany's was, was a multicam.
Epps' wasn't a multicam.
It was a single cam, but yeah.
But it didn't, it wasn't, it didn't, was not good.
No adaptation of Uncle Buck has ever been good.
Yeah.
You're missing the key element, John Candy, but, um, my, this, this
is one of my favorite stories.
It's, uh, so Mike Epps, who I, as you described, enjoyed the weed.
Uh, they said was not good with memorization at all.
He just couldn't get two words in a row.
And they were like, well, this is the pilot, man.
I mean, we're trying to get this thing picked up.
I mean, what do you want to do?
And he's like, I, I'm just an improv guy.
You got to just let me go.
And they're like, yeah, there's not a lot of that happening on network TV.
You know, like we can't just say, like, have fun out there.
You know, like we really, he's like, just let me, let me do one take where
I just like improv and if it's not better than what you guys have, super
insulting by the way, but like, just let me do it and they're like,
okay, we'll do one take.
They start it and the, his wife or the kid or whatever says the line to him.
And he responds.
He goes, man, see, this is why I didn't want to fucking come to St.
Louis and they go cut.
You can't say fuck on CBS.
And the show is set in Chicago.
I love that.
I just thought that was great.
Incredible.
So he goes, yeah, you know what?
I'll just do what's written.
I'll, I'll do the script.
They liked him by the way.
They said he wasn't an asshole.
He just like, couldn't do it.
Um, go ahead.
Let's talk the deliverance.
So the deliverance is a, uh, 20, 24 film.
Netflix.
Yeah.
Netflix original directed by Lee Daniels.
Um, did precious.
Remember when for, he did precious.
And then the next movie was called Lee Daniels is the butler.
Like he immediately got that credit.
Wait, he didn't do precious.
Did he?
Yeah, he did.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
He did precious.
Then the paper boy.
Yeah.
Kidman and Efron.
Then the, yeah, the, I didn't realize he did precious.
All right.
Uh, Lee Daniels is a great director.
Um, he doesn't have a ton of great movies, but he's a great director.
He's not a boring director.
And I will always take, uh, or most of the time, take a director who is like
incapable of being boring over the greats, you know, like he's a guy who
knows how to give you entertainment, you know, fun, crazy, the Glenn Close
character is a perfect example in this movie.
I mean, she's just there for pure entertainment.
Basically.
It's a great performance.
So this is based on, uh, the Jackson family of, of Indiana, who this
you know, these were, this was a real family.
They moved into a house and they claim they experienced a strange and demonic
occurrences, uh, that eventually convinced them, uh, and the community
that the house is a gateway to hell.
There's a documentary about this called demon house where they, the guy that
made the documentary bought the house sight unseen so he could go in and make
a documentary about this house.
He does interview, uh, locals about that guy's wife.
He might be single.
Why'd you buy the house?
Well, it's haunted.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Um, the, uh, he does interview locals in the doc who say like, I would not go in
that house and whatever would have you.
Yeah.
There was been a lot of criticism of the actual events that it was all staged
and coached and it was just an excuse for the mom to, you know, combat the
fact that she wasn't sending her kids to school and some other things or whatever.
I don't know that much about all that, but that that's what this movie was based on.
It's very much like the conjuring or something where it's a story that some
people seem to very much believe and other people say, Oh, come on, it's nonsense.
Um, but you've got, uh, a single mother named, uh, Ebony Jackson, who's played
by Andra day, who's predominantly a musician, uh, and she's got her son, her
son, two sons and one daughter.
Yep.
You learn that they've just moved into this house.
You learn that they're having money issues.
You learn that the father, it takes place in 2011.
He's overseas in Iraq.
They don't know when he's coming home, but you get the impression they're
having problems and they're potentially separated.
Uh, and then her mother is played by Glenn Close, who obviously is white.
Um, but it's a black family.
So you are curious, um, if, if these are actually her children and
grandchildren or, or what, which they do address later in the movie, uh, there's
a lot of very heated scenes between the daughter and the mother about that
hint at how abusive or inappropriate the mother was when they, when she was
raising her, the mother now has found Jesus and has become very religious.
And the daughter is basically like, fuck you.
You think, cause you go to church now, it makes you a good person.
How dare you try to tell me how to run my home?
They do not, they unapologetically portray the mother's foibles in this
thing, which I loved, they show that she's an alcoholic and that she still
indulges and won't stop drinking.
You see that she's, you know, mildly or, or, or maybe not mildly, uh, abusive to
the kids in ways like she will hit the kids, you know, and there's the scene
right in the beginning where she smacks the kid at dinner.
For, for, I forget what he's doing and he's, his lip starts bleeding and
you're like, Jesus, man, they're, they're going right at this.
I found the whole dynamic between, uh, uh, the Glenn Close character and
the, the, the family to be fascinating.
Monique is in this.
She's great.
She plays a child services officer who's coming.
Yeah.
I read she took over for Octavia Spencer with like a couple of days of prep time,
but she is really good.
She's, she's awesome in this.
I was, I was laughing the first time Monique comes into this where she like
pulls up in the car, she's like, she's like Ebony Jackson, I got you now.
Let's see what excuse you come up with this week.
And she's putting on her lipstick and she puts on those sunglasses
and she comes in like peacocking.
Yeah.
I was like, this is great, man.
She's, this is a great character.
Um, I mean, I'm completely with you just at this moment.
I'll pop in to join you.
Join me.
Can you still hear me?
Yeah.
I can still hear Pat, his headphones around, but yeah, uh, hold on.
Your mic went out.
Okay.
Well, then keep talking.
I'm going to replace this real quick.
Keep talking.
So this is so, so for all of you, this is all going to stay in the podcast.
So you can know what's happening.
This is, uh, I'd say every third recording occurrence where Pat realizes
halfway through the recording that he's forgotten to charge his Bluetooth
headphones, uh, has to unplug the headphones while talking, not forgotten
to charge, uh, it's a battery headphone system, a battery headphone system.
He can't wear earbuds.
He says, because they hurt his ears or something.
They fall out.
Um, so that's why he sounds echoey now because his mic is also gone out.
And, uh, you're hearing him through the laptop microphone.
Uh, he is using the beats by Dre, uh, Bobby Brown style headphones with
the little Mike thing that comes down.
Like it's like he's doing NFL Sunday football commentary.
These are the executives, the executives.
Okay.
Here we go.
The headphones are getting plugged back in.
Didn't even notice.
There you go.
Didn't even notice that I was gone.
Now, what did you want to say?
I will.
I'm going to do a rehearsal this weekend with a different kind of headphones.
But, um, what I wanted to say is that for the first hour of this movie, I was
fucking loving it because of every, just everything you're describing great, great
characters, uh, super realistic, bringing in the Glenn Close character.
It's a character like we haven't seen before really.
And if this had, maybe it's based on, on the real life story, uh, their relationship.
I don't know, but it's like, if the mom had been say Octavia Spencer, then this
just would not have been as compelling and interesting a movie.
I love that he just makes interesting choices in his casting, in his characters.
Um, Glenn Close is awesome in this.
She got so much shit for that hillbilly elegy performance, which was not her fault.
It sucked and Ron Howard should have directed her better, but this is kind
of a similarly campy and over the top performance.
It's just awesome.
It works so well.
Their fights have so much more spice and heat and energy to them because it's
real shit.
You were abusive to me as a kid.
Now I'm abusive to my kids.
I can't forgive you.
It's not that easy.
And the white and black stuff is great.
Great drama.
The movie eventually goes off the rails a little bit, but when this guy is just
dealing with people, he's a really, really strong director.
It's trying to be a genre filmmaker.
That's not going to work for him.
It's why you don't see Tyler Perry doing these kinds of movies either.
It's just not going to be his strong suit.
Yeah.
But yeah, let's talk about the horror elements.
Well, yeah.
And Glenn Close, by the way, she, she's a woman suffering from cancer, but, and
they show at one point, there's a reveal where she takes her wig off and she's
bald, but she's still like, dresses it up to the nines.
Like when she goes in to get chemo, they show her getting all dolled up for her
chemo thing.
Omar Epps plays the guy administering the chemo to her.
She didn't even recognize him, but yeah, great to see him.
She's got her cleavage out.
You can see her red lace bra.
She basically sets a date to fuck him while she's getting the chemo.
All the other women are looking at her like, look at this nasty bitch with
her tits out.
Like, yeah, it's really, it's really funny.
It's really quite incredible.
And as Pat stated, the, the dynamic between Andrew Day and Glenn Close, I
mean, these fights, there's a line where Andrew Day is like, say it to me again.
I've knocked a bitch's teeth out for less.
Yeah.
You know, like it's, it's, it's pretty wild.
It's, it's fun.
Um, fun is probably the wrong word.
It's a terribly dysfunctional dynamic, but it's very interesting to watch.
I was riveted by the family and then, and it's real, you know, it's like
you're saying to like, she's got a big drinking problem, a big temper problem.
And throughout the movie, she just keeps on fucking drinking.
You rarely see that.
You might see people trying to go straight, but like in a very weak moment,
they have a drink or something, but this woman's just pounding them back
throughout and everyone is telling her you have a big problem.
It's, it's great in that way.
It's like it, it meets people where they are and doesn't create fake character.
Right.
So then the, the, the, the demonic stuff starts happening.
The children start acting odd.
Uh, there's a great sequence when, um, they show all three kids acting out
in different ways in school, the oldest son is in class and the teacher is
talking about the AIDS epidemic and how horribly it's affecting the black
community and the kid is laughing hysterically as the teacher's talking.
That's intercut with the young son saying he has to go to the bathroom
and then in the middle of the classroom, pulling down his pants and
shitting on the floor and then throwing his shit in the teacher's face.
They take the kids to, to a hospital to see what's going on.
The doctor says the kids are fine.
We, you know, classic thing in a possession movie.
There we don't see anything wrong.
The mother's like, something is definitely wrong.
My son ate his own shit today, which they don't show that part,
but you're like, wow, okay.
So at this moment you're like, it's a possession movie.
They're kind of going through the possession notes that you
see in every movie like this, but they're going for it.
This is pretty intense.
Um, and that's where the, and then after that is where the
problems start and my problems were two things.
The first is every single demon, uh, uh, uh, uh, you know, detail,
whatever thing they do after this device, whatever, it's all just so,
it's just all been done so many times, so many times, the voice the kid
talks with when he's possessed is, sounds ridiculous.
The we are kind of at a saturation point with these movies.
It's like vampires or it's like zombies, you know, we're, we're in
need of some sort of change up.
Yeah.
Like something as simple as making zombies fast changes the whole game,
but now those are cliches, like keep, keep changing shit up.
These possession movies are all feeling like exactly the same thing.
The makeup they put on the kid is, it looks dumb.
It just doesn't look good.
Uh, Glenn Close's character dies midway through the film, but later
when the kid is possessed, he takes the form of Glenn Close.
So there's a Glenn Close possession sequence.
They've got her.
She says, and I'm sure you've seen this meme folks.
I can smell your nappy pussy.
Yes.
She says, you've ever wanted to see Glenn Close say that line while
possessed and looking like Voldemort.
This is the movie for you.
Well, and that's the thing.
They give Glenn Close like black eyes and pointy teeth, and it looks
like a Gollum costume or something.
It looks, it just looks kind of silly.
Um, but anyway, this woman approaches Andrew Day and says, I need to
talk to you of that house.
It's evil, whatever.
She tells the story of the people that lived there before you.
The father murdered the entire family.
So now you're into like a kind of Amityville situation.
Andrew Day at this point in the movie, who's at the end of her rope and needs
help, screams at the woman and says, you're fucking crazy, leave me alone.
And you're like, this is not the point in the movie where this woman would do that.
This is the point in the movie where the woman would be saying,
thank you, please help me.
Yeah.
And then like one scene later, she's willing to accept the woman's help.
It, there's no transition.
It's a really bad jump.
And the jump happens because the son is fully possessed and she needs to, as
they say, conduct a deliverance.
It's not an exorcism.
It's different.
Um, it's, it's all it, it, it, the movie almost just jumps into this.
I almost get the feeling that Lee Daniels wanted this to be presented as
a family drama that all of a sudden took a wild turn.
And nothing at all can be, you know, kept secret anymore with a
movie's twist or plot.
Everything has to be shown in the trailer, but that's how hard the turn is.
It's very odd.
Um, it's just, it's just, they just, they, and, and, and when it does, and this
is, this is what I wanted to talk about.
My friend Chrissy and I were talking and she's, she's not a big fan of the
church and I told her was about the, when the first Omen came out, I said,
the first Omen's really good.
She likes horror movies.
I said, you should see it.
She goes, Hey, I'm not interested.
I said, why?
She goes, I don't like any, you know, any of the devil movies.
I'm not into them.
And I said, why?
They're some of the best horror movies.
And she said, because there's always this thing that makes the church,
church heroic in them.
And I don't think the church is heroic.
I think it's bullshit.
I was like, well, that's fair, but there are plenty that don't, but man, does
this one ever like it is a love letter to Jesus, which fine, you have every
right to make a movie about that.
But the entire thing, and as much as I was mad at this, this, that shitty
exorcist that just came out that they had to make it about five religions
instead of one, yeah, this went so hard in the other direction where by the end
of the movie, Andra Day has to accept Jesus in order to defeat the demon.
And she does it like at the 11th hour and it's the final push and all that stuff.
It's just not a believable turn.
It's just not a moment where you believe this woman suddenly has found faith and
faith strong enough to defeat a demon who kills the exorcist lady in the process.
Because the exorcist lady with her faith isn't strong enough.
You just don't buy it.
It's a really corny climax where Andra Day is screaming, I have the power of God
and the power of God is within me and whatever.
It's playing this triumphant music.
It gives, it gives the Omen three a run for its money with that crazy ending
where Jesus appears in the sky or whatever.
Like, it's just not well done.
And amidst all of it, all of the possession stuff and the stuff that's supposed to be
scary, it's just lame.
I don't like when demons, demons cursing is one thing.
When demons start talking in like slang vernacular, I find it odd.
I'm just like, what is the demon reading up on cultural speaking?
And it's very odd to me.
It's like if a demon suddenly starts talking in like southern
dialect or something, it's weird.
It just takes me out of it.
It just does. And the demon does do this at the end.
And I get that the whole idea is, no, it's talking to the person
in a way that would be most effective to the person, I guess, that's the point.
But it just seems kind of weird.
It just seems kind of crazy.
So but that's a small detail.
My bigger problem with with the with the ending is it's just none of these horror
things work. They start OK, they start kind of creepy
when they're hinting at it in the beginning of the movie or earlier in the movie.
The sequence again, the kid throwing his ship, the other kid laughing hysterically.
That all works.
And then they really try to go for it.
And the minute they try to go for it, you're like, it's just sorry, guys,
you're not hitting this man. This isn't this isn't your wheelhouse.
It's really divided into into two halves.
And that's why I was kind of surprised by how everyone just shat on it,
because I was like, no, I think you have half a really good movie
and half something that just doesn't work critics.
I mean, I get if it's a horror movie and the horror elements don't work,
then you can't really give it a good review.
But I do wish sometimes that critics would be a little more like
this really worked. This didn't.
They're always just like, this stupid piece of shit, whatever.
And I do think there's stuff here worth watching.
Lee Danos is great with characters, people, real things.
And clearly, this is just not his forte.
I liked well, I love the family shit with Glenn Close and Andrew Day.
And as you're saying, as the suspense is building
and weird things are happening, I'm like, hey, I'm completely on board.
But when the. Zelda Rubenstein character shows up, the the exorcist woman,
that character is paper thin, it doesn't work.
The entire exorcism sequence looks cheap.
It's like in a gray room.
It's not scary or suspenseful in any way.
I think the movie might have been more interesting if Monique
had played the exorcist, you'd certainly have a more funny movie.
But that lady just was not compelling enough, nor was the story.
It's half a good movie.
I don't know what to tell you, except that exactly what I just said.
I agree. I think it's half a good movie.
And I wish that and I've made this criticism before of exorcism movies.
I just wish that every exorcism movie didn't seem like a guy
who watched the exorcist and just said, oh, that's what demons say.
Yeah, this is a movie made right now about an exorcism
should not still have the line.
He's in here with us.
It's like it's been done so many times.
Come on, guys.
Like just I don't care if that's what the real demon said
when this happened, allegedly.
You got to change the line. You just have to change it.
I hear you.
I do feel like with these movies.
You're you're getting people just writing off their influences,
watching other possession movies and copying them.
I know it's harder to write a horror movie like from your own personal experience,
because usually, hopefully what happens in a horror movie
doesn't happen to real people.
But yeah, we need we need new takes on these on these tropes.
They're just they're not interesting anymore.
They're not fun.
And scary, like if something is scary, generally, it's something unexpected,
something you haven't seen before, something that takes you by surprise.
So to just keep churning out shit that hits the exact same beats,
it's the opposite of scary.
It doesn't work anymore.
So we've got to we've got to mix it up.
Well, folks, that's the end of this month.
We'll be back next month with probably Godzilla,
maybe Blink twice, maybe the heretic, if that's whatever the hell that's called.
Godzilla minus one.
We're talking about heretic with Hugh Grant.
We're talking about maybe Rebel Ridge.
We're talking about the substance with Demi Moore.
Not sure what we're going to do, but be ready, be prepared.
Hogs half down, half up for the deliverance.
First half is up, second half is down.
We'll see you next time, folks.
And we'll see you in hell.