Here is your bonus ep
bonus bonus bonus
for january, it's very merry
it's the fourth
bonus bonus bonus
bonus ep, Pat how are you?
I'm good, we uh
we're really bad with the the kickoff songs for these bonus ep's
your last one was like here's your bonus ep
I mean they're bad so I'm not trying to make them good Pat
I'm trying to the joke to me is that they're bad
so weren't on this no plugs no segments
no plugs no segments unfiltered hog house
coming to you live from the hog house
the thick veiny pull back the sheath
to reveal the uncut dick house
right yeah uh no segments but we have a nice
discussion let me get to our special topic
we're doing another list this week this is the top five
event movies of Pat and my uh our lives uh so we're each going to name
countdown style our five top event movies the things we are most excited to
rush to the theater to see throughout our lifetime i'm excited for this
i am too i have i didn't plan mine out because like i just immediately knew
what the five would be i named my five for pet
and then after they were all star wars movies i was like
let me break it up just a little bit yeah uh but uh yeah
where there we've got some we've got some juice cook in here
juice cooking juice okay relax all right calm down all right not everybody's
saying terrible shit all the time
Joe how's it going Pat it's going well you know i was sitting here tonight
cooking yeah as you could smell when you came in i was making some
i could smell what the Joe was cooking yeah it smells pretty good it smells like
thanksgiving me i made some paleo stuffing yeah uh
and you know what you learn when you make paleo stuffing
no the whole battle with stuffing is just the five spices that's all it
is that's what makes it taste like the stuffing you could sprinkle that
shit on anything it would taste like stuffing i didn't know stuffing had five
spices what are you using instead of bread i use almond flour and you beat it
with eggs and it it you know it creates a
bready consistency that you can use and honestly i can't
there's a bit of a textural difference but not a huge difference um and then you
chop up some vegetables and saute those and put those in but the spices are like
thyme margarine not margarine sorry tarragon tarragon whatever the
fuck it's called rosemary sage but i mean it's amazing
parsley say rosemary and uh what's that
Simon Garfunkels one but you take that's how that's how badass Simon Garfunkel
where they released a single about spices
called parsley sage rosemary and thyme
i really don't like those guys and that doesn't help
but anyway the second you get all these spices together in a bowl you're like
oh that's stuffing i could just eat these spices right right anyway
you know what i uh i have started to do
man man it's uh you put a sweet potato in the microwave
for five minutes it's so hot the skin falls right off
you puncture the skin it comes right off and you stick your dick in it
you fuck that sweet potato till it ain't sweet no more you know what i'm saying
until the until the skin's falling off your dick till those yams become
candied with come Jesus Christ shocked myself uh
no you you begged the sweet potato five minutes you peel the skin off
you put it in a bowl with i do egg whites
and you you whip it all up you got this batter that's uh sweet potatoes and egg
whites yep and you make pancakes that are better
than actual pancakes um i'm not kidding you they are better
and health of course significantly healthier than pancakes uh we talked about
the other day at breakfast i also make pancake
sometimes with uh banana almond butter we might
talk about some of the fucking podcast did we are we repeating ourselves
i don't know i don't know it'd be bad it'd be bad one thing to repeat
ourselves on a regular app to repeat ourselves on the app that people are
paying extra for would be bad let's get off of this we'll add an additional
minute at the end for this look i mean you had to listen to how to make
fucking vegan stuffing uh we're off to a bad start
paleo stuff paleo stuff in it all right you scumbag
um what's happening in your life joe i mean as but the reason we almost
stopped this podcast is the only time we ever saw each other was to do the
podcast right we decided to keep doing it now here we are the only
times we can be okay are here on the pod that's not true we hang out a lot
you came to my birthday party but i mean yeah and then you were gone for the
whole weekend we hung out last week you we came over
Friday night and hung out for video game night you left
Saturday i went on a romantic getaway with my sweetie
yeah and i heard she was trying to get away from you the entire time
what has some truth to that what's some truth to that where'd you take her
is i'm kind of ice skating rink resort kind of thing you know for about three
years i've had a gift card to this place terrania a resort
in uh it's about an hour outside of the city of
Los Angeles okay absolutely beautiful and uh you know it's a classic LA
gift you know how like i never tell you this story like i donated giz when i
first moved here i ever talked about this in the podcast uh no but the the bad
part was the woman wasn't requesting it
um to a clinic you mean yeah so it was in westwood there's this place called
ditty Reese which is a uh it's a place in westwood so it's huge with UCLA kids
it's called ditty Reese ditty Reese all right and it's a place that used to be like
the go -to spot if your parents can to town or whatever now it's way too far
you go to westwood the seamenbank is the now the the cookie place they give you
they give you ice cream between two cookies and it used to cost a dollar
i'm sure it's now this is not the sperm bank it's behind ditty Reese i thought you were saying
the sperm back was called ditty Reese no all right ditty Reese was this place uh it was two cookies
with ice cream in the middle for a dollar now i'm sure it's 1495 but when i first moved to LA it was
a big deal and i once when i was out there i thought well shit i'm gonna have to move back to Missouri
i have no money i'm not succeeding i hear what am i gonna do i go out ditty Reese with a buddy of
mine and i see an advertisement for this place jizz hundred dollars a load wow i'm like shit i'm
gonna do this three times a week i got a trash can in my office full of liquid gold yeah you're like
Tom Hanks in a punchline remember he says that's how he's making his living was coming he says
i've never seen punchline and i own it i bought it for a dollar i've never seen it uh it's worth
a watch i mean it's not a fantastic would you say it's the most accurate portrayal of the life of
the stand -up uh many stand -ups have actually said that hanks is the one i'm serious i'm not
making a joke that hanks is the one actor that actually seemed to catch like the rhythm of a stand -up
properly like he does sound like a stand -up in it and it's very dark it's the first i it's always
gonna have a shadow over because i saw it when i was a kid for the first time i should watch it i'll
watch when i was a kid i saw it for the first time and it was like the first time i ever saw
Tom Hanks playing like a darker character yeah but that's a line in the movie he's like you've got
seen turner and hooch in uh i never saw turner and hooch what i was a canine kid myself
turner hooch is so much better than canine i'm sure it was i zigged when i should his egg but i mean
yeah he had to pick one of the dog movies i went with the one with the fatter man and it it just
looked more fun to me but anyway i also loved belushi because that move that movie uh the the
smart guys or whatever he was in with him and john real man real man yeah i love that movie as a kid
so i did too one of my favorite Conan bits is i always used to love Tom Hanks that he was the only
big star that would go on Conan when he was on at 12 30 right he just thought he was funny and loved
and uh they were like you know tom we wanted to thank you for coming and gracing our our little show
and we we decided to reunite you tonight with one of your your co -stars one of your favorite co -stars
and he's like oh okay great and they bring out the skeletal remains of hooch
one of the darkest things i've ever seen on television and hanks loved it it was hilarious they bring
out a dog carcass on Conan anyway that's up there with and then you can finish but let's just stay on
this for one second yeah that's up there with uh well when hanks was on jimmy glick jimmy glicks spit
out a bunch of gumdrops that he had in his mouth and hank picks the pangs picks them up off the ground
and eats them which i admire but it's a funny man my favorite reunion reunion bit is uh when uh when
uh harrison Ford was on i think it was letterman maybe it was Kimmel and it was before force awakens
and they're like we have your old co -star here because we know you're doing a new stars movie then
then chubaka comes out and harrison Ford goes on this tirade about how chubaka fucked his wife
and he's just going get out of here you son of a bitch she was my wife that's great yeah i was really
if you don't force him like the kind of guy where if you don't make a hundred percent sure that he's
in on the joke and gonna do it that that's a joke that's gonna backfire you couldn't bring out the
remains of chubaka and and hope that Ford would laugh no no this was clearly clearly planned yeah yeah yeah
but uh it was funny that was i think the third tweet i ever posted years and years ago was
harrison Ford seems like the kind of guy who wouldn't speak to you for days if you beat him at putt putt
and i stand by that i don't know man he seems like he's got a nice sense of humor but uh
i've heard he's the biggest pothead in america uh i've heard the same and i love that i love that about
him too i he he's i've heard him and aniston or like the biggest kind of a less pothead i couldn't
love jammy anymore we'd actually divorced pit and aniston because pit was too much of a pothead he
was like the character in dromance right and he was he was not attached emotionally he was
completely gone from the relationship but then once they split up aniston missed the weed and kept
at it's what i've heard here's a little fun fact for about friends for you okay originally in
phrasier the role of ra's i knew this was lisa kudra replaced five days before i think shooting
yeah uh and then she got cast in front so it all worked out so what i'm trying to say is as i am bound
for a major successful sitcom role since i was taken out of your show that's true you you will be in
the next friends yes um anyway i know you've been watching a lot of phrasier you never finished your
thing about i will all right i'm sorry i bet yeah i've been i'm in season uh i think seven or eight right
now i always love phrasier when it was on to masterpiece i watched five the other night didn't smile
i i appreciated the writing which five first five uh well it's like any other show it takes
a minute to kind of get their stride i don't like the i like it starting with the second season
because that's when he gets the haircut and he looks yeah like he looks through the whole show
and he and the dad starts being a little friendlier right and you know the first season there's a lot
of awkward like where the dad's like your mother would be ashamed every episode yeah and it's like
they get away from that a bit and they start to build a bond in season two it's beautiful by the end of
season 11 like niles is coming in he's like hi dad like you see the love it's such a beautiful
character arc i'll stick with it of course i mean i watch it the first time around but uh i had read
this onion article about this episode that was they said it was the best sitcom episode of the 90s
and i'm like oh here it is on hulu i got to watch this thing season three it's the leap year episode
and he's telling everybody you got to take a chance yeah that's a leap year and then at the end
he winds up singing the song and he sings the lyrics badly and they were describing this as the
the one of the greatest sitcom scenes of all time it wasn't funny it was a rip off of frank
dribbins uh butchering of the national anthem and then they could gun and i was really thrown by it
they had five different critics at the onion raving about that's not a good episode that's an
episode that when it comes on i skip it like that's not a great one you want to see a hilarious one watch
merry christmas misk mousk moscavitch i think it's called okay it's my favorite of the phrase your
christmas episodes and the plot is he starts dating a girl her and her mom come over the girl
realizes that treasure is not jewish and he has to pretend like he's jewish for the mom and it's a
total far it's a the best episode is a phrasier the pharsical ones where i agree the sword fight
episode was always my favorite one it's a total pharsical thing and it's like niles and the dad
pretending they're jewish and everything mm -hmm it's really really fucking funny uh that's one of my
favorites i might start working through i'm i'm i'm working through all the family i'm on season three
i had never seen it i mean i i'm doing a lot with these sitcoms i want to get i want to be a master
look me too i bought an entire i bought the entire series go on the family yes i got up to like five
i was loving it don't get me wrong but i was just like i got to take a break it's it's all in that house
there's so much it's oppressive yeah you know so you got to you got to take a breath but i mean you
want to talk about another brilliant show i mean jesus christmas um anyway folks about my giz
i go to this place i say so this is a hundred dollars of a toss basically she goes yes i am not
exaggerating when i say that the nurse behind the counter was porno hot and eight she was an Asian nurse
from vaguely flirtatious i had just moved to la i was probably twenty six twenty seven yeah they
got to get you in the mood they're gonna have nurse ratchet back there she goes there's two rooms
back there um she goes we'll give you some materials here and she sets a dvd face down on the table
and she goes just take your time coming out whenever you're ready and as i'm walking back to the room
i flip the dvd and it is called in a medical facility
jam it all the way up my ass part two so it it says jam it all jam it up my ass and then it's one of
those where like a cartoon character hammers in a sign that says all the way like the little add -on
i always like a zany porno myself yeah so i'm like jam it all the way up my ass part two jesus
a will i be able to follow the story having not seen the original there you go b which is the only
joke to work making that seriously that's the only joke to make but b um the assumption that i
just be a guy off the street needs to see really aggressive anal porn as opposed to just like
you think in a medical facility they'd give you a sports illustrated swimsuit type deal
no they apparently they want you out i guess well they yeah and i mean also might
our dear friend pinkstone told me a title of a porno movie once in the song college
we've we've quoted we've referred to the title that to this day it's the funniest porno title i've
ever heard my life and it is sink it deep or get the fuck out
haha joe i've heard that from so many women in this time
which part of the sentence the whole the whole thing here's the thing dude when i went i talk about
the story of this in my act when i went to to do a semen's now i had to do a semen sample
because they thought i might have a prostate issue right which i ended up not but i had to go to do a
semen's now either there was gonna be like that like i go and they give me a porno whatever the lady
at the nurse at the place where i went she gave me a cup and she goes men's rooms out our front door
down the hole on the left and i was like wow that's a public men's room yeah you want to go
whack off in the public men's room right now wow so i'm not gonna tell the whole story but i went down
i was like i can't do it yeah i went back i go i'm sorry i can't do this swear my life she goes
that's okay take it home and do it there why would you do it there i go really why don't you
open with that next time lady yeah yeah i go into this booth i shut the door it's pitch black
of course all you can think about is how every surface in this little booth must be full of com oh
yeah i insert excuse the pun the DVD jam it all the way up my ass comes up and we're talking about like
girls just being brutally fucked in the ass i'm watching this i'm uncomfortable i'm thinking
i don't want to come immediately i also don't want to be in here for 30 minutes and then
have to face this asian nurse yeah yeah i was panicked i got it done and what i felt was a very
reasonable amount of time i walk out with a cup of jizz the whole time you're like is this gonna be
a lot of jizz is it too little jizz um you know like what do they see in here just being her first rodeo
i know i know but i walk out of course you're nervous i hand it to her um i start for the door
and as i open the door just uh mr. wash i turn i go yes she goes could we um we get the DVD back please
complete accident i'm holding the DVD it look like i was trying to steal jam it all the way up my ass
i tried to make a joke about it she did not so much a smile and help me out no she got what she needed
out of you it's done the lap dance is over yeah get out of the room i give it back to her
and i go so when does the check arrive i thought all these forms she goes well this is your preliminary
to make sure that your your stuff is good so you don't get anything on this first time i'm like oh okay
it felt kind of used drive home car breaks down on the drive home i'm sitting on the side of the road
having just jerked off in a cup black clouds of smoke billowing out of my right 97 satter than i bought
for a thousand dollars i'm like why did i move to Los Angeles the question i still ask myself to this
without the commerce smoke i go home they come back they're like look
26 year old dude you got good grades in college you're not a mutant
you you pass come in you can do up to three donations a week i'm like 300 dollars a week
done can we still do this yeah why am i not doing this you'll hear why in a moment okay
i go in i do the first one i hand it to her she hands me a coupon for one free AMC movie
okay an AMC movie theater i go i thought i get a hundred dollars a ton she goes yeah but the first
time just to kind of get you in the system we just give you this AMC pass i'm like all right i go to
use the AMC pass here in Los Angeles it doesn't cover the full cost of the movie okay because
LA movies are so expensive i had to pay three additional dollars all right so what happens the second
time second time i go in i jerk off and she goes so just so you know i'm i'm obliged to tell
i have to tell you after this point your semen can be used in the production of a child the first
time is making sure everything is good the second time is making sure the first time was not a fluke
and i get all that now your your face is going to be in our book of like dudes that they can
pick right they can read about your background okay okay and by that she meant it could be used in
pregnant woman not that they were going to build a model of a baby out of your semen yeah okay good
good that's good to know it's a professional kind of place i go in the back i jerk off i hand it to her
and i say now excuse me i just want to make sure because i haven't asked this question yet but
the kid once it grows up like can't look you up right like that will smith ted dancin movie made in
saw in the theater and thanks for blowing one of my event movies now but i go uh the kid can't look
me up down the line right she goes actually as of 2003 or whatever when a child born from a semen
donation um turns 18 in the city of los angeles if they go to the sperm donor place and they say i
want to find out who my father was the city of los angeles is legally required to tell them who
they're that's it that's all that stopped you Joe so so like i get married i have kids and then you
have a grown kid that shows up and says hey apparently you were the donor thank you can i get some
money oh stop it can i get me some money you don't think that kid might ask for legally uh up
up bound to uh uh give him any money or her any money i couldn't do it i couldn't like have somebody
show up my door and be like oh this is my son now that's the exact way i want to have a kid
fully grown kid shows up we got different hey kiddo how you doing let's go get a few beers huh
cuz i'm thinking i don't even know who i'm gonna be married to it that was a single man at this
point i'm like what if my wife freaks out what if anything i i i said throw it in the trash answer me
this the place is there i could go do this right now i could go make three hundred dollars per week
just to masturbate Joe you know you can make money donating semen you know that i didn't know i could
make that much money i'm telling you this they're not gonna love you smoking weed that i don't smoke weed
they're not gonna love certain things about your lifestyle i drink is that going to be a problem
for them you can lie about it but it'll probably be a problem oh why about it all right go donate
just they never said a man can't drink when they're trying to get pregnant i've never heard that before
that's true uh i just i couldn't do it could i couldn't do it it's twelve hundred bucks a month
to go have a great time with apparently some real filthy movies too and this is what they were
showing in in 2007 who know i mean they got to be woo yeah woo woo yeah well i don't even know
how i got on this i was gonna talk about how like the amc pass wasn't enough to see a movie
you know guys i don't know how pat got on this story about getting off i need it oh oh oh
bad he did folks um pat drink your damn wine you know i poured you a glass of
some nice red wine you're barely drinking it over there well i'm not a wine sugar
Joe it's not shugging pat it's been a half an hour i'm sipping like a gentleman um all right well let's
get to our first one uh the topic for today i don't want to do this five to the i mean i guess
we want to say what here's the number one movie we were most excited about five i'm not going to
be able to quantify them we'll just say five in any order i'm gonna be able to quantify them i'm
gonna quantify my number one the restaurant any order we're gonna discuss folks our five biggest
event movies the five times we were if i have this correct most excited to go to the motion picture
where it was an event yeah yes okay go ahead you can go first
unless you want me to go first i'll go first because i can tell you need some time to think
go ready yes uh number five tells him the crypt demon night okay uh and i talked about this on the
podcast we reviewed it but uh Pinkstone and i were were insanely rabid uh tells him the crypt fans
you couldn't pull us away from that show when they announced they were actually going to make a movie
that was an original story uh that wasn't taken from the comic books we couldn't have been more excited
we were so thrilled to hear the whole team was involved um and i mentioned this again on the show
i was so excited that we went on opening night that was sold out we had to buy tickets to another movie
then sneak in sure uh and even though i was on a date with a girl that i desperately wanted to
impress when the lights went down i yelled pinkstone because we were we had to sit in separate areas yeah
and then he made fun of me later like i can't believe you were on a date and you thought
that that was like the right thing to do and i was like dude demon night superseded everything
tonight for me like i can't believe you went on a date and brought a male friend well we were going
as a group it was like a soft first date like we were going as a group of friends and it was kind of
like him yeah i think he's cute like and then you know we all went out like in a no pressure zone
kind of date uh but that was a huge huge event film for me as a kid all right we're a kid teenager i mean
sure isn't that young sure um all right i'll just i'll just go myself um for me
i think i would have a to say well see the only one i truly know is my number one here's what
i'm gonna say this is gonna be the shocker the rest might be a little more expected i'm gonna
reference the i believe 1992 film starring john ritter palm dober and Eugene levy
and the picture is called stay tuned this was an event picture for you i was a weird fucking kid
the rest are gonna be a lot more traditional is this the one before we started recording where you
said i got one that you're gonna be like i just believe about i remember pleading with my dad and
usually it was a rating issue like i begged my dad to see pulled fiction forever and it was just a flat
no stay tuned was pg i was like i'm so excited we have to go opening night we have to none of my friends
were talking about stay tuned this was the movie that was supposed to be directed by tim Burton but
eventually it was just not that basically was just a bunch of parodies of movies and television not a great
driving over miss daisy i know i remember it's it's sort of the like more mainstream version of
uhf that's exactly right yeah uh and i did love uhf i love uhf still stay tuned for me doesn't hold up
it no of course not uh it was a parody movie and i was very into the parodies at the time
and i just remember being like i think probably because when you're 12 that's the age when you're
starting to kind of be like able to control when you go to the movies and like if you want if you
demand something your parents usually take you to see it and you start to realize that i was obsessed
with seeing this movie saw it i liked it i probably laughed way too hard because i had put on such a
show but how i wanted to see it sure but even as a kid you were like this probably isn't as good as me yeah
yeah and they did a wains world spoof and of course i was very obsessed with wains world which could
could just have easily been on this list but it was less interesting uh i remember all my friends
after a batting cage when i was on a baseball team we're all going to see wains world and my dad was like
it's PG 13 so i need to see it before you can see it right and all of my friends went to see wains
world on like a Saturday afternoon and i had to wait till it came to the fucking dollar show and then
wains world is a fucking masterpiece but i wouldn't go that far but i think it's a good movie
it's one of the best comedies ever made in my opinion but uh top 10 comedies ever made
it's one of the best comedy it wouldn't be my top 10 but i think it's one of the best but that's
and that means it's not one of the best comedy i like a lot of com wains world you know listen i'm saying
it's good i think wains world invented a lot of the shit that modern comedy takes that is true
it really did and as far as being an s and l movie like holy shit oh christ it's it's head and shoulders
above i mean the only other s and l movies that could maybe come close are i i hear the ladies man's
very funny i've never seen it but it's fine feral's funny and it's funny uh night at the rocks he's
pretty funny at the rocks bar is fun or rocks bar excuse me um i only blues brothers the only one
i put up with well blues brothers is the number one ever whose brothers is probably right s and l
adaptation movie but just as good i mean these are both classic companies in my opinion i bet you
still better than your family is kind of funny Stewart says his family is a great movie but it's a drama
that's what people were not it's a drama about being in a family of alcoholics it's a drama i'm not
saying there aren't a few laugh attempts but it's like a serious movie about 12 step addiction
so they tried to do like the whole like remember when they did the spin -off from merley marie
tyler more and ed asner suddenly it was like a yeah our drama about journalism and it worked
was i telling you about unis you did tell you about unis but you did not tell these fine listeners
of ours about unis and that's something we need to talk about right now i haven't watched it yet
because i'm too excited and you better wait for me you motherfucker come over and watch it all right
please i was i wanted to make this so special that i haven't watched it in like two weeks but my sister
my sister and i get along fine but you know she lives in Missouri we don't talk much
when we were kids we were not really close either but every night we would watch two episodes minimum
mama's family which in my memory is one of the funniest sitcoms ever made and i'm sure is dog shit
but i love mama's family it was um
yeah just hit comedy white white trash Vicki Lawrence played mama and in the early episodes
carol burnette played unis because mama's family was a spin -off yeah from the carol burnette show
Yes, Carol Burnett played Eunice the miserable and it like it wasn't always a dark character. She was very unhappy
The whole family was kind of unhappy, but it never it was always just kind of Hic lives. Yeah, Betty White played a
Anth -Rumaclana -Anth -Rumaclana -Anth -Rumaclana -Rumaclana -Anth -Rumaclana -Rumaclana -Anth played like the Bibley lady, which is why they switched roles right on the Golden Girls and
And all these characters were gone in the later seasons of Mama's Family, but my sister sent me the box set of Mama's Family
And it was six seasons, which I was blown away that the show even lasted that long
This was a show that after its first season was all straight to syndication, which they don't even do anymore. Yeah, it was just a syndicated show
This box set I'm looking through the special features and what do I see but between the Carol Burnett show and Mama's Family
They released a 90 -minute film a TV film a
drama
Featuring all the Mama's Family Characters
But like a Tennessee Williams play where they're all struggling with being unhappy with alcoholism
I read a review of this thing that got me so excited that this might be one of my top five most anticipated things
The thought of like imagine watching like your favorite sitcom as a dark
Like staged play drama and I have brought I have brought myself to watch it because I'm too excited
I'm gonna watch it with you. It'll be great
I can't wait to see this and now I want to watch Stuart saves his family
I remember Stuart says the family being very interesting my I know my dad wanted me to watch it because he was in AA
And I remember thinking boy, this isn't funny at all because I always thought Stuart's a dark comedy
I don't think it was a drama. No, there were at least the the back half is a pretty serious drama really. Yeah
All right, it's all dramatic actors in the in the roles like out Franken and well
Who else?
Pat why did you tell our frankin to do it?
I threw it back on you for once
You know because he's good enough
He's smart enough and dog on it. I wanted him to sexually assault a woman while he slept. Well
You're a man that always has the perfect retort and that's why you run a TV show
I've said it before I'll say it again. Thanks, Joe. All right my number four
Casino yeah
When I heard now I was a kid I was 12 years old and my mother showed me good fellas
She almost forced me to watch the movie. What a dream. I had to sneak it. Yeah, you weren't allowed to see pulp fiction
You were 26 years old
No, I my mom I was good fellows with my ear pressed to the speaker of my 24 -inch television my mom sat me down
She said I want you to watch this movie. I really think you're gonna like it. I'll watch it with you
They're gonna curse a lot. I'm just warning you. Yeah, that was her big concern not these stabbings in the gut and the stomping of people's faces
Him offering his wife a stack of cash and then pushing her head down onto his day. He doesn't push her head down
She goes down because he goes he goes. I can I got to go. Oh, all right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I see oh no in the in the jail
They you see the guy forcing the what the you see that in the in the call booths and then in
Encino Pesciino, yeah, Pesci pushes the woman's head down the bones head
Yeah, it's not Sharon's well
He does push Sharon stones head down later, but the first time he does it for the foreshadowing. Yeah, you know
This is his thing is when he walks the he gives the woman the tour of the restaurant and then walks her out to the car as he's
Explaining the properties of Ville
Yeah, yeah, and they get into the car and he goes he goes that pink feel you can pound that shit for days
It'll never get tender and he just yeah
He goes move over sweetheart
Yeah, he slides over he slides it anyway. It's an outrageous film. I was the casino
I was excited for it because when I was a kid as I said my mom made me watch good fellows I
Didn't want to and then I watched it and I was obsessed with it from that day forward. I
Just loved it so much so when I heard they're making a sort of pseudo -sequence
The good fellows
It's called casino. It's different characters, but it's based on a book by the same author that wise guy was written by
It's got the same cast essentially
And my mom told I remember my mom telling me about casino and she goes oh, and they're gonna have all these cameos by famous
Casino comedians like Vegas comics and I was like I
Mean sign me the fuck up when I was 15 the first concert I ever saw was Sinatra with Don Rickles opening
So I already had something else an infatuation my first concert was weird. I'll let six flags. Well, I'm not surprised
Yeah, that's right. That was 32 at the time
Yeah, no, I but I had such an infatuation already with this world I
Was just so so excited. I remember being in college. It was my freshman year, and I remember
Me and all my friends in my little dorm hallway
Rowdy friends
What do you mean all my like all my rowdy friends are coming over tonight? What the hell is that?
Monday night football. Oh, I don't know. Do you think I watch a foot?
I don't know no one cares less about football than me. I know all my rowdy friend, you know
Oh, you're ready for the football. Oh, William's junior. Yeah, you know, you know a little bit fired because he said something crazy
We all went on like you know a Wednesday night or something. You in the family? No
And I was so excited and I remember when it started I was watching it and I was I was enjoying it because it was very good fellows
Esk, but I remember the one thing I was upset about was over the first 20 minutes or so I was like
And Pesci's really playing like a nice guy in this one. I don't care for that
And then the scene comes where they're in the bar and
The guy tells the Nero to take the pen and shove it up his fucking ass, right and Pesci takes the pen
Stabs the man repeatedly in the neck the man's on the ground crying and whimpering and Pesci standing over him going
What's that ace? What's that you hear sounds like a little girl?
What happened to my friend? I said the pen is fucking it. Yeah, and I was like
Holy shit. They just put this into like 10th gear
Right, this is gonna be nuts and and of course they did and I loved every
Second of that movie. I loved it. I had such a blast watching it. I
was
15 I remember every single thing about casino coming out and
If I had been allowed to see it Joe
This would have definitely been on my list, but I can't say a most anticipated movie that I was not allowed to see sure
Well, what is your next contest? I was so excited at this same the exact same year. This is how good a December
Denero had heat came out. Yes, which I did sneak into an absolutely fucking loved of course
That's very impressive because when I first saw it at I'm a little two years older than you when I first saw when it came out
I was bored to tears. It took it took my friend
Rob Nettock who's who I was in theater with at in college
Who was in my opinion the best male actor in the program?
And he said to me heat is one of the greatest
The Breckenmeyer of your
That the Adam Scott if you will
Maybe the Kristen Bell
But anyway, he I remember him saying to me like no, you're wrong about heat. You need to watch again
It's one of the best movies ever made. Yeah, then I watched it again, and I was like oh
Now that I'm not expecting Puccino and De Niro to be in every scene together. This is awesome
Sometimes that's all it takes yeah, I felt disappointed as well, but they weren't sharing more scenes together and then
What's so funny is at the time?
They were able to inspire that sort of excitement whereas now
But she knows doing directed on -demand shit. I'm so excited for the Irishman to come out and I'm just praying to God
It's not
Let's not jinx it. All right. Go ahead. Score says he doesn't make shit. He doesn't make shit. No, he didn't make vinyl
Which I wouldn't say vinyl was shit. I just didn't like it. I just didn't like vinyl
It wasn't shit. I just didn't like vinyl was shit
He also did silence which was shit, but it meant a lot to him
So well, but also critics really like silence. I can deal with critics liking it at least silence kundun
I'm saying Marty. These are your these are your movies. I don't need them. I know he goes down that road once a while
Or is a religious man? I'm gonna make a picture about the first Pope's childhood. Yeah, I know, but please don't Marty
I was because I was so excited about casino, but couldn't share with my dad why because he didn't know I had seen good fellows
I couldn't see casino. He went one day by himself. He was probably my age and went and saw it at like 2 p .m
And I was so jealous and he raved about it and
You know, I have friends to this day who like casino more than good films. I don't agree, but I get it
I don't agree either, but I could tell you I could be swayed at the right in the right moment
I could be swayed, but but so so your heat you saw heat you're in your loving it
I'm gonna go forward a couple years to my most anticipated which was hey, I thought you were saying heat was your number four
No, oh Pat, but I'll get I'll get to it quickly
Jackie Brown
Great
Almost made my list and in a very similar situation. I had seen pulp fiction on the slide, but Jackie Brown hit at a time where I was
newly 17 and able to see whatever the fuck I wanted and it came out at like Christmas time and the trailer was fantastic
trailer was get ready the four top song get ready. Yeah get and I I was so fucking excited and the movie
More than lived up to it, and it was so many people have these stories of going to see it all hyped up on that pulp fiction
High and being let down for some reason I never was I loved it from the jump
That's another one I didn't like as much it took a couple watches for me to get it. Yeah, I love the film now
Originally we were gonna do our top five movie villains of all time for this episode right we changed it
But my number four was Odell Roby from Jackie Brown
But we don't need to go much on a Jackie Brown. We've covered it endlessly on this podcast. Yeah, that's my number four
That's a great flick man
It almost made my list. It's probably my number six to be honest. Yeah, my number three. Okay, folks
Sorry, but from here on out. It's all one note for me
The
Phantom Menace
well, look
I'm not saying it's a great flick
I'm just telling you when George Lucas announced suddenly in the late 90s that he was gonna make more Star Wars films of course
I was beside myself I
Wasn't
Quite as excited that they were prequels, but I was really fucking excited. Yeah
And I remember sitting in the theater with again with pink stone and
My friends Scott who you've met Hoffman very many times and my friend Jamie
Jowett all dear friends and old friends and we were seeing there
I remember us gripping hands as the lights went down like this is about to happen right now
Now the only reason it's not higher on my list is because early reviews of it so bad
Well, no early reviews of it. It's tainted
There were early reviews of Phantom Menace that were like it's not good the CG
I remember hearing like Howard Stern two days before and he was like it doesn't make like they look like they're not even in the scene with the things
Cuz it looks fake and the kids stinks and whatever
So that tainted it, but it didn't take away from the fact that this was one of the most exciting moments of my entire life that I was gonna see a
New Star Wars movie something we never thought what happened. Sure
Afterwards outside the theater we definitely had the like
Yes, what
What did you think of that? Yeah, I supported it through and through and was like look I
Like it. It's not exactly what I wanted, but I'm gonna stick in there with it. Saw it a few more times liked it
Saw
Attack of the clones a bunch of times liked it even more so I rinsed the Sith liked it even more so I
Hung in there patiently. Yeah, but but still it was a wonderful experience and
And you know, that's it
I
Need to go back to the future. I was excited to see back the future three the other two
I was too young for but I was very excited three is a yeah made for TV movie. It's terrible. It's I think it's fine
The least of the series certainly but by like a thousand
Percent
I need to go back to and I need to tell you a little bit about who I was as a kid so when I was
1990 I'm nine years old the same age as young Kevin McAllister Mr. McCulloch
Right, and when home alone dropped
Every one of my friends was very excited to see it because it's a kid
Kick an ass, right?
but I gotta tell you I
Even at age nine was so obsessed with the writing of Mr. John Hughes, right?
I had seen Uncle Buck
the year prior and it became one of my all -time favorite movies which it still is and
I was just like okay everything about this movie is designed for a 10 -year -old boy to lose his shit
Sure, but what my friends did not have
Was the knowledge that it was written by my personal favorite filmmaker at that time and one of them to this day
Mr. John Hughes he wrote home alone. I was so excited and also I
Wasn't following there was no ain't it cool at this time
There was no way to find out this shit
But I saw an entertainment tonight thing where at the peak of my excitement. I'm like when will home alone come out god damn it
I was insisting that my parents. I remember as if I was on trial telling my parents
This one cannot be like Batman. This one cannot be like all the other ones
We have to wait for the dollar show. We need to go to the mall and pay full price right five seventy -five
Which it was at the time to see home alone and if I have to pay for me and you
I'm gonna do what I have to do to make that happen. I was so excited to see home alone
I was pleading with my family because and then after all this all my excitement on entertainment tonight. I saw that
Mr. John candy
Was playing some sort of role in home alone and then you're already talking about Prout one of my most anticipated movies
Right, he was my favorite star of the day, right. I was
violently shaking when I went to see home alone at the holiday season around Thanksgiving with my parents
The candy cameo isn't much either. It's kind of a bummer. You want it to be bigger. Oh, I think it's so funny really that
It was all improv. He's funny when he's playing the clarinet. I remember but you just it just made me want more John
Candle when he tells that story which was improv
About how when he was young his parents left him overnight. Oh, I forgot about that. Yeah in a funeral home with the body
And he was
Right, he ever felt all that shit. I mean, I think John candy is incredible in that movie. All right, you're right
It's a bigger part than I remember. Yeah, but I mean, we're talking that this is at a time still when I'm 9 10 years old
Where I know for a fact without having seen it that plans transolomials will be one of my favorite movies because my two favorite actors at that time
We're Steve Martin John candy and still I could not see it because it was rated R and I'm like this is a new movie coming out
I was shaking and I love the movie so much that at that time
It was my favorite movie and it remained that way until
My number one choice which I will get to momentarily, but home a lot of course number three you got two more
Yeah, I know, okay, but I'll get to my number one when I get to all right all right fine
I remember wanting to see plane trains that ought to be automobiles so badly because
I remember like entertainment tonight or whatever the hell the like magazine shows were at that's all we had back then
Yeah, honestly a better time. I remember them showing the rental car scene with Steve Martin and being like Steve Martin takes a
Funny twist in this so you might not expect from Steve Martin and it played the scene. It was all beeps and I was like
I can't wait to see Steve Martin say fuck repeatedly. I
Do you think we were talking on the super dark times episode which we recorded earlier a little peak behind the curtain
Which by the way might come out after this year before this. I don't know. Yes
Do you think and this to me is the age old question do we just know too much now and that is why nothing is fun
And nothing is good and we're not excited about anything because we know everything before we walk into the theater
It's part of it, but no it's it's
It's an actual fact that
Look we talked about Frazier earlier, you know, so it's funny you bring this up because I was thinking about this
The whole season seven or six whatever plot line is that Daphne falls in love with this lawyer named Donnie
Who's not who he's Niles divorce lawyer who plays Donnie? I can't remember the actors name
But he's been on curb your enthusiasm as soon as you seem like oh, yeah that guy all right
And he's the best dude yeah, and because he's the best dude
That's what makes it so
Crazy and amazing when Niles goes to the wedding and finally tells her at almost at the altar
I love you and I'm sorry and she runs and she's a runaway bride
Yeah, and I was watching and I was like they would never do this now
They would be like no Daphne will be too unlikable and it's like no
It's not that she's unlikable for leaving the nice guy
It's that she's so in love with Niles that she has to make a terrible sacrifice for it
And that's the difference now. There is no they wouldn't let you make a movie like home alone now. No, absolutely not
They wouldn't let you make it so it's it's that it's the nuance that's that's gone. Yeah
Anyway
My number I mean luckily outside of stay tuned which I remember enjoying at the time all of mine really lived up to my
My dream that's the goal. I mean do you have any that you were just a slap in the face?
I mean, I never saw Thanda manifest as a slap in the face. I was disappointed, but I wasn't sure
I wasn't like I said I was like okay
This is clearly a slow start, but we'll see where it's going
And my experience as a guy who who didn't love Star Wars as much of my friends was we all go to see Star Wars
Can't get in settle for the matrix
Become very very interested in the matrix, and then when we saw Star Wars
It seemed old -fashioned and even stupider in comparison
It took me a long time to come around the matrix because everybody at that time was like the matrix is the new future
Fuck Star Wars. Yeah, I really took that personally, right much like when I went to see
Mrs. Doubtfire and it was sold out so I saw a perfect world with Clint Eastwood and Kevin Costner
Which is an A -plus movie, right? That's when I learned that like what everyone's telling you to do is not always I saw Doubtfire in the theater
I didn't like it. I said eventually, but I don't think it's funny. Not fire's funny. I'm not saying it's without humor
I just don't think it's that good of a mood. It's a schmaltcy. I don't like it anyway
I'm noticing a pattern with your movies and my movies my movies all needed a precedent of excitement
There was an nostalgia even with every movie I'm picking. They were all set up by something I already loved
Yours are just you saw a fresh thing and you were really excited about the idea
That's interesting. I mean Jackie Brown came off of Pulp Fiction for sure except for that one though the other ones are like yes
That's true. That's true. Okay, my number two is
Another Star Wars film the Force Awakens we don't need to go into this deeply all I can say is this I
Was on Red Eye once when that was still a show on Fox News when they announced that Lucas had sold Lucas film
To Disney and that they were going to do a sequel trilogy to the original Star Wars trilogy with the original cast members
They brought it up. They were mid everybody in the panel is making fun of it
I said this is the most excited. I could human possibly be right now. I can't wait for this
Jim Norton was on that night. He said why why are you excited about this? And I said because it's literally to me like somebody telling you the Beatles
Didn't die
They're still alive and they're going to put out three new records
I was just like I never
Forget I never thought there'd be another Star Wars movie
I never in a zillion years thought there'd be another Star Wars movie and I'd see fucking Han Solo and Luke and Leigh again and Chewbacca and whatever so like
Well Chewbacca was in Rembrandt of the Sith so but you know
It was awesome. It delivered everything I wanted it to deliver. I loved it
Salted multiple times in the theater. I cried multiple times in the theater out of joyous nostalgic excitement and I
Just fucking loved it man. So that was that was a huge one for me
I I knew you through this time. I I knew you to be very excited about it
I and I and I like that you can still have those moments as an adult. I really don't
I mean that the most recent of these like I were talking like no country for old man or something like right and it was just an established director
Who I love right?
But I don't get I don't get that pumped anymore which which really bums me out is an ongoing source of
Well, I mean Star Wars is really the only thing they can do it for me
I can't think of another unless they said they were gonna do like an official sign felt reunion or something like that like sure
There are few things that
That exists that if they brought it back. I'd be that excited about right, but but anyway
What's your number two my number two and and no patick ord I'm gonna have to go
With
You know if I'm being real I'm gonna have to go with boogie nights
All I ever wanted you to be was real. I'm going from this the year basically when I
You know became a man like those late 90s were very big for me because it's it's different than most people I was
Now freed up to see not only new R -rated movies
But movies I have been hearing about for years do the right thing and all that raging bull sure good fellows reservoir dogs
I'm watching all this shit that I had been
Dreaming about seeing but when when one of these things would come to the theater
It's a very big deal. So like we're I'm lumping a bunch of movies that have nothing to do with each other
Except maybe sex and I was I was a horn dog as well
I also did not have porn at this time right boogie nights a movie that is
Rightly compared to good fellows sure one of the only ripoffs that is I would say in the same ballpark
Yeah, boogie nights a movie about pornography so everyone's raving about this movie
Paul Thomas Anderson I can't wait to see it. I'm excited to see it and this element of like
Seeing potentially graphic sex and nudity in a theater sure I had never done in my entire life
Should I was like 18 and couldn't and I went to the Esquire theater which was maybe an hour from my house
Which sounds like a porn theater I know it didn't say a Lewis but the Esquire and it's still there as far as I know but they had six shitty
theaters and then the biggest screen in the Midwest was their claim to fame and they showed boogie nights in the main screen and
Generally, they would show the big blockbuster on them
They were the only theater Missouri sure that first week that had boogie nights
So I was like I am going to see on this giant screen
pornography and that my interest going in was very
Perient whatever you want to call it sexual and
and
I loved and continue to love that movie so much that I saw the five o 'clock who's a leave I went by myself I
walked out I
I had a
Burrito next door and then I saw the 815 as well. I've never done that in my life
Wow saw twice and I just was like that that was the time for me the reason it was also exciting if I'm being real
All my most anticipated movies are when your kids you're most excited absolutely
But that was a time when I was like I can get out of Missouri
I want to do something creative. I know I know what I want to do and
Like hearing that that guy was like 27 Paul Thomas Anderson and all that I was like
This is this is incredible and to see a movie that
For all intents and purposes is porn good fellows right on the big screen because that was at a time where you're like
Well, fuck I'll never get to see good fellows in the bit now occasionally. They'll bring it out of that
Sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but
Well, Chris think about what people did before there was video rental even can you just had to wait until they showed it on TV again
But and I do think that would make for a fascinating episode of this podcast
I I think there was something so beautiful about that though. Oh, no, I agree. I agree
I'm just saying yeah when I think about like circling in TV guide like you need to record it
Three 15. Yeah, this movie which you've been looking for for years. It's gonna be on TV like I think
Future generations have really lost out on that shit. It's a bummer and it's it's it's the excitement of going to the video store and saying
You know, do you have you know Indiana Jones in the last crusade and them saying
You know what we have one copy left right be like
Oh, can I please can I have you know like it was so special and then also these things like the
This is the time when VHS cassettes cost if you like loss it or something or damage it you'd pay like 95 dollars
Which is one of one of the funny bits on side fell when he what's the movie they always keep seeing
Rochelle Rochelle where you like loses the copy and the guys like that's 95 dollars, right?
What
Things of change and when you say any end of Jones it reminds me of one that I've left off my list
But if I'm being real
My friends came out here from Missouri when I first moved L .A. And I remember that morning us or the night before we're gonna
Buy tickets for crystal skull. I know you like more than most
But we were like all right
Well, let's say we wake up in noon. We have a little lunch and then at some point we were like
I'm too excited
Yeah, it's one of the last time that felt that we were like we need to be there for like the 9 a .m. Show at the arc light
Yeah, I saw that by myself
Where we sat afterwards, you know again. I wasn't thrilled. I liked it though
I liked it fine, but but that was one I saw that opening day at not at 9 or 10 a .m.
Alone yeah, because we were already well into
trendy Lucas sucks
Territory and I was like I'm not seeing this with anybody. It's gonna fuck it up for me, right
Anyway, but just like the matrix ease the pain of
Phantom menace me and those same friends 10 years later
Had our pain from crystal skull eased by and glorious bastards. I love it
What's the connection there? We saw them in the same week. Oh, okay. I'm pretty sure I mean
Somebody might prove me wrong, but I'm pretty sure we walked out of Indiana Jones. We were so miserable
And we're like we got to see something else and then luckily the feelings we wanted to get from Indiana Jones
We got from a glorious band. Yeah, glorious bastards is a great pick man
And I'm glad they're doing a fifth Indiana Jones because I'll see it
I'll definitely see it and I just huh, no love buff
The rumor is no love just Harrison coming back. I know the big talk was that love buff was taking over the franchise
No, no, that was really that's never
Everybody repeatedly denied that it was rumors
But I'm just happy after Hansel who died in Force Awakens. Yes to get to see
Indiana Jones hopefully right off into the sunset. I want to pretend that Harrison Ford will live forever
I hope so they did a lot right. I mean having Karen Allen on their side of me, but boy
It was not great for me. My number one
Yeah, as you said there's never more excitement than when you're a kid
This is yet another Star Wars film
But this is hands down the most excited I ever was in my life. I've said it for
30 some years at this point
Return of the Jedi was the most excited I ever was
To go to a movie now you got to under so you were six
Jedi count. Yeah, I think I was about six or seven
I was about to go into first grade so six man. I was two. I don't have I was six and I had seen Empire
a few times I saw it in the theater when I was very very young. That's probably four three or four and
Then I'd seen it subsequently on home video or whatever and I remembered I
New the I knew the story. I knew the story. So here you are. You're a six -year -old kid
I remember saying to my mom one day when does the new Star Wars come out and she goes I don't know and I said
Mom, I bet it's taking so long because they're still paying the actors from the last one
You know like I remember I thought those like a hilarious joke
Anyway
When they said this thing was coming out I didn't see trailer one of this fucking thing before I got into the theater
I remember my dad telling me
We're going to a Catholic grade school today to have an interview to see if you you can go there
And he said guess what if things go well, we're gonna take it to see we're turning the Jedi tonight
He was probably gonna take me either way, but he was just getting me all worked up. Oh, you know
I just got excited here and then so over how exciting a preview was yeah
The only way you saw a preview was going to another movie. So I'm out of my mind excited. I go
Dad have you seen anything he goes I did see the preview on TV the other night
I was like what what did you see tell me anything?
Was Han Solo back what's going on? He's like they didn't show much
It's I just saw Luke and Darth Vader and an elevator which is a scene in the movie
Girl from the epinema playing yeah, yeah
We went to see this thing
Again you're six years old
You don't have any concept of Hollywood you don't have any concept of I
Wanted to be this I wanted to be that all you know is
I want to see the my favorite characters come back
Please let Han Solo be okay. He was frozen in carbonate and this thing was just a chain of dominoes for a six -year -old
One after the next I mean they they tell you in the scroll and the opening crawl like Luke has returned to his home
Planet of Tatooine to get Han Solo back from job of the Hut
So you're like oh my god, we're gonna meet job of the Hut because it's a pre -special edition right
They go into job as palace. You see fucking
Lando undercover in the palace. You see Boba fat. You're like Jesus Christ a bounty hunter brings Chewbacca in
You're like I don't even know what to do with myself right now
The bounty hunter that brings Chewbacca and goes in
The my favorite parts. Well my two favorite parts still the first one is when Jabba
When the bounty hunter goes and you don't know at this point that it's laid she goes
I'm here to bargain for solos life and Java goes. I'll never get fit rid of my favorite decoration
And he goes like this in the camera pans left and
You see Han Solo in carbonate in the wall. I was like I'm getting chills right now. I'm getting overwhelmed and I was like
Oh my god
He's there
He's okay
Right, yeah, so that that cannot happen in this day. It can't
So I don't like Star Wars and I'm excited for you as a child. This was incredible. So that all happens
She frees Han
Mm -hmm you find out she frees Han cuz she's Leia which is when you're sick
You don't see that coming you're not saying anything coming. Yeah, and it's it's playing the fucking lane
And Han music and they kiss and it's it's just you're just beyond yourself. Then
Luke comes in
Because they're all captured at this point
Luke comes in wearing the fucking dark cloak
The job of guards try to attack him. He does the Vader choke move and you're like oh my god like
Luke's like for real now like he's not the kid anymore. He's a fucking real Jedi now
He goes in confronts Jabba pulls out a blaster
Falls into the pit has to fight the rank or the whole time you're like why isn't he using the lightsaber like?
Oh my god, they take all of them out to the Sarlac pit to kill them. I might tear up
They take them off the Sarlac pit to kill them
They put Luke on the plank. You're six. Yeah, you're like my favorite human being that's ever been a movie is gonna die right now
They're gonna push him in the Sarlac pit Luke says
Jabba it's your last chance free us or die
Jabba laughs they say push him in they push Luke over the plank. He falls grabs the plank flips upside flips
It does a back flip into the air whatever lands back on the ship
The fucking lightsaber shoots out of R2T2's head. Yeah, he catches it
Unsheathes it and it's green because he lost the blue lightsaber in the last movie in a very traumatic experience for a kid to see
And you're just like I I was fucking losing my mind dude. I can't I can't put it into words. Yeah
The fact that you finally saw the emperor the fact that you show them shoot Luke's hand and it's like the robotic circuits underneath
The fact that he you he unmasks Vader at the end. I I was out of my fucking mind
Well, then how is it that you speak somewhat critically of Jedi to this time? He is now that I'm older
Yeah, I love that whole sequence to me is is infallible. Yeah, I don't like what he did in the special edition by adding the musical number to it
That bothers me, but I do like some of the other stuff he had in the special edition
He adds a couple more like sort of rank or hints and stuff that actually I think work very well
But that whole sequence to me is perfection and as a kid
You know, I loved Ewoks just like my six -year -old nephew loved Jar Jar Binks when the Phantom Menace came out
It was a thing meant for kids
And right when I got older I was like I don't like how the these little teddy bears are like making keystone cops out of the Empire
Like they're getting hit and head with rocks and shit that bothered me
I still love the redemption of Vader. I still love all the Emperor scenes Ian McClellan is as Darth Sidious is fucking incredible
Is it in McClellan?
Sorry ,emic Dermott excuse me ,emic Dermott
That's the most the nothing will ever top that you can never be in that place ever again
No, that is to you don't know what going in. Yeah, that to me is like when somebody says
Yeah, I saw the doors before Morrison died or so. It's like you don't know that that's gonna be yeah the pinnacle
But it was and it will never be trying to convey to Heather my very first movie going experience was an American tale
Mm -hmm, and I was just trying to convey to her how like it just
Overwhelming and exciting it is and my I'm probably most excited about having kids to share moves with them and take it
Yeah, I mean, that's the dream. Oh, yeah, you can kind of get excited again through them
But anyway
That was your number two. Oh, that was my number one. There's your number one. So I'm a my number one. Yeah
My number one you had two glasses of wine as far as I can tell when you told me this I knew my number one and the rest were gonna be
You know things I had to come up with but my my number one without any hesitation
Was what would unseat home alone and who framed Roger Rabbit as my number one movie of all time at the time
It's changed, but I got to say Jurassic Park. All right, so
You're 13 right there's a movie about dinosaurs where they're like
Legit actual dinosaurs back to life like that was that was one of the few movies where like even like
2020 would talk about like the special effect
I'm sure of 2020 and they'd show you the special effects and my parents were like pack. I'm watch this and I was blown away by it but
My my best friend at the time Ryan who's visiting in a couple weeks can't wait to Sam
He's like I'm reading the book me and him started reading the book and then we did it a couple times
It was the race to get the book done before the movie came out
Sure and I had so many friends in school at this time that we're all reading the book
We're like did you get to the part where this and that right and the book and the movie is not all that I mean
There there's some similarities of course. There's a lot of differences. Oh, I thought you're gonna see the opposite
I was like it's it's it's it's some but like the the movie is infinitely better than the book. Oh really Michael Keaton are
Jesus Christ Michael Crite and RIP is
Is you know, I wanted to say Michael Keaton earlier when we were talking about punchline because he was a stand -up before an actor Michael Keaton
He makes a lot of sense to me and he's I've actually seen his stand -up and it's funny. I'm sure it's fun, but
Michael Crite and
We're all these little kids trying to read this book. It's just like how all these little kids were trying to read the stand the next year
Right before the miniseries aired as I'm sure kids did with Harry Potter. Yeah, I got to get this god damn
Definitely how those book done exactly. Yeah, sure, but
You know, we're reading through dress bar. We're talking about it. We're all excited, but that was a movie where I
Remember to this day it came out June 11th, 1993. Wow, I remember it very well and
Artichets were bought the moment they went on sale the mid -roof is mall six cinema. I went to school that day I
My friends and I are I remember a teacher was like could you guys calm down like what's going on over there?
And I was like I'm sorry Mrs. Taylor
We're all going to see Jurassic Park right after school. Like it was that kind of thing. That's great like the kids
We were all so fucking excited and we went in and we're waiting at the mall. This thing that this stuff does not happen anymore
They pulled back the little
Maroon
Yeah, yeah, and before assigned seating to right to get there right and wait. Yeah, we waited for ever
Good seat and when they lifted that little lever to bring us into the theater
We pushed forward and me and Ryan are good. We'll probably talk about this when he comes out here next week
This is a grown man with kids of his own, but the crowds surged into this theater. They let us in and me and Ryan were so little
That we were pushed between two
morbidly obese people's asses and me and Ryan looked at each other and our eyes locked and we laughed hysterically because we were both off the ground
Pushed between some fat asses right and the entire way down to the theater
We were kind of like early crowdsurfing like we're 13 room
We kind of crowdsurfed our way in we sprinted in we got front and center great
And when direct draft the beginning of dress park is horrifying and I would say way scarier than we were expecting
Yeah, that crate scene is very good at the top. It's great when they lower that the
The goat or whatever and again, it is a very Indiana Jones feel. Yeah, for sure a lot of snap
Oh, yeah movements with the camera and it's a it's the mysterious crate and all that stuff
Spielberg does not I mean Spielberg directed the fucking shit out of Jurassic Park
And it started up and this you're also talking about a time when I'm 13 and it's PG 13 right so I'm newly allowed to see this movie right
But it starts up and I was fucking terrified and my parents never went out
Even though they were they were my age now, probably they didn't really go out much
So they had kids to raise and they couldn't afford a babysitter and I knew that they had bought tickets for the next night the Saturday night show
And that added an element to like my parents were excited enough to buy advanced tickets
That's how big an event this is and you also get to be the cool kid that goes home and goes you gotta see this film
Yeah, yeah, I mean I was spazin out we love that movie
So much it was incredible. I still think it's an incredible movie and
The closest I've come to that kind of excitement weirdly
Was me and some friends and Heather when we first started dating got really high
And went up to the universal city walk and saw 3d Jurassic Park five years ago when they released
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, and it was like seeing it for the first time like that's great
That that to me was the the biggest and to have that much anticipation and then have the movie be that good
That's great is that was that to me was I put your ass park above all the Star Wars
I mean, we're very different of course
But I I flipped my shit over that movie. I was I was terrified by it
It also felt adult even though it was
Kind of a family movie at the end of the day
It made me feel like an adult again. It was a nuanced popcorn film
Which we don't get to see much anymore. You don't you don't feel like anyone is trying to bring you the best product right so
That's great as you said for me. I am not a fan of Jurassic Park
The series, but I'm excited for you
Thanks, Joe. You're welcome Pat. That's our show. We're at we're almost at an hour and 20 here. So
Uh, I'm always happy to bleed into some extra time for these patreon listeners. I love me too
I love that they they give us the support. I appreciate it me too
This might be our longest episode ever that didn't was in a commentary
What was the by the way? What was really quick?
What's the word you use to describe your mood when you went into boogie nights per what
So I went to see boogie nights. Oh, I think I was I use purient
Okay, so if you have a
Perient interest in something it means you want to see people fuck this here. Here's my here's my request
Yeah, from now on in your life when you use that word
Will you say it like cat woman and put a
Perient yes, yeah, I will
I've never used it before. I'll probably never use it again, but if I do I'll say per just do a per
With a rolled our
Folks on the facebook page you know I want to see what your
Uh, experiences were what your top five would be so I remember by the way requested to join the facebook group
I don't know if I've been approved yet, but I did request now you didn't I because I would have gotten that
I requested join you know on facebook. I am on facebook. I have a fan page on facebook. I requested join
Do it today
But I did request to get in. I don't want to make it sound like I don't give a shit. I do give a shit
So I'd love to see what what yours were and I know that
This one I think more than any other topic age plays a big role
Because you're never going to be as excited as you were when you were like 1213 or our kid forgot say
Uh, yeah, let us know please folks
Thank you for your uh, your patronage
mm -hmm
Okay, and uh, see you next time. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell