I see you again.
Welcome to Will See You in Hell.
It's time to talk movies, folks.
And I'm here to do it. And so is my man,
Jotaro's in Patrick Losh. Hi, everybody.
It's me. How are you doing, Joe?
Haircut last week.
Well, I haven't seen you. So I know.
No, I know anybody else in your life, notice?
No, nobody knows that maybe.
We don't strike back like a pit viper.
When I compliment your haircut and just instead accept an embrace it.
It wasn't a strike back. It was literally me, me saying last week, isn't it sad?
The subtext there was, isn't it sad that I only see you twice a month on a zoom?
I, I wasn't awake enough to absorb that subtext.
Oh, that's all right. Absorb this.
I've got I went on a little coffee date the other day.
And this is why I should not be out there in these streets.
I go. This is why not all the other.
I parked my car. So first off, you know, coffee date, like 2 p .m.
I'm like, all right, well, there's no, there's no sex on the table.
You said one of the one of the only stand -up bets I used to do that I can still do
and remember is how no one's doing a post -lunch fuck, you know,
when in the broad daylight, I'll do it someday on the show.
It's funny. But I go, so that's off the table.
I don't have to have sex anxiety on top of everything else.
But I walk in the entire time I'm walking up to the place.
I'm like, is she going to want to fucking sit outside?
It's like 110 degrees.
Girls don't get hot like guys, you know, they're just like, oh, it's beautiful.
It's awful.
I'm walking up. It's hot, sweaty.
I go in. The guy ahead of me is getting a 64 ounce cold brew.
And I find the words coming out of my mouth just because I can't have silence on a date.
Before we've even really introduced ourselves, I order one of these 64 ounce cold brews.
Here it is, Joe. All right, look up at it. Look at it.
Oh, you're holding the key.
This is something I was holding on a date.
And the girl hands it to me and I'm like, why, even if I wanted this, why would I get it now?
I order it and the girl goes, oh, we're out of lids for a 64 ounce jug of coffee.
I go, you want to have a lid?
Who's moving more lids than jugs?
You go, sorry. We don't have any, we don't have any lids for the jugs.
Mother, judge and speed at this point, I could and should bail on the jug.
I recognize my mistake, but instead I hear the date coming up with constructive solutions.
She's like, you put a, put some plastic in the nozzle.
Then you wrap it in a saran wrap, that would have been a, I'll see you later, honey.
This ain't going to work out. I don't need jug advice.
The last thing I need is jug advice.
She hands it to me.
I can tell from step one, this thing's going to be splashing all over my car and it did.
But right now I'm drinking from it from the 64 ounce jug of cold brew.
Still no lid? Did they make good on the lid?
Like one of those gas station promos, you know, we'll mail it to you in a month or something like that.
She wrote down my full name and said, when you come in here to get a refill, I'll make sure they give you a lid.
Not, we'll give you a free refill or anything like that.
This was $30. Also $30.
What made you not just say forget it? I'll do this another time because I watched her cautiously fill the jug and I just couldn't.
It's all about being a, it's, you know what?
Let me just fill in for my therapist here and says it all goes back to my father.
You're trying to keep him from blowing up at you and screaming.
So you do everything possible to keep that from happening.
I was literally going to just say that to you. That's you. It's her dumb ass fault for filling it up and then mentioning the lid issue.
Valet, you know, and you're, you're accommodating her.
And then it's going to be that thing of like, well, I already filled it.
Yeah, well, unfill it.
The hell do you want me to do?
Yeah.
You mentioned no lids. You're fucking moron.
I've been in here 30 seconds.
Two people have bought the 64 ounce jugs. Go buy a lid.
And if you don't want to give it to me, give it to the next guy. Apparently, there's a run on jugs this morning.
A jug run, if you will.
Why is the word jug so funny?
Because it, because it means tits. It's, it's name.
That's what it is. It's, it was a slang for tits in the seventies.
It was mean big J. Oakerson laughed so hard one day about this about like the period from 1970, whatever to 1980, whatever.
Where guys, there were a million terms for tits.
Yeah.
Yeah. And it was like gazangas, the zooms, you know, jugs was in there.
It was, it's just so stupid. It's funny. It's just, it's very funny.
Now I feel like we have one word and it's breasts.
Yeah, I felt a little dirty even saying tits to be honest.
And breasts makes me think of one thing, breast cancer, baby.
Makes me think of a drawing of a woman with her left arm raised.
Cutting her breast with a very solemn face as she realizes she's found something.
That be a great wrestling heel, the breastler.
And he's obsessed with breasts.
That'd be a fun heel character.
And his big move is, is like a motorboat that makes the woman like fall into a trance.
Or he doesn't do the guy.
He motorboats the guy.
That'd be good to know.
There's a lot of stuff we could do.
And then it's, and that's his thing. His manager's got to be some lady with a 10 inch waist and like triple H.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
And then does he respect her?
Yeah, he worships her.
He worships her.
You gotta, if you're going to go that route, he's got to be respectful.
He just has to love breasts.
You know, or is it he's an animal for breasts?
And then the manager comes out and, and tames him with her like matronly breasts.
That's good.
She like puts him in.
Oh my God.
He's in a hypnotic state.
Only, you know, only miscarry can do that.
Animal look here.
No, no, don't look here.
My eyes are up here.
Look down here.
He does the reverse.
This is a gold idea.
It's not bad.
I feel like we know a lot of people in the wrestling world too that could bring this to life.
Do I play him?
And to make your work style.
If third act to my career.
Nothing would make me happier.
Oh boy, the Jesus God.
That's a good idea.
All right.
I'm pulling up my.
This is the sad thing.
Is half the two.
I was saying we only see each other.
I was saying the only time we see each other is on this god damn zoom.
Right.
And then as you said earlier, look up.
I'm looking down because half of it.
I got to.
We got to be like morning radio guys here.
Like as you talk like looking down at your phone to be like, where are my picks for the movie corner this week.
Yeah, I got a.
I mean, I'll tell you right now.
I got a Rex Reed.
You know, I'm excited to hear it.
Pulling that up.
I don't know if I'm going to do it this episode or the next one.
Which movie are we doing today?
We're doing pray.
This.
Predator prequel.
And why wouldn't they call it pray, Colin, a predator prequel, get that amazing alliteration going on.
You're right.
We're.
And people know what the fuck it is.
Why not call it predator.
Predator.
Yes.
I just watched the teaser.
I think I'd have a lot of great stuff to talk about once I watched it for Hellraiser.
Wait.
Coming to.
Coming to Hulu October 7th.
The trailers out.
I didn't know.
The teaser.
Well, that's what I'm getting to.
It's it.
Here's the teaser.
Over a faint grainy image of pinhead.
The word Hellraiser goes across the screen left to right.
There's no footage.
There's no information of any kind.
It's 15 seconds long.
And it says premiering October 7th as part of.
Hulu ween.
Hulu ween's not bad.
I can't.
No, it's not.
It's better than Netflix.
Ween.
That's for sure.
That's any Netflix film featuring a man's lip penis.
I think that.
These it's it's along those lines.
Well, I got two things to say here before before I get too far away from it.
And then I want to speak to the net the Hellraiser thing.
Have you heard the title of this knives out sequel?
I wrote it down.
Now ready for this?
Yeah.
Glass onion calling a knives out mystery.
Oh no.
You can't make the second one a knives out mystery.
It's they're talking like this.
It's like Marvel Universe.
It's ridiculous.
It's not it's not Agatha Christie yet because you had one mystery.
Does anyone even know the detectives name in the movie?
I hope it's Charlie knives, but I don't remember what it is.
It's not it's like it's like it's like master.
You know, you need to know the detectives name before you can call it a knives out mystery.
But also like a brown gets that treatment glass onion.
Which is a Beatles reference.
It's like what that's a terrible title.
I don't give a shit if the thing centers around the glass onion.
It's a bad fucking title.
Well, it must set her around a glass onion.
Or are they saying you keep peeling it and peeling it and it.
It makes you cry or it.
You know, I don't hate it.
Should I know?
But yeah, it's a Beatles song and maybe the worst Beatles song.
It does that thing that Bowie did later where you reference yourself.
Where John let it's like.
And everybody saying that the walrus was Paul.
You're like, no, no, I don't want to hear you guys sing about your legend while you're still making music.
I know you'll disagree.
They suck.
And no, I disagree.
I agree.
It's just a stupid thing to say.
They suck.
They could write a decent song whether they suck.
Yeah, no, they could write about 500 decent songs.
I guess so.
Yeah, they're good.
You don't like when people like things and it angers you.
And everybody needs their blanket brown.
That's my Beatles impression needs their blanket brown.
Yeah, they would always say some stupid phrase like that.
And you're supposed to go.
Oh, they're talking about acid.
Oh, shut up.
Suck my dick, John Lennon.
I'll grant you suck my dick, John Lennon.
But everybody needs their blanket brown.
That's just a bizarre assessment of many years of classics.
Well, I'm listening to the remaster of McCartney too.
Yeah.
And I'll say it.
And now I.
I'm saying this is my opinion.
I know that it's not true.
A truth.
The.
That's growth.
The Beatles have never made a song I found as intriguing as temporary secretary ever.
I find Paul McCartney cranks out stuff that I think is far more interesting and odd and.
And unique and.
You know, that's, that's just my take off.
But all that stuff.
That style of music is not for me.
I respect the hell out of what they did.
I respect the shit out of the beach boys.
I don't like listening to it though.
I hear that.
I prefer McCartney to Lennon as well.
I think he's clearly the genius of the group.
Not the John Lennon's a slouch.
I just think, you know, I don't always follow him down the past.
He goes down.
And he's a total hypocrite like many, many people in the history of music and film.
But I'm a fan.
I'll be a fan till I die.
I got.
Before movie core.
Real quick.
You see the black and white picture that dropped on Twitter of it was on the side of a pool.
John Lennon and Paul McCartney and they each have a woman leg spread lying on her back to the inside of the pool and their face down in her.
They each have their own.
Yeah.
But Lennon and McCartney, the public pool, like broad daylight, each going down on a young fan.
Are they, is it like a joke picture?
Like, let's make it look like we're having oral sex.
That's a good, you know, I guess we'll never know, but my thinking is at the time they could have found a few willing participants to pose in the photo.
Oh, no, that I'm sure of.
I just mean like, are they actually doing oral sex?
I believe so.
I believe that.
Okay.
Have you heard that movie pass is relaunching?
My sister sent me that.
I mean, I fuck you movie pass.
I agree.
I was like, you're, you're Trump at this point.
You know, you should be in jail and instead of just laying low, you're rubbing your dick and balls and people's faces.
And I don't understand it.
Yeah.
We're not, it's not our job to help save you from like the pits of double bankruptcy or wherever movie pass has found themselves.
But I did for a year try to tell everyone on my life to do it and nobody would, but I enjoyed a lot of free movies during that year.
I mean, it's now that everybody, well, I guess the beauty of movie pass was they could do.
You could do any theater.
Oh, yeah.
There's got to be right now.
I'm not taking movie pass.
Gotta be.
I'm regulated to regal.
But I like regal quite a bit.
What's regal's plan?
Is it better than stubs?
Damn, stubs is another one that we've talked about.
It's just a weird word.
I don't know.
It's 20 bucks a month and it's unlimited.
Unlimited everything, no matter how many times you want to go any movie, nothing's off limits.
I'm surrounded by AMCs.
So I do a stubs.
But I don't.
I can't make it to the ends of things anymore.
Yeah, it's tough.
I got to.
I got to regal two blocks from my apartment.
And it's the nicest movie theater in all of New York.
It's a beautiful state of the art brand new theater.
And of course, it's not in any way run properly or whatever or.
Yeah, people talking the whole time.
Yeah, of course.
But hey, what are you going to do?
Can't have it all.
The what worries me about my current lack of interest in like finishing even a TV show or anything, forget a book those days are gone.
But Tony soprano says early on in the sopranos.
Because the other day, I'm watching seven.
I don't give a fuck who the killer is.
I just turned it off.
I'll never know.
And then she's like, that's a huge sign of depression.
Is it.
I mean, according to a trained therapist on the show, the soprano TV show, they did their reason.
I mean, that makes sense to me.
If you're watching seven and an hour and a half and you don't care who did it, that seems to me like somebody who's lost interest in life.
Maybe you just don't like the movie.
No, that's definitely part of it.
I did watch one day.
I bought a bunch of new stuff on Amazon and watched all the new releases and you know, yeah, there's stuff out there that's okay.
I guess.
I will.
Well, you know what?
Speaking to that.
Can I lead us into the movie corner because I want to address something.
Please.
And it's a movie I couldn't finish.
And I tried.
And so you can call this an unfair review.
But I tried.
I really tried.
I was excited to watch this movie.
It's a criterion collection.
Yeah.
It's critically acclaimed.
It stars people I have great admiration for.
It's written and directed by a person I have great admiration for.
And the movie sucks.
It's called Mikey and Nikki.
And people said this is a gangster classic.
You've got to see it.
It is the most boring.
Fucking who gives a shit.
What happens to this cast of Eddie's character?
He's awful.
I hope something bad happens to him.
Why is Peter fork tending to him?
Because they're friends, Joe.
They're best friends.
None of that comes.
Probably ask why I'm tending to you.
None of that comes through in the picture.
This is a masturbatory.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, what's his name?
This is like a bad Sam Shepherd play this thing.
It's like two characters.
In a gross environment.
And I don't give a shit at all.
The only thing I cared about with by the time they get to that apartment with the woman.
And Cassavetes is just kind of being gross.
And you're just, I'm just like.
I don't want to watch this.
Like I'm just.
What am I.
Now you could make the argument.
That well, why would you want to watch good fellows?
Or why would you want to watch the Irishman?
Or why would you want to watch any of these gangster movies that you love so much?
Those people are all despicable.
I agree.
I don't know why there's an element to the other successful gangsters is the difference there.
I would say there's, there's, there are movies about small time gangster.
Rounders is a great example of a guy, you know, of a small time guy that's involved in gangland in his own way.
Yeah, that's a good movie.
There's just nothing exciting or intriguing about this film.
I don't care if he dies or not.
You're pretty, I don't know if he doesn't finish it, but you're pretty sure he's going to.
If he doesn't, I don't care.
What am, what is my takeaway here?
I just don't understand what the hook of the movie is.
It felt like that movie.
It reminded me 100%.
It reminded me 100 % of that shitty movie that Tim Heidecker did where he was like the hipster piece of shit waiting for his dad to die.
And I'm sitting there watching it and I'm just going, I don't understand what I'm supposed to sink my teeth into here.
I don't care about any of this.
Was that, what was that the comedian?
I think so.
So I mean, I, that's a kind of movie that I like is just a character study of somebody with shitty behavior.
I always will like it.
Always have.
Sure.
Just my thing.
I like Mikey and Nikki.
I think it's pretty overrated.
I think that as a study of how shitty men can be husbands is a much better movie with fuck and Gizarre and gas of that.
I've never seen a Lane May which is very strange that a Lane May kind of the Tina Fey of her day was was writing and directing this movie.
They try to take it away from her many times which always gives a movie like a bit more cred than it may deserve.
But I like Mikey and Nikki quite a bit just because of the chemistry of the leads and as a study of male friends.
I dug it.
I'm a huge Lane May fan.
I'm a huge cast of Eddie's fan.
I'm a huge Peter Falk fan which also speaks to the crime it is that I still haven't seen husbands.
But I know this much about husbands.
There's there's a catalyst in husbands.
Yeah.
There's there's a mission no matter how dark it is.
And there's a commentary to husbands that I just don't think this movie has.
It's these guys yet this is a lot like that movie gridlocked with two with two pocket Tim Roth where they played the they played the junkies that are desperately trying to click and every clinic is closed through the entire movie.
It's not a bad movie.
It's not a great movie.
It's just this thing where but but even with that there's a desperation to that that I do not feel here.
They don't elaborate enough in my opinion in this movie on the danger that cast of Eddie's is facing.
Yeah.
There's no element of that at least in gridlocked.
I see them going to clinics getting chewed out by guys that are saying fuck you.
Oh, the world is supposed to bow down because you decided to kick today.
Get out of here.
I don't want to hear your sob story whatever.
There's something that I see them moving against.
And then that builds and builds and builds as there's a reveal that Tim Roth actually is HIV positive and all these other things.
This movie I felt like didn't have it.
The threat is played by Ned Beatty.
There couldn't be a less threatening man on planet earth than Ned Beatty.
I love Ned Beatty, but not in the role of let's see toy story three.
Not in the role of a menacing.
Met Ned Beatty.
I'm watching this thing.
I go.
Here's a guy.
Just seems like you know, he seems like every uncle everybody ever had.
God, what a sweet guy.
I bet he got.
I bet he was a family man.
I love this.
I look him up married five times.
Oh, wow.
This guy was blowing through it.
Yeah.
Honestly good for him.
Always loving that, Betty.
Anyway, that's Mikey and Nikki.
I'm going to be hard to be out there on the scene in Hollywood when you're when you're most notable scene is getting raped by hillbillies while squealing like a pig.
That's not easy.
Yeah.
And did you know he's not related to?
I did know.
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
I got to switch cameras here because my camera is about to die on this side for some reason.
Oh.
You know one of the oddest Hollywood facts that I feel like nobody.
I bet it would blow the minds of kids if I posted it on Twitter today if they knew who these people were.
Surely McClellan and Warren Beatty brother and sister.
Do you know that?
Yeah.
What?
That's wild.
And like nobody really talks about it, which is very strange.
Surely McClellan was real saucy in our day and then.
Oh, yeah, I always like sure.
I like to wrap the terms of a deerman.
I would have thrown it in there.
Yeah, I agree.
Anyway, what do you got?
I got Dave Cronenberg's crimes of the future.
Now, pet, I am.
I want to see this movie.
I didn't know it was out.
Oh, okay.
If you want to.
If you think it's worth saving.
I'll do it with you.
Yeah, especially.
We have how polarizing it is.
All right.
Great.
We've said this before and not done it, but I hope we can.
I forgot about it, to be honest, but I'm writing it down.
Sorry.
I.
Sure.
You know, when I rewatched the other night with a friend who hadn't seen it midnight run.
Bobby, to narrow, chuck, crowed.
Now, there's a buddy move before you with steaks with action with heart.
It's really got everything.
It's it is now hailed as kind of the lost classic that it is.
And I know they were talking about doing that sequel, which thank God they didn't get to.
Honestly, thank God they didn't get to.
I would I would have liked to have seen Grotin and the Nero.
I mean, to be real with you, Grotin's looking like he's got a to pay on in this.
You know, who I would have hated to see his wax melting face up there.
With the Nero trying to work up some chemistry, you know, I don't know, but.
Midnight run itself is the Nero when he's dipping his toe in comedy.
So he I mean, he plays it with zero mugging.
He plays it like it's a Scorsese movie is so funny in it.
But he's only as funny as a scene partner and him reacting to Charles Grotin is just a dream.
Grotin is so he's just playing himself, but he's so committed to this character.
After any scene if your eye goes to Grotin, you will find a bonus laugh.
Every time the Nero is arguing with somebody at a counter, which is a lot of the movie.
If you watch Grotin, he's always looking at the person behind the counter rolling his eyes.
Like, can you believe this guy? I have to deal with.
Just amazing chemistry, the story.
It's like when Joe and I watched honeymoon in Vegas, 20 minutes in, you click pause.
You know, everything that's happening, it's complicated.
But it's very, very clear.
You got Joey Pants destroying in an early role with a insane comb over.
They got him wearing like kimonos and sport coats after the movie.
Soundtrack by a Danny Elfman is just a top tier film.
And as far as buddy movies go.
You know, you can really only compare it to like a plane's train.
And these movies came out not even a year apart from each other.
They used to know how to make a buddy picture.
Now it's always, you know, we've got the rock.
And we've got John Cena and their brothers.
But they got a fight.
Chris Hemsworth, you know, it's just fucking sad.
This movie, you spend some time with the villains you're laughing your ass off.
Dennis Farina.
He's so good at it. He's so good at it.
Farina.
It's just a movie with people telling other people to shut the fuck up or they will kill them.
Is most of the dialogue in the movie.
And it's great.
Farina talking to his lawyer.
Throughout the movie.
Bill Baker Hall.
Yeah.
It's just Murray.
Right.
That fucking look off your face.
I'll bury this fucking phone right in your head.
Yeah.
So he's so funny in it.
Um,
Joe Pat the only own.
Just Joey pants.
Just playing.
Nobody plays a worm like Joey pants.
Nobody.
He's turning everybody against each other.
Yafat Kato.
Yes.
Growing.
What a weird presence.
Yafat Kato is.
I love that guy.
And then the highlight of the film outside of course.
Uh,
De Niro and Roden is,
is the great.
What's this face?
The other guy.
Walls.
Beverly Hills Club.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
John Ashton.
Just.
De Niro plays Walsh, which I love.
He steals the show man.
He's great.
That scene where he's got the.
He continues to know that.
don't reason it's not just the design of the,
the.
Uh,
Purple handcuffs to the radiator.
Yeah.
An actions on the bed eating.
Two cheeseburgers.
With.
Two huge things of fries.
Smoking while he's eating.
Yeah.
And the guy goes.
Can I just have a fry?
Yeah, I already said no pecker breath as if he's doesn't have enough. He would be just won't share it. So funny, man.
Great.
When Grodin goes in and he's doing the litmus test to steal all the twenties. That's just a classic scene.
He walks in and he's like, what is the name of this establishment?
Reds corner bar.
Are you red? Yes, I am.
Do you dye your hair?
No. Then Grodin stares at him for like 20 seconds.
Trying to piece together why you would be called red with brown hair.
Just amazing little bits like that scattered throughout the whole movie.
Yeah, it's awesome.
It's it is. It really is. It's one of the greats.
Speaking of buddy movies, my next one.
One is, and I can't, well, this is actually my last one, and then I'll do a scary stuff after your third one, but.
I put this movie on because I was in a mood. I was like, I just want to put something brainless on.
I'll probably hate this and then like like it because I hate it so much.
I put on uncharted, starring Tom Holland and Mark Wahlberg.
Maybe you don't even know where I'm going with this.
It looks like shit.
That's what I thought.
That's what I loved it.
I'm a big fan of the video games.
And I thought it was miscast.
I thought Nathan Phillion should have played the main role.
I thought there was a fan film made of uncharted, starting Nathan Phillion and the guy from.
DMV.
What's his face? The guy from Avatar.
Steven Lang.
Yeah.
And no good today with the names.
I'm like, like I used to be.
Maybe I'm coming out of a bunk.
They're, they're perfectly cast.
And when I saw the casting of this, I thought that's, this is not good.
Yeah.
And like I said, I put it on to just sort of hate watch it because I was in a real mood.
Ended up loving it.
Twist and turns.
Super fun action movie.
Super fun popcorn action movie.
Hadn't seen anything like this in a long time.
Mark Wahlberg is hilarious in it, which surprised the shit out of me.
Tom Holland doing crazy, like Jackie Chan level stunts in this thing.
It's just great.
It's just a great fun.
Indiana Jones ask action adventure movie.
That's it.
It's a family action adventure movie.
And the one where I saw a clip of him driving a motorcycle off a cliff and onto the wing of a plane.
No, I believe that's mission impossible.
Now it was, it was Marky Mark.
It was his latest.
Now I drop in three movies a year that no one knows.
I don't think you that was in this.
I don't remember that scene.
And Mark Wahlberg doesn't play the, he plays the mentor like older thief.
Yeah, he doesn't get his hands too dirty with that stuff.
It's more Tom Holland, which is how the game is.
But that's, that's really all I can say.
Like if you want to just turn on a fun.
Like popcorn movie.
And by the way, for when it came out early 2022, like so many movies did.
That were so affected by the pandemic.
It feels like a complete goddamn movie.
It doesn't feel like something happened.
And then they had to finish it somehow on the fly.
Yeah, it's, it's a full movie.
And then there's a teaser for a sequel at the end.
There's a, you know, post -credits scene or mid -credits scene.
And it just felt like the games.
It felt like it got all the good parts of the games down.
The games are very fun and funny and adventurous.
And, and, and you know, I just really liked it.
I, I just enjoyed it.
Like it was, you know, it's not going to change your life.
But I haven't seen a studio movie like this in a while that I felt delivered on all fronts.
For what a studio movie is supposed to do.
Also, it felt like the characters were real people that had their own personalities.
Everybody wasn't just, you know, Tony Stark.
Yeah, with a million quips and whatever.
It was like there, these people had goals and different interests.
And there was heart and it just worked.
All right, fair enough, Joe.
All I got.
Um, I watched an old classic from 1986 that I had never seen.
Called Cobra.
Oh, boy.
I hear it's not very good.
Starring Sylvester Stallone as Lieutenant Marion Cobretty.
Wow.
He wrote this.
Why would you name your character Marion when you're playing one of the toughest badasses in the game?
That's, that's why, right?
Like, isn't that the whole, don't you think that's the point?
I'm going to give him an effeminate name.
I guess so.
Nobody really talks about it that I can recall.
Stallone's partner in the film.
And I'm not kidding here.
Is played by Renny Santoni, who you might know as Seinfeld's poppy.
As in poppy peed on my couch.
As in poppy didn't wash his hands.
And now he's making me dare.
Isn't he also the partner in dirty Harry?
Yes, I think he is.
Yes.
Well, this movie is, according to reading about it, very much still owns attempt at kicking off a dirty Harry style.
Franchise.
It did very well, monetarily, but the sequel never came out.
And it's got to be because the cobra character is absolutely pathetic.
It's a guy who even more than Stallone normally does speaks in like grunts and sentence fragments.
It has the line that I thought was just the tagline and not actually in the film, but where he says,
you're the disease and I'm the cure to a guy who's trying to kill him.
You know, it's stupid.
And yet it's 80 something minutes.
It's the only time I've seen Stallone in like a horror slasher setting.
There's a lot of like slasher style kills.
And you're thinking 86.
This is around the Friday the 13th days, the nightmare days.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
And I also love that in the dirty Harry films when they would kind of acknowledge what was going on in the, you know, like.
There were horror elements to some of those dirty Harry movies in the scenes where the killer is doing his, his bidding.
So cobra in that regard is cheesy.
It's 80s.
It's directed by George P. Cosmatos, whose son went on to direct Mandy.
And Cosmatos also did like tombstone and etc.
But he's a guy who got kicked off a lot of movies and is kind of known as being not great.
It's strange.
It's strange if I may interject it's strange that a guy that made such renowned films like Tombstone.
Also made this because this is really heralded as as one of Stallone's worst, which is saying a lot.
Well, Cosmatos was apparently so bad on tombstone that Kurt Russell directed it, but wouldn't take credit.
Kurt Russell is the only movie ever directed.
He had to step up and be like, you can't do this and I have a vision for this movie and I'm going to finish it.
I'm not going to get you in trouble.
You can stick around, but I'm directing it.
So apparently this guy is not the best.
But he does much like his son have a way with creating just like cheesy, violent 80s visuals.
And there was an x -rated cut of this movie.
Apparently it was so violent at one point.
That's the cut I kind of wanted to see because to me, it felt like it was sort of holding back.
But this is Stallone and his coked out.
I can do no wrong phase.
His, him writing this movie after writing Rocky is just absurd.
Something he wrote in an afternoon, clearly.
But I've seen worse movies by Stallone.
I had a decent time with Cobra.
I just typed it into Amazon and I'm going to maybe, I'm going to see if there's an x -rated blue ray out there somewhere.
I doubt it.
But.
Yeah, Pinkstone always.
Excuse me. Sorry, get a little.
Got a little gas in the throat from coffee.
Pinkstone always talks about the scene.
He thinks it's very funny to see him were Stallone rips the guy's shirt open.
He says smart enough or whatever.
He always talks to me about that scene.
And he said it's the only good scene.
I don't know if he said it that way, but he seems to allude to that being the only.
Park that he found entertaining.
There's now, did you watch this pad on what I'm looking at here?
The seven films Stallone collection.
That I believe I found on your shelf and made fun of you for.
Yes, well, no, I think it's less than that, but it's got assassins, which I've never seen.
It's got the specialist, which I've never seen.
Here's the seven movies ready?
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
Listen to this.
Grudge match.
Never seen.
No, I saw it with the nero.
Not a bad movie.
It's, it's, it's a good.
That's why we talked about it on the show.
It was one to take your parents to see.
Yeah, it was solid.
But still, you don't need to.
Isn't Kevin Hart in Grudge match?
Yeah, yeah.
Grudge match.
So, Grudge match.
Who cares?
The specialist.
Cream.
Good movie.
But it's out of place in this box that you want to create as part of a rocky set or something.
I mean, demolition man, bad movie.
That's in my set.
I don't think bad.
I think a lot of great stuff in it.
Overall, not great.
I think the commentary is amazing.
I think the movie is bad.
Who does the commentary?
I don't know.
No, I just mean the, the, the commentary of the film itself is brilliant.
Cobra, bad movie assassins, bad movie cares.
And then tango and cash.
So really.
Yeah, I only have a five film set for 20 bucks.
Well, I got news for you.
The seven film is now worth $63.
I'm looking at it now myself.
God, do you like tango and cash?
I've never seen it.
Believe it or not.
Tango cash is a blast.
The villainy Jack Polans.
And it's got, there's a certain period of nudity that to me.
I don't know if it's either the best nudity ever.
Or it's that I was nine years old and had not seen boobs.
Probably the latter.
But I remember some nudity in this thing that just.
You got Terry Hatcher in there.
If I recall correctly.
Love it.
Also, is this worth.
That's the 80s in a nutshell.
New female nudity in a male prison movie.
They, they were like, we gotta get a naked girl in here.
Really?
Because it's all set in a men's prison.
Now we'll figure something out.
Is this worth ten bucks?
Cobra.
Why don't you get one of these five packs to loans and make it worth your while?
Because I don't want those other movies on my shelf.
You're not going to want Cobra either.
I assure you.
Well, that's what I'm asking.
Okay.
So that's a no.
Cobra to me.
What, what, what this director's son did in my opinion.
And I think it's obvious.
I don't think this is a stretch of a theory.
I think he said.
I'm going to make the movies that you thought you were going to get when you rented Cobra.
Yeah.
When you look at the box art and you, you have a vision in your head.
From the video store from the 80s.
I'm going to actually make that movie.
And that seems to be what he does.
I agree.
I doubt he said that to his father.
I'm trying to correct your mistakes.
But yeah, that seems to be what he did.
The exact opposite, if you will, of a max landess.
Who took everything his father did and made it shitty.
And then also assaulted a bunch of women.
And still walks the streets.
Yes, but it doesn't work.
So now that's.
I, I, I.
My last thing is a scary stuff and it's connected to Uncharted.
The Uncharted collection.
Do yourself a favor.
If you like video games and you like Uncharted.
This collection, it's the first three games that came out on PS3 all remastered.
For HD, whatever you want to call it.
You can, if you have PlayStation now, it's, it's a free download as part of your subscription.
And if you don't, it's $17 to buy this thing at GameStop or Amazon or wherever brand new.
It's well, well, well worth it.
The amount of content you're getting for this price is insane.
Most people who are game enthusiasts of modern systems have probably already played these.
But I'd say with the remastered, they're worse, they're worth a revisit if you haven't gone back.
They hold up.
They're still fun.
Little tedious considering, you know, advances games have made in recent years.
But that said, they're fantastic.
And I highly recommend it.
And you'll get, you'll get a lot of bang for your buck.
Very well.
And my final is a picture called, I love my dad, which is hard for me to even say.
But this is not the Louis K movie.
This is a, this is a, I love you daddy.
Okay.
I love my dad is another film starring a comedian, Mr. Pat Nas Walt, who is, is of course a hilarious comedian.
But I really like him as an actor.
And I find that he differentiates really well between his performances too.
I like big fan a lot.
He generally plays losers.
But I like that.
I like young adult a lot.
I like that he finds time to act in between his obligation of being in every documentary ever made.
That's true.
In the last two years.
And then people forget he's the voice on the Goldbergs.
He's the Daniel Stern, like just he's got so many revenue streams.
I'm jealous of it.
Scott.
The house I need.
Yeah.
One throw away gig that takes him two hours in a week.
Text him and ask him.
Text him and ask him about what that socialism to kick in.
Say, Pat, and I haven't talked to you in a while.
I know, but I'm wondering if you could buy me a nice mid -level house in upstate New York.
See what he says.
It's all I'm asking for you.
Cocksucker.
I won't sign it off like that.
Anyway, go ahead.
Sorry.
I love my dad is starring an actor who is new to me named James Morecini.
James Morecini also wrote and directed the film.
That's the kind of thing that always makes me angry and jealous because I know that I could do it.
But I just don't, you know, I always admire the gumption.
But he's a likable enough kid.
He seems like he's 30 years old or something.
And he's claimed that this is a true story.
And I'm sure it's true up to a point.
But basically it's a guy who has a various strange relationship with his father played by Pat and Oswald.
You get the idea that the Oswald character is a shitty and irresponsible dad and a liar.
But at his core, not a bad person.
Kind of a pathological liar type.
And I think that's the way to go with this is by making him sort of a lovable prick.
What he does eventually is blocks his father on social media because his dad is estranged and is, you know, divorced from his mother and so forth.
So that's his only way of connecting with him and eventually the kids like it's enough and blocks his dad.
Pat and Oswald goes to talk to a friend at work played by the other guy who takes every other job in comedy, little Rell, how are you?
A friend who passed on my.
Like, well, you do it everything.
Why?
Yeah, does do everything.
But, you know, sometimes they do everything if the money's right.
He tells him like, look, he's funny in the movie, little Rell.
He's basically the guy telling him what you're doing is crazy.
But eventually, Pat and Oswald decides to catfish his own son.
He creates a profile of a very attractive young woman and starting disturbing.
He starts talking to his son as this woman and they do a really nice job of making it seem organic that this could happen, but eventually goes off the rails.
When it goes off the rails, it starts to lose steam because you're just kind of like, alright, it's one of those like, it's a reason that sitcoms are 22 minutes.
Because if they were longer at some point, you'd go just tell him, just tell him like the audience will buy the tension of not telling somebody something for about 20 minutes.
90 minutes, you start to lose interest a little bit, but the movie gets some big laughs out of stuff like he has this girl.
She's not just on paper. She's existing and talking to him.
But then when he goes to make out with her, they cut to this kid making out with his dad, Pat and Oswald and this kid like making out.
These are some weird choices that the movie begs.
I don't care for any of this that I'm hearing, but it goes into some kind of gross out late 90s directions here and there.
Oswald is dating Rachel Dratch who plays like a very sexually open woman and like very demanding.
She always wants to do like fantasy shit with him and he's like, why don't we just have normal sex?
And she goes, because you're not good at it is girlfriend.
You know, there's a lot of weirdness around the edges that I like.
It's not a perfect movie by any means, but it reminded me of like a spanking the monkey or one of those late 90s.
It's disturbing indie comedies and it works, you know, it's pretty fun, pretty funny.
Okay.
That brings us to pray a predator, prequel.
Yes.
Now, what do you think of my idea for a sequel to this where it's called eat, pray, love, but PREY and we combine the two universes.
I love it.
I saw on letterboxed two really funny reviews.
The first, for some reason I've run into Sean O 'Connor 10 times in the last week after not seeing him in five years.
Right.
But Sean O 'Connor had a comment that made me laugh out loud on pray.
That comment is me at a dinner party discussing American history.
You know who was even worse than the early settlers, a predator.
That really made me laugh.
That's very funny.
And then my buddy, Demi.
One of the funniest people on earth says this one.
I mean, I, I was laughing for five minutes about this.
My only nitpick is that I thought it was crazy when she said, this predator is going down like Michael Douglas do.
I didn't even know there was a command she word for Michael.
That's very.
I love that.
That guy is so funny.
Yeah.
Anyway, second sentence really sells it over the fence.
It does.
Everyone that I have talked to has said, you see this pray thing?
Everybody says it's fantastic.
It's the, maybe the best predator movie there is.
This thing sucks every single person I've talked to says this.
I think, well, here's what I would say.
I think it was a good movie.
I liked it.
Overall, I've got some qualms that I'll point out in the review.
Overall, I liked it.
And as far as predator sequels go, this thing was a goddamn masterpiece.
I mean, my God.
Now I have gone back and rewatched some predator sequels since I watched pray.
Yeah.
I tried yet again with predator two, which should be awesome.
Predatority should be awesome.
It just sucks.
I don't want to waste any time.
Beauty and Glover, right?
You got Glover.
You got picture issue.
You got Paxton for Christ's sakes.
The movie sucks.
It just sucks.
But Glover and and bucy.
And let's be honest, Paxton, you're dealing with second or third banana.
You are not dealing with leads.
The movie is lacking a lead.
It's Glover could have easily carried predator two, I think.
It's just, it's, it's not the acting that the problem.
And it's not the setting.
The setting of, of, of near future apocalyptic Los Angeles is very cool.
Yeah.
It's like a Robocop two setting.
And this predator two should have been death wish three.
It should have been Robocop two.
It should have been one of these heightened hyper reality sequels.
That's kind of nuts and not as good as the original but like wild and whatever.
And they just blow it at every turn.
There's too many character.
It's a bad fucking movie.
Period.
That's all there is to it.
Alien versus predator, which is not ever considered a true sequel.
It's not a real sequel.
In my opinion, a fun enough popcorn Sunday afternoon movie.
It's as good as the thing prequel or something like that.
But I also understand why people don't like it.
It's also PG 13, which is a strike against it.
Is it?
Yeah.
Alien versus predator requiem is complete dog shit.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
The predator is unwatchably bad.
The predator is horrible.
You don't even want to stick in to be like, is this going to take a turn with this Danny Glover.
It's so bad you turn it.
It's just horrible and crazy that Shane black that it who gave us.
You know, so many great action.
Yeah.
And then there's this.
You skipped predators, right?
With eight.
I'm going to circle back.
Okay.
And.
And I'll cite the scene in the predator that made me turn it off, which is the scene where the rag tag bunch of mercenaries is on the bus.
And the leader is going around the bus.
The rag tag group featuring, of course.
The third man that will take every job in cinematic history, Keegan Michael key.
Yeah.
Please remind me to tell you two stories once we wrap about Keegan Michael key.
Continue.
Okay.
He goes around the bus telling every the new guy everybody's nickname and he's going.
That's Joker.
He's got a smart ally line for him.
What is this episode of the golden girls?
This is terrible.
So.
Yeah.
I shut it off on an airplane for Christ's sake.
I walked out folks on an airplane.
On the special for.
On the special that Kevin James and Ray Romano did where they do the golf tour that like the doc you think they don't age for you.
Kevin James makes that to the people that paid to like stand up close to them as they golf.
Uh huh.
Which is very funny.
He goes folks.
They showed moose port on my flight.
Three people walk out.
I mean imagine the sack on Kevin James to criticize another man still.
It's because Romano takes a shot at him first.
Okay.
Yeah.
And he comes back.
But it's it's just strikes me as extra funny because moose port is such a funny fucking name.
Welcome to boost port.
Yeah.
Gene Hackman's last or one of the last.
It though in the last.
That's what he ended it on anyway.
And then predators.
People like that.
I don't think I saw it.
It's a solid sequel.
It's not going to again not going to change your life better than any of the other ones I've mentioned.
Yeah.
A little miscast by having Adrian Brody in the in the driver's seat as the as the sort of action star.
But that's kind of the thing that's also not a problem for for the reason that prey works.
And this is again to to to cite our friend Jim pigstone.
He he pointed out to me.
I said.
When the trailer for prey came out, I said, give me a fucking break.
The biggest.
Action stars in history in the first predator movie got wiped out by this thing, including almost Schwarzenegger.
I'm supposed to believe that like a 16 year old.
A command she woman.
And I don't mean who I don't mean it like that.
I just mean like she's not Schwarzenegger in the strength department.
You know what I mean?
She's not predator size.
Yeah.
Well now like a kid is supposed to beat this thing.
And he said.
And he's right.
He goes Schwarzenegger.
But that's the point.
Schwarzenegger doesn't beat it with his strength.
He beats it with his brain.
And that's that's the.
And I was like, oh, you're right.
You're that's a great insight.
And then.
Because the Schwarzenegger beat it with his brain.
That should make it much easier for anyone else.
Yes.
I agree.
And that is kind of.
But that's the thing.
That all of these sequels, including prey are, are, is lacking.
What's so brilliant.
And you know, you know how strongly I feel about predator.
What's so brilliant about predator is.
They give you this lineup of the baddest dudes on planet earth.
They establish how tough skin they are in that two minute thing on the, on the helicopter.
You know who you're dealing with.
Even the way they shake hands is, is intimidating.
Yeah.
And then.
There's a sequence of them doing the rescue mission.
That goes on for like six or seven minutes.
And they lay fucking waste to these gorilla soldiers or whatever they are.
And it sets up immediately.
These guys are not to be fucked with whatever.
And then as soon as that ends.
This unseen alien source, you don't know what it is yet.
I saw predator not knowing what it was going to be.
Right.
So if you watch it like that, the reveal that it's this, you're like, what the fuck?
You know, that's cool.
But this thing starts wiping them out.
And it's, it makes very clear immediately.
Your muscle does not matter here.
Your guns mean nothing.
And it's awesome.
Yeah.
You know, pray does a good job of, of, of firing across the message of.
It's not about strength.
It's not about guns.
It's about wits and being the better hunter, which I really like.
I just wish.
I guess it sort of does have a bit of a twist of that when it shows you how they.
The difference between hunting like the lion versus hunting the predator.
Right.
But.
You know, one of my main criticisms with this.
And again, I really liked it.
Was they, first of all, they reveal the predator too early.
They, this is shot and delivered in a way that you know what predator is already.
Now, you've gone far enough to rename the franchise.
Reintroduce it.
Yeah.
Make it so I could watch this without knowing predator and immediately just be like.
What's going on here?
And I think they show you the predator way too early.
Well, it was, this was apparently like the biggest movie in Hulu history.
And they're kicking themselves because they're not able to monetize it because they didn't release it in theaters.
Right.
Which was very stupid because it is the actual, it is theater worthy.
It's, it's well done.
It is.
And much more so than a lot of other shit that these streamers throw out of this.
But.
Yeah, I'll agree with you there.
See, I had watched predator, I've seen predator many, many times.
But I also watched it in 3D.
I always talk up the virtues of 3D even though they don't make it anymore for the home because on my TV, it's better than the theater.
I really love watching a 3D movie.
But predator works perfect because it's already almost 3D when you first see it and it's in its half invisible setting.
When they drop the predator off from the spaceship here, it almost appears 3D.
It's almost separate from the image.
And again, when you, I'm just a little side rant.
When you release something to Hulu, you know you're never going to get a 3D version.
You're never going to get really a quality blue ray version.
That's the problem with these streamers.
It's like it's just there and also they can remove it at any time.
I think at some point, physical media will have to make a comeback or we're just going to start losing film history.
The more directors who go to the streamers to make their movies.
Anyway, pray.
Look, there's a trend I'm enjoying and it's a trend that the studios hopefully are finally realizing can save you literally 20 to 50 million dollars.
Make your movie under 90 minutes.
If you make a 90 minute movie, it's automatically 25 % cheaper than a two hour movie.
So do it because that's why I could finish pray.
It's a simple story very simply told.
Whereas the new predator that you mentioned was trying to reinvent the wheel.
This setting it in like last the Mohicans times.
Was it was a good move?
It changes the setting it freshens things up a bit.
Having a young girl battle him felt good and not like the women are getting their turn at the predator which could, you know, could could have been the way this win.
I agree.
The only thing.
Let me just say one thing.
The only thing I didn't like with the with the portrayal of the female protagonist.
Yeah.
Was that she got she.
She bested the man physically too many times.
Like I was like give me a real protect like I'm rooting for this woman show me show me her getting fucking knocked around to show me both sides of it.
It doesn't all have to be.
You know, no, she outsmarts at every turn.
It's like it's like it's okay.
Like she's this woman that you're showing me a story about is tough enough.
Right.
That that if she if a guy clocks her, she's going to get back up again.
Like that makes the character more interesting to me or or if you're going to have the dog run around with her.
You could have killed her dog.
I was washing it with a buddy of mine.
I was like to kill this dog.
I'm I'm turning it off.
And it's like, well, it it lacked to me a certain raising of the stakes.
Yes.
We all know the predator is not going to kill this girl.
So when you see the girl.
Excel in every aspect of her day to day life and the hunt and everything else.
And then Excel at killing the predator.
It's kind of like it's a little linear.
It's a little a to be.
However, I I understand that maybe they didn't want to show a young girl and a dog in extreme jeopardy throughout, but I will say the movie lacked any sort of suspense for me.
It felt sort of like the final battle between the girl and the predator was cool.
I did like when the trappers came in and that that sort of elevated things a bit.
You know, there was some cool violence in it, but nothing made me go awesome.
You know, it was lacking that thrill factor for me, I guess, which is why I just found it to be an average.
So streaming action movie, but it was well done and competent.
And in this world we're living in.
That's rare.
There needed to be better higher stakes.
I agree.
Dog should have died.
That would have been heartbreaking.
And when the dog dies and I am legend, I mean, I'm on the floor.
It's horrible.
It's it's devastating.
Her brother dying was not enough.
Now, especially because her brother was an asshole to her.
Right.
I also thought that everybody talked way too contemporary.
There's a Comanche language version of the movie.
I watched the English language version because they didn't feel like reading.
But even with that said, they're way too contemporary.
The girl keeps using the word huge.
It's like guys, please at least write it with.
You know what I mean?
And she pronounced it Trump style.
Huge.
Yeah.
The spreader is huge.
But.
Onto what I liked, I thought the setting was great.
I think that if they're going to do a franchise with this, they should just keep telling stories about.
About hunters and warriors in different time periods throughout history with each one.
I think that'd be very cool.
I loved that this was so focused on a period in American history that was that where you you were the hunter or the hunted.
Period.
Yeah, it was an interesting thing to drop that predator character into.
I thought the sequence where he laid waste to all the French trappers was fucking awesome.
That was one of the coolest predator sequences I've seen in the entire franchise.
I liked the ways in which she outsmarted in the end.
I liked that she used the mud against the predator, but it wasn't the same way Schwarzenegger used the mud against the predator.
I liked that the predator had more primitive weapons in this, which was very cool.
You know, but there were thing that it's, it's the little details that stop it from being great.
It's as we already stated, it's the lack of stakes, it's the lack of loss of anybody that we really care about.
Yeah, those trappers are in there.
Just so they could kill a bunch of people, which okay, that's fine, but you got to kill a few people I care about.
And they don't do that at all.
They don't show her lose enough that you're worried about her as we established.
And.
And in the end, you're happy you're like I'm rooting for her.
I'm excited for her when the tribe like celebrates her at the end.
Yeah.
And I just wish there was a rockier journey to get there.
It would have just meant a little bit more.
But that all said, it's a solid action movie.
It's worth your, in my opinion, it's worth your time.
And my hog is mostly up for prey.
I'm curious to see what comes next.
Yeah, I have almost the exact same thoughts on it, except, you know, I would, I would just say my hog is present.
It's present.
I consider this an average action film, but one that I think is standing out a bit more because of how shitty everything got.
It's competent in a way that every movie was 20 years ago.
It was just as a bear, you know, bear minimum, it has to be competently made.
Now that that's off the table, prey looks a lot better.
What I want to watch more movies in this new franchise with the the Comanche people know.
I also feel like the predator is cool.
But let's come up with a new thing.
You know, I, the predator is not an interesting enough villain to sustain, however many of these movies we've gotten.
It doesn't talk.
Well, it's, it's, it's a huge, it's a huge property.
I mean, because, because you got it.
One thing I always forget is it's not just these movies.
There's comic books, there's a lot took, there's action figured there's a lot to predator.
Yeah.
I believe there was a cartoon series at one point.
It's a pretty big property.
So I understand why they keep revisiting this.
And that actually is interesting to me.
It just isn't.
And I get that too.
But that's one of the reasons I liked alien versus predator and a lot of people hated it, including you.
It reads like one of the graphic novels.
It feels right on the bookstore and I was like, this is cool.
This is like a, this is like a, this is like a cool one off like graphic novel.
Where there's this weird story about this underground temple and, and the aliens are thought out and the predators come into it to hunt them.
And there's traps and whatever.
So I am curious to see what they do next.
And I, and I, and, and I do like that they brought it back to a one on one battle.
You know, because I do think one of the things that the series started to do wrong was they just kept adding more predators.
Yeah.
And more things.
And it was like, that's not going to fix it.
So anyway, hogs mostly up on predator.
Jota Rosa comedy on Instagram and, and Twitter.
Please visit Joey roses.
If you're in NYC, Joey roses NYC dot com were open Tuesday through Sunday.
We hope to see you.
Jota Rosa info dot com for all my upcoming live appearances and shows.
I'll be in San Diego September, one, two, three.
And then I will be in a summerville, Massachusetts, also in September.
Come see me if you can. I'd love to see you out there.
Got dates all through October, November, December, all kinds of stuff coming up.
And thank you to all the fans who have who bought tickets so quickly to the to the live podcast.
That we are doing in New York.
We're very excited about that.
And we will be announcing soon.
I think.
Another live podcast that Pat and I were discussing yesterday.
In a state that we have not been to yet.
So more on that to come.
We're just working out the final details.
And last but not least, I said I would announce this here to prep.
I announced it also the other day on taste buds, which that episode isn't out yet.
But so I, as I, I keep dragging my ass.
I want to do this.
And if I announce it here, I'll actually do it.
But I'm launching a solo podcast called down with Jota Rosa,
which is a podcast I used to have and I'm relaunching it with a different format.
It'll be me talking about all the kinds of stuff I love, collectibles, food, video games,
a little bit of movie talk, but I'm going to keep leaving most of the movie talk and reviews for here.
But it will certainly expand on the, the scary stuff idea of, you know, the things I love to buy and collect.
Of course, there'll be some ranting and misery in there.
Just going to basically be me doing everything that I like to do.
So that'll be coming out sooner than later on publicly and on YouTube and on Patreon.
And I'll keep you posted on all that.
I believe I was a guest on the original incarnation of down with Jota Rosa.
You were.
We had known each other for maybe a week.
You were like the second guest ever.
Yeah.
I'm the patchkwalsh Twitter and Instagram.
You can hear me on Lizzie Cooperman's great podcast.
You can see the miss patch show on BET Plus.
You're going to want to watch it on edited season two is up and now and ready to go.
That's all I got.
We will be back with a review of.
We are doing orphan first kill.
Is it that generic title orphan first kill?
Yep.
And we will see you next time.
And we will see you in hell.