Thanks for joining we'll see you in hell it's the movie show with the movie
Bros my name's Joe where were you when we were coming up with the taglines for the show
I'm Pat Walsh we're talking this week about the conjuring part three the what is this the 11th of
the conjuring and it's all it's conjuring universe saga uh the uh yes the the the first of the
subtitled conjurings the devil made me do it what was that make this piece of shit
if you ever seen a title like that like where it's it's the title and then a colon and then
like some long I guess you'd have to go back to like the 80s I don't I don't remember this kind of
bizarre title in recent years um it's it's the no I haven't I thought it was usually endgame or
the reckoning or something it's not a full expression yeah I agree I thought that was odd um
I read up on the real case that this film is based on heavy quotes around based um
and it was called the devil made me do it murders or something so that's where that came from
now that that was pulled directly from apparently this was a big national story that the was the
devil made me do it that that expression come from the case I don't think so I think that's just
with the media coined it but yeah but uh this is the third uh official conjuring trilogy you know of
the of the main movies installment uh as Pat said it's the eleventh or whatever in the in the conjure
verse the worst name ever for a cinematic universe um and this is the first of the conjuring
for a movies the the the actual conjuring movies to take place outside of a haunted house
scenario a lot of people were disappointed in part two because they thought it was just sort of a
rehashing of part one I actually felt that part two was a sort of amped up scarier version of part one
so I liked part two uh but I also understood the criticisms of it uh but this one takes us completely
out of the haunted house scenario and into what you've always wanted in a conjuring film which is a
courtroom drama meets a wild goose chase this thing plays i mean we'll get an exorcism movie as well
and an exorcism movie picture my cousin Vinnie except less scary i mean it's just uh it's just it's
my cousin Vinnie basically except i'd love it if if the courtroom door is open at the back
and everyone turns and looks and there's like oh uh the murmur and incomes Joe pesci as my cousin Vinnie
that would have sent this movie off the charts yeah i agree i agree i remember seeing
the movie Cassandra's dream which was a Woody Allen movie with with um it's not a good movie yeah
with uh what are the Colin Farrell and uh uh you and McGregor you and McGregor it's a murder film
where their uncle played by you know that guy whatever his name is yeah uh has to you know they get
brought in murder with their uncle and their uncle has to you know get them out of you know whatever
to deadly serious movie it's not good it's painfully serious but i remember with my girlfriend at the time
seeing it in the theater and she was like she's like and then they're about to bring the uncle in at
the end of the first act of this just dreadful dreary film and she was like what if the uncle
was Woody Allen and the whole mood just changed and i was like that would be awesome that'd be a great
movie like a misdirection yeah and i feel the same with this like bring in pesh
turn it on its ear but we'll get back to the conjuring three we'll reconjure
the conjuring discussion in the meantime uh pat i got to give some shouts out
to uh band we both love my favorite band in the world Fou Manchu you know how much i love the Fou
and you love the huge fan yeah so i did a i did an interview on metal injection about
comedian where they interview comedians about their favorite band this was a long time ago
or not a month a couple months ago and i talked about Fou Manchu and when the interview posted
Fou Manchu Scot Hill from Fou Manchu who runs the social media account for them reached out to me
and said thank you so much man this was really cool of you let me send you some
stuff nice and i was like cool man are you kidding and he's like yeah and bob bob the bass player
also reached out there they were they were all very nice um and uh i never i never initially got
the box and i was like well i guess you forgot and then the other night he texted or he DMed me on
he did Instagram and he was like dude i am so sorry i'm just now getting to this i promise i'm sending
it out tomorrow i'm gonna send you a bunch of t -shirts bunch of vinyl i was like yeah cool no worries
man i i think it's really cool of you box showed up today riddled with goodies all kinds of special
addition vinyl re -releases from them three t -shirts and a handwritten note from scott uh where he says
let me know if you want anything else yeah love it so um well that's the man the probably you know
they just you never hear about them yeah you only the only way you'd ever like Fou Manchu was
a friend told you about them because they're not written about they're not talked about they're
not made they're talked about they're not mainstream bands you know it's there they're true grass
roots rock band you know what i mean right do they play New York at all man i know they're they live
in like long beach so they're playing here all the time um yeah shit they were supposed to play
New York and then the pandemic hit me and Vince had tickets yeah we were going to it and then and
then everything got fucked um so hopefully they'll be back through but um i very very appreciate it
made my made my week made my month um it was just very cool those guys to send that out so thank you boys
and it's cool to kind of get to know your favorite band that's pretty crazy i'm gonna listen to
these guys since i was in high school you know not well now you got the in you can text them are you
yeah text them are DMM and say ham going to the show tonight in New York and he'll be like oh sweet
you ought to come back and meet the bulls yeah yeah and you know you're going on tour plan tambourine
i'm there warm up comic yeah you can play the cowbell on mongoose
there you go yeah uh i'm a big fan fuck up the whole thing
uh little l a news this week my favorite theater in l a the vista uh which is five minutes from my
home has been purchased by quentin Tarantino who set the pivotal opening scene of true romance at the
vista you see the vista using a lot of movies that's got a very iconic front billboard marquee kind
of thing i thought it was going down last time i passed it it was completely covered in graffiti so
i was like oh yeah nobody's buying the vista tarantino stepped in it's a one screener he said
we're only showing movies on film if that means uh that the new places have to strike a film print of
new releases great that's the only that's the only way you're getting played here if not we'll show old
35 millimeter prints for me they're my collection or that we acquire i'm so excited about this and the
lowest field is three which is also five minutes from my house is becoming an offshoot of the American
cinema tech so it's like we the pandemic sucked in terms of taking down all these giants it used to
be there was a movie theater in every corner a lot of them have gone under Tarantino's point is you
should have gone under five years ago because the cinematic experience for people has been greatly
diminished each and every year over the last 15 to 20 years uh movies are projected poorly people talk
throughout there is no quality control at all the you know he's one of those guys who goes in the movie
starts and he's like this is five shades too dark you know uh he cares about projection you should care
so he's like i have no pity for these places they should have gone under and um i'm going to be
you know he's almost single handedly buying up all these uh second tier theaters and making them
really special place so i'm excited about it i'm going to some of these new Beverly double features
this month if you're in LA maybe i'll see you but uh there's some great ones they've been really
hard to get tickets to and at first i was like how this fucking sucks like nobody used to go to the
new Beverly you could see a double feature every night of the week and there'd be six people in there
and i'm like what am i getting upset about he's got people excited about classic film and going
you know granted you know it's it's LA you need a celebrity saying something's good for
everybody will go do it and that sucks but if that celebrity is him or power to him i'm excited
about what this means for the future of LA movie going i think it's cool i think it's pretty cool uh
quick news psycho i guess that also would count as a new psycho i would say yes
the Halloween kills trailer has been released the official trailer not just the teaser
walk me through i haven't seen it don't waste your time pat it's uh they show 87 kills in
the trailer i don't understand what could possibly be left in the movie itself right um
it's completely over the top completely bloody and nuts yeah and completely everything that
John Carpenter and everybody else on planet earth involved with the franchise
pissed and moaned about the franchise turning into with part two and why part two sucks and
and then you know it was never the same and four and five weren't good and we don't count them and we
got to you know i'll say i said it before i'll say it again h2o gave you a sequel
that brought the movie franchise back to its roots yeah it was a tremendously well executed sequel
it was the coolest way possible to to play out the Jamie Lee Curtis and Michael Myers story
and that's it the only thing they changed in this one now is that they're not related
and it doesn't make sense and on top of it not making sense now that they're not related and i
don't buy for a second that this woman was so traumatized she trained for 40 years to wait for
the return of this man or that he would return there without there being a familial thing going on
uh i'm sorry it's just i don't buy it and this thing is all just gratuitous kills which hey fine man
but this is why everybody said the rob zombie Halloween sucked this is why the whole point of this
reboot that john carpenter was quote unquote blown away by yeah was supposed to be that it was this
new thing that had never been heard of and it was so not done before and it was this and then it's
like no this has all been done before and it's all been done before for the most part better
so i think it looks stupid i'll see it and we'll review it i'm sure
but i just think it looks stupid and i just i don't know i'm just like
just like they show you in the trailer how he gets out of the burning house it's like also
why are you showing your ass yeah why are you showing me everything i haven't seen the trailer and maybe
now i won't watch it but i do think and as much as i truly love the work of dynamic bride um so
do i yeah i was really thrown by the original i i when the highlight is the wisecracking kid you know
the webster style kid that makes quips throughout right probably not a great horror movie but that's
really all i remember about it was that kid being kind of funny well now they got David Gordon green
yeah at the helm of the exorcist oh come on sequel and Jason Blum jackass that he is uh said
in an interview i think people are going to be really blown away by what we do with this you know
think in the wheelhouse of our halloween reboot what's that our sequel it's like that also has been
done yeah didn't official sequel to the exorcist on the exorcist tv show already yeah you're not
going to beat that it was awesome it was awesome then the show went to shit unfortunately
but that was awesome and it's like there's no way you're going to beat this you get an exorcist remake
in this week's movie the conjuring three it opens with a almost scene for scene exorcist remake
i did not know that david Gordon green was doing that but it's like any you know it what what it
probably is almost definitely is that the the only people continuing to make extreme comedy uh you
know hard are comedy are david Gordon green and dynamic bride they have the cloud to do it they
do things in their own bubble down in south carolina they don't allow notes they you know get stuff done
that's really funny and interesting them pivoting to horror now is probably an indication that they know
the time of even them doing hard are rated comedy and your face stuff is over and they're pivoting
to another genre but they're not good at it i hate to say it they're just not good at it and
it's this is something i've noticed people do too it's like the other halloween came out fans
didn't really like it critics didn't really like it it made some money because it's a big name but whatever
and then you'll hear jason bloom go look we're gonna think think about our amazing halloween remake
this is gonna be like that it's like they'll just change the perception you know like he thinks
he can just say that like we all knew and love the original and there's so many people who were like
oh okay yeah i remember that but think about it no you didn't the movie sucked they're they're
using this other halloween decide as like something we can look forward to for the exorcist
i just i just don't get it and it's also one of the it's this classic thing i'm looking up the
rotten tomato score for halloween i'm just curious uh i know we did it on the live show
yeah but we we did it like the day it opened right so who knows if uh
i mean my god i mean just the fact and we've talked about this too it's like the fact that you
made this new sequel that ignored all the other bad sequels or that were what you consider to be bad
sequels excuse me and then immediately when it made eighty million dollars announced we're
gonna do a trilogy you're just you're just doing the same thing and it's that classic thing
of let's see here uh critical response halloween received a 26 % approval rating yeah
wasn't there a dumb twist in it where the doctor turned out to be evil
because he wanted to study Michael Myers or some stupid shit like that yeah which was like a
it's hard to podcast uh it would be like me and you driving up to interview which by the way it would
probably be a better movie but yeah i mean i knew the second it was two podcasters going to
interview Michael Myers doctor i was like come on guys and the um and there was the thing that
it's like carpenters doing that thing that everybody does and sometimes it lands and some a lot
of the time it doesn't but it's like you know like a good example is like Harrison Ford wanted nothing
to do with Star Wars anymore and finally at 75 or whatever he's like i'll play Han Solo again
and hey it worked thank god it worked in that first movie uh i'm not speaking to the quality of that
trilogy but thank god it was it was fun seeing him do that again he was great i didn't like blade
runner two but he was great in it like it worked what he needed to do he did sometimes that's cool
most of the time it's like you guys waited way too fucking long to do this yeah and i think that's
what carpenters doing man it's like it's like he has chastised this franchise his entire career
and then you know you make a few bombs you kind of lose your edge on the cinematic stuff
and suddenly it's like well why am i so against a Halloween being involved i'll produce it and
i'll score it and you know and i'll be back in the mix and it's like yeah did you could have been
back in the mix like way sooner and it would have been better it would have been like way fucking better
you know so yeah sometimes failure is a real you know it brings you i mean it really brings you
down to earth you know like okay look what what can i actually do now and then it's too late um but
yeah it's uh it's not it's like what Stephen King does you know like as anyone's words meant less
and Stephen King go and like wait a you see this week's licey story it'll blow your mind
with i do want to see licey story i never read the book i thought i was going to finish it before
the show premiered and then uh in three weeks i had read two pages of it it's a 900 page book
so i probably won't get there but it got terrible reviews and king wrote it
it's got Clive Owen and Julianne more not one person i know is talking about it so
he's he's he's treading on real thin ice to repeatedly on twitter like he wrote the other day like
what's the worst harm movie you ever saw mine's blood diner and it's like look
stevy i know blood diners no masterpiece but you got a lot on your own resume there pal like you know
take it including your your directorial debut maximum overdrive yes so uh anyway patty take us to
that movie corner let me take you to the corner i uh i my favorite thing to read online is oral
histories of movies um there are many many good ones if you search or the ringer does them sometimes
magazines do them a lot the longer the better they just get everyone together
who worked on the movie that that that wants to comment and it's just like a conversation they
just play everyone's thoughts on the movie and and different aspects of the movie there's a full book
oral history of days and confused that came out last year that's a absolutely terrific read if you
like that film and who doesn't um so i read one on Freddie got fingered and i was like all right
like who doesn't want to know what went on with Freddie got fingered that's a movie i saw in the
theater my friends were all excited they were big -time green fans me and my buddy saw it we met up with
our friends and we were like look we just want to hear what you guys have to say about this we're not
going to say a word but we were i've never hated a movie as much at that point i think and i was
not a big -time green fan but uh god i hated it so much and i was like the movie just seems designed
to piss me off and you read the oral history and it's like yeah that's what we were trying to do
so have you seen Freddie got fingered Jim i never saw it do okay it is it's a hard art it's it doesn't
follow any sort of real structure but basically tom green is an aspiring cartoonist who leaves
his mom and dad played by julie haggity and the great rick torn and he goes to the big city
hollywood to try to sell his wares along the way he jerks off a horse which he actually does you see
this happen at one point he gets inside of the the decaying body of a deer he's playing in the
deer's like blood and organs and and wearing its carcass on his back for a long extended sequence
uh so it's a gross out movie but it's kind of beyond the norm there's a scene where harland
williams breaks his uh knee or whatever on a skateboarding trick you see the bone coming out so you're
like oh god like that's but then tom green starts licking the wound and licking the bone and you're
like well now wait a minute it's like they where everything would stop in like american pie he goes
one step further to a a really gross area but also a point that makes you sort of angry and
when you read this oral history you're like it's by design he thought they're if they're going to
give me money to do this i'm gonna thumb my nose at the conventions of hollywood watching it now
you know almost 15 20 years later whatever it is it's still a really bad movie tom green
tom green directed it it's incompetently directed but there's a certain spark it has that a lot of
these companies from this time don't have and it is that like in your face energy granted reading
this oral history helped the enjoyment of it a lot but um you know the the reason for the title is
is in the end tom green to get back at his dad he has this very antagonistic um relationship with
his father played by i mean rip torn's plan this thing like he it's a jack Nicholson movie like he
doesn't care he brings the same level of commitment there's a scene where and i mean he's accusing his
dad of having fingered his brother's asshole Freddie played by eddie k tomis from the american pie
literally is that the title is literal i thought it was like it's amazing that that that that title got
through but um yeah he accuses father of that and in one scene rip torn goes downstairs he pulls his
pants and underwear down he reveals his giant rip torn alcoholic white ass starts spanking it and begging
tom green to fuck his ass uh he's just being antagonistic he's like you're gonna accuse me of
fingering him okay let's do this of course julie haggard he walks in and sees him bent over begging
his son to fuck his ass and think i mean movie goes in some wild directions to say the least torn
is kind of the reason that that keeps it alive i learned that they offered the role to gene wilder
who was like guys that i'm offended you asked me to read this they offered it to jerry stiller
who might have been hilarious but he was like i can't i can't pull my pants down and beg someone to
fuck my ass but uh rip torn goes for it the movie goes for it it's a punk rock movie to be sure
it's not entirely successful but i i have a lot of admiration for it now i watched uh
just along the similar lines bucky larcen born to be a star oh boy
i was just in a dark place one night i was like i need something that's just gonna take me away from
everything not make me think about anything uh huh it's all nick swarz and in that way i was like this
is this is it i'm gonna settle under this yeah uh most of the reviews i read this has like a two
percent on rotten tomato's this movie most of the reviews i read were like poor Christina richie and
herman uh what's his name herman loit the guy from lost boys al brinard herman brinard herman
you know it's a bad movie when they start bringing up past awards yeah like like one of the reviews was
like poor brinard herman who won a tony once he's in this now you know uh Christina richie's in it they
commit a hundred and ten percent but so does everybody everybody in the movie commits a hundred
ten percent my buddy gene pompus in it uh playing the makeup artist um and i've met nick over the
years i like nick a lot he's a funny guy uh i like his stand up quite a bit and i i enjoy seeing him in
movies and is this a good movie fuck no uh but are there some laughs yeah there's some laughs i mean the
premise is it's a it's a it's a sheltered mist midwestern kid who finds out his parents are porn stars
from the seventies and he gets into porn to follow in their footsteps but he has a micropanus
uh but he it all he can also come repeatedly in giant waves of come do you see the come i don't
remember you do you don't see it come out but you see it like on an old lady shoulder at one point
it's like one guy shoe it's like it's dripping from the ceiling uh don johnson plays the director that
makes the kid famous what a period for don johnson it's just a crazy crazy crazy one of those happy
Madison movies that you know you know they have a formula they follow clearly and that's it
steven dwarf plays the adversary like bad guy uh i'd say the one redeeming quality to the film is
the amount of jokes they get out of the word stink and smell um i believe steven dwarf refers to the
vagina is the stink garden okay there's a portal dwarf dwarf was in the news yesterday for saying
he's embarrassed for scarlet joe handsome that she has to be in the black widow movie and he thinks
that marvel is that is the end of society and he who is in bucky larson i mean people's comments were
like you were in blade yeah and then everybody was like blade was good shut up but uh i love blade
but i mean yeah i should have focused on fucking bucky larson that's hard to argue with
there's a movie in this film called the farmer in the smell oh boy there's a movie called welcome to
the stink which could be the funniest porn title i've ever heard personally and like what is it a
parody of anything no i don't think of anything they just were like let's uh it's an insane it's
insane movie it's not good it's insane but did i stick it out and laugh a few times yeah yeah i got
i remember laughing a couple times at bucky larson whenever i watched it all of these s &l movies
and especially the happy medicine and and it's you know uh swarzen is at the very he's below
Schneider on the uh on the list of sandler friends who they they allow to make movies but there's always
a laugh or two they they understand how to get a laugh in a way that other companies generally don't
these days but yeah i remember that one being about as bad as you can get i mean even the two doose
bigel on movies are pretty solid in my opinion um i watched saint maude which we were originally going to do
on the show and then kind of just abandoned but saint maude is a british horror film it's about a nurse
who fails to save the life of a patient in her care and then becomes like a devout Catholic who works as a
nurse and she's very devout she it wants to like you know scrub away her her sinful past she wants to
help others who are sitting um starts to see herself as sort of a a christ type figure and the movie's
sort of dabbling in in religion and religious imagery is all kind of interesting there are some good
scares in it the last shot the you know the last scene is really kind of amazing um but it's the kind of
first horror movie that that makes you go i'm excited to see what this person does next where i
wasn't particularly thrilled with the movie itself it's it's effective it's a little creepy
uh religious horror when done right is always you know there's something compelling and interesting
about it just because so much of religion is tied into horror i mean the the stigma and
you know even even nailing them to the cross i mean these are all very horror type imagery
um saint maude i found to be a little better than average it's on hulu now
you know it's very much that uh a 24 style you know the uh where everything looks like it was
i don't know filmed with a camera that was made in 1926 and stuff like that but uh it's it's fine
saint maude i think was was bizarrely overrated i think a lot of movies during the pandemic were overrated
because we got presented with so much shit that anything decent came across i think it's a trend
happening in horror now and it was happening in comedy for a long time
these things are are told and it touted as you know um horrifying the scariest thing i've ever seen
done right and then you know you start watching and and it's really at the end of the day it's like
the real monsters are the humans and yeah this stupid shit and it was the same thing was happening
with comedy we know we've talked about it before on here you know i the if you pick up the box of
cold souls one of the most depressing and boring paul jimati movies i've ever seen
it like literally says gut bustingly funny on the box and i'm like this is not a comedy in any way
shape or form so like it's it's it's just that obon guard artsy fartsy bullshit it's it's i'm i
hate to say this because i'm a fan of a 24 i'm starting to cringe when i see the a 24 logo come up now
at the top of a trailer because i'm just like they're starting it's like what happened with
what can you hear me yeah totally something went out here on my end uh there we oh my headphones
went out for a second see folks you see the worts and all in this show um but it's the same thing
that happened with HBO it was like it just uh you know they they started popping with their tv shows and
it was awesome and then all of a sudden it became we're HBO thank you very much that's exactly what happened
now with a 24 where you're like yeah come on anyway uh another they they do they they think there's
some kind of you know elite brand and and meanwhile it's like well what about this 75 % of your output
that's not very good you know there there's lots of their movies that come out and never never hit
it all but we're supposed to act like they had this unblemished track record um they did they
look lighthouse uh they i know not favorites of years joe but i love to redditarian midsummer
they do good work they they've brought some talented filmmakers to the to the public eye but um
yeah by and large i'm a little tired of i'll stick on theme of snl movies i rewatch dirty work i've been
on a real normic Donald kick because i i'm re -listening to his autobiography one of the funniest
books ever written uh it's up there with ipartridge i mean uh it is as funny as a comedy book gets
it's so crazy so and the audio book is great because he's reading it it's just it's just a wild
book uh it's so funny but uh anyway i got an a normic Donald kick uh and of course in the in the book he's
talking a bunch about shooting dirty work so i went back and re -watch dirty work um it's still an
absolutely terrible film um but as badly directed as a comedy could be by bob op sagget he did such a bad
job but it's a hilarious movie i feel bad i'm a fan of bob sagget i'm a fan of norm i'm friends with
already uh you know like i like like i like everybody involved in this thing you know but uh but it's
not a good movie it's got some very funny parts i rewound the record scene three times uh that still
gets me completely uh it goes warden warden yeah i rewound the i enjoyed the chevy chase scene his first
scene a lot i rewound the jail rape scene where we're you know outrageous yeah just ridiculous
you'd be hard pressed to get me to say a negative word about dirty work as as pathetically
as it is directed from any any sort of visual or quality standpoint well the script is horrible too
i mean the script is terrible the lines in the script where where like the doc like chevy chase is
jack warden's doctor and he's in the room with jack warden at the top of the scene yeah he walks out
as arty lang and nor mcdonald are entering yeah and now they need to get arty lang out of the room so jack
warden can talk to nor mcdonald about being his father secretly uh and arty lang goes i'm gonna go
find the doctor i'll be right back i mean this is like three stages level dialogue like
motivations yeah it's it's just a terribly written and poorly directed film that said
you can only get so low when you got a cast like this it's it's they deliver the goods you know
it's true uh i think there's huge laughs in this uh you know i put it below certainly your
your Madison Gilmore your your uh Tommy boy even a black sheep but it above a Tommy boy
above a you're outrageous no i think i think Tommy boy has three hilarious scenes in it and then the
rest of it is like i'm just like i don't care about this anymore it's a comedy classic i think it's a shame
that that that that farly in spade never got a great one off i really think it's good everyone
everyone would say it's Tommy boy everybody i know but you're telling me you're gonna put Tommy boy
i mean you know how we feel about kingpin i mean it i know i don't put Tommy boy above kingpin but
i'm just saying like it when you compare the two i'm like it's nowhere on the level of like a
dumb and dumber or kingpin or something like it's i i absolutely love it and even though it
wraps off plans trains i think it's beautifully constructed i give it an a a a an unquestioned a
would he give kingpin kingpin so you are putting it on the level of kingpin
you know i guess so i think that that was farly in spades big like they they got a one perfect
vehicle i mean i've never heard anyone speak ill of Tommy boy tell right now listen to spades oh no spades
book he talks about how black sheep got all fucked up yeah i think Tommy boy is a is a sea film at best
uh again a boring film poorly directed poorly written but with laughs it's like half baked there's a
lot of these movies where it's like there's comedic geniuses involved but the execution is so bad
that you can just go all right that was like it's like a it's like an snl that has three or four
hilarious sketches in it but i'm not gonna sit and say that was a great hour and a half of television you
know to me half -baked is is the cc plus that's got three funny lines and and not much else to it but
we we differ people differ uh i i i love dirty work i think it's there's a lot of funny shit in
there but yeah god it's badly done um i have been watching dark side of the ring uh the episodes
are on hulu they're also on vice the new episodes are on vice i haven't seen any of the new ones
but i am somebody with zero interest in wrestling maybe less than zero i've never
never been able to get into it and yet this show does a really good job and when they say dark
these stories are like punishingly dark and depressing it's uh it is rough rough rough stuff
yeah it is uh you know the last of the van arix is a classic episode i had never even heard of a lot of
these people and then of course you know i've heard of chris benoit uh been was sorry i guess i
haven't heard of them that much um but let me read you some of these titles cocaine and cowboy boots
the herb abrum's story i mean they how do you know how are you not going to watch that
so uh i can't speak to the new season which my dear friend vince avril who was a huge wrestling fan says
is just as good just as dark but um if you have even a passing interest this will be your new favorite show
because i'm pretty much hooked on it and i don't care so like uh the final days of oh and heart
you know but those big ones that kind of hit the national news are like i knew them and they're
very sad of course but what's really getting me is these wrestling stories i'd never even heard of
the fabulous mula one of uh wrestling's most notorious female promoters the montreal screw job
you know and you can watch them in any order i mean the the titles of these things each of each one
you read the next one you're like well gotta watch that so check it out it's a fun show even though
it's measurably depressing perfect culmination for this movie corner speaking of very dark documentaries
and snl i watched cracked up the daryl ham and story saying it documentary about daryl ham and from
snl the man of a million voices uh i always enjoyed his work i think he's immensely talented
met him a few times in the stand -up circuit very nice guy um but could always kind of tell there was
probably like something beneath the surface there yeah uh and you know sure enough the turn this
documentary on and it's it's a very very sad tale of his his life dealing facing facing finally his
child abuse and his childhood trauma and how that manifested in his adult life through addiction and
some other things and he's a beautiful guy he's a complicated guy but but one of the things i loved in
this was it showed all sides of him it showed him being funny it showed parts where he gets mad at
somebody and then it would show him going back and saying i love you and i appreciate you i'm sorry
about that and like i just thought it was very very very well done and uh you know if you're in the mood
to watch somebody's journey like that uh it does have its uplifting moments it is trying but it's
it's painfully real and uh and i do think it's worth a watch it's not exploitative i think it's just
very honest um and i it's weird to say i enjoyed it i think it's a valuable watch is a better way
of saying it so all right good good story and a decent doc uh yeah did you hear Chris Katan on a plan
this week mucus it the article said mucus falling from his nose uh refused to put a mask on his
publicist for immediately like no no no he loves masks he'd never do this like i mean clearly
masks clearly katana is is uh having some difficulties man but he was in first class you know i i
i actually thought maybe he did this whole story so that he could get the word out that he still
takes first class but um and imagine kris katana trying to sit down next to you with snot falling out
of his nose it's like oh boy yeah and also why is the snot freely running out of his nose with
exactly you know that's why is the why is the uh the mucus that's falling out of his nose white and
powdery is another question that i had oh boy um all right let's get down to this fucking movie
yeah a conjuring part three the devil made me do it the latest installment of films that starts with
of all the cases the warrants faced this one was the darkest third movie now to do that yeah third
movie to come out after these people have been debunked uh exposed as fraudulent exposed as money hungry
as supposed as shysters who behind the scenes tell people if we drum this up as a demonic possession
thing we can make a lot of money here yeah uh they've been innocently investigated when i say
investigated i mean you know paranormal types go to their place and see like what they're all about and
they and look to their defense they had welcomed them over the years when they were alive everybody left
saying the same thing what you're gonna find there are two nice people that have a lot of cool stories
and not a lick of evidence to to support any of it um the amityville investigation which
they were made famous for partly and probably their most famous of all their cases uh has been exposed
as completely fraudulent people involved said it was all a hoax the basis for the conjuring part two
those girls eventually came out and said we it was all a hoax we we planted it was a media hoax
the the case in this one where the kid the plot of this movie and the case was a kid murdered two people
said he was possessed by a demon that had possessed a young boy that his sister his girlfriend's younger brother
the kid not only went to jail because how the hell could you ever prove this in a court of law
but also the little kid at the beginning of the film who was possessed who they claimed the demon
jumped out of uh he sued Elaine Warren and the publishers of the book about this
uh and so did his brother because he said I had a mental thing I had a I had a disorder that was
happening um and you are exploiting it with this nonsense of course the kid who went to jail and
got out in five years wholly supports the warrants because he goes back now and goes now I actually
wasn't a devil I killed those people he could find himself in some trouble but uh can we just sort of
let bygones be bygones on this one yeah my point is is at this stage in the game it was one thing with
the first conjuring this is and look I'm not I'm not I'm not comparing crimes here okay so just
hear me out at this stage in the game it's like it's like making a wholesome Cosby movie or something
you know what I mean it's like when the one conjuring comes out and you look up up the warrants and
you see well there that's a little weird it seems like somebody accused them of fraudulence or whatever
at some point but they denied it okay maybe that was bullshit maybe they're innocent whatever
by the third movie where it's the fifty odd people have come forward and said things you're like yeah
you don't go then make a movie about Cosby where no part of that movie is somebody going you guys
are full of shit man you know so not only are they portraying these people as saintly and um
I'm nip uh I'm nipotent that's without flaw right all powerful no I'm nipotent is all knowing
and initiate is is all seeing all knowing okay I'm nipotent is like god basically no one see
flawless then let's put it that way okay not only are they doing that they're building up the so
called abilities of these people and then at the end of the movie they're playing actual audio
captures from this heavy quotes exorcism that they've been sued by the kid they exercise yeah
I mean it's just a fuck you to everybody um that that's not on their team
and I just think it's absurd at this point I think it's absurd they claim to have investigated
10 ,000 cases if you do the math and they investigated and solved one case per day
during their entire career it doesn't come anywhere near 10 ,000 it's ridiculous it's just ridiculous
ridiculous much like the the gang rape and dirty work um yeah look I have it I have a different
outlook on this although we both share a hatred from for conjuring three I know we've discussed and
don't like the film um to me I'm not watching a documentary here it doesn't bother me that they're
taking some liberties with it um I will say why not dig into that and hopefully they will for the
fourth why not make the fourth about people calling them a hoax you know like the the true story is
so much more interesting than what you're presenting us with this kind of warmed over horror let's
you know do us a story where everybody's calling them a hoax but then it's the boy who cried wolf
then these people suddenly need help and they got to get the warrants it seems like that would bother you
as well because they'd have to be the heroes in it but the war it's a it's a very profitable franchise
they're always going to be painted as like the Sherlock of the uh the ghost world and this
and the heroes of the film that doesn't bother me this to me is is it is like a Trump level propaganda
at this point like it's it's so insane uh -huh like it's so insane and you know of course coming out of
Hollywood you know the the progressive truth seekers of everything you know until it comes to the
bank account then then it's okay to be full of shit but I mean it they're presenting this here's
the thing you want to throw based on a true story up on the screen at the top of the movie and keep
it moving I don't give a shit I've seen it a million times in movies and know the movies represent
nothing like what happened in real life yeah okay but you're going to go to the point and play the
audio excerpts of the exorcism at the end of the film to really try to hammer home like this was real
and it's like no fuck you this is gross at this point in my opinion all right I let it slide that
in real life animal is a raggedy and doll and in the movie you make her look like the most evil ugly
thing of all okay I'm letting things slide everything in the first conjuring movie was palatable
it was all palatable you're like wow this stuff was real like okay all right maybe this
could happen what the second one got crazier but it was still palatable where you were like
maybe the kids said she saw a ghost that was a big tall jangly man and this is just how they're
representing it in the movie for cinematic part I get all that this thing by the midway point
where they have Elaine Warren who's who psychic powers are now give her the ability to embody
the experiences of other people and she merely goes to the sight of a murder and relives the murder
it's like give me a fucking break with this man this is ridiculous they're like solving the crime
based on this yeah it's so fucking crazy well I will say I hated the warrants in this and I've
liked them and the others and I don't think I hate them because they've been exposed as frauds I think
that they completely missed the boat on who these characters even were because like they're not good
characters in this movie and they have like it's it's like the kind of thing where your hero will
suddenly have a superpower that's never been experienced before and it's also like why didn't you use
this in conjuring one if you could see this happen you know that's the kind of shit that bugged me it
just seemed like they threw anything out that they wanted to about these people and I agree two
portray that as fact is pretty shitty when you're just making up your own rules as you go and by the
way you know you know I'm a big one for due process and you know hey man let's not all pile on
here like let's hear all the facts but just so you know Ed Warren absolutely is they had a young girl
living with them for years who said that Ed Warren had inappropriate sexual relationships with her
when she was not of age no she wasn't a child child but she was like 16 or whatever yeah and that girl
said that they had a very dark side to their marriage that he was very he there was a lot of
infidelity on his part you know all these things just seem to go out the window when we need to sell
the story of a certain type of person let's get on to how shittily this thing is directed of course
because it's directed by the guy that did the Curse of Lil' Lorna not Lil' Lorna the Curse of Lil' Lorna
did you see that one no because it was as the trailer let me know immediately this is as paint by numbers
a hard jump scare movie as you can get it was terribly reviewed this guy did nothing before that somehow
got the keys to the kingdom to direct this thing the thing bombs critically but does decently
commercially they put him on the conjuring three yeah it's what but by the way Lil' Lorna was
shoehorned into the conjure verse it wasn't supposed to be a conjuring movie and they like added three
things that made it part of it somehow James won you know while I don't think he's quite had that
masterpiece I think he is one of the best working horror directors he knows his way around horror
he's clearly a big fan I actually loved the original conjuring I saw it with my wife who doesn't normally
do horror and we were we'd had a blast we were jumping and clapping and the scenes with the claps
in the dark yeah it felt like a new classic horror sequence that I hadn't really seen
um I loved it I really did to Joe and I split on a bit I thought it was average a little above
average but still worked and was well directed Joe liked it a lot and then you get to three and
it's like what the fuck are you doing my theory is this when the conjuring was pitched to them they
said and by the way not only this story the warrants have thousands of great stories that this can be a
huge franchise and spin -offs and everybody put their heads together to come up with a classic film
that could launch a franchise they put the time and they put the work in and the conjuring is
is an excellent movie by the time you get to three the franchises up and running they know people are
going to see the shit no matter what and I really do think it's this kind of cynicism that leads to
franchises becoming worse and worse and worse they're like they know people will see the shit
the only time they actually go back and start trying again is when one of these movies bombs
when conjuring six comes out and nobody goes to see it conjuring seven is probably going to be
pretty good because they know they have to try that that's what Hollywood feels like to me these days is
like they'll try when they have to and if they don't you're getting Wonder Woman 2 you're getting
conjuring three it's just like why put all this work in on the script and on getting everything
perfect and spending all that money when we can put out a project that's simply trying to hit a
release date of May 30th and nobody cares if it's good or bad because it'll make money that's when
you get the product like we're getting now in Hollywood this is it's dog shit when when I say it opens
with an exorcist rip off I'm so I'm talking the priest gets out of a car and stands in front of a
house looking up at it in a shard of light in it in a I was yeah what are you doing I mean they might
just they might have just been playing the video of the exorcist next to the camera and and
shooting it in exactly the same way it's like the psycho remake at that point I was telling a friend
yesterday about that and I said of all the ways they could have paid an homage to the exorcist
which is what they're claiming that shot is they picked the laziest yeah they picked the shot from
the cover of the monster poster it's like this is like hey we want you know we want you to do a
we're doing a rolling stones cover album what song would you like to do oh how about a deep cut
like satisfaction you know what I mean it's like it's just like it's such an obvious choice
hey we're doing a pixie tribute of oh I'll take here comes your man it's like come on man like
this was the best way you could pay it out and it's because this director sucks he sucks
why is this guy at the helm of this thing it feels like scenes were redirected feels like
there were reshoots it feels so just it's not a cohesive work it's not it's definitely not well
directed but it's also not well written you know Joe you always talk about the the trope of the
elderly African woman or the Jamaican woman who's like I know about the secrets you know yeah
they go back to that well a ton and horror in this movie when they start talking about the totem
and the powers that the totem had I'm like guys this is like this is shit like from you know
everybody loves Prince of darkness John Carpenter's Prince of darkness I did not I watched it
recently I thought it's fucking suck I think it's such a bore when they when they're dusting off a
magical totem I mean that that is horror at its most like just throwing up their hands and being like
we don't know what to do you got to get all these great stories fake though they may be if you're
gonna use these fake stories as fact you had to be able to find a better one than this and if you're
gonna do a story about the devil made me do it and the trial and so forth then
bring in the actual I'm sure they don't want to bring in the the claims about the warrens
because somebody's gonna dig and then the franchise will be put but like there there were so
many better stories to tell here this is nothing and it doesn't even really make sense seem to seem
they show none of the trial by the way they start to show it and then at the end they put up a
little text blur about what happened yeah or the outcome they you know there's a scene in this where
they find the location of the totem and there's a pentagram on the floor I mean it's just like
how many times are we gonna learn that the pentagram wasn't an evil symbol and how many times you
gonna continue to use it right uh you know and maybe that's maybe that's what they're actually scaring
at this point I mean yeah it's just and maybe that's what they actually found I don't know
turns out what's happening is there's an evil witch uh who is for some reason that I still
don't understand manipulating this family she's risen a demon to earth oh that's what it was she's
summoned this demon and she's trying to bring it to the earth via the one of these vessels yeah
and uh with the young boy and then it jumps out of the young boy and goes in the older boy and then
and then it fails because they exercise the older boy at the end and that's the end of it
but uh the old witch uh who they finally the warrants confront at the end who gets
magically folded into a cube her body starts breaking and crunching and whatever she gets folded
down into a cube and just as she's about to die Patrick Wilson the most boring person on earth yes
since since uh since uh what's her face from uh the good place
Kristen Bell uh he goes the demon needs a soul it can't return to its master empty handed now you're
that soul it's like guys this didn't happen yeah I mean look I'll say this you you're gonna have a
way worse time if you're looking for this to be rooted in fact Joe I mean I'll I'll I'll say that to
but um some kind of truth look the Andy Kaufman movie was did he they say you know we changed things
for dramatic purpose so it's like yeah okay I'll buy that that you know on the same day they threw
him off of taxi dressed as Tony Clifton he got his cancer diagnosis you know what I mean I'll go
I'll go with you that far but it's like it's like this is insane this is crazy but you might also be
brilliant that's that's for me one of the lowest lines in biopic history but I like the movie it's
it's that line the two lines that were pointed out to me that or the most brutal in that movie are
that one which my friend Aaron pointed out he goes this was Danny DeVito's way of telling the audience
he always got it with Andy Kaufman for sure that's why he gets that line and then the line
at the very beginning the Pinkstone always made fun of when his dad goes Andy if you're going to
perform you need an audience you can't perform to no one it's really yeah really dumb but but anyway
that ends our review of 1999's man on the moon thank you all for yeah for me it is I was
annoyed by treating the warrants as if they're Indiana Jones it's like they get the big heroes entrance
and everything and it's like I don't think people love these guys as much as you think I think
Wilson and Farminga are zeros I've seen them both be good in things don't get me wrong but they're
they're zeros and they also don't get the characters right there's no continuity between them
in the other films and this movie to me they seemed like Mormon freaks they seemed annoying and boring
and I just did not like them at all they've got they've got for mega in this get up where it looks like
she smells like oatmeal like they've got her in this weird get up like they got Wilson walking
around just a just a black hole on the fucking screen but they look like the couple that you'd see
on like the Warren's oatmeal like they look like they own an oatmeal company and it bothers me
that they they dress down for mega so much and they they let Wilson strut around all handsome and
it's like have you seen the real guy he's based on guy has like a guy look like Ernest Borgneye
yeah yeah it's ridiculous so it's um yeah you're right the heroes entrance the heroes ending people
think oh by the way there's another big big subplot in this we're suddenly the people over at the
the people over a conger verse and I see I and see think that we give a shit about the love they have
for each other yeah this steered heavy into like their love bond and all and there was like flashbacks
of them meaning what the fuck who cares exactly right and of course it you know the thing crosses the
two hour mark and all this other shit too but it's like um as far as positives go I'll say this as
annoyed as I was by the exorcist ripoff the opening exorcism sequence is cool it leans too heavily on
on CGI and having the guy's body contort and stuff but I was like this is cool the first five minutes
I'm like I'm into this there's some enthusiasm scares and moments and then from then on
god it's it's just a murky mess it wasn't it wasn't bad but it made the mistake that crystal skull made
which is you set up a pattern with your with your franchise and then for some reason they break it
eventually that the mistake of crystal skull was why didn't you open it with like a side thing
that he's like wrapping up right this big fun thing that somehow leads into the main adventure cold
open this yeah this was the same thing it was like every other the first one set up at a bell the
second one set up the none do that again in this one it works yeah and they didn't they just started
right with the story and you were like oh okay so this is just a real linear story just front to back
and look it's it's been well documented on here how much we hate Marvel you know I you don't think
I keep saying I'm never gonna see another one and then I wind up going to do it but
Marvel is a company that for better or worse because I think the movies lose a lot of personality
because of this but every decision is made by a team sitting around a board going how do we
keep this franchise going how do we you know spin it off into other things and there's such a level
of quality control that to me it's it's very dull and and keeps me out of it I don't care about it
all because it feels like a product but at the very least there are competent people in charge of the
franchise this exactly what you're saying Joe if one ends with Annabelle two ends with the none
three you go okay what franchise are we launching in this one what side franchise and they also they
don't follow their own formula well and also the other two end with them going off on the new
adventure right and this one ends with him giving her a gazebo what the fuck is this yeah yeah generally
if if I'm in pitching a movie and then at the end I go and then guys in that final moment
he gives her and everyone's forward and I go a gazebo and they give me a hundred million dollars
to make the movie you know how how I would have fucked up at that point somebody needs to step in
and go we're not ending this picture on a gazebo folks two hogs way down for the conjuring three that's
our show thank you for the support thank you for listening leave those five star reviews big
shout to Emily Simpson as always for taking care of all she does on the fame Facebook fan page for
letting everybody know that the episodes are going to be late this month we apologize again we had
some technical difficulties we will be back mid month with probably the amusement park the new George
Romero unearthed film on shutter and something else I don't know what yet but that's our show folks thanks
for listening we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell