I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the sound of your screams,
it comes up in on my dreams.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, we'll see you in hell.
We're here to talk about the Wolfman.
Wolfman.
Wow, I can't wait to talk about this movie.
Yeah.
Did it make any money?
I hope not.
Let me look.
Lux office.
Who directed this thing?
Lee Straussberg.
What's his name?
Lee 1L.
Who for years, I thought, was the guy that directed the help?
That's the help.
The help is Taylor.
Doesn't even sound like Lee 1L.
What's his name?
The help is Tate Taylor.
Wait, but the help was called So-and-so's the help.
That guy is who I thought Lee 1L.
You're thinking of Tyler Perry.
You're thinking of Lee Daniels, the butler.
Yeah.
You're thinking of producer up.
I think he's the best fellow executive producer on the
mispatch show, Lee Daniels, who has never come to set or given a note on the show.
But he's significantly more money than I do, I'm sure.
So yeah, I thought Lee 1L was Lee Daniels for a while.
Yeah.
Because everybody was like, this guy's brilliant.
And then I realized Lee 1L is not Lee Daniels.
Now I don't have anything against Lee 1L.
But now I do.
I saw the Wolfman.
Well, I went back through his filmography.
Now I thought that, and I believe time will prove me right, just as it did with Barbie.
Because if you look now, there are like feminist outlets now writing blogs about Barbie or think
he's about Barbie being like, now that we've got some distance, can we all admit that Barbie
was not the feminist brilliant whatever that we thought it was?
I don't believe with time.
Good luck saying it opening weekend.
They would around you up and throw you in jail.
Yeah.
I voice that I didn't love it as much as some people, but I did like it.
And that led people to be very angry with me.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's, so I believe personally that with the tragedy of the Wolfman, people
are going to revisit the invisible man and realize that that was not that good.
And also point out how it has nothing to do with the original Universal movie, just as people
are pointing out with this Wolfman.
And furthermore, what's with all the Lee 1L praise?
He made one good movie, upgrade.
He directed in city is three.
Like, why is this guy?
Why immediately was it was everybody like the brilliant Lee 1L and his full look?
I don't think he's deserving of the brilliant Lee 1L, but he didn't he write saw as well?
I got to be honest with you.
I don't think saw is that good.
But Joe, Joe, saw is not one of my favorite movies, but you understand why he would be hailed
for writing a $2 million movie that grossed 500.
I mean, I, yes, it in the economics department, yes, but let's talk about and saw the original
saw is cool.
He wrote saw one, two, three dead silence.
Dead silence is terrible.
He wrote in city is one and two, which I remember being pretty good.
Okay.
He wrote coodies, which I did not see.
In city is one is awesome.
In city is two is completely panned.
I think if you take the oh shit factor out of the saw movies, meaning the whole audience goes, oh shit.
Because a lady gets like her eyelids caught in a mouse trap or something.
I think if you kind of take that part out of it, nobody is watching saw going, woof, the writing.
Except that first saw.
I don't, I don't love saw, I don't love the saw franchise, but there was a genuine story and twist and everything else to the first saw.
You can't argue that.
I thought you were a saw fan.
I don't hate the franchise.
I hated saw one when I saw it in the theater.
I hated it.
I thought it.
I think in your, in your rush to condemn Mr. Juan L, you're throwing saw out with the bathwater and it doesn't have to happen.
Now, I liked upgrade.
Okay, you know, I thought it was a pretty cool movie.
I liked the invisible man a lot, although I only saw it once.
And we will get to the wolf man, but this feels like something bad went on.
Obviously, I mean, it's a goddamn mess.
I looked up the budget when this started.
So it says it grossed 33 million at the box office.
So I'm like, oh, okay, well, that's a bomb.
But obviously it only cost $30, right?
There were no special effects at all in the goddamn thing.
It was a guy in a shitty mask.
And when you look up, it says the film was a financial failure compared to its $150 million budget.
That's insane.
That's what the Irishman budget was.
Not a...
No, it's $50 million more.
The Irishman was $100 million.
And the wolf man was $150 million.
And you have the biggest stars of all time.
This movie stars Christopher Abbott, who would star in an independent movie I made on my iPhone if I asked him this afternoon.
Good afternoon.
After I liking.
Pat, we're fired up here.
I'm going to propose we do something we've never done on this show.
I'm going to propose we move right into the review of the wolf man at the top.
And we'll do the movie corner after.
Why not?
That's fine.
Now I'm already wound up because now when I Google anything, I get an AI overview.
Hey, you know that thing that's about to destroy your livelihood in the next couple of years.
Now you have to see it every time you ask a question.
Do you trust it?
Don't know yet.
It's brand...
Oh gee, but I guess so.
You're fired up today.
Do me a favor.
Check your audio level.
Make sure you're not peaking when you talk.
That's all.
I love the editors.
He call over these listeners.
It's not a criticism.
No, I'm even went...
Now maybe a little bit high there on input volume.
Yeah.
I'll bring it down a little.
But I love the heat.
Okay, cool.
I love the heat.
It's...
All right.
The wolf man.
Starring Christopher Abbott.
I didn't know who that was until I saw this.
Who is that?
So I quite like Christopher Abbott.
He had an excellent arc on girls as a really self-destructive boyfriend of Marne's.
And then he's been in a lot of movies.
Which one's Marne?
He...
Marne is...
Alison Williams.
Okay.
See the ass eater?
See the one that eats her ass?
He doesn't eat her ass, unfortunately.
I'm sure he regrets not taking that opportunity.
But he's actually been in a lot of stuff.
If you look at his...
And he's got good taste.
I mean, he's in a lot of acclaimed small...
He was in poor things, so you have seen him.
He was in...
Okay.
Who was he a zesser?
Who was he in poor things?
General Alfred Blesington.
I think he got turned into a goat, if memory serves.
He played this exact same part in the wolf man.
And it comes at night.
The two movies look and feel identical to each other.
And they have the same star.
That was like that first A24, John.
It comes at night.
Okay.
He's been in a lot of shit.
I generally like him.
And Julia Garner is excellent on Ozark.
In this movie, it's like Muppet Babies.
She comes in and she's like,
Dinner's not ready?
Just had a hard day at the office.
And you're like, honey.
Maybe you just got out of your sophomore year at high school.
But we are not buying this community college play that you're acting.
It's wild.
The woman looks 16 years old.
They've got her as a mother of an 11 year old.
I mean, this is nuts.
And I think she is 30.
But like on Ozark, she plays a 16 year old.
And she's a foul mouth like ball-breaking bitch.
You pull it gun in her face.
She's like, shoot it, you fucking mother fucker.
That's her part.
She like commands the screen.
She destroys J and Laura Linnie in their showdowns.
And somehow in this movie, she comes off like a child.
It's very bizarre to me.
She is...
Well, let's just move right in.
She's terrible in this movie.
I mean, she's terrible.
Like I was like, maybe she just tapped out because she was like, we were in trouble here, guys.
I think there is something to that.
You know, like from...
I'll dress it from a comedian standpoint.
If you're a comic and you're on a bad show because the producers are assholes and they...
You know, they fucked the show up and the crowd is rowdy and nobody's policing the room.
You know, as a comic a lot of the time, you'll dress it and kind of throw the show to be like, this sucks.
And I'm not going to sit there and pretend like it's okay.
I think actors kind of do that in movies when they think the movie is sucks.
They're like, you'll see for my performance that I was not happy to be there.
And I don't believe in this fucking thing.
So that seemed to be what she was maybe doing.
I don't know, but God damn, she's bad.
And when that is happening on set, I have experienced that.
You want to just throw the person into traffic.
It's like you're making $5 million for eight weeks of work.
Bring it.
Bring your limited talents to the game.
And it just wasn't happening.
I'm looking now, it says Ryan Gosling left the project due to production delays.
I'm sure that was the reason.
But his creative influence remains in the script.
So I don't know what he had to do with this goddamn mess.
But films development was impacted by the COVID-19 pandemic and Hollywood strikes.
But to me, director 1L praised the extra time for helping to refine the movie.
Oh boy.
To me, this feels like a classic Blumhouse.
And that to me, this was a $5 million movie with no big stars and a killer premise.
The Wolfman.
And they just completely botched it, but oh well, because it falls under this Blumhouse umbrella,
or Blum Brella, if you will, where we only lose $5 million.
So who cares?
That's their bit.
But when I'm seeing this cost 150, I don't know who to believe.
This is 150 is insane.
I hope that's inflated, but I don't know.
That's insane.
And also to, I love that the, well, I just, I feel that the Blumhouse agenda is really started to become exposed.
Because they skated for a long time on, but we had a message.
And that message was one of importance about women.
And I think they got a pass on a lot of their bad fucking product.
I've been calling this company, you know, and their bad product out for years on this show.
I stand by it.
I don't care what your message is.
You got to make a good movie.
This movie is fucking terrible.
It is fucking terrible.
Now let's start at the beginning.
The, the universal Wolfman.
This is a movie about what Lawrence Talbot.
Nobody in the movie is called in this new one.
It's called Lawrence Talbot.
Nobody's even called Talbot.
It's just a, of all new names.
I don't personally mind taking it in a new direction, new characters.
I'll, I'll say I don't mind that.
We've had enough classic Wolfmans.
Okay.
But if you're saying we're remaking the Wolfman, then remake the Wolfman.
Otherwise, just call it, call it Wolfie.
I don't fucking know whatever.
I don't know what you call it at this point.
You know, call it Man Are Wolves, which is really what you're trying to say here.
Yeah.
With about as much subtlety.
So, and our remake of the Wolfman, the only connective tissue to the original Lawn
Cheney Jr. film is that our main character is returning home and his family is in some
way tied into likenism, which we will get to.
I don't even remember if in the original Lawn Cheney one, like, yeah, because it's his
brother gets murdered by a wolf.
That's what it was.
And then in the Benicio del Toro one, the dad, Anthony Hopkins, turns out to be the
werewolf that's attacking people.
I don't think they do that in the Lawn Cheney one at all.
But anyway, they don't, but kind of a cool twist.
And we can discuss that Wolfman as well, now that we both seen it.
But anyway, it opens with a pretty riveting sequence where it's the 1993 or something.
It's a father and his son.
They live out in rural.
Where the hell are they?
Washington state or something like that or Oregon or something like that.
They live in this beautiful countryside.
And the father sort of disciplines his son military style.
You know, they show the dad waking the son up in the morning and he goes,
10 hut and the kid gets up and like, make sure that his bed is perfectly made and everything.
And then the dad takes the kid hunting and the dad is hammering the kid with safety protocol
as they're hunting.
And you think the dad's an asshole.
You're like, what's wrong with this guy?
And then what happens?
They spot a wolf man in the woods and the dad goes into like lock down mode, which
by the way, if the dad's aware of the wolf man possibility, it's odd to take your kid
hunting in those very woods that you're trying to protect him from.
But anyway, I know as a father, if I were to be asked, hey, where would you most likely
find a wolf?
Man.
My number one answer would be the woods.
So I take my kid to David Buster's where I know there will be no wolves.
So that's just me.
Maybe that's why I'm not a father.
So they encounter the wolf man, the dad, you know, goes into like super survival mode
with the kid.
They climb up into this like deer hunting tree house thing.
I forget what it's called.
And the wolf man is at the base of it and you hear him sort of rattling the base of
it and he's going to climb.
And it's a tense scene and you're like, this is pretty cool, man.
And then what happens?
Nothing.
The wolf man just goes away, which does make sense by the way, and I'll circle back to
this later, because a wolf is not an apex predator.
It's not a philosopher raptor, a wolf attacks in defense or to hunt or whatever, but they
don't attack for no reason.
And they certainly don't seek you out the way like a bear does when it gets a blood
center or something.
So yeah.
So it makes sense that the wolf kind of goes after them and then they're hidden and
the wolf is like, okay, whatever, it goes away.
The wolf man, excuse me.
And then they go back home and the dad gets on a CB radio and says, I saw it.
I saw it today.
It's real.
And then we cut to, you know, 30 years later, whatever the hell it is.
It's an odd opening because you're waiting for something to happen.
There's an immense buildup that's where you believe something is going to happen.
And it ends with absolutely nothing.
And that's when I thought, okay, we're in trouble here.
We're in trouble here.
That opening didn't have any kills.
Didn't have any real scares.
This is not going to be good.
And now we meet the father who is now 40, right?
Yes.
Or so with his daughter and they live in New York City.
And the dad who you think is going to be like this extra gushing, loving, emotional,
nurturing dad to his daughter because his father was so hard on him.
No, he's just like his dad.
He's kind of an asshole, which by the way, takes away any tragedy of him turning into
the wolf.
Yeah.
You don't care.
Correct.
Yeah, it's like there's a million ways to go with this.
You know, like the alcoholism is the wolf.
You know, like he's a drinker and we sink it up that way.
But however you do it, it should be about, in this case, man's temper and how he can't
control it.
And if you want to tie in, you know, the sins of the father, you can.
It's easy to do.
The deltoral wolf man did it.
But you're right that they sort of choose nothing.
There's no real clear theme.
And the wolf man, every bit as much as the invisible man, lends itself to like obvious
themes, obvious themes that this movie just doesn't really explore.
Here's the thing.
The theme is as far as I can tell.
The theme is supposed to be that the, as you just said, the sins of the father, in fact,
the sins of the son or manifest the sins in the son or whatever.
To me, that is what the theme was supposed to be.
It was supposed to be that this toxic masculinity, even when it is applied to survival and
whatever, is passed from father to son and it's something now that the son struggles.
Okay, fine, fine.
But then when he gets attacked and starts turning, make it that the wife is like, we've
been in this abusive, he's not abusive, but you know what I mean?
Up the ante and make it like we've been in this abusive scenario.
And now he's literally becoming a monster.
Do it fucking a, a, a, a tales from the Hood style, the David Allen Greer story and tales
of it.
Do it like that where he's a literal monster.
And they don't do that.
Instead, they just kind of make him sort of a dick.
And then when he turns, the wife is like, I need you and I want you and what happened?
It's like, you do make it that you don't want him.
And now you're stuck with this and it's a problem and you've got to get out of it.
Like none of the decisions, there's no commitment to anything.
None of the decisions are firm.
Yeah.
None of the choices are distinct.
This is a soft, soft movie, down to the fact that there is one kill in the entire
movie.
One person dies in the Wolfman movie.
Yeah, it's so lacking in like action.
And then you're dating for the transformation.
We've seen it in American Werewolf.
Any, any documentary like shutter does these.
Let's look at the best horror movies of all time.
Whenever they talk werewolves, they talk the best transformation scenes ever.
The howling American Werewolf.
There's been several.
And this movie decides just not to compete.
Even with all the technology we have at our disposal, it decides just to simply not
do a transformation scene.
It's like, it's literally like he goes behind a curtain and comes out and he's a wolf.
But the wolf looks so dumb and bad also.
The creature design that Joe showed me a year ago and I said, all right, I actually can't
believe that that's the wolf, man.
I won't believe it and I don't believe that a studio would fund that movie.
It pretty much is what the Wolfman looks like.
A little like billak hint or like the Notre Dame mascot.
It's ridiculous and not scary.
They and it's funny.
I went back and rewatch that footage and I was like, how are we questioning this?
He's in the park standing in front of Wolfman logos.
I was like, yeah, they put it right in our face.
We were all like, that can't be real.
And like, oh, it's 100% real.
It was, well, just because with the amount of people that's have to sign off on every
decision, it's just so hard to believe that you could show that photo to a room of anyone,
even as dumb as these executives are and that everybody in unison would go, yep, that's
our wolf, man.
I don't understand.
Well, you're talking about the company that went to what's her name?
Who's the lady from the lady from wet hot American summer, the blonde Elizabeth banks.
Elizabeth banks.
This is the company that went to Elizabeth banks and said, take your pick.
You're directing any any one of the universal properties you want.
Remember when Blumhouse did that and we were like, what?
Yeah.
The lady that directed, what did she even direct?
Did she direct power rangers?
No, she just played the bad guy in it.
What the hell?
Yeah.
Anyway, so the plot is they're in New York.
I don't want to say, by the way, that tales from the hood may have been more effective because
David Allen Greer is one of history's greatest monsters.
So I didn't require any acting.
I was hesitant to bring his name up, but it was crucial for the reference.
I usually cannot hear his name this early in the morning without blacking out for a while,
but so I'm getting stronger.
I'm getting stronger.
Um, the plot thickens when our new fat or New York family gets a notice that his father
has finally been declared dead after missing for a long time and that he has inherited the
farm he grew up on.
They go back to the farm.
They meet a stranger.
They're completely lost in the wilderness.
They see a guy who's out in the woods hunting hunting hunting.
Folks, I'm going to say it again, hunting.
Here's why I'm stressing this.
They're lost.
They asked the guy for directions.
The guy knows the dad from when they were kids and he goes, uh, you know what, I'll hop
in.
I'll tell you where we're going.
The wife immediately go in a turn that makes her the most unlikable character on planet
earth goes absolutely not.
He has a gun.
I mean, it's the hunter.
Yes.
The hunter in the woods in Oregon.
Yes, he has a gun.
Yeah.
This is what he's doing.
He's waiting with a hunting rifle with a scope on it for a family to come along so he
can car jack them.
It amidst the pine trees in Oregon, you stupid fucking idiot.
Uh, and then when he finds the family, he doesn't wait to cut, car jack them.
He says, I'm going to let them come to me.
Yeah.
I'm going to let them approach me before I do this.
So anyway, he shows them where his farm is, uh, which that was confusing.
It's like, you can't find your house that you grew up in like what?
I mean, it just was so anyway.
And that was pointless.
There was no point to that sequence other than we need a guy we can kill.
And I thought, by the way, I was like, Oh, this is good.
They're going to set up that she hates him or not hates him, but doesn't trust this guy.
This guy's going to direct them.
He's going to get creepier as the trip goes.
He's going to take them to their place.
He's going to disappear.
And then later, he's going to be the one that saves them.
No, they don't do that at all.
Van gets attacked by the current wolf man out in the woods.
This guy dies because for some inexplicable reason, the wolf man, well, no, I guess, never
mind.
I take that back.
I won't even finish that point because it was dumb.
This guy dies in the process of the attack.
The dad gets scratched, not bitten, but scratched.
Not even attacked, scratched.
And then the three of them find the house.
Somehow the house they couldn't fucking find when they were in a car with a GPS.
They now find it on foot after being turned upside down in the truck they were driving.
And they take shelter in the house and they know there's a werewolf or something.
They don't know what it is, but there's a monster outside.
The dad starts to transform in the house.
They think he's losing his, he's like sweating, losing his teeth, noises become louder.
But like, you know, it might as well be a play the way they handle this.
This by the way, Pat, I'm glad you mentioned the noises thing.
This was the dumbest, most inconsistent thing in the whole movie that he hears this thumping.
This incessent thumping, he doesn't know what it is and it's so loud and it's like rattling
his brain.
And he is searching through the house frantically to find the source of the thumping.
And he finally goes all the way upstairs into a back bedroom and opens a closet and sees
it's a spider walking on the wall that he can hear the leg prints with stamps, whatever
of the spider against the wall.
And it's like, you any noise would definitely, why is it that that is, but his wife talks
to him and it's fine.
Like it doesn't make any sense whatsoever.
The borderline derelict sitting behind me at the mall when I saw this movie made that
point.
He leans over and he's like, no, wait a minute.
And sometimes I just don't have that kind of mind when I sit down for a movie where I'm
trying to find fault.
I'm trying to enjoy myself usually.
I try not to put on my critical hat.
But this guy just had me laugh because he was so dumb and all of his comments were so
dumb, but this was so spot on.
He's like, so he can hear this spider in another room.
Wouldn't his wife yelling kill him?
His wife standing right next to him yelling and I was like, yes.
And how did everyone miss this?
That guy, yeah, that guy stands up and addresses the theater.
Folks, I know I'm the shoelace guy carrying a bottle of his own urine, but I think I have
a point.
Can he just discuss this?
Jimmy Stewart style.
He's like, no, what I'll wait just a minute.
I don't know.
He's here in the spider like it's cannon fire.
And we're supposed to not just wait a damn minute.
Yeah, it was crazy.
It was crazy.
Anyway, they eventually are now this is the part.
This is this really bothered me.
The wolf man outside is like stalking them now.
He's like lurking around the outside of their house like and he's trying to get into
the house to hurt them and it's like guys, this isn't like what a what a wolf does.
Watch any other werewolf movie.
The wolf doesn't hunt you and terrorize you.
It's like you encounter it and it's a wild beast and it kills you on the spot and keeps
it moving like that's what it does.
So this bothered me.
Of course, the reveal that you know is coming is that his dad is the werewolf.
And then you're like, okay, I guess this is kind of cool.
The son is going to become a wolf and protect the family.
And that's cool, which does happen.
He does kill the dad.
But then the son becomes like full wolf, which again is indesernable from half wolf because
because wolf man means you just get like like like bushy eyebrows and it's like it's
crazy.
He looks like like Tommy Lee Jones in a period piece, you know, like yeah.
Yeah, what are the rules here?
And in a movie with if we're counting the wolf, four characters, why do we not have a
clear and established set of rules for this wolf?
This thing is introducing and abandoning rules and logic in every scene to the point
where you just don't care.
It's like I always cite Gremlins.
You can call Gremlins a kids movie.
You can call it, you know, dumb, whatever you want to call it.
It sets its rules incredibly clearly from the beginning and it doesn't deviate.
Now you can say, well, it's after midnight all the time, isn't it?
Whatever.
You're being a bitch.
You know what the rules are and you can engage.
If you don't know the rules, you can't engage.
Pat, the scene, the scene where he minimally transfers and it's supposed to be the big
transformation scene.
He stands up from the ground, yeah, after arriving around in full their version of wolf mode.
Yeah.
Camera pans around.
He does the like chest out, claws out, pose that all wolf men do.
So it tilts his head up to the sky as the camera's panning around.
I'm going, okay, they're going to reveal a full moon.
There's going to be a great shot and they don't, they just go to the trees and the trees
start glowing.
I guess to show you like that's how he sees the trees, I guess.
I was like, what the fuck is going on?
Yeah.
Now, from here, from here, it's mother and daughter trying to beat the wolf or survive the
one.
Pat, you want to go to...
It's Kooja.
Exactly.
We've got a lot of lost opportunity here.
Why does the mother not die protecting the daughter?
Why does it not be like, here's the wolf, she becomes the bitch, she's going to protect
her cubs.
It'll be tragic, but heroic because she will kill him and also die per saving the daughter.
Like, that's a fucking ending and it doesn't happen.
You do, you do aliens.
You do get away from her, you bitch and the whole place cheers.
It's in, it's like obsession to not be cliche.
The movie makes no choices and it is not dramatic or exciting or fun ever, ever.
Terrible movie.
Yeah.
It's a terrible, terrible, terrible.
Terrible movie.
Yeah, it's really bad and I will say...
So I just started seeing AI pop up for Google last week.
I don't know how long that's been going on.
A while.
The budget of this movie according to Wikipedia, the budget is $20 million and it was still
a bomb because with production and ads and everything, 35 is not good enough.
But AI, the first thing everyone sees now, not Wikipedia, not IMDB.
The first thing everyone sees, the IMDB result, had that wrong by $125 million and I reported
it as fact even though I said that seems wrong and now that I've looked, it is confirmed
wrong.
What is the future of America hold if that is our source of knowledge?
We're fucked.
We're done.
I was in a, I had to take my car to the shop this morning here in Pennsylvania.
I was maybe a mile from my house, maybe.
It was 20 degrees.
I would have walked home.
It's so cold.
Yeah, I was like, I can't do this walk right now.
It's too much.
I called an Uber.
I didn't like the Uber prices so I jumped over to lift, see the lift prices.
The starting price for lift in Pennsylvania to go one mile was $36.
Beating Uber's terrible price of 17, which was also insane.
I was like 17.
This is like a $6 ride.
What are we doing here?
Is it surge pricing or what?
That big Friday morning, 7am surge.
It was about eight o'clock in the morning, 8.30.
I guess maybe there weren't a lot of drivers.
Maybe.
That's what it was, but we're in rough shape, folks.
This is not going to go well.
Oh, yeah.
I'm praying for a Wolfman to come get me quite frankly.
Well, at least bite me so that I can go live in the woods and have a better time.
That'd be a great last line to a Wolfman movie.
If the way the Wolfman turns people's bites them and then the hero at the end goes, hey,
Wolfman, bite me and the thing turns around and he shoots it.
That'd be a great last line.
Our heroes suicidal are something.
At the end, he's like, I don't give a fuck.
Hey, bitch, he turns around.
Bite me.
Love it.
Bite this.
Well, it's like, you know, Universal, I'm just reading all the different people through
the years who have toyed with doing various versions of the Wolfman.
There's tons.
There's just tons and you got to wonder were all the other options worse than this?
I don't believe that.
I actually don't believe that.
Well, what are you going to do this with Gosling and Derek Sian France?
Now, he's a really great director, Blue Valentine, place beyond the pines.
Oh, wow.
That would have been something special.
But you just get the feeling these people are like, I'm on a sinking ship and I got to
get the fuck out of here.
Pat, it's almost like Jason Blum doesn't know what he's doing.
It is.
Yeah.
I just heard him on Smart List.
If you want a full interview with the guy who I had never heard speak before, I just heard
him on Smart List.
And he seems very intelligent, but he seems like a man who doesn't know or care about film
in any way.
He talks like, you know, Mosque or Bezos or something.
He's like, well, you know, I got to get my money.
You know, like he's obsessed with money.
As all movie producers are, not a crime, but to also then act, it's like what Ted
Sarandos does.
Well, I'm also this great lover and supporter of international film.
No, you're not.
Stop.
I am so tired of the cinematic model for success being.
We didn't spend a lot and we made a ton.
I'm just tired of it.
I get that that's an interesting part and I get that that's a very beneficial part.
And we'd all like to spend a little bit of money and make a lot.
But it's become the only criteria for what is considered success in the world of cinema,
in an American cinema.
It's disgraceful.
I have been, you know, if one more fucking person tells me that Marvel sucks now, I'm going
to choke them.
It's like, I've been saying this for four fucking years, at least.
Marvel has sucked for years.
But everybody's so fucking gassed up on, you know, MTV movie award popularity with these
stupid fucking releases and what they think is supposed to be cool because it made money.
And it has popular people in it.
It's just fucking gross, man.
It's just gross.
You see the director of that Adrian Brody movie, the brutalist, he said he made zero money
off of the movie.
He's like, I've never made a dime off of any of my movies, including this one.
And he never will, you know, and then they don't get on people the way they used to.
Thank God about quote selling out because fuck you.
You know, the brutalist wasn't as much as I respected it.
It wasn't quite for me.
I didn't see Vox Lux, the guy's other movie with Natalie Portman.
I heard it's interesting at least.
But it is a crime to have a guy.
And then he's talking about how he has to spend six months on the award serve.
He's unpaid for as well.
Wait, say that again.
You broke up.
They're like, you got to do the dance.
You got to go out, do all these interviews, talk to all the film magazines, go to Sundance,
and then he said, he's been promoting the brutalist for six months.
And trying to get it to where it's at now, where it's nominated for everything, maybe
going to win best picture.
But the studio puts that all on him and doesn't pay him to promote his own film.
So he's like, I finally made some money.
I did a couple commercials in Mexico.
And it's like, that's what people have to do now.
You do your passion thing and then hope somebody will pay you to cash out.
But that's not how it should be.
It's terrible.
I'm getting ready to do a show for a network now that got picked up.
And the budget they offered was so low, it was like, well, I'd almost rather shoot this
independently, like tires.
You know, like, I'd almost rather control this and not have to put up with your constant
bullshit if you're going to offer me this little money.
You're basically not picking up my show.
You're saying like, yeah, we'll do it for the lowest barrel.
And the thing is a movie like Blair Witch was made for $30,000 in gross $300 million.
But that's because, like it or hate it, it was a special thing.
It was a new thing that thrived on creativity and the people who passionately tried to make
that thing happen and bring it to life.
And then, oh, look, we stumbled into some money.
You can't reverse engineer that and make a shitty product for no money that looks like
shit.
And hope you're going to do great.
The product needs to be great.
Yeah.
Should be making a bunch of $1 million movies and supporting up and coming filmmakers
and taking that risk.
And some of them will hit and some of them won't.
Some of them will hit on a get out level, though, which eliminates all your debt.
You're fine.
But the fact that Blum, who's making all these $5 million movies, doesn't set aside $10 million
to make $10 million a year and actually do something to support up and coming filmmakers
is sick.
Yeah.
That's a gamble to you.
Blum, $10 million?
Come on.
I had a meeting, excuse me, I had a meeting recently about my script with an independent
producer that works for an independent production company.
And I was all excited because I was like, you know, man, they're looking for horror.
I'm going to talk to them.
They're looking to make things within the budget of this script.
This is grassroots shit.
This is, this is, okay, finally, going to get some movement here.
And I talked to the guy and all he did was talk about how he couldn't pursue my project
because it shaved sort of, sort of, similarly, thematically to another project he was working
on that he was trying to get merely, merely a cooness in.
Okay, great.
You can have two projects with a theme about women.
First of all, second of all, and then all he did was keep telling me, you know, if you
have anything like this because you know, I'll tell you what, Netflix wants this.
And this is, and it's like, you're an independent producer.
Yeah.
I don't need you to tell me what the fuck Netflix, I know what Netflix wants.
I have friends at Netflix.
I can take this to Netflix myself.
The reason I'm fucking talking to you is because I don't want to do that because it's
a headache.
I need to, I need to add more people to this soup so you can go walk it across the street
for me.
Not independent production companies and producers, not all of them.
A lot of them are functioning like middle agents.
What do I need you for?
Well, they've got candy bars in that 7-11 so I can get you one.
I can go get it.
What the fuck do I need you for?
You know what I mean?
Either give me a candy bar right here in the middle of the street or I will go over to
the 7-11 and buy my own this shit where these people, everybody's just positioning themselves
to cow-tow, to whatever the latest boss is.
You know, and this makes relevant your AI rant.
You know, a big part of this is algorithm.
You know, that Maya Hawk just had that interview, which he said.
I can't delete my Instagram because they're telling me like I won't get hired.
Like this is insane.
This is insane.
So it's not going to change.
And by the way, it's proven to me nothing.
I'm friends with these guys who worked on this show called Undatable and it was a multi-cam
with Chris DeLia and Ron Function.
I remember.
And it lasted about three years.
It was a, and it didn't do great out the gate so they decided to make it a live show.
Every Friday night they do a live show.
And the network is like we got to get this ticked, even ticked out at the time.
This vine guy or this Twitter guy or this, this Instagram personality to come by and visit
the show because they'll announce to their followers, their millions of followers.
You guys got to watch Undatable Friday night.
I'm appearing.
And they did it every week for like 60 episodes and it never had a effect on the ratings
positively or negatively at all.
And every week they would say you got to get another influencer on the show.
It's unbelievable.
They don't even look at the science of their strategy.
It's like, so you think people that want to watch, insesently watch, four second long videos
want to sit and watch a 30 minute TV show?
They don't even understand that much of it.
It's fucking idiotic, man.
It's idiotic.
They have lost all concept of if you present a, I just rewatched Malcolm X.
It's the scene where Elijah Muhammad and Malcolm X are in the office and he has the
two glasses of water and he puts the ink in the one and he goes, yeah, offer this to
people.
They will drink it.
But if you offer them this, the clean, pure thing, they have a choice and they will
choose purity.
It's that.
It's that they have lost the concept of giving the people the choice of choosing pure
water.
They think like, oh, well, they seem to like the dirty water.
So we have to keep chasing that.
It's like, you don't have to keep chasing it.
You don't.
Or maybe you do because there's some global economic, a secret group of skulls at play here
that I am unaware of and I don't understand what's happening.
But I don't know.
It's just, it's just fascinating to me.
I'm going to shoot my, I think I'm going to shoot my movie myself.
I'm talking to some friends about it.
And it's the way to do it.
We've talked a lot of shit on here about the Duplos brothers.
I think needlessly and I think irresponsibly there was, there's been no reason for us to
ever talk shit about the Duplos is they've been pioneers of modern independent film one.
And now they're really leading the charge, particularly on, on you broke up again.
They're leading the charge, particularly what?
Particularly Mark Duplos on independent television production.
They had a show on Max, a horror show, Room 233 or something that I didn't really watch.
But like they're doing, you know, the creep tapes on Shutter is picked up for its third
season and is one of their biggest successes.
But they do them themselves.
They don't involve any production company.
They raise the money.
They shoot it.
They bring it to a distributor.
They say, look, it stars Mark Duplos, who's been doing it for a long time.
Who doesn't put asses in the seats, but people know who he is.
He's on the morning show.
You get the feeling he's doing the morning show to fund the other projects.
And he's become sort of this modern day on a much, much smaller scale, like a Roger
Corman.
He's literally working the system to get the money to keep making independent shit and
then selling it to the majors and making a great profit at it.
And as soon as ten people notice what he's doing over there, these studios are in great
danger because we used to go into them for the money at least.
And now they don't even have that.
Their notes were always shit.
Their creative thoughts were always shit.
And if you don't even have the money to pay me or to make this a production that doesn't
look like it was shot, you know, at a laser tag facility, then I'm not going to watch
it.
Period.
There's better production value on TikTok sometimes.
I just watched a trailer for Walter Hill made a western with Willem DeFoe and I think
Nick Nalti.
Okay.
And I'm not remembering the name of it.
Hold on.
Let's see here.
Walter Hill.
Yeah, because I was I had watched, well, I'll save it for the movie corner.
But I just, you know, I was watching something of his and I was like, well, what's this guy
up to these days?
So anyway, he had made a movie called 2022 was his last movie.
It was called Dead for a Dollar.
I'm sorry, not Nick Nalti.
It was Christopher Waltz in Willem DeFoe.
I was like, and Rachel, and Rachel, uh, bras in the hand.
Um, I was like, wow, okay, that's a good cast.
Oh, shit.
And it's a western.
This is cool.
Walter Hill.
So I look up the trailer.
It, first of all, it made $81,000 at the box office.
But this thing, this is Walter fucking hell.
This is, this guy was one of the Titans.
This thing looks like it was shot on iPads.
I mean, it, the quality was so low.
And, but it's a period piece full wet, which is always weird to me when like a full period
piece looks cheap because you're like the, the set cost and the costume cost.
That's very high.
Yeah.
Then the camera work looks terrible.
So it was confusing and it was tragic on two levels.
It was tragic to see Walter Hill being reduced to having to shoot something on that
shoestring of a budget, even with the talent that was in it.
Christopher Walsen, well, those are two big names still.
Yeah.
Um, but so, so broad in the hand.
I've never seen it.
But that show was huge.
Yeah.
But then furthermore, what was even sadder was reading the comments on the YouTube trailer
where people were saying like, you know, what a disgrace to have these two stars in
a movie on this cheap.
Oh, hey, director, what'd you shoot it on?
iPhones, what are, and it was like, as you read the comments, you realize nobody knows
who Walter Hill is.
Yeah.
They don't even realize this is, this is not your, they're talking.
Warriors.
Yeah, they're talking like this is a guy that's like, it's amateur hours.
It's like, no, this is a guy that's amazing.
That's being forced to do this.
Yeah.
Well, to, to me, even sadder is that Joe Danty is like the in house.
And then, you know, I think that's what I'm saying.
I think that's what I'm saying.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, let's close it out with a movie corner.
I will do documentaries this week.
I will start with Sligh Lives, aka the burden of black genius directed by Questlove, who
is coming out with a very good documentary every six months in addition to like his
storied career as a musician on Spanleader, less storied in that latter example.
But he's a really good director.
His SNL music documentary on peacock is killer, especially the mashups at the beginning
of it.
I've watched that three times now.
I just think it's so well done.
And this is really well done too.
I love Sligh and the Family Stone.
And aside from knowing Sligh Stone had a drug problem that impacted his career, I didn't
really know much about them.
So this was great.
It was way more in depth than like the Beach Boys doc that Hulu put out way more in depth
than the Jim Henson doc that Disney Plus put out.
And it's just really well done.
Sligh Stone is a fascinating guy.
There's all kinds, you know, Andre 3000 and you know, big music people of the day talk
about how great they were, how influential they were.
But to me, the really fascinating and kind of cautionary stuff was just how much drugs
and alcohol can destroy your genius, especially for prone to anxiety, mental illness.
You know, he was a very anxious guy.
Did not like the spotlight.
And that's not a good combo when you're thrust into the spotlight.
It's very well done.
I really enjoyed it.
You know, they talk to like George Clinton and all these people that used to do the drugs
with him.
And they talk to Qtip and a lot of hip hop legends and people have great funny stories and great
sad stories.
And there's a lot of great music and it will definitely guide you to check out more than
just the Sligh and the Family Stone singles.
Because I do feel he is sort of weirdly unharleded, especially because of what a direct palpable
influence he had on prints in particular.
And how much prints and outcasts talked up, Slice Stone.
You just don't hear them cited that much nowadays.
So I'm glad that this documentary exists.
It was very well done.
Um, well, uh, in the spirit of Walter Hill, uh, I watched another 48 hours.
I'd never seen the sequel.
I was completely panned by critics.
Apparently there's a much longer version of the movie that's never been released that
is even more violent and fills out a lot of the story that was cut.
The movie was shaved down to 89 minutes at the last minute by the studio because the
studio panicked because another movie that was popular that week of release or that month
of release was only 89 minutes.
So they said we have to shave our movie.
I mean, these are the fucking decisions.
These idiot fucking morons make.
But anyway, yeah.
What was that other movie?
It's Angle and Cash, something like that.
I don't remember.
It was on the Wikipedia.
But so anyway, I, you know, they said the version that was released was terrible and blah,
blah, blah.
So I went in with hesitance, but skepticism rather.
But I enjoyed it.
I thought it was a fun 80s action movie.
It felt like I think it came out in 1990 actually.
But it's certainly bigger and flashier than the first one.
It's not quite as gritty.
It's not quite as character driven.
But at the end of the day, I had a good time watching it.
Eddie Murphy charming as always, Nick Nalti fun to watch.
And I thought as far as like 80s action movies go, it was a fun watch, man.
You know, again, Walter Hill directed it.
So it's very well directed.
Even with the cuts and edits and whatever, it was, it was well written, I thought and,
and made sense story wise.
I would love to see this other version that has so much more in, you know, involving
the characters and, and flushing them out and whatever.
But I guess that's not going to happen.
So anyway, another 48 hours.
I think it's worth a watch, especially if you like the first one.
Yeah, remember when I finally caught up to it feeling like, well, this isn't the disaster
it was made out to be, but also not.
I think the bars fall in so low that failures become at least adequate.
I thought that move was all right.
Also very weird that at that time, Nick Nalti was considered our sexiest man alive.
That is odd.
I don't know.
And when you ask women, like I asked my mom, was that legit?
She's like, no, no one I ever knew has ever said Nick Nalti was attractive ever.
I'm like, well, all right.
I do like the man.
And again, I'll recommend a fiction as I always do.
I watched this is the Tom Green documentary directed by Tom Green.
I thought that I was sort of unfamiliar with Tom Green outside of Freddie got fingered.
My recollection was that I saw Freddie got fingered and it was my first exposure to him.
And then when I sat down and watched this, I realized that I have seen tons of footage
and episodes of the Tom Green show.
And weirdly, what made me connect the dots was his side guy, his Andy Richter, that guy
Glenn Humplock, the kind of heavy set guy that was his right hand man.
I was like, oh, wait.
I used to watch this all the time in my friend's house.
And Tom Green was never in any incarnation my thing.
They talk about how Jackass replaced him when he went away to get his testicular cancer
surgery.
They replaced him with Jackass, which blew him out of the water and became a much bigger
phenomenon.
I personally prefer Jackass and I always did.
But when they talk to Steve O and the Jackass crew, they're devastated by it.
They're like, we were obsessed with the Tom Green show.
This was our Bible.
This was the only, this was we ran home to watch this.
And a lot of people are that way.
A lot of people talk about how much they love the show, what it meant to them, big people.
I always found it so cool that Letterman loved Tom Green that he loved, be with some
bloodhead that he supported these dumb, funny, stoner, comedy things, even in his 40s and
50s.
And there's a lot of that.
He got some praise.
He got some flowers.
It's a sad story as well.
You get the feeling he genuinely loved Drew Barrymore and she loved him, but he did not
know how to connect to a woman.
And that is a sad truth of a lot of males in comedy, for sure.
I don't know about women in comedy, never dated one.
But I just thought this was really well done.
It's sad.
There are definite moments that he leaves in this thing where he just starts crying because
of what he's lost in terms of his career and fame.
I watched his stand-up special too, which was not amazing, but certainly not a failure.
I found it funny.
A lot of it is kind of, can you believe I'm playing this shitty theater doing stand-up
when I used to be this, when I used to be this major star?
And I hope he can get past that and let that go.
At times in the documentary, it seems like he has and at other times it seems like he
hasn't.
There's a real sadness to it, but I came away feeling like I understood and got Tom Green,
way better than ever before.
And if you're a fan or even interested in the man, I recommend you check it out.
I will watch it.
I'm lucky enough to have become friends with Tom over the years.
He's a really, really good dude.
Really good dude.
Like genuinely.
That comes through, yeah.
And funny.
Really funny.
Like he does like Tom Green, when you're hanging out with him and it's super funny.
And he's a good time.
He looks to throw a few beers back and, you know, like he's a great dude, man.
I have one more in the spirit of independent film.
I rewatch Disorder Release.
Hey, the movie makes me laugh.
It's the fat boys doing the three stooges.
They're slapping the shit out of each other throughout the entire movie.
You know, and the thing that killed me was the Disorder Release is about the guy that played
Luke of Luke and Lara fame of the soaps.
He's the nephew of a very rich uncle played by Ralph Bellamy.
He wants his uncle dead so he can inherit all of his uncle's money because he's got gambling
debts.
The way he's going to do this is he's going to fire the uncle's competent orderlies
and find the worst orderlies in the country.
So they initiate the uncle's demise through their own stupidity.
So the fat boys play the orderlies.
He brings them in their mistakes and up leading to the uncle getting healthier.
The uncle loves them wants to keep them around.
Now this guy's got to get four people out of the way instead of one.
That's the plot.
The thing that I am still awestruck by is the fat boys get billing over Ralph Bellamy in
this movie, which is so funny to me.
It's just so funny to me.
And I was a big fat boys fan as a kid.
I still am.
And it was maybe sad watching it.
The two of those guys are gone.
But you know, I remember seeing this movie in the theater for my birthday, the weekend
it came out or around the time it came out.
And it is literally the hardest I ever saw my dad laugh throughout a movie.
So it's got a soft spot in my heart, but disorderly is, it's not going to change your life.
But maybe a day you're hungover.
You don't want to think you want to just kind of have a couple dumb laughs.
Check it out.
Were the fat boys in the Weird Al Fat video or were those different fat guys?
Different.
Those are different fat guys.
Okay.
Yeah.
What a video that is.
It's incredible.
I wonder if he still does the song or if it's like two non PC.
I heard he does it.
It's also the video for that.
Like I used to have the Weird Al video watched constantly.
Like those videos that the makeup on the fat video.
I think that's Rick Baker, but it's like we used to just care about shit.
You know?
Yeah.
We, we, the makeup on the fat video reminds me of how much we used to care about shit.
I watched American murder, colon, Gabby Petito.
But I don't watch a lot of this true crime stuff.
But the American murder series on Netflix, I had really enjoyed.
They're not too long.
They're always, you know, under the three hour mark in parts.
And they're always talking about a crime that I should know about, but don't because
I don't really follow the news.
And I have heard the name Gabby Petito, but I did not really know the story.
And it's a very sad story.
It's, it's a girl and her boyfriend who were like van life people.
They drove around this, you know, you know, camped out in parks and stuff.
That's becoming more and more popular as everyone loses all their money.
And you know, very beautiful young woman, very beautiful young woman and her boyfriend.
You can just tell his off, you know?
He's, he's above his weight class with this girl.
You can tell it the second you lay eyes on their picture.
You're like, she's, she's too good for him.
And he is in a constant state of feeling that he all, you can tell.
He's just jealous, controlling, manipulative.
And you see as her parents, you know, like it's every parent's saddest tale, we don't like
the guy our daughter is dating.
We could be potentially a problem, but we don't want to push so hard on the situation
that they alope and she never speaks to us again, you know?
And this is a case where it goes really, really wrong.
He winds up killing her while they're out on the road together.
And then the craziest twist of this thing is he go, he buries her, goes home, tells his
parents like, hey, I killed her.
The mom never liked the girl.
So the mom actually put in writing.
She's like, you, you, you kill someone.
I show up an hour later with a shovel to help you bury them.
You're my baby boy.
You don't have to explain anything to me.
I'm there.
So then there's this scene.
And because it's true, it was such a weird and deeply unsettling scene.
These nice friendly cops show up at the kids' parents house.
And they're like, hey, we'd like to come in.
We need to speak to your son.
They're like, he's here, but you can't speak to him.
They're like, well, there's a van out here that's not his.
It belongs to his girlfriend.
The girlfriend's not here.
So we need to either talk to you or talk to him.
They're like, nah, sorry.
They keep shutting the door.
They're like, no, his, his girlfriend's missing.
They've been dating for two years.
That has no effect.
They don't even, it doesn't even register to them.
They're just trying to shut the door.
They're like, we'd rather talk to a lawyer.
Sorry.
They're dismissive as though you had come to the door and been like,
did you vandalize this sidewalk?
That's their attitude.
So if the case interests you at all,
it's really interesting.
There's a lot of kind of chilling moments like that.
The best of these American murders,
although it's sick to say, is the family next door.
That's one that has stayed with me for five years.
And I think about it often.
The Lacey Peterson one was good.
And this Gabby Petito one is very interesting as well,
if you like true crime.
Joe.
That's our show folks.
Big shout outs to Joe Ramone from Hats Off Entertainment.
We spoke about Joe an episode or two ago.
And then lo and behold, he reached out to both of us.
One of his fans listens to our show and let him know
that we talked about him.
He reached out to both me and Pat quite kindly.
And it was very nice to hear from Joe.
And I think we're going to probably
bring him on as a guest and interview him
and talk to him about movies and stuff.
It seems like he's doing a lot of these keynote commentaries,
which is really cool.
Yeah, I still knew to write him back
because I wanted to watch the Uncle Buck.
I got my Uncle Buck 4K with his commentary.
But unfortunately, I met an Airbnb without a DVD player.
So I need to write you back, Joe.
And yeah, we love your stuff.
We're excited to meet up.
We are on C-Win Hell Pod on Instagram.
I am on the Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
That's all I got, Joe, plugs.
Just Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram.
Check out my upcoming live dates.
Oh, thank you to everybody that sent the nice messages
about me having to cancel some stuff
due to the family stuff.
And everybody that sent me nice messages
after I talked about my dad getting surgery on the show.
He is recovering well,
but it still required my presence to be around,
just to assist for some time.
But I will be heading back into the performance space
in March, starting with South by Southwest shows.
The first full weekend of March,
followed by Rosemont, Illinois, Xanies,
Rosemont, March 14th and 15th.
Desert Ridge Improv, March 28th and 29th.
I'll be with Shane Gillis over in the UK
at the weekend in between those two shows.
I don't really have any details on all that,
but I'll be over there with him.
And I hope to see you.
April 4th, I'll be at Q West,
which is Brian Quinn's little Q West festival.
He's put together.
April 18th and 19th, New York comedy club in Stanford,
Connecticut.
And then there's other dates after that.
But anyway, let's just go to my website,
jodaroza.com, get your tickets, get show info.
I hope to see you out there.
Folks, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.