I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
Now it's your favorite podcast dealing with your favorite types of movie, which are
the genre films in the horror and the fantasy and the sci -fi and the action and the things
that you like.
We're here to do this show for you today and our movie is The Fly.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh and let's address something right off.
We don't know what order these are airing in but there's one to clear the air.
Hear it from the horse's mouth by horse I mean myself.
I would have said from the horse's ass.
I'm referring of course to the horse -like size and shape of my penis.
Joe, you think we could put the phone on silent?
I'm looking up my Pat's movie corner picks.
Then I store my phone.
My question remains.
Oh, oh silent.
Do we need the ding?
I didn't know that was on.
I had it on for when you showed up.
I wanted to make sure I didn't miss it if you texted.
Sorry, for five minutes I'm going to be in anger mode because I just came out of my
personal training and it whips me into a frenzy.
But yes, Joe and I have decided we have put this off for a very long time but Joe is going
to start being bicostle in addition to bisexual living in both New York and Los Angeles with
no real set times he'll be here.
It was going to be really tricky to keep this podcast afloat.
We've tried out a lot of different podcast studios networks without talking shit.
Just none of them seem to make any sense to us.
The ad revenue doesn't generate anything and I'm sorry we have to be doing this for something.
You know, we have to make a little money or else why are we doing it?
I see a lot of my friends shows go this way.
My personal favorite podcast which I was obsessed with 80s all over fell apart around 1985.
I'm devastated.
They're not going to get to the back half of the 80s.
I didn't want to go away and just be like, peace out, Joe and I have hashed it out.
We're going to keep it going and we are going to start being Patreon only.
The charge will be $7 a month for that you get two episodes.
They will be great episodes.
I'm also now that I know how the uploading system works going to pop in the occasional solo
Pat's movie corner.
You know there might be little treats and surprises but you're guaranteed to get two episodes
a month for that $7 Patreon.
We have been stockpiling and recording and you know if you got a problem with it I'm sorry.
If you can't afford it or can't come with us I'm sorry.
I hope you enjoyed the years of free entertainment, no hard feelings.
You have those to listen to those are yours forever.
But you know it's been free a really long time and we've got to make some scrillex Joe.
I would say that we don't, we're not doing this just for the money.
We do it because we do love it.
For sure.
I know and I know what you're saying, I just want to make sure that our sentiment is clear.
We do love doing this.
We have a lot of fun talking about these movies.
We have a lot of fun seeing these movies and we have a lot of fun meeting all of you and interacting
with all of you.
As we've always said, we're extremely flattered by the support of the fanbase and the outpouring
of nice things that people say and show us and send to us and all that.
And we've never been a show you know a lot of podcasts tell their fans you know here's
a PO box send us stuff or you know can we use this of yours so we can review it or can somebody
get us this so we can talk about it or or or you know we contacted these places to get
free movies so we can talk about their blue rays or what we've never done that.
I think one time we try to we reached out to scream or shout factor to see if they wanted
to sponsor us to know a veil we've never heard back.
And another time we reached out to the horror box guys I forget the name of the horror pack
and said do you want to sponsor us and they flat out said it's not really worth the money
for us.
So what I'm getting at is everything that has gone into this podcast whether it's the movies
we see or the live events or just getting the merch made or whatever all comes out of
pocket and some of that is coming out of the pocket of Emily Florence and Simpson and some
of it is coming out of the pocket of the kindness of the time that the artists put into this
artwork and stuff that ends up on these t -shirts and stuff like that and there have been several
artists that have done that and we thank you from Will Potter to everybody else we thank you.
So there's been a lot of investment in the podcast and even when we do the live events
at best at best we all break even by the time people travel at best yes you know by the
time you buy booze to have at the place and get everything we everybody kind of just breaks
even the live events that you know the thrill really is to to see that we have I mean of course
you can read on Facebook but you just see people there and know they love the show that's
what keeps us doing it but we don't make any money from those you know this isn't a my favorite
murder to shout out Karen and Georgia yes who are buying houses from their podcast we and that's
a slight no they fucking deserve it they work hard too but you know I know this thing sounds
like me and Joe sitting around drinking whiskey and shooting the breeze but like there's a great
deal with our schedules of coordinating and you know it's not a job like going into an office
but it's kind of a job and we didn't want it to start feeling like misery to be doing the damn thing.
Well also and I'll be I'll be frank too also with you know in in addition to what I'm saying
of we're not turning a huge profit on this thing also to me the money that we continue to make off
of patreon allows me the plane ticket money to come back here with enough frequency to get some
of these episodes recorded and in the can or vice versa for pat to shoot out to New York to
record a couple or for us to invest in studio time on a buy coastal in a buy coastal recording set
up which we will have to pay for like we we're not with the network we will not be just we we're
not just able to go into a professional studio and say let us use this and I'm certainly opposed to
Skype I hate listening to podcasts where the two hosts are Skyping I think the main reason the
show took off and it's an underdog podcast we're not a smash but the reason we have our fans is
the chemistry of Joe and I and I think that's really hard to capture with a five -second tape delay
and some people would define it as sexual tension I would and if you're not in that room but to but
on that couch you tell me how that tension is going to get us to ask so we record this
in position like at the end of Requiem for a dream yes double -headed dildo asked to ask and then
we sort of inch closer to each other lady in the tramp spaghetti style until our asses kiss that's
usually when Pat says we'll see you in hell at the very end we'll see you in hell but it's through
gritted teeth so anyway the best solution we could think of to to for all of these sort of moving
parts was to go to a pay and also I think everybody knows we weren't we haven't been too pleased with
the last two networks we've been with and look nothing against those networks it's just we didn't
really see the point anymore in being thrown into this pool with 800 other podcasts where we weren't
really getting anything out of it and if we did get something we had to we had to give a portion
of it away anyway and and by the time it came down to it it was pennies so as of yet we haven't made
a dollar from the entire last season of the show the we did ads we did Viagra ads you know we haven't
been paid so and that's kind of how it wasn't the network before that and that's not the networks fault
it's it's these networks always say the same thing that they have to chase the money every network says
that so I'm a I'm going to give everybody the benefit of the doubt and say that it's true
it doesn't matter the point is is even when we do get the money from those ads it's going to
literally be like a hundred fifty dollars total by the time you split it up and and you give out the
portion of the network it just didn't make sense to us anymore to be beholden in any way to another
party besides ourselves and we thought in this day and age of digital distribution whatnot
why not I've had a lot of luck with it myself my last record that I did stand up wise I put it out
myself I gave it directly to serious XM and it's been one of the more successful records for me and
we wanted to kind of do that with the podcast we didn't want it to end but we also didn't want to
get into a situation either where we were saying to you guys hey we know we've only been back
for two months but now we've got to take another two months off we didn't think that was fair to
the listeners and we appreciate the people sort of pining and asking frequently where is the show
why isn't it not that we wanted to get into a position where we could give you guys the show with
some regularity that you could count on and the best way we could do that was to say okay let's drop
the patreon top tier by 30 % let's eliminate the other tiers and try to find an even fair in the
middle price between the five and ten dollar customers that will hopefully work and we will give
people two podcasts a month for that and who knows maybe sometimes some bonus stuff will get on
there whatever but the very least we can give you a movie's worth of entertainment every month
that you get to keep for far less the price of going to a movie correct so that's that's how we're
looking at it and you know nobody's buying Christ we're not even going to be buying pants from it no
and and one segment I am going to do is this I've been forcing myself because my last job you know
was it was essentially a PTSD type situation and I have been forcing myself to sit and enjoy and watch
movies and relax and I've watched so many movies and when we talk about three in the movie corner each
week I got a bunch so I'm going to sit down and do sort of a solo pats movie corner segment maybe
ten movies talk about we'll do stuff like that fun little uploads treats for you guys but if we're
in real I think this is probably going to be the last season of the show I don't know how long
it's going to last but we wanted to go out with a good quality season and we thank you all for
supporting us throughout yes I that last part it was news to me and now I'm heartbroken well who
knows this is kind of like when Carson quit at the upfront well then you know Carson also stayed on
20 years after saying he was going to quit we'll probably do that so no I'm being dramatic I
I understand why Pat saying that I understand where he's coming from again who knows how long
it'll last but we wanted to we wanted to give this an effort instead of saying we're done and what we're
avoiding saying is that Joe and I have stopped speaking to each other we're talking to each other
from separate soundproof chambers so we don't have to look at each other yes still connected by a dildo
yes exact which costs a lot of money that's what you're paying for yeah we're we're full on
in actual slash separate tour bus mode let's get off we're kidding by the way no of course let's get
on with the show and at the same time on with the Joe it's very nice
uh today's episode is the fly the fly yes I'm super excited uh the the the 87 1986
686 fly yeah and folks I have watched the fly in the last three weeks three times I saw it when I was
a kid it was too gross for me and I'm I've just become obsessed with it in the same way I did
with zodiac about five years ago and I think I'm just going to be watching it once a week until
I'm I'm bored of it I can't get enough I'm obsessed and I watched it last night with my dear friends
Bridger and Jimmy and my lovely bride Heather and we all fucking loved it but as I checked the Wikipedia
page after the movie airs I realized that we were watching it on the anniversary of its release
August 15th oh wow that was kind of cool um so you know we're celebrating sort of the
23rd anniversary excuse me 33rd anniversary of the fly with Jeff Goldblum and Gina Davis
but Joe what's going on in your world uh nothing okay absolutely nothing moving on uh I'm about to go
well again we don't know when what month this one's coming out but I'm about to head down to
North Carolina North Carolina come on and take your shirt off that one yeah that one that's the only
one I know of wait what's that song North Carolina come on and throw your hands up take your shirt off
roll around your head like a helicopter you know that song I literally have no idea what you're
talking about maybe I made that up I mean I don't think so that sounds like it could be a real song
yeah it's a catch a sign I don't know who doesn't I'm going down to Wilmington to do some shows
at the Dead Crow Comedy Club that's one of my favorite spots oh for the last two weeks I've been
co -hosting the bonfire on Comedy Central Radio series XM I've been hearing you have very
funny stuff thank you with my dear friend Big J. Okerson and Christine Evans producing I'm so glad
that I never reached a point where they had to add big to my name I think that was Jay's own doing I'm
sure it was I just yeah I wouldn't like that at all it's like how you know like when I would
be in high school where people go hey big guy or my dad would call me big guy I was like shut the
fuck up right I always like to be called big guy I mean people do it to people who aren't even heavy
it's just annoying what about large would you like that hey large like large it in charge no I don't
like that okay Dan Soder the regular host of the show with Jay is is in Scotland doing the
Edinburgh Festival and I've been sitting in for him okay we've been having a hell of a lot of fun
yeah a lot of laughter I there there are you know we have though that handful of friends that you
really can like laugh with yes you're one of them Patty oh Jay's one of them like to sit in the room
with him and just it's just it's just very fun you do it daily radio show heat well they do it
day out they do it I guess four days a week okay we're doing it three days a week for two weeks
um where's Sirius HQ here in LA there's a new studio on sycamore and it's gorgeous okay it's a
beautiful beautiful state of the art facility the old original Sirius XM studios were like way down
on I don't know where the fuck they were but they were kind of off the beaten path and they were
really small and cramped and not great yeah but this new facility is pretty pretty brilliant so anyway
that's that's what's new I've just been kind of doing that and enjoying myself fantastic I'm out
pitching a show around town had some bites nothing I can announce just yet but you know I'm just
relaxing doing that and getting ready to start writing having a good time all right if I may
let me take us over to Pat's movie corner you may have said I've been watching a lot of shit you may
now then I saw I've been using the letter boxed app by the way it's my favorite it's the only
social media app that doesn't give me anxiety and make me want to kill myself you I keep I use it as
a diary a movie diary you can rate you what you put in what movies you watch each day you give them a
star rating one to five you can write a little review if you want to and you see what your friends are
seeing you say hey I saw you saw that what do you think some people don't put reviews because you know
they're worried they're gonna somebody else see that they didn't like their movie something Joe and I
have obviously never worried about as we do this podcast though we probably should but I love it if
you want to follow me I'm the Patrick Walsh on there as I am on Instagram and Twitter and it's a
way to see what I'm seeing whether I like that or not try to get Joe to do it I pretty much just
blew me off but I'll do it I don't know why I haven't done it to be honest it sounds like fun it is fun
um I watched a movie I had never seen now I since I was a kid one of the first like adult pictures my
dad showed me not not adult pictures but uh American graffiti
so you know I loved it when I was a kid uh Harrison Ford Dickie Dreyfus Ron Howard if you
watched Lucas movie which I know will send Joe into hysterics but I I don't have any problem with
that statement okay I love the picture I don't know how the guy made something so sort of human and
lovely and then was never able to do it again uh and you know has such a problem with dialogue
and everything else but that movie really feels warm and human and good I love the soundtrack blah blah blah
but I had never seen more American graffiti the sequel and Lucas did have a hand in it
and it was a huge bomb but weirdly I've heard it getting a lot of play lately first on 80s all over with
Drew McQueen and Scott Weinberg and then Tarantino has been programming at the New Beverly now you
look at reservoir dogs with the radio soundtrack Wolfman Jack and American graffiti and Stephen
Wright and reservoir dogs running through the film it's clear the man has some affection for both
movies but this thing I didn't love it it came out 1979 directed by Bill L. Norton not Lucas but
he did have a hand in it I got to say it's really interesting there's three different sort of stories
and areas of the film and they're each completely different film stocks so the one is in sort of
a split screen like the Woodstock documentary or like De Palma would do the Vietnam segment with Charles
Martin Smith is sort of a grainy 16 millimeter and then there's a race thing going on a car race
business that is in sort of a more standard format Ron Howard and Cindy Williams are going through a
bitter divorce they're fighting all the time it's dramatic it's intense it's kind of depressing
they do tell you at the end of American graffiti like what's gonna happen to each of the characters
so you're kind of just waiting for those things to take place which kind of takes any of the excitement
out of it but as a curiosity it does not deserve to be to sort of brushed aside it does a lot of cool
things I can't recommend it really but as a student of film you're gonna have a good time with it
okay there you go I'm gonna start with one we both saw in the theater together which was the thing
from another world yes Pat and I went to a horror movie marathon at the Egyptian theater
six hours no I'm sorry yeah no six films about nine hours they're not long films
um Pat said I'm going for the whole thing do you want to join I said Pat I got two in these in me
at best he said I'm going for the full ride halfway through the second movie Pat was like I got to
get the fuck out of here I can't do this yeah and I'm usually fine with it but I was fall asleep
but the second movie was the thing from another world I'll do the first movie on another episode
I want to do a little thing theme here today
really cool fun 1950 sci -fi film I had never seen the original adaptation of the novella who goes there
or short story whatever it is and this one as far as I know from what I've read and whatever deviates
the most from the source material but it's a really really fun you know invader from outer space
kind of movie it's beautifully shot they do a lot of pretty astounding stuff out in the snow
uh for that time period in film in Hollywood film and it had me scratching my head at times where I was
like is that I was just a really well done set or are they out in the fucking Arctic right now right um
so I really really enjoyed it and I enjoyed seeing it uh having after very much familiarize myself with
the carpenter version to just kind of see like oh they took that from that and that that okay I see
and oh and then they switched this and so I really enjoyed it the monster you know I remember here
in carpenter say for the time was like very was terrifying uh I you know in this day and age it's
not very scary but I did think he looked cool um and surprising surprising amount of humor in the film
it was almost a comedy Howard Hawks was a comedy director you know his girl Friday and a bunch of
really snappy dialogue type movies that was his thing overlapping dialogue uh and you know I
need I saw when I was a kid liked it this time as I said was dozing off I started a medication I've
been sort of adjusting and getting better at staying awake but um yeah it's uh that's that's what
I like I like I like horror movies with a sense of humor basically or I like them to be deeply
disturbing and that's my two favorite things well I look forward to buying the blu -ray of the uh
of the this ad up to of that version uh in fact I might take a little trip on over
to a mabe of records this evening no I can't tonight but I'm always with you for a mabe of trip I know
you can't tonight maybe this weekend you already told me it's you got moved you got to see a movie with
Heather or something tomorrow had one yeah it's not an old -day movie Jim how do I know you're not
going to see Warren peace we're seeing the good boys about boys that curse which appears to be
the plot of that movie the good boys this month's adaptation of super bad that's true yeah uh but
they're young this time uh no it looks cute I hope it's funny all right you know I'm not I'm not
terribly interested but whatever go ahead I saw on Hulu a really surprisingly terrific documentary
I just expected it to be kind of a generic look at this lady but I really loved it called Ask Dr.
Ruth it got zero press all the press went to the insanely boring RBG documentary um but Dr. Ruth
man I would argue she is every bit as important as RBG and this things it it does what I usually
hate in documentaries where they animate segments of her life I usually hate that shit but it's done
uh sparsely and effectively it talks about her time in the Holocaust which I was unaware uh was part
of her life she escaped uh she had a lot of great tragedy in her life as you can imagine and she
demanded she fuck to get through it she did I mean she remains relentlessly positive I knew her from
some you know cameos and like repossessed with Leslie Nielsen and I should watch the talk show when
I was a kid yes I did too I wasn't allowed to but that's what I loved about her there was such a
fierce uh repression in my family Irish Catholic about sexuality you know like we like still
no sexual matter has ever been discussed between me and my parents I know that's weird but
I know it's weird to to discuss it at length but like we all just act as if sex doesn't exist
and uh my god I grew up repressed my friends used to tease me very recently that when I'm at a restaurant
and I mention anything about sex my voice immediately drops on any word that's dirty uh which is just
me being trained that way I you know what Dr. Ruth did was let people talk about sex people who in
their marriage had not had an orgasm in 20 years to start talking to Dr. Ruth they started getting
their nut she was fixing people's lives their home during the day and it's like hey honey
I watched Dr. Ruth today I want you to put a finger in my butt what do you think and that cannot be
underestimated how important that is for these people to get what they want in the goddamn bedroom
doctor they call and their embarrass and Dr. Ruth is like say the word say the don't be embarrassed
and of course she courted a great deal of controversy for it which is completely fucked up
because she's just trying to help people enjoy their lives but um the second half of it plays kind
of like a documentary private parts of her moving up the radio world ladder she had a very similar
trajectory to Howard Stern people wanted to shut her down and my god this scenes with her today are
so funny she is such a ball of fire and very inspirational for somebody with such a dark life to bring so
much joy to people couldn't recommend it more highly uh yeah that RGB I tried to watch that I was
like I'd find a documentary about literally red blue and green more interesting yeah I thought
this was the Roy Roy beat what is it Roy G biv the color real rainbow uh red or yellow blue green
indigo violet I'm kidding I didn't watch it I just wanted to make that joke it's boring as hell uh I
finally got my hands on the 2k transfer of John Carpenter's the thing
amazing watched that movie for the first time in a few years what can I say it's a fucking masterpiece
piece there isn't a flaw to it everything is perfect I wish I knew Kurt Russell and Wilford brimley
personally by the way plan in 35 millimeter tonight at the arc light at midnight just saying oh
oh well maybe if you weren't running off to see her after this Joe calls my wife her now uh no
it's uh I don't even go check that out though uh let me know if you do I'm I'm I mean all right
I haven't been drinking and it's man hitting that sack early lately same here 10 pm I don't do that
early yeah I'm just like well I guess it's there's no reason to be awake anymore anyway it's a great
movie I was interested in seeing some of the modern day uh interviews in the bonus features very
disappointing that they didn't have a Kurt Russell Kurt Russell wasn't part of the screen factory
doc yeah I think in some cases they're just on a movie they always you're always like boy is
they're bad blood but they're probably just shooting a fucking movie yeah no everybody had great
things to say about him and I think he just wasn't available but it was just a bummer but um
but I was surprised to your brimley say that he's like you know look it's just my taste I'm not for one
for Gore and and graphic whatever and he's like that part of the movie I didn't really like I think
you're robbing the audience of the wonderful imagination and what things they can think of to
scare themselves but he still had pleasant things to say about the movie and the experience go go get
yourself this this transfer I mean it's it's fucking beautiful man I mean see it really is and the
thing is a great honestly a perfect double feature with tonight today's uh movie the the fly
yes the thing the fly and they are both just they just have some beautiful Gore effects in them
and I agree with Will for brimley to some extent you know there there is a the power of suggestion
that is great but I think both of these movies are great examples of like just showing you
some really creative explicit amazing Gore effects that uh really stay with you in a way that honestly
you know suggesting that he's turning into a fly by showing you like a shadow on a wall
wasn't gonna work that's what they did in the original well if you it also too if you're able to do
if you're able to do a Gore effect that's literally haunting because you're like you made a thing
that I couldn't imagine yeah that's a huge success that's very hard to do so when you can do it
hey man my hat's way off to you and the thing and the fly are also amazing examples of pre CGI effects
practical effects from and you know in both cases 30 almost 40 years ago yeah that I would say put
most of what's happening in theaters today to shame um your third is up my third is up and I
saw my criterion copy of an early Robert Zemeckis film called I want to hold your hand
which I had always wanted to see and it was either out of print or just not available at my
video store but uh I love Zemeckis I love for you know he had a run that was almost unparalleled
he doesn't get the same respect as Spielberg but just as much of a pioneer in terms of special effects
and back to the future I would say unquestionably the man's masterpiece prior to that he and Bob
Gail worked together on used cars with Kurt Russell which is an absolutely hilarious movie
that I strongly recommend picking up there's a great new uh Blu -ray of that out hilarious movie from
like 1980 and before that was I want to hold your hand Spielberg loves Zemeckis and Bob Gail
uh they wrote 1940 what is it 1941 1941 for him which is a sort of a notorious bloated production
that's got some fun shit in it frankly but you know it's not an amazing movie uh Spielberg love them
really mentored them there's some great documentaries on there there's a great sit down with Gail
Zemeckis and Spielberg where they're just thanking him for like shepherding their career in
they still even though Zemeckis is 55 and has a billion dollars in the bank just a reverence
that he has for Spielberg for helping him out that really made me remember you know like how much it
means to people when you when you show them a little help in this business because few people do help
anyone um that's true I want to hold your hand is an early film uh it contained two early student
shorts of Zemeckis and Gail that are fun but ultimately you know not amazing but cool to see
that criteria out the shit man I mean two student films of Robert Zemeckis are like
fucking great and I want to hold your hand is the story of a group of teenagers who are trying to
get into the Beatles' first performance on Ed Sullivan and they do some pretty amazing shit similar stuff
to what he would later do obviously much smoother in forest gump where the Beatles actual
footage is being used they had access to a tremendous amount of Beatles songs which you would never be
able to do today but um just a really fun time not a great movie not a classic and I think they
took a huge step up with used cars and then a massive step up with back to the future but if you're
curious about the early films of one of the greats this is a great set to pick up Wendy Joe Spurber
who plays uh Marty McFly's sister rest in peace rest in peace at far too young an age I always
liked her as an actress she is hilarious in this movie she is really great it's an early performance
of hers uh Nancy Allen from Carrie Eddie Deeson who you'll recognize is playing the the nerd in
50 % of 80s movies yeah um you know it's just a fun cute movie I liked it a lot the desperation
these kids go through to go see the Beatles is a lot of fun it's got kind of a mad mad world quality
to it a lot of running around and screaming and likes the mac like you know back the future is
hinging on will Marty McFly fuck his mom this movie has some real dark shit too there is a girl who
nearly commits prostitution with a big fat guy so she can make the money to get in and see the
Beatles right right and the movies PG you know it was it was a different time but um if you want
to an early an early film from one of the greats check it out it's fun uh I'm gonna close it out with
the thing prequel uh I wasn't a fan should I see it again you should uh I watched it right after
I watched the thing 2k again just a gorgeously gorgeously shot movie uh if you can get your hands
on a blu -ray copy of it which I'm sure you can it looks spectacular uh it is much better executed than
it got credit for they do an excellent job of planting of showing you how the seeds in the thing
carpenter version we're we're planted um how the axe got into the wall why the guy on the chair was
burned alive you know all that kind of shit uh or had slit a throat rather they they do a really
good job of doing the back the so the sort of retcon of how that stuff happened uh I will say obviously
there are far less characters you give a shit about there are far less memorable characters
and there are far too many characters there's one scene in this thing we're like eight people get
iced in like 30 seconds because clearly they were like we gotta lose some fucking people here man
right uh that all said it's practical effects mixed with enhanced by CGI so the effects look cool
they don't look quite as cool as the carpenter version because you can tell that some CGI is happening
but they still look cool and there still is some really disturbing weird shit and it fits hand in hand
with the with the the vibe and the style of the carpenter version so the prequel from like 2012
yeah yeah okay I liked it I think all three of those movies is a great night at the movies
personally I think that's a great triple play in your house uh and and you know I'm not saying
you're gonna watch the prequel and go my god what a masterpiece but you watch it and you go this
was enjoyable this was an enjoyable addition to the carpenter film is it a James Marsden vehicle
no it's actually your boy uh what's his face is in it uh I saw it I just have no
who they come at night that guy oh uh Edgerton it's Joel Edgerton yeah it's um what's her face
never saw they come at night what's her name you've given me literally nothing the lady from
uh she's the main girlfriend and Scott Pilgrim versus the world or whatever Mary Elizabeth
Winston Mary is Elizabeth Elizabeth Winston is the lead yes and then the third lead is a guy you'd
also know from stuff who's like a Danish actor or whatever they actually went and got actual Swedish
actors which I like okay to play the sweet they talk about them special features they're like
the studio is kind of like what do you mean you want to hire Swedes and they were like it's about a
Swedish team right we can put a couple Americans in the lead if you want but like yeah they have to
be at a Swedish bit so they're like so we went and got like and they're they're showing the guys in
the movie that have like kind of supporting roles and they're like this guy is fucking Brad Pitt
in Sweden like right right I think it's Sweden right um anyway uh I enjoyed it and uh I would say
it's a it's a more fun watch than the 50s version um the 50s version has a bit more charm though
and of course carpenters is the is the ultimate version so um so that's it uh I want to do a quick
news psycho here um this this Bruce Lee shit is still going on it's relentless
now so daughters involved and Quentin Tarantino did a sort of arrogant comic portrayal of Bruce Lee
in once upon a time in Hollywood I thought the scene was very funny and I took it as it served as a
it only served as a means to me to be like look how much of a badass Brad Pitt is you need to
be aware of that for when the end of the movie comes right what's a fun way we can establish that
oh wouldn't it be funny if he fought Bruce Lee that's just how I took it um I think that's how
nearly everyone took it unless you are one of the people who obsessively looks for problems
in all entertainment which is a lot of people Kareem Abdul Jabbar spoke out against it today and he
was very you know gracious about it he's like I love Tarantino his movies or events I see every one
of them I can't wait and he goes it just bums me out that he portrayed Bruce in this uh unfair and
and he said mildly racist way and I was like well what was racist about it yeah but he did make
the point of he goes I knew Bruce he was like I was with him a million times when boneheads would come
up to him and try to fight him he would always pass yeah he was always very polite about it he was
always the guy that said you only fight if you have to right you don't just fight and he so I was like
okay I get it like you're showing an Asian guy that's like gotta be like whoa you know in all this
right um so he made he made the best point of it but I mean here's the thing here's my thing and he
didn't say to his defense he goes Tarantino can portray him any way he wants I don't have to like it yeah
so I thought that was a very level headed rational way to react to it if you weren't into it but
it's also like like this is a movie that spoiler alert ends with with history not happening the way
it's supposed to happen so why are we mad that this wasn't an accurate portrayal when nothing
in the movie is an accurate portrayal I don't think it's I think it's a shame that that that that
that a comical portrayal of Bruce Lee is in the controversy surrounding that is overshadowing
the like kind of endearing celebration of Sharon Tate right and how things turn out good at the end
for her instead of awful right uh instead of the worst way possible I think it's a shame that more
people are talking about the thing they can kind of bitch about oh so you mean the white woman gets
a happy ending oh great um meanwhile I'm watching Fossie Verdon still or Verdon
Jesus Christ not one paper about Fossie they're making the two of these people look like fucking
animals well you know and even in Fossie's work like all that jazz he paints himself as an
absolute monster so I don't think he'd argue and it starts out where you feel bad for Verdon and then
she starts taking a turn halfway through this thing and you're like this evil witch was like you
should do the musical even though it'll drop you'll drop dead you're like sure you're like I get it
when he was bad to you but you don't have to kill the guy sure sure uh it's so but my point is
is nobody's coming out being like my mother was a saint or my father was right they're just like
hey what are you gonna do yeah yeah yeah uh by the way both the both projects Fossie Verdon
and once upon a time feature Margaret quality yes who is the daughter of Andy McDowell who I would like
to marry okay probably won't happen I don't think so probably never even made her that seems unlikely
but it would be nice if we got married right I don't see a problem with it right I got to find
to Andy McDowell right or right or a nice letter Andy McDowell is in my neighborhood so come on
over that would be creepy or at least Mrs McDowell I like your daughter at least she walks in my
neighbor by the way so she's in ready or not yes which I'm excited to see it looks like a lot of fun I
I'm not I'm more way more said about knives out knives out looks very fun to me ready or not looks
kind of just like they look very similar and they kind of your next family but I've watched this trailer
because I go to see a lot more movies now 50 times they've shown this trailer and I thought every single
time that that lead actress was Margot Roby and it's not it's not it's not it blew my mind somebody
put it on Twitter the other day and I was like what I immediately go to the IMDB page it's a look
alike and she's got the same vibe she seems like very talented she's funny but I guarantee 50 % of the
people going in there I think they're seeing a Margot Roby movie I that was the only redeeming
quality of the film to be honest like it must be good if Roby's doing it well it's like she's at
she's in a pretty good spot right now this must be a hell of a script it's like how on Amazon you'll see
like you know like it'll be Lord Lord of the ring goos or something how they change the title by one
letter so that you accidentally watch it yeah mark busters um I think that's honestly this woman's
gonna keep getting work because they can fool people into thank you she's Margot Roby her name is
Samara weaving um she looks identical Samara weaving some of us are staying that's pretty good that's
pretty good I guess she was I made myself laugh with it she was in the babysitter on Netflix which I
didn't see she was an ashverse evil dead which I don't recall I bet you she was seasoned three
ashes daughter right because I didn't see season three because of the daughter I was like guys yeah
can you not completely mail this in at this point now he's got a daughter that was the cool part
about the Kelly character and ashverse evil dead it wasn't his daughter but it was like the daughter he
never had right and then they're like no he's actually got a daughter yeah oh god I love that they're
making fun of that stuff in the Jay and Silent Bob reboot I look did you see the trailer I have not
seen the trailer there's a part in the trailer he goes to Shannon Elizabeth's house because remember in
the first film they like date kind of it sees she's alive yeah they stop at her house the whole
movie is you've got to go to Hollywood and stop the reboot it's the same movie right it's really a
funny but he goes to her house and she's like Jay I want to introduce you to your daughter it's like
that's really fucking fun man um it looks very funny and I'll be all psyched that Affleck's in it back
playing uh what's his face from chasing Amy uh I always like Affleck in a comedy uh Kevin Smith said
that the Affleck reunion their friendship reunion happened because of this movie yeah they had
a falling out and he goes it allowed me to do a seven minute chasing Amy sequel in this movie so I
think there's a big Joey Lauren Adams then Affleck thing in this flick you mean Affleck and Damon
out of falling out or Affleck and Smith no Affleck and Kevin Smith had a major falling out what happened
I don't know but they were Smith was relentlessly talking shit about it for a while sorry I think it was
when he married Jennifer Gardner there was some friction and then Smith started being like she
don't like me and that's never good when you start saying that out in public yeah your wife don't
like me and you're saying like a fucking podcast you know talk about that stuff yeah um anyway uh who
she shouldn't be liking was the man who was publicly cheating on her for a decade folks um don't
let's not bring down Affleck now please no I like Affleck uh okay so we are going to talk about
the fly David Cronenberg's the fly Cronenberg is an undisputed horror master you you could very
well make the argument that he is the equal to a John Carpenter or West Craven and his movies are
certainly more consistently intelligent um I would put him in an overall category I would put
Cronenberg above either of them I think I would a filmmaker because he's he's proven himself in many
area many genres at this point you know like I'm not knocking those guys his run you know video
drum dead zone uh you know even his later stuff crash these crazy crazy concepts that dead ringers
with Jeremy Irons is amazing and that but he's a uh he's a William Friedkin to me it's like here's
a guy that dips into horror when he does it's amazing because he knows how to make a movie and he
you know like what I really really love about the fly and watching it today the fly would be a
superhero movie because when when gold bloom starts to turn he gets sort of superhero powers
that turn very quickly against him and he becomes as hideous mutant but it works so beautifully as a
superhero movie and it immediately makes this horrific turn the movie is 95 minutes long it is
so fucking tight gold bloom and Gina Davis were dating at the time their chemistry is off the
fucking charts gold bloom should have been nominated for best actor uh of course got no attention
everything he's makeup whatever it won best makeup wisely I would say it's some of the best makeup in
history of film and they and the the effects they created a spinning room to do the right how they
shot they put a stationary camera in a room that actually rotated 360 degrees to actually get the
effect of him crawling on the ceiling that is old Hollywood that's that's a trick used in singing
in the rain actually it's amazing um I mean I I told you on the last podcast or whatever order we put
these in there's a there's a fly box set on blu -ray with fly fly two and the old ones I've
never seen fly two I'm very excited to watch it I've heard it's of course not as good but it's got
it's it's high points fly two is a straight up exploitation monster movie but it's great it was
directed by the guy who did the uh the makeup effects for the original fly it's a lot of fun uh you
got stilts in there right uh that and stilts has a real ability to go from charming charming and
boyish to creepy as fuck yeah um I mean the this this movie is just a master class in
screenwriting really I I think that's why I've been so obsessed with it and why after a third
viewing I'm excited to watch it again um the documentary is one of the best film making up
documentaries I've ever seen it walks you through the movie and what you really feel in it is there
is none of that Kronenberg doesn't participate he does a commentary but there's none of this
going through the motions that you get when you watch almost anybody talk about their films on a
late night talk show or whatever else every single person down to set design down to cinematography whatever
it may be just speaks with such delight and passion about this movie and that really really shows
and when you look at Kronenberg's filmography he works with the same people again and again and
again fun fun fun fact produced the EP by Mel Brooks he produced well Mel Brooks produced the fly
yeah I thought you said he produced an EP of Mel Brooks like a CD by Mel Brooks yeah
EP by Mel Brooks uh Brooks I would say this uh also another interesting fact that you may or may
not know dear listeners the reason the film is so haunting is because it was that the time it came
out it was at the height of the aid scare and David Kronenberg said unlike in the first movie where a guy
goes into a machine and comes out a monster I thought it would be much more interesting to do a version
of this where a man was slowly dying and being eaten away by this transformation as if it were a
debilitating disease right and he was turning into something not a giant fly a thing an organism
that had never existed before that's this is why the guy's brilliant he did a page one rewrite of
this original script I've read the original script you can read it as a bonus feature on these blueries
you're talking about okay the but the original reads so differently that when I first started reading
it I thought I was reading the 1950s screenplay um it's just got it's just it the original script
of this thing was just sort of a it had some cool moments but it was more or less a paint by numbers
big budget remake of an old horror movie uh it felt like that and the and Kronenberg took this thing
turned it on its ear and again to mention the faussi verdant thing did the faussi approach right like
like what faussi did with pipin where he's like this is fucking boring this ending is stupid yeah
let's go let's say something let's go dark and that's one of the things I love so much about the fly
is that is number one Kronenberg's the filter he pushed it all through but then also one of the only
movies I've ever heard this about the original ending of the movie showed Gina Davis sleeping
and then you would the camera kind of like magically went inside her womb right you saw that she was
pregnant and instead of being pregnant with a little brundo fly thing she was pregnant with a baby that
had like angelic like butterfly wings right it was this sort of sweet moment tested that tested poorly
yeah they cut out the sweet ending the fucking thing ends with her blowing gold blooms fly
head off and then weeping uncontrollably on the ground when it just ends there he grabs the she's got
the shotgun and she's like I can't do it and goblum as the fly grabs the shotgun puts it to his
temple like kill me and makes a noise he goes yeah where it's he's like a little dog at the end yes
exactly it when the credits roll on this thing we even watching it in your living room it's like oh my god
I can't even imagine being at the theater for that in 1986 but Kronenberg is does not shy away from
depressing in any of his shit dead zone has an amazing bummer of an ending a lot of his movies do but
it is pretty relentlessly grim it's fun for the first half takes a big old turn and he climbs it's not
about AIDS they sit a lot of people say it's about cancer um goblum himself refers with as cancer in the film
he just says it's about aging and how when you enter into any relationship you are entering into it
knowing that if you don't die first you're gonna have to slowly watch the person you love die
Kronenberg is definitely said I wanted to make it about a debilitating disease yeah and he did
he did reference the AIDS scare he didn't say it was about AIDS but he said that's what was going on
and that's what was scary at the time right you know I never heard the second part though that's
that's pretty interesting that's what yeah and something on this DVD is what he says it's that you
got to watch the person you love die and Gina Davis for the end of this she's amazing in it too but
she's just playing this miserable painful horror there they linger up seems you would never get
in a modern day retelling of the story of like when she sees him and every time you see him he looks
significantly worse in a way you kind of have to laugh to make it less painful but they linger on her
walking out of the apartment out to the street and just sobbing like she doesn't want to do it in front
of him just like you would do if you went and saw your mom and she was passing away you'd try to
keep it together and then cry on your way to the car like it's a very painful sad movie it works
beautifully as an action sci -fi thriller and I think it works especially beautifully because the
science all makes sense and Goldblum is saying things that makes sense and it all seems very plausible
but it also and a lot of people probably don't even pick up on this but if you're looking at it
as an allegory it's a rough sad film there's an opera they did an opera version of it in Germany
okay I've seen clips of on the on YouTube horrifying you'd think it's an opera so I get I bet they don't
make them look like the monster right no they do and it's fucking terrifying yeah to see that thing
singing opera I mean the other the other thing the I think the turn it's again it's it's hats off
to to Cronenberg what a good directory is the there's a there's a there's a distinct turn in the movie
when he arm wrestles that guy in the bar oh yeah and everybody's cheering and all that and the guy's
wrist breaks and pops through his skin that's the breaking point in the movie that's where nothing
good is happening anymore this is going down a really dark road yeah and it doesn't stop and then
you see the shit they cut out of the fucking thing that deleted there's a deleted scene where he's
trying to he's desperately trying to figure out how to be human again and he's like since I've been
integrated with the cells of the fly if I can integrate with a human I could maybe be human again
and then of course his brain is being eaten away by the disease so he's getting more and more obsessed
and crazy and thinking this this thing this technique and theory will work and he does an experiment
where he he combines a cat with a baboon yeah and it comes out as a cat by boon baboon hybrid and it
jumps on him and scratches him and the thing is so hideous that he beats it to death it's well it's
clearly suffering yeah and he beats it to death with a stick and then he then he runs out to the
roof and starts screaming to the heavens why no no no he can't believe what he's become then he has
a shooting pain inside he falls down the building side but he stuck to it because he's the fly
and then a fucking arm comes out of his side that he has to bite off with his teeth and he lays
there sobbing yeah and they said when they tested the movie they were like the scene was too much you
just were in no way rooting for him anymore it was yeah I mean he becomes an asshole like when he
tries to get Jean and Davis to go into the machine with him this is sort of the first moment he's
mean to her but she's like no I'm not doing that as anyone would say in that situation and he goes
God you're a fucking drag yeah screams at her and basically they said no matter what he did the audience
was on his side and he was sympathetic but watching him beat a half cat half baboon the audience was like
nope nope but this thing much much like the thing I mean you're watching this I watched it with
three people who hadn't seen it and the screaming in my living room like the terror the jumps the like
oh shit you know like for a movie from 1986 to have that effect is really really cool and I think even
though the fly you know it made 60 mil on a 10 mil budget or something like that which is a nice hit
had a sequel made but like it is a sturdy movie that really fucking holds up and I do feel it sort of
underappreciated and under scene no one I was hanging out having dinner with last night had seen it
or even really heard about it so turn your friends on to it if you haven't seen it check it out really
I'd say it's a horror masterpiece I met Simon Rich the writer a little while back yes we did a show
together and man seeking woman right yeah and we hit it off and we became friendly I haven't
talked about a while but he's a very nice guy but anyway we talked a lot after the show and he
and his wife who was then pregnant since had the kid congratulations guys they told me that their
favorite movie is the fly that they it was like I think they said they had watched like their second
date I was like that's that's one it's either gonna bring it together or push you apart I mean
if you come together on that one that's that's your you might be getting married after that yeah
so anyway that's the movie today that's our show catch me as Joe to Rose a comedy on Twitter again
I'm back not tweeting much but I'm on there and Instagram and I hope to see you soon out there on
the big open road or in New York City or in LA doing shows on the Patrick Walsh thanks for sticking
with us through our many changes through the years we've been doing this thing at least five years
which is unbelievable to me and we will see you next time we'll see you in hell