Welcome to we'll see you in hell your favorite podcast reviewing the films that you love we rank them
we discuss and we rate them my name is Joe to Rosa my name is Patrick Walsh how are you Joe I'm doing well Pat you know we're trying to work through these slight audio issues here we're aware of them we know that Pat and I both sound a little different we're trying to make it work but we're on opposite sides of the country and you know it's listenable it's just we sound different I haven't seen complaint one so we're probably just putting complaints in people's heads but
all I notice is you sound rich and full and I sound like I'm in a bit of a wind tunnel or something a little tinny a little weak you sound the kind of like you were maybe up all night doing blow it's got that kind of navely you know
imagine anything darker than like in a pandemic home with your wife nowhere to go can't leave the house and you're just doing blow every night like that's that is bleak well I don't tell you a bad time to me but I mean the blow is a going out substance you'd be surprised how much fun you could have at home with just with a with a meager wife and bag of cocaine
well I might have the fun I don't see her having fun with me talking to her for 20 minutes about the history of aviation or whatever I would be talking about I have a well -documented hatred of cocaine I'll never try it again because I don't want to suddenly flip that switch and love it so I'll be dead in a week
hey you know everybody's got the thing they like everybody's got the thing they hate I have grown to hate pot in a way I can I hate it so much I hate pot culture I hate people that are high which is most of my friends at this point all the time constantly sure I just hate it I I hate weed I hate it
I've never disagreed with anything more I know but it's all been building to this six years I'm not I'm not I now if that's helpful to you I know you haven't I am for me I know you're I like to be high
I can't stand it I don't like the way it feels I hate I've grown to hate all every sort of hallucinogenic like the last time I did mushrooms I hated it
okay the last time I tried Molly I hated it like I don't like that kind of high I don't like that whole like hey it's a body thing and your mind is going to other place it I don't like that anything that resembles a trip
and I don't like it however you give me a couple of Adderals and a bottle of whiskey I'm having a great time I just feel tuned in and ready to talk
the Adderals are not for me at all I just need something to shut up my brain or free me from the constant
oppressive horrifying loops that my brain gets into
so for me it's just an immediate release from the spiraling thoughts that are constantly on my head it's very helpful
are they your standard types of loops or they loop deloops
loop deloops I'm sorry yeah no no loop deloops indicates fun so yeah these are just straight loops
yeah sort of like a waterpark fly that keeps swirling and swirling and swirling and then right when you're about to hit the water you realize that it's a pile of shit
I just thought of my picture of hell is I
pictured a waterpark slide when you said that yeah that right when you think you're going to hit the water you don't and it just keeps going and then you realize it's a never ending water slide
because that to me that would be hellish because when it started you'd go this is fun this ain't so bad and then when you realize oh my god it never ends and it's just you're going down down down it never stops
that'd be pretty freaky that's a darker and probably more accurate look at my my loops you know like I'll be
just I'll just immediately flash to like something mean I said to somebody in 2011 or something mean they said to me and that's a night gone
and I'll be sitting there trying to watch a movie going why are you don't talk to this person you don't see this person what's the matter with you and it doesn't matter
like I can't talk myself out of it that's where the weed comes in I uh I get that too yeah it's usually something I said to my mom or a fight I had with my parents at some point that haunts me
I get racked with crippling guilt of course and that's where the booze comes in for me and then when the booze starts to make you go I'm a little tired
and you go you know what'd be nice right now is an Adderall that'd pet me off I could get out with this booze for a little while longer
I mean just for my experience but obviously as we're talking everybody's different all that stuff
Adderall quote etc is the worst possible thing I could do for for looping thoughts it just makes them
amped up to like 20 and uh drives me insane isn't that interesting because my I have the exact opposite
thing that's why I don't like pot because pot makes me focus in harder on it I start to get panic attacks
and I can't get out of it and then I start to irrationally process I'm already a rationally processing thing
then I really start to where I'm like you know you're gonna everybody hates you right like and I'm convinced
fully of it that the people in the room I've been on your your couch high next to you and I'm like
this guy hates my guts well that was true but uh no the uh I know exactly what you mean except it seems
like as as similar as we are it seems like we have very different brain chemistries because whereas
weed makes you go everybody hates me weed is off and the only thing that can shut off the everybody
hates me for me interesting I had that when I was younger I had that I think it's the strains of
weed now to be honest with you I think it's the strength and the purity of it but when I was young
man and we used to smoke a decent level of uh what they used to call uh shwag weed yeah kids out there
Philly shwag weed no less yeah uh you know sometimes they'd call it mexican brick because it would
usually come from Mexico in the form of a brick because it was so dry uh when you bought it
and um you know man it was it was very uh weed back then you actually there was a reason it was
called grass at one point it looked much more like grass it was stringy it was almost like green big
league chew except not sticky right and um and it was just a very different experience and back then
I loved weed I thought it was just the best thing it it it put me in a fun state of mind it took me
out of reality a little bit I really loved it and it wasn't until I tried I started dabbling around
with edibles in my early 20s uh and then also being in a position where I was out of school and had a
job and was able to smoke better weed that weed turned on me where I started to have panic attacks
it would hit me way too hard I hated it I would freak out like and that was it it was just never the
same after that every and then and then of course over the lat since then the last 15 to 20 years
whatever it's been weed has slowly become more and more accessible eventually legal
much stronger and the introduction of medicinal marijuana and whatever so every time I've revisited
since my twine in my I'd say mid 20s um it's been you know it's been a tight row walk you do it and
then you gotta I gotta sit for 15 minutes and tell myself everything's okay right and then I'm
kind of having fun but then I'm like I need a drink and then I'm just like what am I doing I just
might as well just be drinking because this is now just amplifying the booze sure to a point where
I'm gonna be hung over tomorrow and whatever else a lot of people have that I I've never had a panic
anything on weed mushroom sure uh Molly gets you there almost immediately you feel like uh gotta
get out of my skin sort of um yeah but we doesn't do it for me last time I did Molly last time I did
mushrooms I was with a group of friends both times I had to in within 15 minutes of taking it because
my body also processes things very quickly because I have a high metabolism I'm not in great shape
I should weigh four thousand pounds though the way that I live uh so considering what I do to myself
I'm in good I'm in fantastic shape um but my body processes stuff quickly so I remember last
time we did mushrooms it hit me so 10 11 minutes in I said I have to go in the other room and everybody
went 11 minutes and I go just trust me and sure enough I laid on the bed and it was just like whoosh
and at 11 minutes you probably weren't having effects you're probably just freaking out about the
oncoming effects and freak yourself out well it was an hour of staring at the ceiling
deal with it and then finally I felt good enough to get up and walk back out into the
common area and talk to people but that happened to me last time I took Molly about 20 minutes in I was
like I remember I said to my friends I go weird wave weird wave I'm getting a weird wave and then
I went into the bedroom and laid there for three hours yeah I'd always prefer to be alone on mushrooms
alone you know in Joshua Tree or alone in my house or whatever I don't like somebody there I have
to entertain because I get to a very isolated place and I mean in my opinion you should be using
psychedelics mushrooms to like get to know yourself better so the whole friends all going through
different brain journeys in the same room never appealed to me I hear you I have heard from various
sources that you don't want to do it with like acquaintances no like or like because everyone
just starts looking evil to you and you're like I hate these people and definitely don't do it with
somebody who you're not you know everyone's got that let's say you're hanging out with six people
especially you and I Joe we'd have our hangs out here there'd be someone in the group probably
that we can't stand you can't be doing it in that situation because I think it just makes makes
them look like the devil to you and by the way the the drug is always right the person you
and fear the next day you're like oh my god no it's right that's true it's like it's like a dog
you know how like dogs can sniff you out if you're scared or yeah person or whatever mushrooms
immediately kind of have that effect yeah exactly but yeah the only time I ever had one of those
situa and then we'll get off this because there's enough drug podcasts but I was I went out to
Joshua tree right after this last big job I had where I was really at a breaking point and I that
was the only time I had an experience where I was sitting in a hot tub I took what maybe triple my
normal dose I sat in the hot tub at Joshua tree at an Airbnb and sobbed for what might have been one
minute it might have been 17 hours I don't know then when it started wearing off I was like
wow I need to eat something I didn't eat just you know if you don't eat it's supposed to
hit you much more intensely so I walked out of this like roadhouse oh god no ordered a giant salad
a nice roadhouse you know there it was a nice one but still just in that state of mind I can't
imagine I was a salad I ordered a big salad well I knew that it was a slippery slope you're not
really hungry on mushrooms but I knew that I started eating I would go nuts so I ordered the salad
and the second I set it down in front of me I stood up I put a 20 on the bar and I left I didn't touch it
I didn't take it home I just went but walked back on so interesting but it was one of those deals where
all night I was very raw and then the next day I woke up feeling like I much better understood my
wife that's the ideal motion experience to me yeah I mean I could go without that I'm abandoning
the salad I wore the salad yeah Pat learned that night he doesn't like salad
I was I was looking in a mirror with a flashlight under my chin and I just the damn broke as I learned
that I can't pretend to like Caesar salad anymore it was a Caesar salad too that's a real
pungent like yeah like I love anchovies but if this had been a Caesar salad with anchovies on and I
saw the little eyes I probably would have screamed and thrown the salad at the bartender last time I
did mushrooms a friend of mine had made a bunch of before we took them had made a bunch of barbecue
chicken yeah and when I got hungry on the mushrooms I ate a bunch of the barbecue chicken and it
was wonderful it was exactly what you want like right neutral enough and flavored meat but then the
sweetness of the sauce I feel like on a heavy trip like that it's like give me a chocolate cake
you know what I mean or a pie or something like you know something that's comforting in some weird way
you know yeah I mean well that's that's my issue with weed and what I eventually you know
because I always say don't let's not have any food in the house because as a guy especially during
this pandemic where you're like that's 4 p .m. why don't I get hot you don't want to just be eating all
night but what's another great thing to do is just have celery sticks or mini carrots around or
something because all you want to be doing is just like for me and I'm stone and you know if all
you're eating is celery then it's great but if you're a house where you've got like a 5 pound
bag of chocolate chips and the pantry then you know yeah well you could do what I do on the rare occasion
that I smoke weed and that's smoke a pack of cigarettes back to back just one after the the next I
think in conclusion Joe and I have very healthy coping mechanisms for the the the demon playgrounds
that go on inside of our heads and just a tip by the way for any listeners out there if you are on
mushrooms or Miley and and the acquaintance in the room is freaking you out don't try to avoid it
that's going to make the trip worse start pointing at them yelling baby sees a ghost and see see
what that does to the room that'll that'll that'll spike the party up a little bit now I don't speak
Spanish but I like to yell at the person in Spanish to really freak them out so I'll point and scream
L .D. I blow L .D. I blow
and that's really to make them feel as scared as I am all right by the way how many movies are called
La Loura there's there's a word La Loura on Criterion channel there's a new La Loura on shutter and I
think there might be a third La Loura and I don't even know what La Loura is last summer last summer was
the curse of La Loura yeah I think it was called yeah now there's a new La Loura I didn't know
about the Criterion one so there's three yeah see it's interesting that these things happen well the
that La Loura is an old foreign movie is it a horror movie it's a horror movie yeah okay so you know
apparently it's a it's a Hispanic legend some reason that feels weird to say a legend for
the Hispanic people I think it's a Mexican I think it's from mech I think Mexico it's a go it's
like a witch a Mexican witch legend or something I think but it's weird that like you have these ants
bugs life Armageddon deep impact situations right especially in those cases where the movies cost
300 million dollars and they're just like yeah we'll both just make them right but meanwhile if
I have a great idea that's set in California it's always like you know there's another project
happening now in California so you might want to think of something else you know it's just it's
strange how they decide to move forward on on some things and not others I guess Armageddon made
probably 300 mil deep impact probably made 200 mil that worked right some bugs life were both
hits that worked so they can yeah and as my friendship pointed out to me once and I think you
actually have also point this out the most absurd case of what you're talking about was when the
illusionist and the prestige dropped in like a week of each other you're like there's never been
a movie about a magician let alone two at the same time there's never been an old -time
magician movie and it was like let's get him out same weekend actually so I talked on the last
podcast about dangerously A -Zones and now I always love to read the Wikipedia page as I'm sure
most people do when they're watching a movie and Milos Forman the director you know did Kuku's
Nasson Amadeus etc he went and saw this play it was the hot play in in England Alan Rickman in
the mouth of its role and it was dangerously A -Zones there was this big critically acclaimed play
and Milos Forman went and saw it apparently like four or five times because he really wanted to make
a movie of it he loved it okay then he decided I want to make this story but not do this exact
script he wanted the credit basically so he went off and made it made the movie Valmont that came
out at exactly the same time dangerously A -Zones rushed to get out ahead of him but after being seen
in the audience talking to the playwright he goes yeah I'm gonna do this exact same thing but I'm
gonna do it my way and sure enough dangerously A -Zones wins a bunch of Oscars it's a big hit Valmont
comes and goes nobody sees it no nomin it was a net -bending version of the same story but I was
one of that too you know when they're like yeah you know like they did a remake of the Out of Towners
Steve Martin Goldie -Hon remember the Jack Lemon movie and you're like why did you spend a million
dollars to get the rights to the Out of Towners nobody remembers and has great fondness for the old
Out of Towners and that's that's that's not even a good example I mean sometimes they'll rip off a
movie wholesale steal everything from it but pay the people who wrote the original nothing and
sometimes they pay that huge fee to do the remake when they don't need the title I never understand
one of the most can the the most confusing version of that to me is is haunting of Hill House yeah
the Netflix reboot of it because here's a thing they've changed so much of it from the source material
so much of it is is different there's so little connective tissue and who the fuck is sitting
around in this for that audience who was sitting around the Netflix audience especially the audience
of that show in particular is geared towards going I'm such a big haunting of Hill House fan I've got
to check this out that nobody watching that show has ever even heard of the haunting of Hill House
it makes no sense or is one of the biggest honors for that like all throughout my high school years
in the 90s it was everything was a remake in horror that the haunting then they that 13 ghosts and
all this stuff whatever they were all you know castle movies old movies now maybe they got the rights
cheap but that audience who's like going to see urban legends final cut and then going you know
just going to see whatever horror movie comes out none of them have seen these these old horror movies
none of them care none of them are comparing and contrasting so I never get the decision I think
sometimes it'll be like one or brothers has the rights and they're like hey you want to remake this
thing and maybe they don't have to pay I don't know how it all works well with the show we've brought
attorney Chuck Glevenstein here today is our first ever guest to talk to us about copy right
law while me and Joe leave we'll be talking to you for it's more of a TED talk it's like a three -hour
copy right law podcast we're not interested now maybe you are at least with the out of town I'm sorry
I chose the name Chuck Lieberman for the attorney it feels president feels uncomfortable
I think with the at least with the out of towners you could say you know maybe the studio still had
the rights to the script from the original story right and said this would be a good thing to do
again and we'll throw Steve Martin and Goldie Hahn in it that that makes kind of sense to me yeah Netflix
absolutely had to acquire the rights of haunting the Hill House correct they did not have those lying
around and said let's just repurpose this or else it's going to waste you know what I mean like yeah
no sense I have two really good friends or a husband and wife writing team and they had this
great spec script feature and it was kind of ready to go and it seemed like it was going to sell
and at the last it was at New Line and at the last minute New Line was like I'm sorry we can
basically make one comedy this year which is generous for today's market and we've decided to put
our money behind a all female remake of throw mama from the train so it's like I like throw mama
from the train I love it's one of my favorite movies uh why are you doing this it means nothing
that's it means it means nothing to the kids of today who pay who pay to go to the movies it means
nothing to them but it also I think like my parents I guarantee my parents are early 60s I guarantee
they saw throw mama from the train they rented it watched it in 1987 but I guarantee they're not like
oh I want to know what a 2020 version of this story it looks like so it's really for no it's for
it's for nobody and it's also why a all female reboot of a movie that already is one third female
you know what I mean like yeah there are more significantly male led movies that you could do a female
reboot of if that's in the business that you're in to do it of that movie it's like it's not even
really an all female reboot it's three characters and now all three are women instead of just one of
them it's not really yeah does it make any sense now that you like the two of the ghost busters were
women and then they were like we're gonna do it all female reboot no one a new one may have even seen
throw mama from the train I mean that's how these executives oftentimes are just making it up they
haven't even seen it or they may have seen the poster and thought the late Anne Ramsey was a man she
was certainly man -ish nominated for best supporting actors for throw mama from the train it's a
wonderful film it's it's my second favorite Danny DeVito movie after Hoffa meaning that he acted
in and then also directed sure I love the more of the roses man in a very big one I love that movie too
I like I never saw I never saw I never saw I never saw I never saw but he did it's great I need to
veto made some really great movies man as as a director but he's got an amazing visual style and as a
producer man produced full fiction for Chris yeah but the oh I don't know I was gonna say dirty
rotten scoundrels they they remade that which I mean people people might not even know I don't
even remember what the name of it is the hustle the hustle within halfway in rebel Wilson there's
another word how many movies are gonna make what hustle in the title right hustle and flow the hustle
hustlers it's like all right guys find another word just make a movie like you know you know what the
the really great and really funny female dirty rotten scoundrels is heartbreakers and it was an
original story that's a very underrated comedy with subordinate weaver team hack men and Jennifer
love you it and Ray Leota it's really really funny it was done by David Merkin who did get a life
for Celia and yeah Romeo and Michelle you know he was a really funny and the Simpsons of course but
watch hardbreakers who knows this throw -off from the train might never even see the light of day but it's
like and what's interesting is throw -off from the train is a remake I don't know whether they paid
for the rights or not of strangers on a train the Hitchcock mode yeah no it's it's they came up
to bits of it throughout yeah they must they must have it must be an indirect remake I mean I mean
they they must have had to do something because they they couldn't show the clips otherwise I don't
know what I mean so but I love that movie but you know it's it's a it's a it's a
point that we've visited before on the show with with some of these all female reboots
they're doing these needless projects that aren't resonating with the audience they're trying to
so it's kind of pointless and in the meantime you see a movie like hardbreakers or you see
70 % of the movies Kristen Wigg has done these wonderful female led female centric vehicles
that get absolutely no attention nobody watches them nobody they get that they get marketed like
shit they fall by the wayside they're critically acclaimed and that's it they make no money because
nobody ever finds out they exist and then when it comes time to redo things it's like so redo
heartbreakers yeah remake heartbreakers for the modern audience nobody is going man you showed those
boys by recasting Billy Crystal with you know Debra Messing or what you know what I mean it's not
going to be Debra Messing I couldn't think of his name but you know what I mean it's like it's like
you know man Anne Hathaway now as mama that really was what we need you know it's like
make something that's going to resonate with the audience man yeah I mean the the time I went
to the movies the most I saw every single movie that was released was my high school years the 90s
and especially once I could see our red movies by myself there was such a glut of
women fronted movies you know people act like that some sort of new thing but they were always
low budget but there's heartbreakers they there's drop dead gorgeous which was a really really funny
mockumentary with like Kirstie Alley Ellen Bark and Denise Richards and it's in the Christopher
guest style it's as funny as like some of the later Christopher guest stuff it's really inappropriate
Will Sasso plays a mentally handicapped man throughout and the jokes are a little rough but that's a
movie that's getting a new discovery now too these movies would come out and just kind of get dumped
and I don't know everyone thinks of the 90s as oh everything was wrong everything was like American
pie or Tom Katz with these sex comedies there were tons of really funny weird female Joseph
and the pussy cats is an amazing satire of of the time you know of teenage fandom and how
vapid everything was in corporate sponsorship while these movies are getting their due now when
they made no money at the time but I don't know seek them out there's good stuff but what am I talking about
well you make a sense you're making good sense I'm listening quick quick scary stuff and then
we can get to the movie corner and I will highlight female centric projects in today's movie corner
all right but I mean this isn't really a scary stuff I guess maybe it's a new cycle I don't know
I listened I finished I told you about this the other day and it's so funny I have to say on the show
I I finished listening to the Woody Allen autobiography apropos of nothing
whether or not you like him I get it he's clearly a polarizing figure at this point
yeah yeah yeah that's yeah that's all right if you have any interest in his trial and
accusation and that stuff whether you think he's guilty or innocent if you if you find an interest in
that the book is very worth listening to I think because it shed some very interesting information
and you can draw your own conclusions and if you're a fan of him it's a great book to listen to
because he goes through his entire movie catalog and and you know it's it's interesting um but
does he I had heard he doesn't go movie by movie he does he goes into all the movies and he's got like
good stories from the sad or what I know listen to Barry Sonnenfeld's autobiography and he doesn't
talk about any of his films it's really annoying he kind of just kind of just goes over kind of like with
what we're going to review today in search of darkness it's that style of conversation of each of me
he kind of covers it briefly talks about all great everybody was including me a Pharaoh
he'll be like mea was fantastic in the moment you know which is interesting but um he uh he doesn't
get too into anything in fact he says at the end of the book he's like I'm sorry that there weren't
more like you know tension on the set stories and whatever else he was like but I've been very lucky
and and I you know I've had a nice experience doing this or whatever yeah but anyway he talks obviously
in the book of of the trial and the accusations of of him and his his daughter that mea Pharaoh
leveled against him uh and he talks about at the end of the book when the accusations resurfaced
and what a dark time that was in his life uh and what that has been like experiencing that
and he talks about how he's friends he and Louis ck had become friends uh via the movie blue jasmine
that Louis ck was in and he said Louis ck was getting us two guys out on the town of New York who
were probably like let's just keep our heads down while we enjoy these rubens
let's can we get a booth in the back
so he said Louis was starting to write and direct and said to him like I and I'm not talking out of
school here it's in the book uh he goes he goes we we got along very well and he goes and Louis started
to write and direct and Louis said to me uh you know I'd like to do a thing with you I'd like to find
something and what he said yeah that'd be fun so he goes so anyway Louis calls me it says I have the
project and he goes okay great what is it and this is at the peak of Woody Allen's uh Marla
station accusations resurfacing he's getting scared in the press it's just trash and he goes I will
always he goes I have this movie called I love you daddy and I want you to play a director that
has sex with a teeth my teenage daughter and Woody Allen is reads the audiobook himself and he's
going in the audiobook and I said are you crazy what are you nuts and Louis said no no I think
it's a good idea I think it'll exonerate you it'll show people and he goes what what I like I like
Louis what was he thinking and he has like a full on Woody Allen style meltdown reading his own
autobiography about the situation and it was just one of the funniest things I've heard a long time
there the reaction was just so visceral and honest and and he just couldn't wrap his head around
that Louis had called him and said I think you should play this part had that happen the as they
called cut on the movie it would have been sent directly to the Supreme Court
for the amount of crime on display and then he goes he goes he goes but I'm not
wanting to tell someone not to do their things so I said god bless and you go make the project it's a
it's a good script and then he goes and now poor Louis has had problems of his own it
well Louis yeah it was it was played in the movie by John Malkovich I am one of the few people
in the world to have seen I love you daddy I know I discussed it on the show but you know it is
one of the craziest cases of like hiding in plain sight I've ever seen it's just it's a movie that
every frame of it feels wrong to its core but Malkovich plays Woody Allen in it they might have
well as as has called him have called him Woody it's a film director that Louis idolizes
who comes after his daughter Chloe Grace Moritz who spends the first 20 minutes of the movie in a
bikini sitting on Louis lap um any who just the name I love you daddy like it's in
I know I said in case you missed that episode I worked with Charlie Day and I would give a brief
but sold time but there is a 10 minute scene where Edie Falco one of my favorite actresses is chewing
out Louis CK in his office while Charlie Day sits on a couch behind her and mines jerking off the entire
time this woman is trying to like make her make her case she's talking and talking and talking and
Charlie Day is miming Jack up behind her while the WCK tries not to laugh this movie would have been
released during that scandal breaking like I feel like this is a guy who was just like I've gotten away
with it for so long I'm just gonna make a movie about it fuck it and then it went wrong well yeah I
mean let's yeah you know we have different opinions on this we can't believe it by the way anything I
just told about the Woody Allen story that's not me trying to pile on with Louis or anything like that
it was just a funny thing to hear you can draw your own people I just believe at the end of the day
everybody should be allowed to draw their own conclusions and nobody should be canceled for having an
opinion on something that's of course yeah that's not the world we live in but of course oh god no
I don't understand why you think you would have the rights Louis doesn't put it up on his website
for ten bucks I love you daddy you must not have the rights I guess yeah or I mean or maybe he
realized it's an interesting it's not a good movie it's a really bad movie too and on top of
everything else it's an interesting thing because I watched Louis last special and he did he does
wreck it when he talks up he doesn't talk a lot about this stuff but he does when he does he does
recognize some I don't know if guilt is the right word but he the way he explains it is you need to
keep checking in that somebody's okay you can't just assume because you're in a situation with them
and they they said they're okay they're okay you have to keep checking it and uh
and it's a very funny joke he goes it's like a negro spiritual if you heard slave singing in the fields
you wouldn't go they're having a great time out there he's like you have to check in and make sure
that you're treating people properly so he uh so I don't I it's a it's a it's a it's and then in
Woody Allen's book obviously Woody Allen is like adamantly like I didn't do it I didn't do it I didn't
so it's interesting to see how two different people have a different perspective on this thing
you know what I mean with a project like that because Woody Allen's perspective was clearly I'm trying
to prove I didn't do a horrible thing and you want me to play that are you fucking crazy yeah and I
think Louis was coming at it as like I fucked up but I don't know if I did anything totally wrong but
maybe I did but hey you got to just stare it in the eye and and whatever right I have no idea
if either approach well like I actually yes I do I think Woody Allen was probably the smarter one
to go let's just not touch it I guess I mean I don't know but like that was like in the 90s and 80s
like that was kind of the way you handled controversy was like you'd get in trouble for something
and then you'd go on TV and make like a big joke about it and everybody would go oh remember when
Peeley Herman came out at the yeah yeah and good jokes lately yeah again Hugh Grant goes on Lennon
yeah bumble -bub with a doctor and then what did he say you see that when that happened no that was
it you know I you know but but Lennon's whole the that it's considered one of the greatest interviews
in late night history because Lennon goes what were you thinking right that's the classic line Lennon
came up with what were you thinking right right yeah yeah now that gets handled with you know you do
the 10 minute call bear interview and at the end they do the whole like now I have to bring something
up yeah and then the audience goes silent and you somehow get an applause break for saying
you're a decent person amidst all the shit getting slung at you or whatever one of the most intense
ones is when Jerry Seinfeld was on Letterman and they they video conference and Michael Richards
after he was calling people the end word at the comedy store and my god it's just a man who can't
even get through his apology without kind of admitting that he's racist he's like look I know I'm
not and then Jerry is telling the audience to stop laughing he's like it's not funny no no no no no no
hold on you let me correct you if if I may Michael Richards is the one that corrects them for laughing
I start laughing and I heard the clip pretty recently Jerry does go it's not funny stop like a mom
scolding but Michael Richard also goes I don't know why anybody's laughing right yeah it's it's
here's the here's here's where Michael Richards we're laughing because for 10 years every night
at six and six thirty they watched you slide into an apartment with four foot tall hair and they
see you as a funny person like you don't know how to how to suddenly accept that you're a racist as
well yeah you picture him in a in a in a plantation you outfit sliding into a room knocking cotton out
of somebody's hand you know what I mean yeah exactly picture it like but but I remember that and I said
I I remember saying at the time of that I go this guy fucked up and he fucked up because he looked
he looked guilty yeah like he was being like sweaty and he was like the guilty guy and I always felt
like if he had come out with confidence and just said hey guys I fucked up like I don't know you
know like I know that I fucked up and I'm very sincerely sorry and like had just some sort of
composure about it I think people would have been quicker to forgive him I think like because when
you start to get wormy sure oh forget it but I mean but then again nowadays you apologize with confidence
and people go you piece of shit you're not groveling enough I mean now they would destroy him what's
they kind of did at the time but I mean look the video was horrible it's horrifying I still remember
it was it came on the evening news or whatever and I was like holy shit that's right but I don't
think that incident killed his career because Michael Richards is not a guy it's you know you don't
want to see him another thing he did that movie trial and error which was kind of funny and he was
a supporting guy early on in his life but post -sign felt you don't want to see Jason Alexander
and anything you don't want to see Michael Richards and anything Julie Louis Drivefist is very
different she is a in addition to being you know a beautiful traditional leading lady she's super
funny and she can handle a bunch of different parts so guys are such specific look character looking people
and that you just think of them in those parts for the rest of your life you can't I've seen Jason
Alexander in a few things in Seinfeld ended one was a horror movie called Snoop Dogg's Hood of
Horror and he's also in three or four of the Twilight Zone audio dramas which I'm a big fan of
okay and in every single one of these things he's done a different accent because he is clearly
just trying to be like I'm not George yeah I was a Broadway actor I'm not George but unfortunately
typecasting happens and and that's what you want to see same thing with Kramer I'm surprised that
Kramer I think what I think Michael Richards thought that that success on Seinfeld and him being
the breakout and the you know that it should have launched him into leading man status in other things
and I think that was wrong I think what he should have done was gone back to playing quirky supporting
roles and had he kept doing that I think he would have been fine but I think he probably turned a lot
of stuff down I'm theorizing obviously but I think he probably turned a lot of stuff down and kept
holding out for this like no I deserve better I'm Kramer and even Seinfeld got that that wasn't
the case like Seinfeld made one movie the movie you know yeah and then was like I'm gonna go do the
marriage ref and I guess I'll produce it or whatever you know what I mean yeah like the comedian movie
and then comedians and cars getting coffees like I people people know I'm a comedian I'm not I can't
really do much more than that as an actor so this is what I'm gonna do they just made much smarter choices
I mean Alexander was in shallow hell he had a tail so remember in shallow hell I believe the final
joke of the film and at that point I was like okay he's gonna be like Rob Cordray is now he's gonna
have that career where he's the funny best friend the the guy who's like you got to get laid buddy you
got to get back out there right right but I'm sure he didn't want to do that either you know like
well he's good and like pretty woman he would have been good as like the villain but
post Seinfeld you're not gonna take him as a guy who tries to rape Julia Roberts on the back of the cat
you know but funny enough in shallow hell when he played that part that was the party played in
pretty woman yeah it was almost like a full circle thing so I was like yeah go back to playing like
the little buddy that's kind of a sleaze bag and you know they mean like you're good at that you're
good at playing weasily like you know it's like he was great as the weasley version of himself
on the on the Seinfeld curbsies he was awesome as like the smart big guy who wrote a book and you know
he thinks he's above everybody which I was kind of based on right he was at the time and by the way
you want to talk about staring down the barrel of the thing you did yeah that's the best example of
it ever I mean so they did where they finally addressed because you're sitting there all season going
are they gonna address the Michael Richards racial slurs video and when they finally do and they do
it with JB smooth and yeah you know that he's in on the joke and everything I was just I was that
blew me away when I saw that I think that is the most excited I have been in my I was still living
in New York and when curb my favorite show was doing the Seinfeld my other favorite show season
remember the first night it came all we all went to this girls house in the city and she had like a
party and drinks and everything we're gonna watch the premiere and I was so excited and also nervous
that it would suck that I got too drunk and wound up sleeping in a in a back bedroom and missing it
having to watch later but I felt such investment and to have it be that great was awesome obviously
yeah it was really fantastic let's get to the movie corner jump oh Jesus here we're we're a little
behind schedule here we are kick us off I'll go fast on this first one I said I would do the female
centric movie corner I watched a little film based on a heavy recommendation from Pat Walsh himself
called death becomes her starting the great Goldie Hawn the great Meryl Streep and the pretty
good Bruce Willis and I just basically told Joe this was going to be a I'm I'm rewatching Tales from
the Crypt which we will do as an episode or watching I've never seen him I'm on season three but death
becomes her was going to be a Tales from the Crypt movie they use Tales from the Crypt music
and the advertising and I told Joe this feels like a big budget top of the line Tales from the
uh it does feel like a Tales from the Crypt movie in the sense that they took a 22 minute script
and stretched it to its limits to reach 90 minutes the performances are all great a wonderful
performance by Isabella Rosalini Goldie Hawn and Meryl Streep they're they're at their best it's
they're at their funniest their their tremendous and Bruce Willis for once playing a sort a sort of
sheepish sheepish excuse me cock failure kind of guy and he plays it well and it's nice excuse me um
funniest comedy screen for me outside of Daniel Stern with the tarantulas Bruce Willis it's
high pitch scream and death becomes yes that part is funny yeah that said the premise of the film if
you've never seen it is these are two women who are very competitive they're both obsessed with
out sort of out -beautifying one another uh and they both find a potion supplied by Isabella
Rosalini that basically means it gives you eternal life you can never die but if your body gets
damaged the damage won't heal so that's kind of the goof of the movie is now they can't die but like
when these terrible things happen to them it makes their body look crazy and they're just going to live
forever um it's a funny premise it's an interesting premise and they basically take what I just told
you and make it eventless there's there's like two sequences in the movie that deal with this the
entire thing takes place over a matter of 48 hours or something like that there's almost no
expanish exposition there's nothing setting up these characters to make you care about them
there's just nothing it's just seen after seen of very repetitive back and forth stuff about people
you don't care about and everything you learn about these people it's just something they say in
dialogue they so I guess there is exposition but they never show you any of it you know you only know
that Meryl Streep and Goldie Hawn are competitive because they say it a couple times you never really
get to see any of the fun backstory of that um it's just a boring film had it been a 25 or 26
minute episode of Tales from the Crypt it would have been fucking great um so it's one of and it's
Robert Zemeckis so it's well directed it was it was also a uh special effects marvel at the time
I mean it was it was right at the time of like uh you know like far as gump like it was like right when
they were getting into the I don't get one best special effects uh I'm 90 percent shared but you
know like the stuff still looks great in it they the stuff that we do each other's bodies is awesome
so so that's that's kind of it it's not a bad it's not moving you're not gonna be mad at it but it's
just not anything memorable at all I own it I don't think it's a classic by any means but I just
think the effects and the performances are so much fun so cool I love the vibe of it um big fan
and it apparently thank you Mike our producer here says it did win the Academy Award for Best
Visual Effects um I liked it what can I say all right I'm gonna go with uh original movies on
on the streamers today but the ones that are kind of getting dropped off so let's start with
Eurovision song contest the story of fire saga which I didn't even know until right now was the full title
of movie good I mentioned on the last one that I had watched the first 10 minutes and was like
fuck this um I came I decided to give it another shot based off some surprisingly good reviews I was
seeing and a lot of people saying like it's a movie that could have been made in 2000 you know I was
like all right then it's like a comedy with jokes that sounds appealing to me um and it's a bad movie
it's not a disaster but it's a bad movie it's Will Ferrell um doing his thing with no variance at all
fierce brazen playing his his dad who's like ashamed of his son for wanting to get into this
Eurovision contest and the movie is over two hours also a man who's about what 10 years older than
Will Ferrell I don't even know if he is 10 years old and he looks he looks way better than
brazen looks better than he did in gold night in Eurovision which is infuriating and he also appears
to have no work done he just looks fantastic but um basically the movie just kind of goes and every 10
minutes they cut to pierce brazen and sitting in a bar going like my stupid son my stupid son and
it's a movie with its tongue in cheek sometimes you keep hoping they'll go the walk hard route and spoof
these movie tropes you know like in walk hard everybody tells them the wrong son died they all say
to Johnson right is character and they just kind of it's just kind of weeks I mean weeks story time
to say at least Ferrell co -wrote it but man it just kind of lurches from set piece to set piece that
doesn't work uh there are full songs performed from the first note to the last note
full five minute songs and then in some cases the songs are re -performed later in a comedy that is
already two plus out that's what kills that's what kills the um David Brent documentary because
the David Brent documentary is very funny yeah they show so much music and only half of the songs are
kind of funny some of them you're like this sounds like a song a decent songwriter would write like
for sure why am I listening to this right now um I had seen all these raves for Dan Stevens
who is the actor and the guest which is a movie I like a lot you probably seen him in a bunch of stuff
Dan Stevens plays like the villain um and it's in one of the it's just it's it's somebody like
Will Ferrell getting card blanche or do whatever he wants because Dan Stevens is very clearly
closeted in the movie they they refer to it five hundred times but the conflict of the movie outside
of them winning this contest is that Dan Stevens is trying to steal Rachel McCattons away from Will Ferrell
how can there be any tension when they're constantly making jokes and then flat out acknowledging
that Dan Stevens is gay right it's just like nothing works in it on a on a story level you don't you
can't get engaged in the story because you don't feel the threat how does it compare stack up against
homes and Watson now homes and Watson is a bad movie don't get me wrong but they're like three full
sequences in that movie that are laugh out loud funny uh and then the rest of us you
uh the part where she's the female doctor and the morgue and they go yeah they go you must
be here grieving your dead husband she goes no I'm a doctor and and they're going my god the grief is
rattled her brain right that part's really funny uh this is better than homes and Watson don't get
me wrong it's also a half hour plus longer so that's uh strike against it but um you know like
Dan Stevens for example sings this five -minute song where he's like a lion he's like you know
it's there's not a laugh in it but he's like you know I'm walking through the planes looking for my
prey or what is he singing you know on stage or is this okay on stage full performance Dan Stevens
is not funny enough to be carrying this but it goes on and on and on and on way after you get the joke
and it's not even a good joke he's just singing a song from the point of view of a lion that's not
even there's nothing funny about it so when at the one hour 45 -minute mark Dan Stevens then
performs that song again when it's the finals and you watch the whole song again I could have ripped my
hair out Rachel McAdams is the best part of the movie she plays it just like it's another you know
very serious role she's great in it she's funny she's cute she's sweet there are jokes in it like
Will Ferrell the entire time everybody says you guys are brother and sister right to
McAdams and Will Ferrell is like I'm I'm pretty sure she is not my sister I'm pretty sure but he's in
love with her you know like so that there's some dark sort of jokes like that that feel kind of like
dirty work like really weird jokes there are the kind of 80 style jokes where Will Ferrell will scream
and like a glacier ill cut to a glacier falling and then landing in the ocean you know like big silly
stupid shit there are some weird jokes that kind of work but all told I can't see any reason to watch
the songs you don't don't stick with yet it's a weird film all right this is a fast one I've been
like the show if you're a fan of Glenn Howardton in you like it's always sunny in his character
and it's always sunny you'll you'll like AP bio it basically it's it's it's it's it's a slightly
tone down version of Dennis and surprise at how little it is tone down considering it's NBC and not
FX but it's a very funny show he's tremendous in it it's fun to watch it and pretend it's what
Dennis did when he left the it's always sunny show for a little while that's what I do at least when I
watch it but anyway the reason I bring it up is not for any of that it's to talk about Alison Ashley
Arm who to me steals the show she's a supporting character she plays one of his students and she plays
like the sort of quintessential super super nerdy weird like coke bottle glasses kid in the class
and they do the I guess it's sort of a trope that they do where she's got a lot of dark secrets so
everything that comes out of her mouth is kind of like wait what do what did she just say yeah
and that's the gag but manda she sell it manda she carry it uh and it's just so funny it's just so
funnily written my favorite line what she talked about she she goes I steal getting caught as the fun part
like you know just stuff like that makes me laugh really hard uh she'll often make a lot of sexual
references and it's really awkward she's in real life she's 25 she's playing like 15 yeah so
it's really really funny she's great on it um everybody's really good on it but she she's somebody
like when I was watching and I was like I have to look this person up and like she's got to she must
have been in some other stuff and she has been in a bunch of stuff but this was the first thing I saw
her um but she was in uh well she's been acting since she was a kid she did one of the first
things she did was an episode of friends in 2003 which she was in Mr. Woodcock she was in
an episode of Woodcock yeah law and order I guess this was actually her first big gig though so
she's great so watch the show yeah I watched most of the first season I liked it Glenn is
a highlight of course I'm a fan um yeah his best line and it is when he's writing on the chalk
wherever it's back to the audience and he goes last night I tried to have sex with my ex -girlfriend
which she declined so then I proceeded to get horrendously drunk and relieve myself on a hospital
police officer tried to stop me and I suggested he sexually pleasure me yeah that's fun uh yeah
um all right if you do a show I'm gonna do a show uh you talked about Hulu's high fidelity
and I finally watched the whole season the show has insanely been canceled um it's so I'm so sad
about that you know there's there's so many just bad shows overhyped shows shows that no one even knows
what they are but they last for six years I don't know what happened here uh high fidelity I told
Joe my only sort of weird issue with it is that I know the book and especially the movie extremely well
um and they use whole chunks of dialogue from the movie which I was not expecting and I also
don't normally see when I'm watching an adaptation they usually try to go their own way
um huge chunks of dialogue that Zoe Kravick's character says were said by John Qsac in that film
um and that's cool yeah and the supporting cast you know they they put different phrases and
different people's mouths but I would write up to the end episode 10 they're using chunks of dialogue
um the show really worked for me the music is great I recommend watching it with subtitles because
they tell you what every song is as it pops up uh it's like you can't understand what people are saying
but I really like knowing what all the cool music was in it quest love was the music producer did a lot
of the selecting of songs um it's it's laugh out loud funny just because of uh joy Randolph
divine joy Randolph I hope is her name I'm gonna look it up um she is hilarious in the jack black role
uh everybody in it is good the stories are good the New York vibe is great they moved it from
Chicago uh the film was sent Chicago to New York everything works great it reminded me of being young
and and single in New York and having fun so to see a good cancel is just kind of nuts and it's a
show you know with a very organically diverse cast it is a show that doesn't feel pressured or forced
into having like this this group of friends where everyone has a different race or sexuality it feels
natural um I don't know I was a big fan of it I'm sorry to see it go but the first season is there
for you to enjoy and the woman's name is divine joy Randolph she was in um dolomite is my name she's
extremely funny I hope she has a big grip um all right my last one is a documentary this is not
a light documentary but it's a documentary that is somehow shockingly flown way under the radar
uh especially considering the public discussion about uh sex and assault and that sort of thing
that we are having and continuing to have uh but it's called on the record it was released on HBO Max
and it's a documentary about uh women that have accused Russell Simmons hip hop mogul Russell Simmons
of rape uh which is heartbreaking to me because I am a huge huge huge hip hop fan and Russell Simmons
is the godfather and the last thing you want to hear about a guy that you admire that much is
something like this but uh I watched it and I believe these women are a hundred percent telling the
truth um this was a documentary that at one point Oprah Winfrey was attached to she left because
apparently she cited it as creative differences and said that um also that there were some
inconsistencies apparently in the women's stories I don't know what those could have been because they
show a very very thorough version of each woman's story and each woman's story to me was
incredibly convincing um are they investigating Russell Simmons I've never even seen
it being on trial or anything else well he lives now in uh where did he move to he moved to tell you
quick uh what the hell is it he moved to oh for god's sake where is it
I mean I don't really care where it moved to I don't know but Bali he moved to where there's no
extradition treaty okay so you know makes you you know kind of supports the the the take that he's
probably guilty here right um but it's very sad it's a heartbreaking thing and the women talk at length
uh in the film about how they why they didn't come out and accuse him sooner um primarily
uh one woman in particular who says like this you know she worked at deaf jam and she worked
underneath him and um she said this this was not just some guy that you know worked in you know some
black guy that worked at some job or whatever she goes this is Russell Simmons this man was a pillar
of the black community he was the godfather of hip hop and to go against him and also then simultaneously
deal with the backlash of you're you're taking you're another black woman taking down another black man
she said it was too much and it was too hard for her to deal with and then eventually it got to a
point where she said she she she couldn't keep it in anymore and sure enough and this is really where
you know where there's smoke there's fire uh you know with this sort of thing as you hear each story the
similarities uh between each story are pretty startling so you know it's it's it's a pretty
damning documentary um um i'm upset to hear it because like i said this is a guy i really admired but
obviously that is far away by the sympathy that i have for these women and uh and the and the
uh uh uh fulfillment i i have in the fact that they or that they i hope they have in the fact that
they were able to come out and talk about this stuff so it's a riveting documentary uh i will say one
thing i think that these films are good because they're getting people's stories out there and they
are helping bring closure i do still think it's this might have come out on an apple tv by the way
it's either it's real max okay it is um it's still a little weird to me that
that that that that's something like this is monetized in any way you know what i mean like it is
that is a little strange to me the the subjects aren't certainly making any money but
uh because you don't get paid to be in a documentary or anything but of all the people that should
get some money out of it i feel like it should be the subjects you know what i mean but you you see
these documentaries and they they shed light on these awful awful things you go that's good
but then you wonder is that exploitative in a certain way does it do further damage to certain people
in a certain way i don't know it's a very complicated issue uh but i'm i'm i'm always conflict about it
and and and the truth crime documentaries too um you know it post me too there have been a lot of
these where it's it's talking heads of women talking describing being sexually assaulted
um everyone who sat down and watched that long archelly documentary myself included
you wonder about yourself and about others what what part of you is there just to hear the
salacious details the gossip you know right um at the same time it is great that these women have a
platform to tell their story i just don't know how many people are watching these things for that reason
it's it's well that's the great line that's a great line in the tanya harding movie
yeah when she looks at the camera and she goes so let's talk about the incident that's why you're all here
you know yeah that's that's a great that's a great moment i tend to not like that sort of thing when
they've turned to you and are like you're just as much to blame or whatever i did like it in that movie
that for sure um but yeah it's uh it's always uncomfortable there's you know the Harvey Weinstein
documentaries i've watched a couple of them now and it it's good to sort of i don't know get let their
voices be heard and yet i do feel like why is the documentary filmmaker probably making big money
and setting up a documentary deal off the pain of these women while these women get nothing
it it doesn't really feel good to make right um also i'm being told that pierce brosin is 67 and
will feral is 53 so i guess he in the in the in the film we're supposed to believe brosin had an
image brosin is doing something right man jesus christ oh yeah no it's uh it's incredible that's like the uh
uh what was the you know when nor mcdonald was on the tonight show and he's like i saw dick
clock backstage i asked if i could drink some of his blood you know brosin's carrying it like that
dude he looks great brosin and look i mean uh dick Clark look like a wax statue pierce brosin
still looks like you know just a 30 -year -old dude with gray hair real yeah it's it's madman um
i saw if we're talking about dudes who are probably not going to age as smoothly
uh Seth rogan in an american pickle
and uh i can't believe you sat through this one either i'm shocked
well it was short again short goes a long way but i i texted joe i can't believe the critics aren't
going for the movie about a man who is frozen for a hundred years and pickle bran
yeah um but then sure enough over time i'm like oh this movie is getting kind of good reviews you know
like there are just some people who nobody will ever say how do they explain that the pickle bran
is never inspected uh that his body somehow goes unfound for a hundred years that is the one that
kind of genuine uh lol in the movie for me they did it in my opinion exactly right uh there's
like a press conference and you know they're asking so how did this happen or whatever and they
they call it out they gloss over how stupid it is in an amusing way um i don't remember the exact
dialogue but they they acknowledge that this is extremely far -fetched and like it's like you know
for me all there all those movies about two guys pissing in a fountain and then trading bodies that
came out in the 80s then they made that one with uh bateman and Ryan Reynolds and that one that's
the one where they pitched in the fountain that's the pissing trap one yeah yeah for me i would just
rather it be something quick and stupid like that or like you know gym carry wakes up one day and he
can't lie you know i don't need a 20 minute hit him hit you know like him big i don't need him going
and talking to the zoltar machine i it's i like it it works but in those movies i think if you're
willing to suspend the disbelief needed to enjoy a comedy like that let's get through it as quickly
as possible american people did that well in a fun way you don't need as detailed uh and drawn out
in explanation is cross -pissing in a fountain no i don't yeah why are you weighing me down with the
right uh scientific details they have a sense of humor in that moment about how stupid the premise of
this movie is but it's based on a short story by Simon rich who is a uh i love Simon rich yeah he's
it he did man seeking woman with you know he wrote for s and l all right well now i want to check
i'm no Simon he's a he's a buddy but uh i didn't know he that makes me want to see it a little
bit more now he writes in a style for me that is a little more clever than funny but that is the
popular style right now um and i didn't really love man seeking woman either to be honest but this
movie is not bad it's just also not really good you you just sort of spend the whole time going
why did they make this movie this this man getting brined and pickled but why did Seth
Rogan make this movie why did everyone do it and i don't really know Seth Rogan is good in a dual
role he also plays his grandson uh in Brooklyn they do have some fun some surprising fun at how a guy
who was uh frozen a hundred years ago might be racist might say things that aren't
cool in a modern day you know because he's from a previous time they do a couple interesting things
with the premise i can't say i was really bored by it it's just not something i would really
recommend to people i i can guarantee that whatever studio put it out was very relieved to have a
premiere on HBO Max and not the theaters because it would have died a horrible death in theaters and i
think it could have had a major impact on Seth Rogan's career coming after that charlie's there um
romantic comedy that lost a ton of money uh i mean he would have been in three form you know you
can't have book three big comedies in a row tank like that and you pretty much out of the business
right so look uh i mean we're all just sitting around looking for entertainment
it's about middle of the road you know check it out if you want to all right uh i don't
but uh like i said i'm a fan of Simon Rich and he's a pal so it makes i you want to be supportive
but who am i getting a lot of friends of mine have made things that i've never set eyes on because
i thought that that wasn't into it uh you know look it's it's clever you know it's it's well -written
all right uh let's get to the movie at hand here yes um the movie at hand is in search of darkness
i was so so so excited to see this a four -hour documentary about 80s for who was showing here in
LA at the Egyptian of course it was showing the night where my dad came and visited and we had to
go see van Morrison at the bowl i was livid and i sold my tickets to a buddy of mine or game
my tickets to a buddy of mine and was like please let me know how it was i want to see this so bad
he wound up not going either and they did this as a grass grass roots go fun me thing where it was like
for $60 you get a blue ray of the movie that'll be the only way this documentary is ever available
i missed the cutoff for signing up for that because i thought i was going to go see it in theaters
and basically stupidly i thought i was never going to get to see this movie then the more i thought
about it i was like wait a minute if shutter offers them any money they're going to take they're
going to go back on this pledge to never be available and they did so it's on shutter four -hour
documentary on 80s for um whether due to its popularity or just due to them expecting it to be a hit
they have already commissioned a alternate sequel to insert your darkness where they will do different
movies from the 80s i'll be excited to watch that one too i heard it's going to be deeper cuts like
it's going to be like for hardcore fans which i think is great because this this movie covered a lot
of the real tentpole films of the 1980s and horror but there's and then there were a few that i hadn't
seen or or was less familiar with that i thought oh that's nice to kind of learn a little bit more about
that but i did walk away saying i wish there would have been like some crazy or shit in there
that i'd never even heard of and i think that's what the purpose of the second film is going to be
right i thought they did a good job of having kind of a mix of the popular and the obscure but for four
hours it's it's in the style of and i used to watch these shows when i lived at my parents house i would
i would stay up all night watching these shows bravo's hundred greatest skate they did bravo
scariest moments they did bravo scariest moves there i used to live for these shows vh1 did him as well
just talking heads and clips you know they're very entertaining but they're not super nourishing
it's not like horror and war also available on shudder that we did on this show where you leave
feeling like you've taken an eight week course in black horror in addition to the documentary being
super entertaining you've learned a ton you've gotten a whole new perspective you walk away with a
list of movies to check out in search of darkness unfortunately is very much like those bravo shows
very skin deep very surface any fan of horror 84 is going to have a blast watching it but for me
the drawbacks were pretty obvious number one if you're doing you know 200 movies over the course of
four hours every movie is going to get one minute roughly devoted to it so the the movie winds up
feeling like let's say it's 260 minutes it winds up feeling like you're watching 261 minute
documentaries and that winds up not being satisfying an old you wind up going wait i wanted to hear
way more about that one or why are they talking so much about this one see i disagree i actually like
that format quite a bit and i thought that that i thought that that was the only way you could do it but
i also thought that they broke it up nicely with packages intermittently throughout so like they
would do a thing where it would be like the birth of the final girl and they would get into a five they
would do a five minute little vignette about this is what the final girl in a horror movie means these
are famous final girls and then getting the opinions of women like Heather Langenkab for instance saying
like i hate that they call it i think she's the one said this i hate that they called final girl it's
that so strong woman it's a strong person like you know what i mean or and then other people are
like i love it i love a girl kick an ass you want to i thought all i thought the woman from
chopper or chopping mall and a bunch of and a bunch of other movies at the time had had the best
quote on it which was this whole final girl saying and oh my god she's the final girl and and people
ask me do i like being called that and she said well i would prefer to be called what it is the
star of the movie yeah yeah they used to call it the star of the movie of course i didn't like being
reduced to being the final girl i thought that was great yeah i thought it was too um yeah it's
so i like these little vignettes i thought they broke everything up nicely uh i liked the way they
covered the movies i hear you there are times when you go i want more of that but i thought that was
actually an effective thing because it made me say oh i got to see that movie yeah you know it gave
me the urge to see the movie if i wasn't familiar with it they did cover some movie my two
criticisms are they covered some movies that i didn't think needed to be covered i don't need i don't
need a blast feature at on uh Jason takes Manhattan just to watch five different people say it's not
a good movie but there's some good kill no shit don't cover it it's not worth it's not significant
enough to be on this list there's other things yeah as i texted you that was a big grievance of mine
is at least an hour of this four -hour doc is on the Halloween right in the thirteenth
um and night bar on elm street and there are already four hour documentaries about those
franchises are long in depth documentaries and i understand you can't do an eighty -four
documentary not mention these films but for me it felt repetitive and like time that would have
better spent on different things i get that but i also get to that you you have to look at this as
its own entity and it's not for you you can't make a film and go well if you i hope you already saw
the four -hour nightmare doc because if you didn't you're screwed you got to do your job and so it does
i thought it was repetitive in the sense of in some of the vignettes that i'm talking about that
were thematic they would talk about specific movies so in the final girl girls one they would talk
about the importance of Jamie Lee Curtis in Halloween right and so then don't show me also the one
minute highlight reel of Halloween too at that point you already talked about i saw it don't do it
again right you know what i mean so um that in that sense i thought it was repetitive but uh but all
in all i thought it was very well done i think it's a shiny example of how you can take a very very simple
great idea and execute it on a on a shoestring budget neatly and succinctly uh you know very little
flash but still make it very interesting uh and i can't wait for the next one i really enjoyed it
i feel the same uh my criticisms are just coming from the fact of like it wasn't specifically designed
to my tastes which is going to be everybody's criticism you know i wish it would have spent more
on this and less on this that's right it's the nature of the beast but it's super entertaining and
the one uh thing that they could have and should have dealt with and me and joe talked about it and
every other body of mine who has watched this is the first words out of their mouth
why the hell did they devote so much time to this talking head guy in the blue shirt he's some film
blogger he is he thinks he's on the e -channel in 1999 uh commenting on things and he's making these
quips that suck so much and he's doing them in this i'm making a quip vocal style that is so annoying
i'm glad i don't know his name i don't want to shout him out so you know because i'm just basically
criticizing his personality he sucked out he's my god he is so annoying and they devote so much time
to him they devote so much time to him that i think they edited together the movie and they said
you know what it would be great to have here is somebody saying this and we don't have that and every time
they hit that they made this guy say something about it and plugged him in because there's no other
reason he is he's the most annoying presence they got to drop him for part two he almost derails
the movie when when he is allowed to talk it's a problem and meanwhile there are people in it that
don't get anywhere near enough screen time what one of the guys i wanted to see way more of was James
Rolf from Cinem massacre who also plays the angry video game nerd for anybody that knows the youtube
show here's a guy that does monster madness every year on his channel and reviews tons literally built
a video store in his basement not for the public just to house his movie collection his basement is a
video store yeah and he collects laziness collects DVD collects vhs like this guy has seen every movie and
has a very very heavy working knowledge of horror and he's barely in it he's barely in it so please
in the sequel give a lot more screen time to these guys you know you know i'd rather as pretentious as
i can find Doug Bradley to be i want to hear Doug Bradley talk more than blue shirt you know
when he and john carpenter you want to hear all these people uh i i thought who stole the show for me
was keep david and he a guy who also stole horror and war by the way but his stories are so good he talks
about being in the thing and his favorite moments of the thing and all that um yeah there's huge things
to recommend and and the quibbles are just that quibbles obviously if you listen to this podcast
you're you're gonna love it i would advise you to check it out yeah bonus uh bonus lightning round
of uh movie corner here if you like this kind of film i suggest you check out flesh and blood the hammer
heritage of horror which is the documentary about the hammer films wonderful uh birth of the living dead
which is the documentary about George Romero's making of the night of the living dead wonderful
and finally nightmares in red white and blue uh which is a documentary based on the book of the same title
that talks about uh the social commentary of horror and the how it's based on the fears of americans
throughout the 20th and 21st century uh it's narrated by the great lands hendrickson so uh those are three
that i i went right into after i watched this and loved all three of them so you watch those
four flicks you got a pretty good uh you got a pretty good uh encyclopedic uh dose of horror history in
america so um scream factory is also uh you know at least half of their blue rare releases have feature
life documentaries on movies that you know i i bet if the people that knew and loved these movies knew
that there was a 90 minute documentary out there they they'd seek it out you know uh i hope these
labels stay in business what we'll do on the next step joe as part of the uh screaming in
uh you know people shutting down their blue their blue ray productions which is very scary um i know
it's terrible um okay if you have a full length documentary on say texas chants i'm asking too
which is discussed in uh in search of darkness for maybe two minutes there's a 90 minute doc
on the on the blue ray so uh always always research it if you if you want to go deeper on things there
are ways of doing it um but this is a a perfect primer to 80s forwards a really good document
that's our show folks next episode we're talking cats the uh uh uh
2018 2017 film not the play the movie oh no that it came out this year didn't it no no no no no it's it's
under the last year uh it's 2019 18 whatever the hell it came out with me anyway we're discussing cats
i got a lot to say this is one of the few movies where i have actually wrote a document in my phone
as i was watching it because i couldn't forget any of this stuff um if you want to hear more of me you
You can check out me and Corinne Fisher on the without a country podcast where we try
to find some sanity amidst the craziness of the tribalistic news.
It's on the gas digital network.
Use promo code WAC to sign up, get yourself free month trial for all their content.
And Sal Volcano and I have a new podcast about food coming out very soon.
It will, I can't reveal much more than it will be debuting on August 31st.
That's all I can tell you right now.
And that's it.
I'm the Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram.
You can hear me on some friends podcast, a bunch of the jam with me out.
I said no gifts with Bridger Weinerger, Lizzie Cooperman's quarantine podcast.
I popped around and did some guest spots if you want further listening after you've listened
to Joe's of course.
We will be back with cats.
We'll see you next time.
And thank you so much for coming with us on this Patreon journey.
If you're listening, it means you have up to your tier to get four a month until people
were doing four a month spread the word.
That's the only way people find things out.
We were also instructed to inform you that we know that there are issues every time we
make an adjustment to the Patreon that things you have access to suddenly for some reason
you don't.
Thank you for letting us know.
Just rest assured it will be fixed.
It should be fixed by now by the way.
It should be fixed by now.
Right.
People were saying they couldn't see my movie corners.
I'm going to go in there today when I upload the new movie corner and make sure that that's
all up to snuff.
We don't know why this happens.
Just rest assured we're not trying to screw you over.
I know you know that we're not, but we're definitely not.
We don't understand.
It's just tier.
There's a lot of things you got to tick and boxes and things like that.
So when you change the tier.
So it should all be fixed.
Patel Fix is today as he said and that's it, man.
All right.
See you next time.
We'll see you in a minute.