I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
To this discussion, thank you, about a movie called You're Cordially Invited, that we're going to have a lot to say about, we'll get to it, Will Farrell is back, Reese Witherspoon is back.
First things first, are you team Blake Lively or team Justin Baldoni?
Well, I was Blake in the beginning, it's starting to really shift towards that Baldoni, the more info that keeps coming out.
Shifting Baldoni is way hard. You can tell Ryan Reynolds is like, I've fucked up my life. He has.
Yeah, I mean.
They're not going to trust those two anymore, and that's what Hollywood is built on, trust.
I mean, Jesus Christ, it's like, you know, it's never good when the guy you're saying did terrible shit, turns around and goes, I'm going to sue you, take me, take, empty my pockets and turn me upside down, and try to find something.
I have proof that none of this is true. That's never a good sign.
I really think that they just completely thought he would kowtow to them like everyone else in their life does, that he would go, I'm sorry Blake, you're right, you know, I apologize.
I'm glad he sued back. I believe he's a little weird and awkward.
Sure.
Probably not wholly innocent in the thing, but like he doesn't come back like that if he's not innocent, I don't think.
I wouldn't think so, but, you know.
You're nuts, but especially against that juggernaut. I mean, those two are giants. And then they got him fired from his agency.
It's like they're, a lot of these Hollywood people never got out of high school. They're the same people.
Yeah.
Just nasty, out to ruin other people's lives, and it's bad.
Well, I mean, if I'm not mistaken, Justin Baldoni was,
what am I trying to say? He's self -correct? He's sort of self -made, no?
I've never seen the man before. I did see that movie, which was, I can't believe people are this upset about this movie.
All right. Well, we'll see what happens. Are you close to your mic? You sound real quiet again.
I'm here.
All right. I don't know what the hell's going on, but I mean, hopefully it sounds okay.
Yeah, you sound quiet. It's weird. Now it says you're muted. Oh, boy.
I just turned it up. I don't know if that's going to read on your end, but I turned it up.
Okay. Well, we'll see what happens, folks.
I'm in a big cavernous lake house.
Well, that doesn't affect your volume of speaking.
I mean, I feel like I'm yelling now, but I can go harder.
Now you sound normal. You sound, I don't know, it just sounded like it got lower or something. I don't know.
I'm just asking.
All right.
And I like to let the people peek behind the curtain, see how the sausage is made.
God, I just got really sad about my breakup. Okay. I'm going to try to snap out of that.
Here's a good thing that happened. Very cool. Shout outs, big shout outs to one of our favorite bands and my favorite band,
Fu Manchu, Mr. Bob Balk, lead guitar player, came to my show in San Diego.
Nice.
And we hung out backstage and he watched the show and we had a fucking great time and we drank a bunch of drinks.
And it was awesome. He's the man. Happy to have met him, happy to be getting to know him, becoming friends with him.
San Diego was a really great trip. Shout outs to the American Comedy Company.
They put on four really amazing shows, Gordon and Jesus Christ.
How am I blanking on my own friend's name right now? My friends that opened for me were great.
Let me look that up real quick.
Pretty close. Pretty close.
I just went, whoa, crazy blank right now.
The shows were incredible. The crowds were incredible. Thank you to everybody that showed up.
I really, really appreciate it. Gabby, Jesus Christ, Lamb, and Gordon, thank you both for opening up.
Thanks to the crew over at the American Comedy Company. Everybody over there is really awesome.
I just, it was great. It was a great time. And then Bob Balk from Fu showing up really was awesome.
He brought me some records and a couple of Fu t -shirts.
And we hung out. And it was just an awesome, awesome experience.
Especially, it was right before my dad had to get a surgery. I flew home on Sunday.
Surgery was Monday. And then went through a breakup.
I love Fu Manchu. This was the first December in many years I didn't go.
I don't know. Oh, I know why Vince texted me. Hey, are you here? I said, where? He goes, the Fu Manchu show.
I said, no, I usually go with you. When is it? He goes, I'm here.
I said, oh, well, you didn't invite me.
Oh, there you go.
Made him feel bad because, you know, Vince always feels bad. So I needed to pile on, make him feel worse.
Yeah. Why not? Why no invite from old Avril? That's weird.
I don't know. We always go together.
I'm dust in the wind.
You're not boozing currently, correct?
That's correct. I'm enjoying a peach strawberry spin drift.
What is that? Like a seltzer?
It's a seltzer, yeah.
Now, are you weed free as well?
Correct.
Whoa. So how long on both are you off?
Well, I'm not even intending to be weed free permanently or anything like that.
Nor have I been the entire month of January, but just scaled it way back.
And then drinking is the intention to be done for the year.
OK, good. Let me know how it goes.
I mean that I'm yeah, I'm trying to do a dry out at least for the week, if not for a couple of weeks, because I really all this shit going on, man.
You know, I steered into the curve, as you might imagine.
And man, the booze intake was starting to get a little little crazy.
You know, you start getting that when you start getting that hangover anxiety multiple times where you're like, am I about to have a panic attack right now?
What's going on? Like, that's that's not good.
That scared me a bit.
Yeah, this is the first time in my life where I've taken time off and not missed it at all in any way.
And it was for that very reason. I can't keep doing it and going crazy the next day.
I'm already I'm like improving all these aspects of my life.
So why am I trying to drag it down with this shit?
Basically, I don't miss it.
And I got weed there in a crutch.
If something goes awry.
See, my problem is, is I got no crap.
I got no crutch.
You don't need a crutch.
Man needs a crutch.
So, yeah, I got no crutch.
So, you know, and then you so then you throw a few back and then you're like, fuck.
Yeah, maybe you start opioids.
I haven't heard anything negative.
How about a Jewish one person show?
About an opioid addiction called opioid.
Joe, I haven't shut the door yet.
Keep talking, young man.
I've I just finished listening to Sonny Boy, the autobiography of Al Pacino.
Highly recommend.
But you are throwing your money away, much like with the Norm MacDonald book.
You're throwing your money away.
If you just buy the book, you need to hear Al Pacino read it.
He's doing crazier readings than he was than heat.
He's out crazy walking at this point.
And it was so delightful to listen to.
He's way too honest about like his relationships and how much money he throws away on women.
And it's just great.
It's like he kind of goes movie by movie and those stories are really fun.
But it's all just good.
He'll be like.
I was with John Kazoo.
I said a dog day after noon.
And Johnny says, Al, I want a sandwich.
I go, what?
Like, that's how the book is read.
It's insane.
And it's that way throughout.
So funny.
What is now?
Let me ask real quick.
Does he do?
I know you're essentially saying he does.
But does he honestly do like heat style things where he's like screaming?
Like, you know, like where he gets angry?
But, you know, not so much angry, even when like his manager steals a bunch of money.
But he's and again, like Norm MacDonald, he's been bankrupt numerous times.
These stars, they don't get that.
We don't sympathize at all unless your manager loves you.
But at one point, Pacino's like, look, what do I got to lose?
I'll just tell you.
At one point, I had 90 million dollars in the bank and now I got nothing.
I got nothing.
Well, they said it's great.
It's great.
They said that the reason now it might have been hearsay or bullshit, but the rumor was when when
Pacino and De Niro jumped the shark and started making lots of very bad movies.
The reasoning was that De Niro was doing it because he wanted to get the Tribeca Film
Festival going and he wanted to help bring New York back after 9 -11.
So he was doing anything he could to make money.
And Pacino, it was because of the Beverly D 'Angelo divorce that
us see that he doesn't he doesn't really mention that in the book.
Maybe it's not true, but that was the rumor that the divorce like cleaned him out so bad that he was like,
I got to go rap in the Adam Sandler movie.
You know, like he does say he goes, that was the first movie I did totally for the money.
I needed to do it.
But he's like, I don't know.
Adam is great.
I mean, it was a very good, good, good read.
Good hang.
Now, what was the part that you played me?
His voice is so gravelly.
He like Tom Waits.
Tom Waits is like, buddy, go get this checked out.
You played me something about his aunt taking his pants off.
But what the hell was the scenario?
I didn't understand.
He's like he's like more than 10 years.
He's a boy, but he's over 10 years old at this time.
Yeah. And he's like he tells this story and he's like he got hit in the nuts at school and he comes home.
And it was like apparently a pretty bad injury or whatever.
He goes, I'm lying in bed and I'm trying to sleep off the pain.
I wake up.
My mother, my grandmother and my aunt are all yanking my little penis all around.
They're all yanking on my little penis to make sure I'm OK.
It's the most insane story.
And it's 10 minutes into the book.
I just bought it.
I just bought it on Audible.
It might have done a little psychological damage.
I don't know.
So he's saying basically they they were jerking me off to make sure my dicks wasn't to make sure his dick still worked.
But he wakes up to like three generations of women jacking him off.
I lost it.
He says my little boy penis at one point.
Here's what he sounds like reading the book, by the way.
Many years later, when I was 14, my mother took my father to court again to plead for more money, which he said he didn't have and which we didn't get.
I thought the judge was very unfair to my mom.
Yeah, it's it's great.
But I'm not exaggerating, though, like that.
That was a little snippet.
He does he does insane things with his voice in this book.
I love the cover.
I love when they write these autobiography.
It's him at like 19.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Always.
Something I wanted to mention in the last episode was in Den of Thieves 2, and it was because I watched them back to back.
Ice Cube's son has put on 60 pounds since Den of Thieves 1 and whatever.
He's got a lot of charisma.
Him and Gerard Butler really it really are great together.
I'll watch him do anything at this point, but it just got me thinking.
And we've been we've been too critical of the ladies on this show and Nicole Kidman's of the world.
What if Anna de Armas shows up for her new erotic thriller with Ben Affleck and she's 60 pounds heavier?
They would simply not make the film.
Or if Sidney Sweeney shows up for anyone but you and she's 60 pounds, if she's 25 pounds heavier, they do not make the film.
It's pretty backwards.
And you could say, well, OK, OK, it's two different things.
It's not though.
In Den of Thieves, Ice Cube's son shoots the Batarang thing.
Not an actual Batarang, but you know, he shoots the thing up where the string goes up the building.
And you know, you know what I'm saying?
Shoot the OK, the claw.
So that and then he climbs up this thing and it's a clear stunt double who's 60 pounds lighter in all black, whatever.
And he comes out. It's like Naked Guns style.
He takes the mask off and it's back to Ice Cube's son.
But you're like, no, he was not equipped to make this movie.
This is ridiculous.
It just got me thinking.
You ladies have it tough.
And to that I cheers you a peach strawberry spin drift.
All right.
The here's a yeah, I agree.
I think it is an immense double standard and it's not OK.
I agree.
It's gross.
There's always got to be some sort of sexual or romantic element tagged to the female actresses or actors in a movie.
I think it's very unfair.
They do do it with men to an extent, but nowhere near the way they do it to women.
And I'm not I'm not I'm not joking around.
I think it's a bunch of bullshit.
There's a new movie.
I don't know if it's out.
Oh, God damn it.
Now it comes out March 7th.
I got excited about this.
Well, it's not far off.
The rule of Jenny Penn.
Have you heard of this?
No idea what that is.
Shudder produced apparently a horror movie starring Jeffrey Rush and John Lithgow.
John Lithgow in the trailer.
I'm just reading the description.
Huh?
Lithgow, Jeffrey Rush, and it's a shutter a ridge.
No, I think it's shutter produced.
It's going to produce.
OK, gotcha.
The what I'm reading here about the trailer is, is it says John Lithgow terrorizes a nursing home with a creepy doll.
I'm like, all right, I'm listening.
Yeah.
So yeah, that'll be cool.
I'm excited about that.
I was going to say, I just thought of this because of the judge thing.
It's a very funny clip.
There's a clip of Dice.
He was one of the panel judges on Kill Tony recently.
And some comic comes out and the comic story is about how he got arrested and went to jail.
And then went into his gym when he got released and took a shower.
And the judge that sent him to jail was in the shower next to him just by chance.
And the guy goes, it was weird.
I had just gotten out of jail and I went to the gym and I got a shower.
And who's sitting next to me but Judge Fine.
He's like, whatever the guy's name was.
And he goes, so shout outs to Judge Fine.
Like no animosity.
The kid's literally just saying hi.
And it just cuts to Dice.
And Dice just goes, you just said the judge's name to millions of people.
And the delivery is so funny.
It's so funny.
In the same montage, there's an Asian kid.
And Dice goes, what's your name?
And the kid goes, TJ.
And he goes, shit name.
That's not an Asian name.
Very funny.
Very, very funny.
I thought of that because of Pacino saying, the judge was terrible to my mother.
It was very bad to my mother.
I thought I had another...
I got a scary stuff.
Yeah.
What the hell was it?
Oh, it's...
I want to...
I want to shout out...
Yeah, it's a scary stuff, I guess.
It's a YouTube channel I want to talk about.
Hats Off Entertainment.
This is a guy from, I think, Philly.
Because he's got a hardcore Philly, South Jersey accent.
I should get his name.
These channels, you get so used to just the title of the channel.
Hold on a second.
Let me get the guy's name.
I want to give him a proper shout out.
How do you find...
Oh, well, whatever.
I'll figure it out.
Anyway, the point is he does a great YouTube channel that I think any fan of this show would really enjoy.
It's basically mini -documentaries about all kinds of films, stuff.
He has different series that he does on here.
One of the series he does is called They're Not That Bad.
It's all these movies that have been panned or maligned that he's like, it's not that bad.
He does a legit mini -documentary on the movie.
He did the Dennis the Menace movie.
He did the Wolfman remake.
I love the Dennis the Menace movie.
Yeah, me too.
I was surprised it got so panned.
I didn't know.
The Super Mario Brothers movie.
Nothing but trouble.
Anyway, he does another one called Forgotten Failures that are about these movies that massively fucking flopped
and that Time kind of forgot about but are worth talking about.
He does another one called Almost Cult Classics where he gets into movies that just kind of just sort of missed getting the respect they deserved or the following they deserved.
And then he does like little docu things on like Chris Farley or Leslie Nielsen or whoever.
John Candy.
He's a massive John Candy fan.
His name is Joe Ramone, which is the most Philadelphia South Jersey name ever.
Oh, shit.
Joe, this is insane because I Googled Joe Ramone today.
Are you kidding?
I'm not kidding because I pre -ordered Uncle Buck on 4K and it said it had a commentary.
I said by who?
It said film historian Joe Ramone.
Okay.
There you go.
So I Googled him.
He's doing the commentary on Uncle Buck.
You said John Candy.
I put it together.
That's great.
Well, that is weird kismet.
That's very weird kismet.
He's awesome.
The channel is awesome.
Trust me, Pat.
Subscribe to it.
And it's, by the way, it is a perfect channel.
He does a really nice job with these mini docs.
They're very well put together.
They're television quality.
But it's also a perfect channel for like just comfort food.
It's a great channel to fall asleep to at night.
You know, he's got a very calm, soothing voice.
And he's talking about these things that you love and these movies that you love.
And it's very charming.
It's very sweet.
And he's funny, too.
The documentaries are never really.
They're not meant to be funny, except for the clips he's showing in some of the comedies.
But he, what's it called?
His Twitter is very funny.
Like he gets much more biting on Twitter.
He tweeted the thing about Ellen.
I might have talked about this, but he tweeted the thing about Ellen saying she's moving to England.
And he posted the headline and then he wrote, fitting punishment for them sending us James Corden.
I was like, very funny.
So he's great.
So check out how self entertainment subscribe.
It's great.
I will.
I absolutely will.
Hey, I'll do a scary stuff, even though I'm not sure that it applies as always.
But I ordered the Lions Gate Limited special editions.
Lions Gate Limited is a brand new boutique, shall we say, Blu Ray 4K site.
Oh, they just announced the Den of Thieves collection in 4K.
And, you know, your boy is going to buy it.
I just went to the website.
But as of right now, they have very few titles.
You go to lionsgatelimited .com.
Joe and I received no money from these people.
Reservoir Dogs, Jackie Brown, Kill Bill 1 and 2.
You're next.
The Third Man, The Conversation, Apocalypse Now, and now Den of Thieves.
So very limited titles.
Steel books, but they shipped real fast.
They're, you know, they're great quality.
Whether you got the steel book or not, or the Lions Gate Limited or not,
the big find for me of the year is the Jackie Brown 4K.
I assume that the Kill Bills and all the other ones I just mentioned will look great as well.
I can't speak for them.
All I've watched is Jackie Brown.
But to me, it is maybe the best transfer I have ever seen.
I thought it looked better than it did when I saw it at midnight on Christmas Day in 1998.
It looked amazing.
It's what 4K is all about.
It hits a certain kind of movie just right.
And this one, I thought it did.
It was leaps and bounds above any other version I've ever seen of this movie.
So I highly, highly recommend it.
And as you know, it's one of my top movies of all time.
We talk about it on the show all the time.
So what is it about it?
I know what I speak.
What is it about it that looks?
Because, you know, it's interesting.
You texted me how good it looked.
The only reason I didn't get sort of excited about it was, you know, I just was like,
well, Jackie Brown already looks pretty amazing on Blu -ray.
And it's not like it's an it's not like Total Recall where it's like, oh, my God, the Mars sequences look nuts now.
Like, you know, I so I was like, you know, it's insanely bright, vivid colors.
Like every like scenes just look different.
There's a scene where they go to the bar together, Forrester and Jackie Brown, and it's got a red filter on it or whatever.
But it just something about it, the 4K.
What it does the best really is it's going to be the best reproduction of like an avatar type thing, of course.
But I what I love what it does is brings out the color in movies.
Like I just watched the blue velvet 4K.
Perfect example, the opening scene with the white picket fence and the red roses and everything.
It makes that shit look like art and probably how it was intended.
But I would say, especially since I was watching these on like Missouri Mall movie screens,
I have never seen some of these movies look so good, especially Jackie Brown.
So I would say the color was the number one for me.
And look, I'm a film nerd, but I'm not like Sue.
I don't get, you know, get out of ruler and check on this stuff or aspect ratios and all of that.
I just know what visually is appealing to me.
And I just thought it looked better than I could have ever imagined.
So the bummer for me is, is I would like to purchase these.
You know, they're not that I mean, 30 bucks for Reservoir Dogs, 40 for Jackie Brown.
Yeah, I always think these things are overpriced.
But but, you know, I'd like to own both, but it just kills me because it's like I paid Christ.
I paid one hundred dollars for the used version of the Tarantino double X.
All right. Yeah.
Box because it was it went out of print so quick and then used for the and it's all the blu rays.
So I have all these and now I've I've now bought Reservoir Dogs already on 4K, regular 4K.
I bought it. I sold it.
Pulp Fiction on 4K.
I need Jackie Brown for it.
But I'm like, I don't want to spend the money again on Reservoir Dogs just because it's a steelbook.
You know, I don't know if it's this.
Is it the same 4K? I'm assuming it is.
I'm assuming the movie won't look any different.
Yeah, I don't know.
You know.
I don't know.
This stuff's tough.
I assume that the movie would be the same.
But, you know, so then you get just the Jackie Brown 4K.
Yeah.
And it's like, well, no, now there's going to be twelve dollars shipping or whatever.
You're like, God damn it, man.
I don't want to spend fifty four dollars for this.
You know.
Anyway.
But take us to the corner, Joe.
Take us to the corner.
Well, I saw a little picture called The Apprentice.
About Mr. Roy Cohn and one Donald J. Trump.
Starring Sebastian Stan.
He is nominated for this movie.
So I thought I'd check it out.
He's really, he really is good at it.
It was weird because, like, he doesn't really do a Trump impression.
He kept he very much captures his mannerisms, but he does not try to make his voice sound like Trump.
He doesn't move away from sounding like Trump, but he's not there doing like an SNL like ridiculous impression.
He just kind of captures the embodiment of the guy.
He's very good.
Within two minutes of watching the movie, I was I forgot it was Sebastian Stan.
And I kept being like, wait a minute, that's about that's wild, man.
I keep thinking this is actually Donald Trump.
So that was great.
The guy from succession that played Roy Cohn was awesome.
The movie is very, very interestingly directed by a director I was unfamiliar with.
But they shoot it very it's very grainy 80s.
It looks like the 80s feels like the 80s.
I thought that was cool.
I thought the pace and the score and, you know, I downloaded the score on Apple Music.
It's by like I think a Swedish composer.
But the sense that whole synth score in it that almost sounds like horror music was fucking cool, man.
No, you know what? Not harm of music.
It sounded like Scarface.
The movie reminded me.
Yeah, it reminded me very much of Scarface.
And I think that that was probably done on purpose.
It's it's a nice film.
Look, it's a biopic at the end of the day.
It's it's biopics are never going to be amazing.
But I thought this was a very well made biopic.
And I thought that they did a really good job of just sort of honestly portraying each of these two people.
And, you know, he it's it's it's it's it humanizes them.
But without sympathy, without pity, it just shows you this is the kind of person that can end up doing this.
And that's it. You know what I mean?
Yeah. So that's what it is.
It's but it's a great movie.
Or as great as it can be.
Yeah, I like The Apprentice for a biopic.
I mean, you know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah.
I saw a woman of the hour on Netflix directed by Anna Kendrick and starring Anna Kendrick.
The true story took place in the 70s.
A serial killer appeared on live television as one of the eligible bachelors on the dating game.
And Anna Kendrick goes out with him.
She is an aspiring actress in L .A. 1978.
And the movie is a thriller.
It's not terrifying, but it's a really nicely done movie.
It's a tight 90.
It is really about the various subtle and, of course, not so subtle ways that men give women a hard time,
ranging from her male friend who won't stop hinting at something more, even though she told him she's not into it,
played by Pete Holmes, which was a surprise.
Then she also has encounters with this serial killer.
And it's really just about the ways women in the 70s, but, of course, you're supposed to make parallels to today,
just had to deal with an onslaught of terrible behavior, big and small.
In that way, it's a good movie.
I liked what it was trying to do.
As a thriller, it certainly wasn't scary or suspenseful.
I kind of came in hoping for a Silence of the Lambs type of vibe, and that's not what I got.
So that's always kind of tough when your expectations are for a different genre than the movie really is.
But this was a very well -made drama, I would say, with occasional thriller elements about what the ladies got to go through.
You know what I mean, Joe?
Yeah, all right.
I haven't, given all that's been going on, watched too much more, so I feel like I'm kind of...
It's always hard to put comedy specials in the movie corner, especially when they're not Jamie Foxx weeping for 35 minutes.
Play, play, play, play, play, play, play.
But I will say this, I did watch, and it has brought me great, great joy.
I watched Nick Swartz's Make Joke from Face.
Ooh, I'll watch it tonight.
Which you can watch on YouTube, and I think it's somewhere else too, I don't remember.
And then also his comedy, I think it was a Comedy Central special, Taste It, which was the one before that.
Both made me laugh really, really hard.
Make Joke from Face is my, I prefer that of the two, but they're both great.
And it's awesome. It's Nick Swartz in being Nick Swartz in.
He's really funny, he's very animated, he's very goofy.
He's great.
It's a wonderful, just little escape.
It's nice to be able to put something like that on, and there's no commentary, there's no whatever.
And I'm as guilty as anybody of doing commentary, so I'm not saying there's anything wrong with that.
But I like when you can find an escape like this, where you can just kind of put it on, laugh, be silly, and have a good time.
So I highly recommend both of those specials, if you want to do that.
I do, and I'll watch them this evening.
I've been watching a lot of stand -up.
You know who I really enjoyed special was Liza Traeger.
Or is that I'm saying that right?
Traeger.
Yes.
That made me laugh, I thought she was really funny.
All right, I have to highly recommend Kunk on Life.
Okay.
This is on Netflix.
Kunk is a character, much like a female Alan Partridge kind of vibe.
A British lady played by a British actress, Diane Morgan, who I have fallen in love with.
And it's your classic David Brent, Alan Partridge, British character, very cocky, very dumb and misinformed.
And that's just always a great combo for me.
It's always going to make me laugh.
And she has a couple specials up on Netflix.
The brand new one is called Kunk on Life.
It is a little over an hour, and it is laugh out loud funny throughout.
Similar to like a Borat or something.
It's a lot of her character interviewing very stuffy, serious British pompous scientists and people that work in the arts, philosophers.
And just asking them really stupid questions.
It's a lot like between two ferns.
I mean, you feel the influences in it, but she's so funny and the writing is so sharp.
Like the one liners they keep giving her to ask these people are so funny.
And it's great.
The people never break either.
It's not like the goal is to make them laugh.
It's just people like, you know, The Daily Show is another pioneer of this format.
But it's just really serious people trying to answer her question without letting her know how stupid she is because they don't know who this woman is.
She has the benefit of anonymity because she's I truly never seen the woman before.
But I immediately went back and watched the other Kunk that is on Netflix, which was just as funny.
She's great.
Really recommend it. She's really funny.
I've discovered her on Afterlife, the Ricky Gervais show.
Oh, I loved Afterlife.
Yeah, she she plays his I guess just coworker.
But and at the at that newspaper that he works for.
And yeah, she's very much this kind of character like clueless and sort of out to lunch.
And then, you know, in typical Gervais style, as the show goes on, you start to really kind of feel for her because you realize she's she's she's very awkward and has a hard time, you know, meeting people and is kind of lonely.
And it becomes quite sympathetic.
It goes from being very goofy in like a David Brent way to being sympathetic.
But I always thought she was really good on it.
Really funny, but just really good, you know, very convincing at playing a character that was really just a space case.
And and then I looked her up and then I discovered the crunk thing and I was like, oh, man, she's she's fucking funny, man.
It's a great character.
I hope they do a lot more specials because she's great.
Yeah.
Or Kunk.
Sorry.
C -U -N -K.
I wonder if if I mean, no, like that is her real last name, right?
That's her real name, right?
It's now a character.
Her name is Diane Morgan.
Oh, her name.
Oh, did you say that?
I'm sorry.
I missed it.
Yes.
OK, sorry.
On the show, her name is Philomena Kunk.
Do you think she did that because of how much it sounds like cunt?
And like that's probably and the and the K sound is funny.
Yeah.
She was in the David Brent movie as well, which was I remember being pretty funny.
And she was in Alan Partridge Alpha Papa, which was great.
Great as girl and crowd, though.
So early.
Is it my turn?
It is my turn.
I don't really turn.
I don't have anything else, but I watched yesterday.
This was really just an amazing thing, a moment, realization.
My friendship and I went out and got some food and I started to talk about my breakup and had a panic attack and had to leave.
So we went back to my house and.
Brought our food with us and turned on the YouTube on TV and said, let's just watch some funny stuff.
I got to get my mind off of the sad stuff.
And we put on a bunch of old WC Fields sequences and clips from things.
The one that stuck out the most was it was I think it's I forget which movie it's from, but it's the poker game.
It's a pretty famous WC Fields thing where everybody at the table is getting multiple aces.
Yeah, they do this gag in this thing, man.
I was we're laughing so hard where it's that classic like old school comedy thing where he's like he has five aces.
He knows it's impossible to have five aces.
If he has five aces, they're going to think he's cheating.
Yeah, he keeps discarding the fifth ace.
And every time he pulls a new card, it's an ace again.
And every time he sees the fifth ace again, he does the like startled thing like.
Yeah, we were laughing so fucking hard at how simple the idea was and how funny it was.
And this is from 1932 or something.
Chip, Chip turns to me, he goes, he goes, this is a hundred years old and it's making us laugh this hard.
And I was like, holy shit.
That's which brings us to you're cordially invited.
Brand new. Yeah.
And not a laugh in it. Let's get right to it.
Now, are we?
Yeah, that's all I had to say about that.
I just found that I found the historic aspect of that incredible.
But we've only done.
We still have one more movie to do.
I did three each. I already did three.
Oh, you started this.
OK, I'm sorry.
I guess it would have been a nice transition.
That would have been a great transition.
And I can't I can't allow it.
I watched Gentlemen Broncos, which I thought I had seen and realized I had not.
It is the third Jared Haas movie, Napoleon Dynamite, then Nacho Libre, which is about half as good as Napoleon Dynamite.
And then Gentlemen Broncos, which is sadly half as good as that.
The cast is incredible.
Funny you bring this up.
Kurt Metzger was just like raving about this movie.
He's like, it's so funny.
Well, and there are moments that are.
I mean, I think even masterminds with Galifianakis and wig, I think this Jared Haas makes really funny movies, even when they're kind of bad.
And I'm very curious to see what his Minecraft looks like.
It does not look good.
What's the other one?
Don Verdean.
Wait, he's doing Minecraft.
I thought McElhaney was directing Minecraft.
That was 10 years ago.
Yeah, it's coming.
Gentlemen Broncos is a boy, Michael Angarano, who is an aspiring sci fi book writer.
And his hero is played by Jermaine Clement, who is very, very funny in this.
The way he says his name is a laugh every time he says his own name when he answers the phone.
It's very funny.
Jennifer Coolidge plays the boy's mom.
She's great as always.
Very heartwarming performance.
Mike White, who is now the creator, showrunner of The White Lotus, one of the best shows on television, plays the role of a snake wrangler.
The snake often has graphic diarrhea on screen.
So this was a different time in his career.
But the movie itself only works sporadically, but what's funny is really, really funny.
So I can sort of recommend it.
There's all these fantasy sequences in the book world that star Sam Rockwell in a dual role.
He's like playing a cool astronaut and he's playing this like almost Paul Lind type astronaut guy.
And that that character is very funny.
Those sequences kind of tend to get a little tiresome.
But I got to say, I'm going to start going back to a lot of these older comedies that I just missed, especially ones that just got bad reviews and I ignored.
Because I think that now where we have no comedies, they're probably going to seem pretty fucking good.
Like this movie seemed like, all right, I wish this was this funny throughout.
But the scenes that made me laugh, I thought were really solid.
So check it out.
All right.
Let's talk.
You're cordially invited, Joe, to give me your thoughts on this film.
The premise is so basic that if I thought of it on the toilet, I would not pitch it anywhere because I would not have thought it was a good enough idea to pitch.
Two families book the same resort to have their wedding on the same weekend.
I mean, it's it's a Golden Girls at best.
It's it's yeah.
And my God, is this is this premise over explained?
And oh, yeah, I mean, my God, it's like it's like they they actually show like Will Ferrell setting the date.
And then the woman, the old lady who owns the estate or whatever you call it, where they want to have the wedding dropping dead as soon as she writes it down.
And that's the reason the mix up happens is because she never got it fully written into the ledger to put it on the books.
And then and then the day gets booked by Reese Witherspoon for her sister's wedding.
It's on paper, I imagine.
And so anyway, so both families show up.
They're completely different types of families.
But I mean, this entire fucking movie should fall under the title White People problems.
I mean, you know, I'm sorry, but it's just like, Jesus Christ, guys, like, who gives a shit?
Your little fucking Nantucket wedding thing like who fucking cares about any of this?
Like, it would have been so much more interesting if it was like people that didn't have money and couldn't solve the problem in two seconds.
Will Ferrell, the one of the big jokes at the end of this movie is the reveal of his job.
Finally, he goes on the CEO of Delta Airlines.
That's his job. Reese Witherspoon runs like a TV network or something.
It's like, guys, this is a problem that could be fixed instantly by each by one person in each of the families financially.
This is a fix that they could afford ten times over and not even bat an eye.
It's it's such, you know, privileged who gives a fuck like like make it about two blue collar families or make one of the families rich and one of the families blue collar.
You know, it's like they do nothing with it.
So I guess on paper, this sort of red like wedding crashers, like everybody's going to go to this island and the high jinx will ensue.
Well, I guess that does happen.
But man is the jinx not high, let alone jinx.
It's just it's terrible.
I did a lot of time and sold some projects back in the early 2010s in the film world back when they made all those, you know, sex comedies and like the hardest part is coming up with the high jinx because they're not necessary.
You're trying to think of just something crazy to shoehorn into these movies, but they don't happen organically from the plot.
And this one, the fact that there's an alligator crawling around this movie at all, you're already like, all right, where's this fucking thing going?
And where it went was so lazy and so stupid that I was like, all right, I was willing to go with you on an alligator bit.
You know, I'm not happy about it, but if you give me a good alligator bit, I'll give you a laugh.
This thing ends with Will Ferrell cuddling what he thinks is a dead alligator in bed.
Why are you doing that, Will?
Whether it's dead or not, why are you doing that?
He's cuddling it.
Believe it or not, it's alive.
Then we watch Will Ferrell wrestle a CGI alligator and he throws it out the window.
Pat, it's not even CGI.
It's a it's a dummy alligator.
Was it a dummy?
It's ridiculous, Pat.
The whole thing is ridiculous.
There is some CGI, I think.
Then, folks, he throws it out the window.
He throws the alligator out the window and he says, and I quote, See you later, alligator.
And I said, you know what?
Take me back to the year 2010, please.
Yes, Joe.
The poster is him gripping an alligator.
This is supposed to be the big set piece of the movie.
You're supposed to really love this part and really get into this.
By the way, people, you say to yourself, a set piece like a man wrestling a dead alligator turns out to be a live alligator.
Well, this is clearly the climax of the film.
This is so bat shit that whatever.
That's what I thought.
Also, I thought that because I felt like I had been watching the movie for three hours at this point.
I pull up the time bar thing.
It's like, no, you're about 40 minutes in.
You got an hour still here.
I'm like, what the fuck?
Who puts this?
This thing is so uneven.
It's so imbalanced.
It makes no fucking sense.
Some of these top.
We're going to put the word top in heavy quotes here.
Critics on Rotten Tomatoes praised this thing because this is Benjamin Lee for the Guardian.
The real win here is watching Witherspoon and Farrell show off, both unrestrained by a harder rating and a more raucous spirit than the normal they both make for wonderful, petty antiheroes.
None of that is true.
They don't show off.
Reese Witherspoon is, as you've put it before, sleepwalking through this fucking movie.
There's zero motion.
Farrell is mailing it in.
He says fuck like eight times and you're supposed to be like, oh, this is edgy.
It's not.
It's not funny.
They have done funnier versions of everybody in this movie.
And I have some friends in this movie.
I'm not trying to knock whatever, but everybody in this movie is playing a less funny version of a thing they've done way funnier somewhere else.
Everybody.
And it's it's it's a real disappointment, man.
It's just a real disappointment.
I mean, I didn't think there was any reality where this movie was going to be great, but I thought, you know, maybe there'll be some laughs.
There's there were one or two jokes that made me laugh.
I did one full laugh out loud at the joke that Will Farrell makes about having the threesome with the two widows.
That was it.
This thing's an hour and forty nine minutes.
It feels like you're watching the Godfather three uncut.
Like, I mean, that widows joke hits at one forty seven.
So you're late in the game for that laugh.
Yeah, I had a couple laughs when they're all asking Reese Witherspoon, like, how are you adjusting to the fires in L .A.?
How are you adjusting to the pedophiles?
And how are you just that made me laugh a little bit.
All the bad things that are here.
But that's just because I'm a local.
And then by the way, how weird that they make the fires joke.
I know.
And left it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Good.
Beyond that, there wasn't a lot of laughs for me at all.
There wasn't many at all, folks, to be honest.
The romance when it brews up like I was seriously asking you, Joe, like are Reese Witherspoon and Will Farrell supposed to be falling in love?
Because it is so not apparent.
They have so little chemistry right up to the end.
They do a song and dance together.
And you're like, I'm not buying that these guys even like each other.
Will Farrell always has that problem.
Like an elf.
I'm always like, get away from that girl elf.
I don't know.
I love the man, but he doesn't scream romantic lead to me.
I thought they did an interesting thing when what's her name?
Leanne Morgan.
Yeah, I liked her in this when she said she's fine.
Just it's nobody's fault.
The script sucks.
There's nothing funny.
So, you know, but anyway, I thought they did an interesting thing when she said like about Will Farrell.
Like I'd climb him like a redwood or whatever.
And Reese Witherspoon was like, really?
And she's like, yeah, he's a good looking guy.
I thought that was a nice little detail because that is something I've seen women do where they'll go.
They'll go, oh, that guy's kind of hot, right?
It's kind of like a try.
He's kind of, you know, like, oh, I didn't notice it because he's not the traditional square jawed lead or whatever.
I thought that that justified it enough.
I don't find Reese Witherspoon and Will Farrell to be an unbelievable match or couple, but they just had zero chemistry, zero.
It was kind of amazing how they could not have any chemistry because they're actors.
So you're supposed to be able to fake it.
People that hate each other can fake it.
The cast is stacked.
You know, there's a lot of funny people these days sitting around with nothing to do because there's no more comedies.
So you get a bunch of funny people in here.
But, yeah, unfortunately, they're not given much funny stuff to do.
I liked a lot of the supporting cast.
I was rooting for the movie as I root for all comedies, but it just wasn't hitting.
The few moments were kind of the smaller moments.
I liked when like Will Farrell and his daughter would connect or whatever.
And when Reese Witherspoon and her mom connected, I really like Celia Watson a lot as an actress.
And I liked her in the movie.
I liked that moment.
I bought it.
They took those little character moments at times that I appreciated.
But on the whole, there's just too much that happens that's just dumb.
And you're forced to believe that everyone in the scene is dumb for it to work.
Ebert called that the idiot plot where you have to just go, oh, I guess this person's an idiot.
But like she goes outside at one point.
She sees one of the groomsmen making out with one of the bridesmaids, something that has happened at every wedding since the dawn of time.
She runs in and says, I'm very like, I know that that was the groom cheating on the bride, which throws the wedding into chaos.
And it's like, by the way, which, by the way, is because they're dressed exactly the same, including I'm saying a hat.
It's really insane that she you'd have to be an idiot to go.
That's got to be they're all wearing the same clothes.
So you're the whole time like what?
And then when they come in like, oh, that was just us.
It doesn't play like a fun twist of the plot or anything.
You're like, of course it was them.
So that's kind of what the whole movie is like.
It's like, would you believe this, the alligator thing?
And you're like, no, I don't.
And that just keeps happening.
If this is me, I would have probably said to that woman like.
Hey, what if you do yours for these this four hours and then we do a late night wedding at ten?
You know, and you work it out, you negotiate, you cut a check.
There's you can't have that many ways out of your movie before it starts or you're not going to buy.
There's such fixable problems.
Yeah, it's it's it's you know, one of the things at the beginning is they go, well, when you're outside, when you're inside the barn, we'll do our thing outside.
And then we'll switch and you guys do your thing outside and we'll go inside.
And it's like, well, wouldn't you know it?
It rains when they're out.
It's like, guys, this is the best you got.
This is your plot device rain.
Yeah, come on.
Like, this is terrible.
And it also, too, to me.
Is who who did something's got to give and it's complicated.
What's her name?
I'm blanking.
Nancy Meyers, Nancy Meyers.
It shows you why, like a Nancy Meyers or Nora Ephron succeed in the types of movie they make, because this is very much the vibe of a something's got to give.
And the difference is, is something's got to give is completely simple.
It is completely believable.
It is completely just what it needs to be.
And it is not riddled with with gags and stunts and big, ridiculous set pieces and alligator wrestling and all this stuff.
It is driven by the characters.
The scenarios are simple.
The scenarios are believable.
And that's just all there is to it.
Folks, our hogs are down.
Our hogs are down.
For this film, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You are cordially invited to come see how down our hogs are for your cordially invited.
And I am speaking for both of us.
And as Pat is not interrupting me, he knows that that that I am correct in saying that both of our hogs are down.
Do you have anything to add to that, Pat?
My hog is very down.
There you go, folks.
Yes.
You know, I dropped out of this recording.
Yeah, that's why I just wave my hand like, don't say anything.
I got it.
People think I just stopped talking.
I covered it.
That's why I said don't.
But now they know.
So there you go.
I want them to know.
I'm a professional.
What happened on my end?
Why did my thing stop?
I don't fucking know.
It's your computer.
I don't know.
Because you're in it was weird.
You're in an Airbnb in fucking Atlanta where nothing works.
That's true.
No, you froze for a minute.
And I just said I wrapped it up.
I said the movie sucks.
Nora Efron and Nancy Meyers don't need alligator wrestling to make their plots about families and whatever simple or fun.
This could have just been a thing about characters.
You look, you're in a bad spot when you go.
Wedding Crashers was more grounded.
You know, it's all I can say.
Hog is down.
Too zany, too wacky.
Although this isn't an F movie to me.
It felt like, honestly, having a sitcom on in the background pretty much.
We'll be back.
Yeah, look, just from its basic construction, it feels, you know what it feels like?
It feels like right before COVID when the movie industry, when we were all like, I'm not going to the movies anymore.
When like the internship came out.
Yeah.
And stuff like that.
And you were like, guys, I can't.
I'm not. What was the movie where they both go work at Google?
Vince Vaughn and Owen Wilson.
That was way before COVID, but it was the internship.
But, you know, when those things started happening or like, you know, whatever movie Ben Stiller did when we were like, all right, Ben, take a fucking year off, please.
Like, it just felt like one of those movies where it was just lifeless.
Everybody was there for the money.
But I don't think they were.
I think they actually thought this was going to be good and it was just terrible judgment.
I don't know.
But yeah, so anyway.
So it's not an F for that reason.
Construction wise, it was it was well put together and the budget was on the screen and whatever.
But I mean, it is a D minus, you know.
Not great.
Thanks for your time, everybody.
Not sure what we'll be doing later in the month, but we'll let you know.
I think we're still going to probably do Wolfman and there's some big horror movie coming out.
Oh, The Monkey.
We could do The Monkey.
Yeah, The Monkey.
I'm excited about.
I am going to try to force myself to see Wolfman.
We might do Companion, which fucking dumbass fucking Entertainment Weekly.
I go on Google News today.
Big fucking headlines.
Yeah, they put the spoiler in the fucking headline.
Oh, I didn't see it.
Unbelievable.
They're doing that lately.
They're like you had you had a weekend.
Yeah.
So anyway, we'll be back, folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.