I'll see you in hell.
Folks, welcome to We'll see you in hell.
We're back for the month of February.
My God Almighty, the lover's month is upon us, Valentine's, and we're talking about a movie
Choc Full of Love today.
Blink twice.
What a romantic venture this film was.
You know, it's usually a compliment when I say I don't know where a movie was going, but
sometimes as with a movie like this, you're not pleased with that reveal at all.
You're not pleased at all.
And the reveals just keep coming till they lose all meaning.
Yeah, but it's on Amazon Prime.
If you want to stop and not have it spoiled for you, it's free of charge to watch with your
Amazon Prime membership.
All it costs is your soul.
Things are interesting right now.
It's a slow period for movies.
As we've said, these are the slow months, but some interesting stuff happening.
Let's kick it off with the news psycho story.
Everybody wants to hear old Amelia Perez in a little bit of trouble.
I never expect the person to say Amelia Perez.
I'm always delighted when I hear it.
Yeah, no, my friend was sending me that the other day.
I was like, wow, I can't believe you don't delete that Twitter account or at least do a
quick scroll when you are up for all the awards for being the wakos movie ever made, trying
to check every possible box and failing quite frankly.
Yeah, I'm like, oh, what did she say?
What are they blowing out of proportion this week?
I read them and I was like, oh, Hitler was on to something.
It was like the first one I read.
Oh, Amelia, sweet Amelia.
Amelia, Amelia, Amelia.
I read a lot of them.
This guy, Mike Fleming, Jr. who wrote the article for Deadline.
I mean, what a fucking punch this guy is.
Well, he writes for Deadline.
Yeah, he writes.
If you're writing about me, I love you, Deadline, but otherwise you suck.
Hopefully, where is the line?
Oh, ready for this line?
Yeah.
Considering what the actress went through herself, her fans deserve to show her more compassion
when describing the differences between people.
Really, Mike, would you give that to a, if she said she was pro fucking Trump, would you
say that, Mike?
I doubt it.
I fucking doubt it.
I mean, it's unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
The contradiction and the double standards.
I mean, it's just fucking disgraceful.
And by the way, some of the stuff she wrote was pretty inflammatory and pretty racy.
Some of the stuff she wrote was being like, I don't think Islam should make women wear
hoods.
And you're like, yeah, they, they, they shouldn't.
I agree with that.
And people are like, how dare you?
Guys, what, what argument are we having here?
I don't understand anymore.
The answer is we're having every argument all the time at all times.
And everyone has just lost it.
They've lost their minds.
Yeah.
I can't even give a fucking rats fucking ass anymore about anything.
I was talking to Pinkstone earlier tonight.
And he wasn't like going on and on.
He just was like, you know, he just was talking about, you know, some of the stuff in the
news that's happening right now that he's that he's very unhappy about that that Trump's
doing.
And he was making great points.
I a lot of it, I think was shitty.
And I, but I just was like, bro, I, I, I hear you and it sucks.
I don't have the emotional or mental bandwidth anymore to even read about it.
Like yeah, I feel like we're on the roller coaster anymore with everything.
And they're like, here we go.
Here we go.
Like yeah.
Well, you can easily lose yourself in it to avoid dealing with your own shit.
And nobody wants to deal with their own shit right now.
We've been doing it for too long because the pandemic, we had to look in the mirror for
too long.
We got scared.
We got sad.
We got angry.
We were tired.
And yeah, I don't want to sit every day and hear about how horrible the world's going
to get tomorrow.
I can't do it either, Joe.
I know I sound angry, but I'm agreeing with you.
I can't do it.
And I feel, and then, you know, I go to work and I, you know, I love my job and my co-workers
and everything.
But it's like, you say, you slip up and say that.
And it's like, well, well, look who can afford to not care.
Look who can.
And it's all funny and in good nature.
But it's like, guys, I know we, we're all, you know, trying to be more caring in these
up and coming generations.
They're younger writers of course, my co-workers.
And it's like, we're all struggling here.
I'm telling you what I need to do for my mental health.
Why is that not valid?
Yeah.
Isn't mental health and self-care a thing?
Why do I sound like Bill Burr?
I didn't even know I had that register.
Look, there it is.
Yeah.
Well, Pat, it's a terrible time in the world.
The terrible time in life.
I am a recently single.
Didn't last very long.
Did it.
And right before Valentine's Day.
Right before Valentine's Day.
Right before the lady's birthday.
It was coming up right around Valentine's.
That whole thing planned.
I was going to jump out of a cake.
Now I'm just, I'll be alone eating the life-size cake for the person's nice cake.
Students still get in there.
And they just eat your way out.
Might be kind of fun.
I'm going to escape room.
A delicious escape room.
I'll do it.
I'll have them meal it.
On escape room.
Do we make this a business?
I don't think it's a bad idea.
I'd your way out.
I say wheel the cake down out into the street.
I'll eat my way out and give video to you.
It's like a Jamie Kennedy experiment thing.
Everybody gets scared.
What the hell is going on?
That's what my 4th ex-wife used to say.
She'd say, eat your way out.
That's upsetting.
Yeah.
It should lock me between her legs while I was down there and then just say, eat your
way out.
I realize now life actually becomes real because I wanted to say, you know, the rowdy danger
club, you know, my ex-wife, you know, she, but I actually have an ex-wife.
So I can't do that anymore.
I had to say 4th ex-wife.
This recent breakup made me realize I will have an ex-wife at some point.
I'm clearly not, Joe, I had the same realization.
I don't know that marriage is in the cards.
I'm at peace.
I'm enjoying myself and, you know, I think this is my natural state and I'm in a relationship
ish that I enjoy quite a bit.
It's complementing my life nicely, but I'm not letting it overtake my life.
That was the mistake I think.
I don't want to say it was a mistake.
I enjoyed the relationship.
We had a great time.
It didn't work out.
I don't want to say anything negative.
But I will say a misstep could have been moving it into the exclusive territory.
We were doing just fine.
Yeah.
Until we put that exclusive fucking stamp on it and that's when all the goddamn problems
started.
And, you know, I don't know.
There's just, I don't know.
It was, and by the way, it wasn't like cheating or anything like that.
It was just like, it applies a pressure.
And, you know, I'm feeling my dad and his stuff now.
I'm a raw nerve with my family stuff happening.
And by the way, thank you to everybody that reached out.
Emily and Liz and Matt and Will and so many people from the show, friends of the show,
and fans of the show reached out with well wishes for my dad.
I probably should have led with this.
He's fine.
He got through the surgery.
He's good.
He's progressing.
Now, it's a long road to recovery after open heart surgery, but he's doing very well.
He's doing as well as you can.
So that's great.
But it doesn't mean that it's not a challenge and it doesn't mean that it wasn't stressful.
It was very much both.
So, you know, man, you apply that to a relationship and it's tough.
It's tough.
Yeah.
I just sort of changed my perception of things and met somebody who also had kind of a
gotten out of a long term thing.
And then we both just communicate about it.
A real flaw of mine is my communication, flaw of a lot of men, flaw of a lot of women,
flaw of a lot of people.
Yeah, yeah.
But, yeah, I was just like, I'm just going to start saying what I'm thinking and it's
so far as worked out, beautiful.
We're all good.
The same.
And I think as far as the label thing goes, it can make you feel needlessly weird.
It's like, we're having fun.
Who gives a shit?
But you got to find somebody who doesn't need the label it and that's increasingly rare
the older you get.
People want to know you're there for the long haul and they want to know they're not going
to catch something.
Okay.
That's what I told her.
We pulled the rubbers and said, like, look, if you want to go on a date, let me know.
But if you're going to have sex with somebody, that's a whole different thing, you know?
And it's like, there's a respect.
I like that.
I think I'm moving forward.
I'm just going to say, look, if you have sex with somebody else, please wear a condom.
I don't want to know anything about it.
Not the, and again, we, me and this lady did not do any of that.
We were very, even in the beginning, we weren't sleeping with other people or anything.
So it just is a shame.
I'm going to, you know, whatever.
It is what it is.
It's fine.
We'll bounce back at some point and, you know, move on and all those other things.
But I will say, the big takeaway for me in this was, and this is kind of the opposite
to what you're saying, because it's the reverse situation.
It made me realize I actually do like the companionship.
And I do think that that was a more than fair trade for the freedom of being single.
You know, we're human.
You're only going to ever want, you know, everybody's going to have a bit of a wondering
eye to some degree.
It's human nature.
I had never felt like I had given myself fully over to that thing.
And like having a partner was a really cool experience.
It was short, but it was very cool.
So, you know, it's nice checking in with somebody at the end of your day and all the generic
shit that goes along with it.
It's nice, of course.
Yeah.
Anyway, life lessons learned.
What else we got going on here in the news?
Have you seen, well, there, I saw they're rebooting Buffy the Vampire Slayer.
No Joss Whedon, but they've added the lady who directed the Eternals.
The movie that completely bombed.
Correct.
The first Marvel bomb.
Yes, let's bring that person on.
What the hell is everybody doing?
I don't know.
That's just what I saw before I logged in here.
You know, I got to say, and I don't think I'm wrong.
God, did you know Joss Whedon is 60 years old?
I thought he was like 43.
No, we're old.
I mean, yeah, people are going to be getting old.
No question.
Today, I asked, there's another way.
I trapped these gen Zers today, or however old these people are.
But I was asking about Rosie Perez.
And I was like, we need to get her on the show so I can marry her.
Because we're doing a little do the right thing, oh, mage.
I was like, we should ever come in.
And I was like, well, what's her age?
Is she like late 40s or something?
And I'm like, no, wait, Pat, you're in your 40s.
That's crazy.
So then we were like, well, she must be 60.
And I thought she's too old.
She's like, I'm going to get her on the show.
I'm going to get her on the show.
You just said this was a problem.
So the exact opposite can't be a problem.
So wait a minute, two.
They're getting weird, Joe.
What did...
What did we didn't do that he's so canceled?
Didn't he just get accused of being an asshole?
Yes, we didn't...
Was accused of being an asshole,
but also some inappropriate sexual overtones
to his female co-workers.
I mean, this is...
But that was right in the heart of like...
Yeah.
...the collision of me two and asshole,
job culture, stuff.
So he really went down hard for that.
But he's done, done, I think.
I mean, I feel like he could bounce back from this.
I think he's just not...
Yeah, I think he's maybe just being like,
fuck it, I'm done. I don't want to.
Maybe? Probably.
I don't know.
Who knows?
I never really liked the guy's stuff.
He's a bit...
Quippy for me.
I like...
Can you pull the mic a little closer?
I feel like you're leaning back.
And it's like...
It's amazing after 10 years,
still zero concept how a microphone works.
It's true.
I said he's a bit...
Quippy for me.
Yeah, I liked Firefly quite a bit.
Never saw it. I know Crumboltz is a part of it.
I want to see it.
Barry Mendel, I'm pretty good at this.
Crumboltz is on Firefly?
Who was?
He was in Serenity, the film.
Oh, who's on the show.
Okay.
Serenity was good too.
I forgot David was in...
I don't think I realized it.
Because I didn't know him at the time.
I don't remember who he played now that I think of it.
Anyway, I liked Firefly quite a bit.
You know, look, the guy did the fucking Avengers movie.
That first Avengers movie was great.
You know, like he's done some cool shit.
And he did Buffy.
I know it was never a Buffy fan, but...
But yeah, I mean...
I mean, this guy's made his money.
You know, like...
Obviously, I think maybe he's just like...
I'm good, guys. Thank you.
Thanks for the...
I don't...
Just go, I'm...
I'm done. Much sooner.
Like you make the bank and you quit.
I saw today Will Arnett sold a home for $22 million.
And I love Will Arnett.
I like him on Smartless. I guess that's where I forgot his money.
But I was like, this guy's never been in a hit.
A rest of development was no hit.
He's been in...
Like, he's host of game shows and stuff.
How do you have a $22 million home?
And he's got Alomony and Child Support.
Is he...
I mean, he's works constantly.
I think it probably adds up.
He does. He does.
And I will say, Smartless probably...
Has made him...
An immense multi-multimillionaire.
I mean, there is serious money...
Yeah, all for money.
To be made in podcasting.
For sure. He's also along with Ham.
Yeah.
Although we appreciate every dollar, folks.
Yes.
We had along with John Ham.
Are you always here going like...
The Toyota Tacoma.
Well, that's...
He goes there a lot of that shit.
Yeah.
But I mean, also too.
His house... He might have bought that house for 10 million.
That's true.
By... With a wife.
And then G-Chip.
Yeah.
And then this is how insane the world is.
The article about it.
He's saying...
That he was not selling to take advantage of the fire situation.
It's like...
You have to make a public statement about your intentions upon selling a house.
Just sell it.
Also too.
Taking advantage.
This has got to be the hardest time ever to sell a house in Los Angeles.
Well, no. People are looking for housing.
But I had this realtor I dated a while ago.
She was like, can I rent your house while you're in Atlanta?
And I was like, well, what can you get for it?
And she told me. And she had insurance will pay for it.
And I was like, I really don't like the idea of anyone else in my house.
But she's like, meet this family.
They lost their home.
Insurance will have to pay a bunch of money.
They're really cool.
Older my friends come by.
Come by, look around the house.
They're like, we're looking for something bigger.
Some man a woman and a kid.
My house is more than big enough for a man a woman and a five-year-old.
It's for two months who are out of a house.
I know it's they were Jesus Christ.
That's incredible.
I had to be convinced like Pat, no really.
Like they're really in need.
Like you should meet with them.
I'm like, okay.
They look the rest.
She complimented my home on its energy.
And then she turned around.
Here's another real quick.
Another news cycle before we go to the corner.
This comes from the independent overseas there.
Amanda Land star.
I think the movie or show.
I've never heard of it.
BBC TV show.
I've never heard it.
Start Lucy Punch.
Okay.
This is the quote.
My list of failures.
Question mark.
I did a film with Woody Allen.
You did one way after you had any excuse to be like, I didn't know.
You were late error, Woody Allen.
Like the audacity.
Yeah.
What was she in that one with Wally Sean trying to sell a movie on the beach?
I mean, come on.
What was that movie?
What was that movie called?
Something festival.
Riftkins fest.
Not good.
Riftkins festival.
That's very funny to me.
I watched half of that and had to bail.
I tried.
The second Gina Gershon is going to fuck Wally Sean.
I was like, guys, come on for Christ's.
Yeah.
Look, maybe she's making a quip at herself saying like, in my opinion, that was a misstep.
I shouldn't have done it.
I don't know, but I don't know.
I'm just so tired of it.
I'm so, you know, this, this thing of I did the thing.
And now I'm going to act like I'm more virtuous than the thing.
You know, during the election, if I saw one more fucking commercial.
Of an extra Trump supporter being like, I urge you as a man who voted for him.
I cannot vote for him.
It's like, fuck you.
You did it already.
I didn't do it.
You did it.
Now you're going to get righteous with me.
About what I need to do.
Go fuck yourself.
Yeah.
No, I kind of agree there.
I kind of agree there.
It's like that John Lennon Christmas song.
So this is Christmas.
And what have you done?
Well, you're the billionaire.
What have you done?
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Pointing the finger, it's Christmas.
I remember being in the back of my dad's 82 Chevy celebrity freezing and hearing that song
and being like, why is John Lennon judging me?
The worst, the worst.
I should bring this bit back.
I had a bit about this where when people do that, I go, it's like our Kelly being like,
you know, gang, I'm just here to talk publicly about how it's really wrong to piss on teenagers.
It's like, yeah, how about you just don't do it anymore?
How about you just don't do it and shut the fuck up and stop talking like we're all as
deranged as you are.
Like, yeah, like it's just the thing we all do.
Like shut up and just don't do it.
That's it.
That's all you got to do.
I missed who's paying on teenagers?
Our Kelly.
But is he lecturing people on how to know?
No, I'm saying the funny analogy in the bit was I was like, when David was like,
when Disney is telling us like, don't be racist after they get all the racist shit.
I'm like, it's literally like if our Kelly started campaigning like, you know guys,
it's wrong to piss on kids.
It's like, we know we didn't do it.
You did it.
Just shut up.
I thought he had actually done that because that's how strange the world is right now that I know he said I'm that my problem is I'm too giving.
Yeah, I always see that clip of him and as sad as it is, it always makes me laugh where he goes.
He said, I hog tied these girls.
I don't know how to hog tie.
Why would I hog tie?
It sounds like a side felt bit.
I don't know how to hog tie.
It makes me laugh so hard.
But it's terrible and I feel for the victims of course.
So why did you tell our Kelly to do what he did?
Because he, because I knew how to hog tie.
I had to teach somebody what good is a knowledge if you don't share it.
Truth.
Let's go down to that movie con.
Yes.
Did you ever go listen to that new Billy Joel song that he put out?
Yeah, I thought it was very good.
I couldn't do it.
I just assumed it would be unlistenable.
But all right, maybe I'll listen to it.
It's not like I throw it on like this is one of my Billy Joel jams.
But it was very good.
It's a, it's a, it's a piano ballad and it sounds very Billy.
It sounds like 80s Billy Joel.
Yeah.
But it's, you know, but it, uh, imagine you putting a CDR into your car's, uh, disc changer that said your, your Billy Joel's mega jams.
The, uh, what did you say?
It's on your list of Billy Joel mega jams.
Is that what you just said?
Did I say that?
I believe so.
I don't know what I said.
Let's check the tape.
Something jams.
I thought I said all time jams.
Maybe it was all time jams.
Yeah, turn the lights back on.
Billy Joel single.
Yes.
You know, the lights back on.
It's, it sounds like, um, that's weird.
The, wait a minute.
Hold on a second.
Why is the video him in the 80s?
Well, I guess because it sounds like it sounds like one of those songs he did in the 80s.
Like, like, like, like, the night the lights went out on Broadway.
It sounds like one of those kinds of songs.
Yeah.
And we would all go down together.
I don't know.
Um, I'm not a Billy Joel.
Like, I'll never listen to a full Billy Joel album.
It's just like, it's not my thing.
I like glass houses.
His quote punk album.
But I'll say this.
Billy Joel has 20, 15 to 20 songs that I'm like, that is one of the greatest songs ever written ever.
Like, yeah, he wrote some standards for sure.
You know, doesn't mean I ever want to hear him again, but yeah.
I put on a Billy Joel best of mix frequently.
I get it.
Allentown and.
All the lights.
Good.
They all sweet me away.
Yeah.
Uh,
I like to direct you if you haven't yet to a very special two hour.
Uh, Pat Solo movie corner where I went through the entire photography of David Lynch.
Rewash a lot of his great films discussed everything the man put out.
Let's do it over there.
And I just want to add one movie to kick off the solo movie corner that I had not yet seen when I recorded that episode.
Uh, but it would be more of a.
An add on.
It's called Lynch Oz.
A 20, 22 documentary.
And basically.
It's about the link between the work of David Lynch and the Wizard of Oz.
It's kind of a pointless documentary like that shining thing, but the shining thing was real bullshit where they tried to talk about.
And I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why
I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I
think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think that's why I think
that's why he's so angry at this kid who's on trial. Anyway, right.
Anyway, right.
And Al's like, and you know what?
And you know what?
She was right.
And it's like, what you say?
What you say on the night, Al.
Yeah.
What you say on the fucking night.
And then they're talking to Lord Michaels.
And he's like, you know, we always celebrate this.
And then they proceed to edit 10 times.
He censored people and banned them off the show, which I liked.
I loved the other one he did.
And this one, I just thought was great from start to finish.
There's awesome stories from the bands rage against the machine.
Tells really fun story.
It was great.
I was a big fan.
I urge you to check it out.
Get that peacock membership, ladies and gentlemen,
before they fall into the ocean.
Yeah.
Second pick for me is I watched the 12 Angry Men 1997.
Adaptate.
That's good too.
Very good.
You got Jack Lemon in the starring role in this one.
George, he's Scott James Gandalfini, Tony Danza in the Jack Warden role.
And he's great.
They're all great.
Everybody's great.
William Peterson, Courtney B. Vance, Aussie Davis, Hume Cron, Edward James,
almost in, almost, I believe in the Klugeman role.
I think.
And, uh, McKelty Williamson, who I had only ever seen in, in, in, um, heat.
Uh, while he was Bubba and Forrest Gump.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot about that.
Yeah.
Everybody in this is excellent.
Um, I, the, the one thing that bums me out, this was directed by William Freakin.
Look, this is every bit script wise and performance wise as good as the original.
It was made for showtime.
Uh, it's, of course, well directed by Freakin, but given the budget, it doesn't have the texture that the original film has.
And I think it does suffer a bit from that, that said, it was very well received and it was well, uh, nominated and all that stuff.
Um, it's Jack Lemon said once, I think it was on inside the actor studio.
This was the greatest cast he had ever worked with outside of Glen Gary Glen Ross, which is saying a lot for the amount of shit that guy was in.
Um, the one thing that bums me out a little bit about it is it's that error.
It's the last error of Jack Lemon and he's very, uh, bloated.
I think due to medications, he was on because of his illness or whatever, but it always kind of makes me sad to see him like that at the end, because you can see that the end is near, but he's still great in it.
Um, it's a very, very well done, uh, piece of work.
And worth checking out, even if you've already seen the original and, uh, were have just seen the original, I watched these almost back to back.
That is the one where Bing Rames gave his golden globe to Jack Lemon.
Bing Rames is an in it.
No, Bing Rames won for Don King playing Don King.
Oh, oh, I said he was like, I have to give this to Jack Lemon.
He's my idol and gave it a jack.
Oh, Jack Lemon was nominated for this.
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
I get it.
Now I get it.
Well, lovely moment.
I never knew that I, I, it's a lovely moment, but he shouldn't have given him his golden globe.
It's come on.
This is you.
You earned this man.
Yeah.
Um, anyway.
Back to you.
I'm going to do a quick two for with Denith thieves and Denith thieves too.
I saw them both.
And I'll do you one better.
I saw them both on the same fucking day.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Uh, they're really fun movies.
There.
The first one is clearly just a heat knockoff.
You know, probably like outlined while heat was playing in the background.
A lot of similarities.
It's Gerard Butler.
Visibly drunk and hungover.
I think not due to the makeup department, but actually drunk and hungover in many scenes.
Publish driver who's fine.
Oh, she Jackson, Jr.
Ice Cube son.
Who's great?
50 cent.
And it's just a really great crime movie.
It's too long.
It's about two and a half.
I don't know if you can say.
Um, the ringer.
My friends always talking about the ringer, which is their movie putt.
They are a little broy for me.
They're kind of podcasts about movies.
But, um, they talk about Denith thieves all the time.
Like there's hours of Denith thieves material.
So it's become like the, I know it's a cable staple.
It's a dad movie.
And I'll be damned.
It's very entertaining.
You know, it's, uh, it's a big gritty LA cop movie.
And it's a lot of fun.
Then Denith thieves two.
Immediately, uh, flips it to France.
It is called Denith thieves to Pantera, but unfortunately there is no appearance from the band Pantera.
Uh, but they're in Europe.
So it's basically the characters who I realized I did kind of like and care about.
Gerard Butler and Oshed Jackson.
Teaming up.
And, you know, taking on the mafia.
And I had a blast.
They're, they're long like two and a half hour action movies.
They don't have a ton of action in them.
They have a very strange sense of humor about them.
And there's just something very watchable and compelling about these movies.
They just announced a third one.
I'll be there.
This hits the spot for me like an equalizer.
Um, unfortunately, you don't have a Denzel, but I think story and vibe wise.
I probably prefer the Denith thieves pictures.
Uh, I think they're great.
I recommend them highly.
Um, all right.
That's, that's all I got.
If you want to, if you want to move to the, uh,
picture at hand.
Sure.
Sure, which is.
Blink twice.
Link twice.
I cannot remember that title for the life of me.
It was originally called pussy island.
And you bet your ass, I would remember that title, but they wouldn't let them do it.
What is the meaning of the title?
Blink twice.
It means nothing.
But pussy island means something.
Uh, my one sentence review for this film is blink twice.
How about snooze once?
People I was dozing off throughout this thing.
Uh, blink twice.
How about stink thrice?
Um, I was excited to see this movie.
I really was.
I'm a big fan of Zoe Kravitz.
Um, I heard she did a great job directing and she did.
She did.
The cast is a great cast.
You've got, you've got a, uh, uh, um, Channing Tatum.
You've got Haley Joel Osmond.
You've got, uh, wait, who's the guy that plays, uh, I'm kind of blanking.
Who's the, the, the, like the right hand.
Christian Slater Christian Slater.
Um, Simon Rex.
Simon Rex.
Yes.
Great.
Kyle McLaughlin speaking of David Lynch.
Kyle McLaughlin.
And then Gina Davis in the weirdest performance I've ever seen.
I love Gina Davis in this.
I never saw her play a nervous wreck.
And she was great.
Uh, and then the lead is Naomi Ackle.
Ackie.
Sorry.
Yes.
And Aliyah Shawcat from a record.
And another stuff in certain party.
Of course.
And then so there's, there's, there's more supporting, uh, both male and female cast.
But these are, well, Adrienne, uh, or, or, or Joe, our Jonah, I think it's pronounced.
She also is a quite a significant role in this.
But, um, look, this thing was.
First of all, it was touted as a horror movie thriller.
I mean, yeah, the horror is that people do terrible things.
I would not call this a horror movie, but it was certainly sort of marketed that way.
And, um, it was very, uh, uh, uh, a lot of people love this movie.
I don't know, man.
I was in, I was intrigued.
It opens with, uh, our main character, our lead character, uh, Naomi.
She plays somebody named Frida.
Uh, and it shows that she's a fan or has some sort of marginal interest, uh, or obsession even with this guy Slater,
who I guess is sort of an Elon Musk type.
Sure.
Some big business mogul guy, he had to step down from his organization for a while because he made some mistakes.
They don't get to into what he did.
Um, and she's still a fan of his.
She works in event that he is at a charity event.
He, she meets him.
Uh, he takes, takes an interest in her and her friend.
Um, played by Aliyah.
And, um, he, he invites them to.
Drea.
Huh?
You mean that Drea?
No, Aliyah.
Aliyah.
Aliyah, shot cat.
Okay.
And, um, he takes an interest in them and he invites them to his, he says, you guys want to go to Africa?
I have an estate there.
And, uh, they go.
And it's a crazy vacation and a beautiful house and a big party and private jets and everybody takes Molly every night and they have these amazing dinners and blah, blah, blah.
And it goes from there.
Things start to get weirder and weirder.
The second thing started to become odd on the.
A state.
The first thing they do, it's the maid walking up to the main character and saying something sort of strange and ominous to her.
And the second that happened, I went, oh, they're doing get out.
Does get out.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Just get out.
This is just get out.
Let me guess.
I'm not here for a reason.
It all looks beautiful, but it's not.
There's a trapping set.
Blah, blah, blah.
And sure enough, that's what it was.
And instead of it being a commentary on race, this was a commentary on the genders.
And, uh, spoiler alert, the reveal is is that not only are these women brought here to be drugged and repeatedly raped every night.
They've been brought here before and they keep being brought back.
Yeah.
And their minds are erased because they are given a parting gift of perfume that erases their minds or memories of this place rather.
And or have having ever ever met any of these people before.
Um, yet it doesn't erase their memories of knowing one another as some of them do.
Um, and also it erases their memories sort of like like there's a part where.
And then when it's all revealed of why they don't remember because they they give them this perfume every day or something that makes them forget.
And it's like, but but but then you would forget that that that that that you would forget everybody.
How could they just make you forget one person?
It's very, very loose logic.
Um, it's it's I appreciate the commentary.
It's one of these things that's that's too depraved for me.
It's too gross. It's too upsetting.
You know, it plays she shoots it well, but it plays almost like a reality show or like a comedy.
It's like very light.
They're doing a lot of drugs once they get to this island.
It's this pussy island, if you will.
And they're doing a lot of likes, you know, harmony, Karin style drug neon montages and everybody's all Molly and having fun and hookin up.
And it's very hot.
You're like, okay, cool, got it.
Then when it takes its turn, they're doing us a real slow motion fairly graphic group rap scene.
Basically, there's all these men outside like on the patio and in the in the lawn.
Violently raping women in slow motion while like funk music plays.
Now that's a background.
I think I might be wrong.
I think you're misremembering how they shoot that because this is something that I found very jarring, which I guess was the point.
No, it kind of snap out of it.
And it's just like they're just all of a sudden the guys are like, oh, oh, oh, you're like,
what the fuck is going on?
Man, this is upsetting.
Like, yeah, no, I'm just for me, the music video style of you.
They I didn't imagine that.
No, no, I think when they show the assault part, it's not.
Yeah, they cut out of that style.
No, because Simon Rex is like, I remember him like grinding the porno, porno style and slow motion.
Okay.
All right.
And I mean, I found that whole part to just be sort of baffling.
I mean, and a woman directed it.
Okay.
But it also is the only movie I think I've ever seen that it had a warning before it, a trigger warning.
I don't know if that's going to start happening or what.
But it's a decent amount now.
But yeah.
It does just kind of like dump you into that scene.
And then not take it seriously enough for what it is.
It's like, well, if you're going to have an island where women are raped and then show that to us,
you can't also be like a winky comedy like death becumseur, which is what this kind of reminded me of,
or like a steppered wives, like kind of vibe.
Because then in the home stretch, it takes another very ill-advised twist that Joe,
you can share with them now.
I assume I thought I'll get to it.
But I agree.
I think that the tone of the movie does not match appropriately to the subject matter.
Yeah.
I found the shock of the subject matter outweighed getting the point across of the subject matter.
There's a lot.
It's like people.
It's a fine line.
Okay.
I remember when the M&M is it relapse?
The one where they're all the pills on the cover?
Yeah, relapse.
Remember when he put out relapse?
Makes sense.
There's like a fourth song on it.
I think it's track four or something where he's like wrapping about his uncle raping him in the shed.
But he's wrapping it like M&M.
Where he's like, Nope, can.
I want my dick sucked into the shed.
And you're like, I don't want to listen to this.
I don't want to listen to your zany cartoon delivery about how you got raped.
It's weird.
It's uncomfortable.
It doesn't feel appropriate tonally to me.
That's how I felt with this.
I was like, this is way out of balance and out of whack.
And to try to make a commentary on something this dire and so serious and such a problem and an awful, awful, awful problem that this occurs.
To make it with such a wild premise and plot, I thought it just did it kind of a disservice.
I just did.
Like I was like, this is, I don't know.
Like it's just doing this a disservice.
Like, you know, and like.
That was the beauty of, you know, what, what get out did very well was it did start funny and it did start strange.
And when it started to tonally shift, it really tonally shifted.
And this kept bouncing back and forth.
Yeah.
You know, like in the midst of the climactic showdown when they're trying to escape and whatever,
you got Christian Slater on the couch being like with his face bashed in being like, I'm like, it's supposed to be funny.
And you're like, guys, this is insane right now.
What is going on?
So it reminded me of, at times of cocaine bear, which a movie about sexual assault should not be reminded me of cocaine bear.
This all said very well directed, very well acted.
You know, there were no missteps there.
I just, I just felt like the script was, was a little too nuts.
So, and then I will say this.
And I thought that this was a bad piece of writing.
The end of the movie is the main character uses the mind eraser drug on Channing Tatum.
His character.
Yeah, because he has a vape that he keeps smoking.
She spikes the vape with this perfume or whatever.
He smokes it.
And then he forgets.
Now, when he forgets, and his mind is erased, as you see in the little coda or epilogue of the movie, he forgets everybody and everything, which is how that would work.
Which is why the earlier part where the girls just forget one person doesn't make any fucking sense.
But whatever, these are whatever.
And the reveal at the end is that Naomi's character is now has taken over his company and is basically running the company for him.
And he's kind of like the dumb trophy wife or whatever you want to call it on her arm.
And she's living like the good life because now she reaps all the benefits of his fortune and what it.
And I'm like, wait a minute, this is the lesson.
Like don't turn the fucking monster into the authorities.
Don't make him pay for his crimes.
In fact, allow him to forget his crimes.
Which he says in a very sinister Joker-style monologue that forgetting is a gift.
That that's a beautiful thing that you can forget pain and forget what you've gone through.
And then it's like, but now you're using it so he doesn't have to be accountable.
And you're just using essentially blood money to live a good life.
And it's not in my opinion supposed to be up for interpretation like, well, makes you think.
Maybe she did make the wrong decision.
It's like, no, it's not portrayed that way.
It is very much portrayed like girl boss what?
Yes.
So I thought that was terrible.
I was like, yeah, I don't even understand what the point of this is was now.
Yeah, it's sometimes in this pursuit of like we need a good twist.
You wind up with a twist that is both not good and derails your whole movie.
Like everything that might have kind of worked before is now you're just like, what have you done?
But I found it hard to really even pay attention to this.
It just didn't really work in any way.
The cast all seemed to be kind of performing in different movies.
And story was not there.
I didn't like it at all.
I don't even know what John would call it.
I mean, no wonder they called it horror because they thought maybe somebody somebody will go see it.
Because if you call it what it is, it's like, it's a sort of dark comedy action thriller drama, social justice movie, but not in a good way.
It just sort of seems like a mess to me.
How did again, like, and then it's and here's the thing.
It would have been enough.
If it was like, okay, they're drugging these girls.
That's what they're doing.
Whatever.
But then when they start getting into the stuff about like, you know, and they're making them forget what happens every night or whatever.
But then when they get into the stuff about like, no, you've been here before.
Yeah.
And all that shit.
It's like, then how the fuck does she remember some of the none of this, but she knows who you still are.
And I don't fucking know.
I was like, I don't know.
It's just too much.
It's like it's too convoluted.
It's like it doesn't need to do all that.
But anyway, I am sad to say.
And I feel like we're going to get shit for this.
I feel like we're going to get grief for not liking this movie because it's it is not my hog is down for quite some.
Well, I'm just reading here.
Here's what Kravitz had to say about the ending of the movies.
It was sweet revenge.
There's a lot of open ended questions that I hope sparked conversations.
Is this the beginning of something or is this the end of something?
Is it the continuation of something?
I think those are all up for debate and I'm curious what that makes people feel.
So I'm not sure.
She knows what this movie's about.
That does not sound like a confident answer.
Yeah, I took nothing from it.
I was not entertained by it.
I didn't like it.
My hog is down.
And I just don't think twice.
Blink twice.
Okay.
My hog is down for blink twice.
Yeah, my.
182 out of a thousand.
Mine is two.
I'm curious about something.
I want to see something here.
By the way, do you think now, Zoey Kravitz, you know, I'm not.
I'm not a big.
I don't have a big problem with the whole neppo baby thing.
It's like, I don't care.
I really don't.
And I don't fault her for her lineage.
I don't fault anybody.
It's, you know, and as far as I'm concerned, people getting into the family business.
A lot of people go do what their parents did.
But do you think.
Without.
The, the coming from, you know, without the dad of, oh, she was married by the way to.
Oh, no, I'm sorry, the actor that was in the on demon, not the director.
Do you think without the dad being Lenny Kravitz, Zoey gets to direct a movie like this or, or no?
Well, what does Lenny Kravitz isn't even in the film world?
But I mean, he's of incredibly rich, successful celebrity.
Sure.
Who can say, I mean, she's cool.
That's all you need to be able to direct a movie.
She's cool.
They'll let anybody direct a movie.
Well, that's, that's not true than anybody would direct a movie.
I mean, yeah.
But I mean, yeah, it's not as, to me, it's not as blatant as like Jessica Spielberg or whatever,
who's directing a movie now.
No, but, but yeah, if you got the chops, you got the chops.
I guess it's, it's yet to be seen.
She technically, I thought it was a pretty well directed movie.
I just didn't work any other way.
I thought it was too.
I'm just curious, do you get to do that without, do it?
By the way, Jesus Christ, I saw this.
I saw this.
I almost fell down the steps.
Finn Wolfhard is about to make his directorial debut.
Now, folks, I stand by what I said.
They'll let anybody direct a movie if you're a little bit cool.
That's all I'm saying.
And I like Finn Wolfhard, but I'm just, I mean, I don't know.
I'm like, I guess, guys, like, what the, do you think that in our lifetime,
Finn Wolfhard will be doing a complete unknown style biopic of Julian Casablancus?
From the strokes?
I don't think there's enough of a Julian Casablancus story, but, but I think it's a good question.
No, you're right.
I don't think he'll want people sniffing around his dad's story either.
His dad was like a notorious creep.
Oh, he was, wait, Julian Casablancus, the dad, John Casablancus was the Casablancus models.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just, it's just odd like this, this like, I don't know.
You know, I just looked up Jack Lemons IMDB.
I'm like, he never directed anything and he directed one thing.
I wonder what it was.
I clicked, I clicked, I tried to click on it and it made it disappear.
So now I can't see what he fucking directed.
But deep throat actually, people don't know that, but Jack Lemmon directed deep throat.
Jack Lemmon directed a film called Koch in 1971, saying it with Walter Mathau.
That was a criterion release.
The picture I'm seeing is Walter Mathau dressed as a 90 year old man with his face up against
a giant tiger.
Yeah.
Oh, I don't know what it was.
What is this about?
Koch, I saw when I was like 10 years old.
Like a wacky uncle is what I remember.
All right.
But I don't remember anything about a tiger.
Yeah.
Big stuff tiger.
Hires him to babysitter infant son Duncan and then they fall in love and blah, blah, blah.
All right.
Folks, we'll be back.
Believe it or not, with you've been cordially, you're sorry, you're cordially invited.
Got these titles are so.
Titles are getting worse and worse.
Why wouldn't it just be cordially invited, cordially invited.
That's it.
That's the title.
Why the year?
The fake titles I was saying to you on the phone last night were better than the title.
This movie was.
Anyway, we'll get there.
I am at the Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
We are at CU and help pod on Instagram.
Joseph.
Jota Rosa comedy on Instagram.
And I think it's, I don't know, it's tick tock still there.
Jota Rosa comedian, I think.
Anyway, still there.
Listen, we had to cancel some tour dates, folks, due to all that's going on in my personal life at the moment.
I apologize, but the Midwestern dates are now gone.
Those were, you know, where the hell was we?
Grand Rapids in Minneapolis were Milwaukee.
Whatever that three day run was that we had to cancel that.
I apologize.
Also had to cancel a Mayus, Pennsylvania.
I apologize, I apologize, I apologize.
I apologize.
Also had to cancel Tampa.
Tampa was canceled because it's the weekend of South by Southwest.
And I have to be at South by Southwest in order to tend to many activities involving both comedy and hopefully,
Joey Rosa stay tuned for all that.
And there should be, I hope, fingers crossed some, some very cool stuff.
I'll be announcing going on during that festival.
The other dates just happened to fall within an unfortunate time frame with, with the family stuff going on.
And whatever.
So I apologize.
And I'll keep you posted if we're going to reschedule or what.
But in the meantime, go to joda Rosa dot com for all other available dates throughout March.
And I'll be in DC this, this coming weekend.
I was able to keep that one February.
I think it's the eighth Saturday.
If you're in that DC, Washington DC area, whatever northern Virginia, come on out.
And if you're in New York, go to Joey Roses.
JoeyRoses.com.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.