🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
And this today is no exception. We're both very excited to discuss our top ten favorite sitcom characters of all time. We're each doing ten. We're gonna rank them in order of our, you know, least favorite of our favorites to most favorite. And that's it. You know how we do.
I would like to give a disclaimer that, you know, everyone on this list is beyond worthy. As far as ranking them, that was almost impossible for me to do. There's different criteria. Single cam versus multi and all this stuff. You know, we're doing any thirty minute format show. Thirty thirty minute comedy. We're considering a sitcom.
My other question, Joe, that we did not decide upon, are we allowing multiple characters from each show? Or can you only do one choice from each show?
Okay.
No, I think you can.
I did. I only allowed one from each show for myself, but I will be sure to mention the other characters that could have easily had that spot.
And I have an extensive, no, not extensive, but at least a ten name honorable mention list. And I'll read that at the end so I don't blow any picks that we have.
The hard time I had with this, Pat was saying before we started that he had a hard time. I had a hard time too. The hard time that for me was getting it down to this ten that I have here because there were so many.
And I have my reasons and I will say before we begin.
I eliminated a couple shows, so I have, even though I think it's the greatest sitcom of all time, there is no Seinfeld on my list.
And there's also.
Well, I eliminated Seinfeld and I eliminated Peep Show, two of my top five sitcoms of all time.
Why? Because I think that those sitcoms function solely, in my opinion, not solely, completely as ensemble shows.
The picks I took were characters that I thought could function on any show.
You could take them off this show, put them on another show, and you'd be like, they'd be the same character.
I feel like Seinfeld, so much of it is based on them reacting to one another and the dynamic of the different personalities are so contingent on the other personalities or whatever.
And I felt Peep Show was the same. I couldn't be like.
Well, what is it, Dez and Mark? Mark and Dez?
Peep Show is on my honorable mention list, the David Mitchell character, the dorkier character of the two.
I've never related to a character more, hardly. I thought the character was just about perfect.
However, when I sat down to write him down, I couldn't think of his name.
And I was like, if this guy's a classic character, I would know his name. So he was eliminated there.
But David Mitchell is the actor. I forget his name, to be honest with you.
I think he can't function without Dez, which is the other guy, because that character on another show is just a straight -laced guy to me.
And I'm like, I'm not saying he's not funny, but the whole reason the show works is because the two of them playing off each other as each other's foils.
So Seinfeld was very similar to me, like, well, George's neurotic. Kramer alone doesn't work.
Kramer with Jerry and everybody else works.
They learned that when they tried to do shows with those guys after Seinfeld. They all just collapsed.
Anyway, would you like to start us off?
I will start. I'm realizing I currently have three choices at number 10. So that's a mistake. Everything else is properly labeled.
But all right, here's my number 10.
All right. Bill McNeil has played by Phil Hartman on the classic news radio.
Oh, it's a good one.
I think news radio is one of the finest multicam sitcoms ever made.
The ensemble is without flaw.
You know, it's like a 10 -person cast where everyone scores.
But the standout by far is Phil Hartman coming off of SNL where he showed us he's a chameleon who can do all kinds of characters.
He was the funniest supporting characters on The Simpsons, Troy McClure and Lionel Hutz.
I think the decline in quality of The Simpsons happened right when he died.
I don't think that's, you know, that's not the reason.
But I think there's definitely some connection there. When he died, the show kind of started to slip a little bit, in my opinion.
But Bill McNeil is, you know, narcissist. He's obsessed with himself.
All of my characters, I think, are anti -heroes. They're all deeply, deeply flawed people.
There's no real good people on my list.
But it is without question, I think, outside of SNL and his sketch work, the absolute best showcase for Phil Hartman.
If he had to pick one episode, it's the one where he gets a cane. It's just a masterpiece of like physical comedy.
He's a great dick, but you love him. I just I love that character.
And I love that we got a lot of concentrated Phil Hartman that we can go back to because his movie career is shit, you know, outside of his supporting roles.
So I give it to Mr. Phil Hartman, Bill McNeil.
My number 10 is George Jefferson.
The Jeffersons is not one of my favorite sitcoms. I enjoy it.
This is the only reason he's at 10 and not higher is because the show itself isn't one of my favorites.
But I do like it very much.
However, the character of George Jefferson, I love tremendously.
Why it's it's there's multiple reasons he's he's on this list.
It's it's it's the first is that Sherman Hemsley carried that style of character into a couple shows like on Amen.
He is sort of still George Jefferson. He just doesn't say like honky a lot and stuff.
But he sort of always the way I've seen Amen and two to seven.
I've never seen the Jeffersons. You should watch the Jefferson sometime.
But, you know, George is always a guy looking, you know, what's what's a good business endeavor.
How can we make a buck on this? But he's successful at it.
He's good at it. And he's kind of a loudmouth guy, which is always funny.
And he's also, from what I know, the first black character in in American primetime television
to not just challenge white people, but to flippantly like dismiss white people and slam doors on their faces and stuff,
which is incredibly groundbreaking and really funny to fucking watch,
especially when you consider the time period that the show came out in.
So Sherman Hemsley, I think, is a is a is a strangely undersung hero of the sitcom world.
He's great on this show. He's great on Amen and George Jefferson,
especially when he's being the foil at first to Archie Bunker, you know, in in on all in the family.
And then eventually showing that he can definitely, along with Weezy, of course, and Florence Henderson, carry the sitcom.
But, you know, he's it's just an amazing character.
And again, one that you could plop into any show, any show.
You could be like, here comes George Jefferson and he would be exactly that character.
It would be really funny and and fun to watch. Love it.
I mean, I've seen his episodes of All in the Family, but I'm sure I would love the Jeffersons.
We had what's her name?
She was ninety five when she came down to Atlanta.
Mary was Marla Gibbs we had on.
Oh, Martha. She was awesome. It was like Anderson.
We're like, would you mind doing a line where you say shit?
And she goes, fuck yeah.
She's great. She's like literally almost 100 years old.
I'm sorry. Number nine.
Let me just say that I called her Florence Henderson.
That's the from the Brady Bunch. Yeah.
My number nine is my only tie.
I have to allow one tie and it's a battle of the straight men.
The two best, my two favorite straight men.
Actually, that's not true because Jerry Seinfeld would be probably one of the classic straight men.
But he's an honorable mention on my list.
My choices are Jason Bateman as Michael Bluth on Arrested Development.
That is a talk about just like News Radio, a deeply stacked comedic cast.
Some of the funniest people ever, David Crossburn, Lucille Bluth, the mom, Jeffrey Tambor.
Just everybody on the show kills Tony Hale.
But the show does not work if it's a bunch of lunatics running around bumping into each other.
The show works because Jason Bateman, the driest, most sarcastic, just the he's the he's a textbook straight man.
And he is so flawless on this show.
He gets, in my opinion, the biggest laughs just by playing it straight.
He has the best intonation.
And then you watch him or you listen to Smartless or whatever and you see that that's just him.
He has a way of very, very casually and non hurtfully cutting people to the quick
and just calmly and casually pointing out what's so ridiculous about other people.
And then to your point, to your point, you know, in the great in the in the era of the great comedy teams, you know,
the straight man was the higher paid.
Yes, straight. It was all contingent on the straight man.
And that eventually flipped.
But, you know, he is he harkens back to that classic necessity of like, this is what a good straight man does.
A good straight man will also get laughs for you.
He does straight straight man nowadays.
Straight men nowadays are just playing a normal, boring person.
They're not bringing comedy to the table.
I know you don't like Tommy Boy Joe, but like David Spade is it's a two hander.
David Spade is there to make fun of Chris Farley and give you laughs as well.
Equal laughs.
I just think Bateman fucking destroys on that show.
I don't count anything past season three, which I think is an abomination.
I've seen a lot of it, but I just I don't get it.
And I think it was a huge mistake.
But yeah, Bateman Bateman is is a killer on that show, an assassin.
And then I'm going to tie him up.
I could not do this without mentioning Chandler Bing.
Friends is not is not an all time favorite show of mine because it aired with Seinfeld.
I just saw it as the knockoff version, but highly superior to everything else.
They aired on that night on must see TV, whether it be the single guy, Caroline in the City, whatever.
Friends is a classic sitcom and I've seen every episode of it.
And I wouldn't have watched it without Chandler Bing, Matthew Perry, RIP.
Another example of just a very funny straight man.
He's making fun of everybody, but he is delivering all kinds of jokes and laughs.
I've talked a lot before about how that's a cast that that'll make a C plus joke into an A plus.
They know how to find it. They all six of them find it.
They play off each other beautifully.
But Chandler is definitely the standout and he you can tell he'll say a straight line in an unusual way and get a laugh off it.
That's what everybody talked about after he passed is how he could just find the funny and everything.
And you know, he's one of those characters like the Seinfeld crew other than Julia Louis Dreyfus,
where you never even wanted to see him do anything else because he just was that.
And everyone called me Chandler in high school.
I dressed like Chandler in high school to kind of play into that with Tony Soprano shirts a little bit.
And you know, he's a character who is scared of intimacy, scared of women, scared of life.
He was an early kind of anxious character.
And he compensates for all that by just making relentless jokes.
That that is who I maybe not who I am so much anymore, but certainly who I was for the vast majority of my life.
A classic character without question.
Most people's favorite friend and with good reason.
My number nine.
And not a tie because I follow the rules, but.
No, my number nine is David Brent from the office.
I mean, what can I say? Ricky Gervais as David Brent in the office.
It not only is the prototype for basically the character or the style of character that Ricky Gervais plays in almost everything that he does.
It is the prototype. I get that it's all sort of based in the spinal tap.
Oh, for God sakes, who's the guy waiting for Gufman and what's his name?
Christopher Guest.
Christopher Guest. I get that it's all sort of based in that Christopher Guest style of comedy.
But the office is it cannot be overstated what that did for television.
It was adapted into American television.
Every sitcom.
Or every single cam rather for 10 years or more that came down the pike was a copy of the prototype of the office.
It was all shot docu style.
It was all, you know, Parks and Rec and all of that stuff.
It was all derivative of the office.
Rob McElhenney says to this day that if you watch the first five, six scenes of Always Sunny, he's just constantly doing a Ricky Gervais impression.
And like sometimes they would call him out on it.
Like it just it became the way to do comedy for a while.
Certainly awkward comedy.
And I've noticed I've actually noticed that with the there was a when when the Frank gets an intervention episode premiered of It's Always Sunny at the beginning when Mack awkwardly tries to hit on Nora Dunn as the sister of Dennis's mom and fails and then has to walk off very awkwardly at the funeral and like touches the tree branch.
Like as if he's that's his goal because he doesn't know what to do with himself.
Right.
I remember watching that on the premiere night and being like, oh, that's very that's he just did like a Ricky Gervais.
So Ricky Gervais just in this show.
And it's not even my favorite of the Ricky Gervais shows.
But this character, again, my approach to this was, could you take the character and put him in anything?
Well, you could because the life on the road movie is not a great movie, but it's proof that you can take the David Brent character and go, he's over here now and it still works.
Yeah, it's just an amazing character.
It is what awkward comedy is.
It is what a false confidence comedy is, which is what Will Ferrell also did so well.
You know, a guy with hubris for no good reason.
A guy whose nothing is his kingdom, you know, and just has way too much stake in himself and what he does.
This is this is the master performance of it.
It's David Brent, period.
I couldn't agree more.
And you will see David Brent later in my list.
My number is Valerie Cherish from The Comeback as played by Lisa Kudrow.
The first season, I like the second season quite a bit, but the first season of The Comeback, I would say maybe my least favorite character on Friends was Phoebe.
I was definitely not excited about a Lisa Kudrow show.
I never understood why they had two dumb characters on Friends.
You know, generally you would have one.
They had Joey and Phoebe.
It kind of bothered me.
So when the show came out, I was just not into it.
But time has come to show that this is probably the definitive portrait of Hollywood narcissism.
I think Lisa Kudrow is so fucking brilliant and amazing on this show, and they have just never used her right again.
You know, it's like because she helped write it.
That's probably a big part of it.
But I just think she's so great.
And I'm sure that she was heavily inspired by Gervais in The Office and Awkward Comedy as well.
This is one of the most painful and awkward sitcoms in the history of TV.
And as somebody who works, you know, it's in the multicam sitcom world.
So it hit me hard.
I think the show reached kind of a beautiful ending.
You know, I liked how it ended.
I liked the second season just fine.
But the first season, I think, is the best example of Awkward Comedy female division.
We've got a million men doing this.
Nobody did it like Kudrow.
I think that show is a masterpiece.
My number eight.
Of course, he's on the list.
I got to go with Al Bundy.
Sure.
I think the first seven, no, six seasons, sorry.
I think seasons one through six of Married with Children are in their own way very much a masterpiece.
Incredibly groundbreaking.
Whether you think it's crass or obnoxious is a different story.
But the point is, is there was nothing like it.
There had been nothing like it.
And Ed O 'Neill in this role is just, he's just spectacular.
Until season seven is when it starts to jump the shark and become a little too much a parody of itself.
But in that first six seasons, his delivery, his demeanor, his portrayal of an absolutely beaten man
who lives to work because he has to, not because he's a workaholic.
He's so much like my dad was growing up.
It's so reminiscent of my dad.
Like the body type, he dresses exactly the way my dad dressed.
My dad, I remember him coming home from work with just this, this defeat of just like, God damn it, man.
They don't appreciate me there.
And I love you both, to me and my mom.
But I feel like maybe you don't really appreciate me here either.
And we did, but you don't show it in the ways that you should.
And then the shit rolls downhill.
He's in a bad mood because his work sucked.
That comes into the house.
The house is, you know, there's constant bickering and tension in the home.
You know, he takes that back to work and the cycle starts all over again.
I don't mean to make it sound like I had a bad childhood, but this concept is so relatable to me, so relatable.
And a man getting just the little victories, the little victories, the comfortable time in the bathroom, you know,
saving up to take the family out for a decent dinner, his car, you know, not breaking down for once.
I just, he just nails the everyman and what the working.
And I say none of this to discredit the female roles on a show like that and what they were dealing with or whatever.
It was just that I saw my father in Al Bundy and I appreciated it and I still find it very funny.
And to this day, there are a few things in a sitcom that make me laugh as hard as him having a collapse into tears as he's trying to convince himself his life is pretty good.
It's just, you know, at O 'Neill being like, and it's going to be great, whatever.
And then breaking down into tears and going, my God, what a charade.
It's hilarious. It's hilarious. It's a defeated man.
There you go, Al Bundy.
Al Bundy, not on my list, but hard to argue. I just haven't seen enough of the show.
I was not allowed as a kid and I own it. I just haven't cracked it open.
I've seen episodes, of course.
My number seven is the most elite straight man female division.
So let's say straight woman.
Got to give this to Dorothy Zbornak.
Bea Arthur on The Golden Girls.
Another unquestionable ensemble.
But for me, from when I was a young boy up to the present, when I rewatched it over the pandemic,
I'm a Bea Arthur Dorothy man.
They cut to her so often to add a laugh.
It's like great joke, you know, great setup, great punch line.
And then usually the third step is getting the Bea Arthur reaction shot.
Sometimes that's just Bea Arthur looking at the person who said something stupid with no expression on her face.
She's just looking at Betty White and it's a bigger laugh than the punch line every time.
Now, when she does come back with a comeback, they are always the most vicious and nastiest of The Golden Girls.
And with good reason, because all they do all day is call her ugly and unable to get or keep a man.
So you don't feel bad when she lashes back. She deserves it.
And to me, that's the show.
You got your dumb person, you got your slut, you got your old crab, and then you got the straight woman.
I clearly am a man who loves a straight woman.
I love being the guy who makes a quip, who cuts you down, who makes fun of you.
So, of course, I like watching that type of person.
I never saw Maude. I have never actually seen Bea Arthur do anything else.
To me, she is Dorothy Zbornak.
If I showed you my grandma, you would be stunned at how much these two women look alike.
My grandma was Bea Arthur, she's still alive, but a classic example is I had a fat grandma and a thin grandma.
And the fat one at Christmas was like, well, you know, this is my last day eating cookies because my diet starts tomorrow.
And my grandma goes, fat chance, like within a second of her finishing that.
And she would do that kind of stuff just all the time.
She was great.
Bea Arthur, a legend, and my favorite of the Golden Girls, my favorite female straight man, woman.
Bea Arthur, so here's the thing.
I am going to break, maybe I will break the rule a little bit here.
Zbornak's my number two, Dorothy.
You've said everything I could possibly say.
So instead of retreading her, I'm going to delete my number two.
And I'm going to plug in here one of my honorable mentions and just add her to my, you said it all about Dorothy.
She's my number two of all time. I can't add anything to what you said.
But the person that didn't make the list from the Golden Girls, it was an honorable mention.
I will now talk about Rue McClanahan as Blanche.
I feel Dorothy is my favorite character.
But Rue McClanahan as Blanche gives, in my opinion, a Broadway level performance in every episode.
She becomes another human being.
That character is so believable.
Now, Dorothy is my favorite because it's the zinger person.
It's the straight woman and the zinger person.
I love that. I hear you.
There's nothing like a gangster smart ass that stands in the corner and then goes, yeah, well, you're a fucking slut.
You know, like, whoa, there's nothing funnier than that.
Rue McClanahan, as far as sitcom characters go, she becomes she is that woman.
I've met her in real. I met her before she died.
She was at a show I did not for me, but she was just there.
But I met her. She's nothing like that person.
Yeah, it's like it's fucking wild.
Like she is she is truly, truly, truly incredible on that show.
They all are. But Rue to me.
Yeah, I mean, Betty White, obviously so intelligent, but you completely buy that she is, you know, borderline handicapped on the show.
So I will say Rue McClanahan as Blanche Devereux, who you could literally pluck out of this and drop right into Streetcar Named Desire as that Blanche.
And you'd be like, you'd be like, yeah, that's seamless. I do. I buy it.
And you push her forward. She's blondie on Sex and the City, Kim Cattrall.
Yeah, it's the exact same thing. And that's the other important.
That's the other important aspect of the Rue McClanahan character.
She's the prototype. The Golden Girls are prototypical in a lot of ways for the for the four women configurations on a sitcom.
But like Rue really is the prototype for the like own your sexuality.
I want to talk about groundbreaking. Own your sexuality.
An elderly slut. We'd never really seen that at all outside of maybe one joke in a broad comedy.
But yeah, an old slut.
Well, yeah, we probably shouldn't call her slut.
I'm not shaming.
Well, they call her a slut on the show all the time.
They do. There's such a thing as an ethical slut.
But I mean, look, sure, slept around.
Yeah, but I mean, like, you don't have the Kim Cattrall doesn't the Samantha doesn't exist without Blanche.
Right. Right. The the English girl on Girls doesn't exist without Blanche.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
Like, it's it's it's the like, honey, get out of my way.
I like to fuck. What are you going to do about it?
You know, and and she's just incredible.
Agree to you.
Uh, yeah, my number, we're on six.
I'm down to, yeah, six.
My number six.
Now, so my my number.
Well, OK, my number six is Alan Partridge, played by the great Steve Coogan.
So everything Joe said about Ricky Gervais, which is 100 percent true and the David Brent character.
You could argue.
And I and I know Steve Coogan argues this often that that was lifted from Steve Coogan's performance as Alan Partridge.
To me, they're different enough.
You know, but but that and by the way, British awkward comedy has been going on a real long time.
And it's been going on since before Faulty Faulty Towers as well.
But. I do think you could get him to admit it probably, but Ricky Gervais took a lot from Alan Partridge.
To me, they're they're very different, beautiful characters.
Partridge. You know, he works in a variety of formats because his audio books are about the funniest things I've ever listened to.
His first one, as I've always recommended, I Partridge is a classic and the Nomad is just as good.
He's done a movie that is hilarious and he's done several in a wide variety of format shows as Alan Partridge, usually six episodes.
The funny, you know, the funniest, the most classic is the most like The Office, his first show.
I'm Alan Partridge. Well, there's knowing me knowing you, Alan Partridge, which is the live audience show where he's interviewing guests.
That's funny, but I prefer the more constructed I'm Alan Partridge series.
That's probably the best of it. The one where he's a podcast host that they did recently.
That for probably five bucks and his salary is like screamingly funny.
I mean, it's so good. And the character has been been around now for twenty five years.
He just keeps finding new wrinkles in it and I think he knows that's what people want him to do.
So he never gave it up. I love Steve Coogan so much.
I love that. I don't know anything about him. I love that.
I love that so few people know about him. You know, I sort of it's one of the things that that like everybody got to the office because of the American version.
Alan Partridge really and The Office are both things that I got like the foot fist way with Danny McBride.
All these things I got in like a bootleg format.
Like I ordered them from like they used to have all these websites and stores in the mall where you could buy like bootleg concerts and stuff like that.
My local mall had a store that was completely bootleg concerts, which is I don't know how that was legal.
But you had to find these things because it wasn't like that.
We had the BBC, you know, network over here at that time.
So seeing those early Alan Partridge's and I'll get to David Brent as well, but like blew my mind.
You know, British comedy is a comedy of awkwardness, tension, embarrassment and humiliation.
And I think few people play that better than Steve Coogan.
I agree. I agree. It's funny.
I didn't even think of Steve Coogan because or Alan Partridge because he's in so many things I almost right.
I must look at him like like for lack of a better example, like Carrot Top or something like, well, he's always Carrot Top and all this stuff.
My number six, right? Yeah, we just counted is Hank Kingsley from the Larry Sanders show.
An honorable for me, for sure. Barely missed the cut.
This was a tough call with Larry Sanders.
Artie was always arguably my favorite character because Artie represented something I desperately wanted to discover in show business.
And he is very funny.
You know, I always wanted to find this old school barrel chested, hard nosed rep that would get your back no matter what.
Like a guy you could literally be in a foxhole with or in a pitch meeting.
And he was just as savage and shrewd.
And I just love the character so much, but I love the character more than I think he's funny.
And since we're talking about sitcom and he's very funny, but since we're talking about greatest sitcom stars, funny had to tie into it to a great deal.
And there's nobody funnier than Hank Kingsley.
Again, this is a guy you could drop into any scenario on any show as Hank Kingsley.
And it's always hilarious. It's who you want Jeffrey Tambor to be every time.
I still get bummed out when Jeffrey Tambor turns up into something and he's playing like a prick or a nice guy or whatever.
I always want him to be Hank Kingsley.
I always want him to be incredibly insecure with a very thin facade of security going on on the exterior.
And then when that facade cracks, which it always will, and he collapses, which he always does, it is the funniest thing.
Him exploding into mania and screaming is so funny every time.
And then also another guy that fires like gangster shots.
When he when Hank Kingsley gets his back against the wall and he feels challenged, he is such a prick.
You know, Elvis Costello, when he save it for your limey bullshit love songs.
The thing when he's talking to Larry and he goes about the ex wife and he's like.
And now I guess I have to suffer because you got back together with that cunt.
And then he goes, oh, oh, no, no, no, I didn't say that.
It's yeah, it's it's it's just it's the best.
It's the best. It's a completely insecure guy desperately trying to be secure in a world as savages show business.
And it's just a recipe for for brilliant comedy.
And nobody could play that part except.
Jeffrey Tambor, that's another thing I think we're saying with these parts.
Nobody, the person playing it, that's it.
That's who plays it like you can't recast these parts.
Yeah. In any way. So for sure.
Hank Kingsley, ladies and gentlemen.
Yep. On my on my just missed list, for sure.
My number five is Kenny Powers, the great Danny McBride.
That show. Hmm.
That really, you know, in addition to being just crazily funny for four straight seasons.
And only giving you six per season.
So leaves you one more very British influence to both in the six episode thing
and also in the just despicable awkwardness of the show.
But this was before Danny McBride was sort of played out.
Not that he's played out, but a lot of comedy people.
You know, to me, John Candy never got never hit this point.
Steve Martin never hit this point.
But some comedy people, Jonah Hill is a good example.
You just get sick of their thing.
You know, at first you're like, I will never get tired.
Dan Levy, you know, you're like, oh, my God, what a fresh, great new comedic thing.
I love this. Not not everybody can sustain that.
You know, sometimes a comedic character and a comedic vibe just wears out, runs out of steam.
When I watch Righteous Gemstones now, I'm never laughing at Danny McBride.
I'm laughing at the other characters.
Vice principals was kind of the same way.
We've seen him in this wheelhouse for too long.
But you got to remember back.
So he had popped up. He was he was in every big comedy for like a year.
He was in The Heartbreak Kid. He was in Pineapple Express.
And he would steal these movies with like a scene or two.
But he was just a little pop in guy. Yeah.
So when they gave him his own thing.
And for him to like write it and for it to be this fucking good.
It's it's crazy to me.
This that's this is the darkest comedy on the list.
I think Eastbound and Down.
I remember at the end of the first season when he abandons his wife at a gas station,
who is his wife, who loves him very much, and they don't really have any problems even.
My my ex was like, I don't want to watch this anymore.
She was like, I'm not watching the show anymore.
It's the show that took the biggest of swings to make this character despicable.
He's beyond David Brent. He's beyond Alan Partridge.
He's beyond all these people. He is a shitty person.
But you love him. You know him.
You in my case, sometimes you are him at your absolute lowest.
He's arrogant. He's angry.
He's he's just in his own head all the time.
He can't make connections.
He can't stop his vices.
He's a nut.
And I think the first season is the masterpiece.
But the rest of the show is just a bit of a step down.
Love that character. Love his kind of redemption arc.
And I love that.
You know, they'd give him wins and stuff,
but it would always be his win would be like beating the shit out of a child or something.
You know, like it was always with this feeling of like, oh God, you know,
that's one of my favorites.
I don't think we'll ever get a better version of McBride,
who is, you know, one of our modern day comedy greats, I think.
But that to me, that the time that was running to have something that made me laugh
that hard every Sunday night was just such a gift.
And I miss it terribly.
My number five is Ralph Cramden from The Honeymooners,
you know, Jackie Gleason, one of the comedy greats
and a sitcom character that he created
that has cemented his footing in sitcom history
with a mere 29 episodes of a show.
I mean, it's a pretty incredible thing to do.
But what can I say?
29 episodes of The Honeymooners?
Or 39, I think it was. It's the classic.
I've never seen it, but I thought there was like 400.
No, he did one season.
Everything else aside from that one season is the sketches from the show,
from his variety show.
He did once, and then they did terrible reunion movies and things,
but like he did one season, they want it more, and he was like,
nope, we did it. It was great.
We're going to ruin it. And he left it.
And that was it.
You know, The Honeymooners is a pretty simple show,
but it's a show that was quite honest
and especially for a sitcom in the 50s.
And what can you say?
I mean, Ralph Cramden, it's a recipe for hilarity every time.
You've got a guy who's desperate, who is insecure,
and who is massively explosive,
and you drop him and who has a thirst to try to get rich
and try to figure it out finally for his ship to come in all the time,
just desperately thirsty for that to happen.
And you drop him into situation after situation
where he's going to get prodded and things are not going to go his way,
and then you sit back and watch.
I mean, it is great.
And then you surround him with people that spur that along.
You make his best friend absent -minded and kind of dim with Norton,
but that guy always lands on his feet, and it's not fair.
You have his wife be able to intellectually outsmart him all the time
Alice is the Dorothy of the honeymooner.
She's the one that makes the quips about his weight and his waistline
and his job and whatever else.
And people have disparaged the honeymooners and said it inspires violence.
It doesn't.
Well, he threatens his wife, but he never means it,
and if you watch the show, you know he doesn't mean it.
It's a guy being like, oh, I'd like to not get through that war.
And then she gets in his face, you and what army?
It's all in good fun, in my opinion.
And the honeymooners, though not an amazing sitcom, an important one,
and Gleason, a comedy giant, this is his funniest.
This is his absolute funniest.
Yeah, I've seen clips, of course, but never a full episode.
I need to.
What I learned really is that people just watch,
like somebody last night we were doing a taping and somebody was shocked
that I'd never seen a living single, I'd never seen a minute of it.
And it's really just whatever your local affiliate plays and reruns is what you see.
I never was in an affiliate that showed I Love Lucy, so I've never seen it.
I watched whatever they played, which most of the time was Mama's Family,
I guess because people in Missouri are hicks, but I love Mama's Family.
My number four is Homer Simpson.
I have not watched The Simpsons in 25 years,
but I have seen every episode 10 times.
Me and my sister would watch it two or three episodes a night
when it would air in syndication.
And it's easy to forget how groundbreaking this show was.
I was about 10 or something when it premiered,
and George Bush, the President of the United States,
was talking about what a disgraceful role model for kids Bart Simpson was,
what a horrible dad Homer Simpson was, etc.
The country was up in arms about it.
My parents let me watch The Simpsons, I think just because they saw how brilliant it was.
They wouldn't let me watch it in living color, I think because they were probably slightly racist.
But The Simpsons is a masterpiece.
The first 10 seasons of the show is as funny as animation gets.
It destroys everything in its path, South Park, all these other shows.
For just sheer jokes, the stories are sweet.
I would even go maybe through season 12.
But Homer is, you know, talk about Ramden threatening to beat his wife.
Homer Simpson chokes Bart out as like a recurring bit.
He chokes his son, who is going, you know, that's beyond dark.
I just laughed when I was a kid, you know, I didn't think anything of it.
But Homer cannot operate without six beers in him, you know.
He is obsessed with drinking. He is obsessed with donuts.
He is horrible at his job, which involves public safety, nuclear health.
He is a mess. He is loud. He is stupid.
He is also just unbelievably funny. Dan Castellaneta voiced him.
And, you know, nowadays, who would that have been?
Putty, you know, they'd have to get a name in there.
It never would have been Dan Castellaneta.
But it is one of the great voiceover performances of all time.
The Simpsons has a deeper character bench than any show that has ever been made.
We're down to the smallest character. They are funny and memorable.
But Homer is the giant that stands atop it all.
He's a legend. He almost slipped my mind because of...
I would cite The Simpsons as one of my top 10 shows of all time.
But it's hard to say that when you haven't seen 25 seasons of it.
So that's why Simpsons is in a weird place for me.
But I do think it's the best animated show ever made,
and Homer, one of the best animated characters of all time.
I will go with Archie Bunker for number four.
Left him off my list because I knew you would pick him, but certainly a runner -up.
He, you know, look, people, I've talked endlessly on this show
about why I think All in the Family is such an important show,
why I think it's such a masterful show.
It is another show from the Norman Lear universe,
the greatest sitcom creator of all time.
And, you know, the nucleus of that universe is All in the Family.
It's a challenging show. It is a show that pulls zero punches.
And whether people are laughing at it for the right reasons or the wrong reasons,
I believe the intention behind the show was pure.
And I believe that it was to show that different families need to function as a unit
despite glaringly opposing opinions about things
and people having opinions about those things that are not just unsavory,
but at times downright hateful.
And to make a character like Archie Bunker somehow endearing
when he personifies so many awful traits
that needed to be done away with and progressed past
while still having many redeeming qualities of a generation
that knew how to work hard and to provide and do their best for their family.
It's just an amazing character,
and it's played pitch perfectly, of course, by Carol O 'Connor.
The rest of the cast is...
I would say Edith equally excellent.
So maybe this is a tie.
Edith equally excellent and equally portrayed brilliantly by Maureen Stapleton.
Was it Maureen or Jeanne? Is Maureen...
How do you get the Stapletons mixed up?
Jeanne.
It's Jeanne Stapleton.
Maureen Stapleton is from Johnny Dangerously.
But they're sisters, right?
And she's from Michael. They're not sisters.
I remember looking it up.
Okay. Anyway, the two of them together are just a...
Yeah, they're unrelated.
That's wild.
Just a brilliant, brilliant sitcom team.
And her dim -witted innocence up against his pointed condescension,
it is a perfect fit.
And the fact that he believes he is smart and she is unaware that she isn't
allows for the stage to be set for her to often outwit him unintentionally.
And watching that exchange, watching that battle happen,
and watching him lose is quite brilliant.
And again, characters that you could take out of this show
and plop into anything and they would still be as robust.
Challenging, brilliant, hilarious Archie and Edith Barker.
I love it.
My number three is Larry David himself on Curb Your Enthusiasm.
The final season is rapidly approaching.
Just an unbelievably consistent comedy show.
I was working at Blockbuster Video when Curb Your Enthusiasm was coming out.
And I was like, you might have seen Larry David at an awards show or something,
but we didn't know anything about the guy.
And I was like, the writer of Seinfeld is going to have his own show?
I thought, well, how many writers can actually perform?
A. What is he thinking?
He doesn't look like a guy who should be on television.
He's too old. He's too ugly.
He's too nerdy, whatever you want to say.
He just doesn't have the charisma that you would think you would need to lead a TV show.
Of course, I knew he was brilliant.
He created my favorite sitcom of all time.
But I certainly didn't have the highest of hopes.
And then for it to be arguably every bit as funny as Seinfeld,
certainly in the first 10 years, you know, they've had a few seasons that were still good,
but maybe dipped a little bit.
The first few years of the show, I was like, these plots are just as good as Seinfeld.
No one has come up with just more genius plots over time than that man.
And he was doing for an app on Seinfeld for plots that would combine.
So I'm a huge fan.
And obviously the improv aspect of the show makes it a little different than everything else on the list.
But who is really funnier than, you know, on that show?
You'd be hard pressed. And he's the misanthrope.
He's the angry guy. He's the guy who gets into fights.
He's the guy who says everything we want to say.
That's not necessarily the freshest character trope.
But my God, does he put his own spin on it.
I had never seen anything like that before.
And yet it has the feel of Seinfeld. That's what makes it so great.
He did something that has the feel, but is a completely different thing.
And to be a writer who is now a yearly nominee for best actor at the, you know,
this man is a talent like none other. He's one of the great humans of all time.
I am remorning the day Larry David passes away.
And Curb Enthusiasm is one of the best comedies ever made.
He was my number three as well.
And my number two was David Brent.
All right. I'm going to jump to my number two.
But I will add to what you just said.
He is I had to pop a Tic Tac because my sugar is dropping.
All right. It's a fun thing as you get old, you sort of get lightheaded for no reason.
Anyway, but one thing I'd add to Larry David is it's the most that's my Chandler.
He's the most relatable person I've ever seen on television.
I've never felt more shoes of somebody.
Yeah, 100 percent to the I can't let things go.
Yeah, you've heard it on the show.
I mean, he's me now, although so many people say they're Larry David.
That's the beauty of it. Everyone says that's me.
Many people are like, no, it's not fucking you.
I can say that it is actually me.
No, I feel the same.
And I think you've got the explosive anger more than I do where you'll actually yell at people and call them out.
I don't do that. But he's he's the ego unleashed.
You know, he's what we all want to do and say and be.
But I will I will go out of my way to go back to the place to be like, I got to tell you, I can't let it go.
I noticed you did this. It's really bothering me.
You know, like, yeah, so I relate.
And then the only other thing I'd say is the what I would add.
You said, who else is as funny as him?
I had a hard time. I almost picked Bob Einstein because, sure.
It's the character is so funny of Funkhouser, but Larry is the goat.
And that's just all there is to it.
I tell you now, I mean, he is surrounded and you want to talk about because he because he knows funny.
Everyone he spars with on that show is fucking hilarious.
Everyone. They all compliment him beautifully.
Whether they're screaming in his face or whether it's Jeff and they're they're good friends.
You know, everybody is just perfect.
I take you now to my number two.
Mr. Dennis Reynolds of It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia.
He's my number 11.
I decided I couldn't pick a show I had written for.
What can I say? He's I mean, it's just a masterful performance.
You watch Glenn Howerton as Dennis Reynolds.
You're like, this man was born to play this role.
Nobody else could do this.
You want to talk about a guy taking things that aren't funny, not just aren't funny on a page because there's no joke,
aren't funny because they are so fucking dark and fucked up and making them hilarious.
I don't even know how it's possible.
I don't understand how him doing to telling a woman inside of a Wal -Mart.
How dare she not know that the invitation to come back to his bar was to bang him.
Yeah. And you're laughing hysterically.
And it's it is it's it he looks like a serial killer and it's somehow still funny.
I don't understand the latest seasons.
They have strongly intimated that he has killed certainly videotaped every sexual encounter he's ever had.
They they don't they don't even try to make it subtle anymore.
Like he's he's killing women.
Yeah. So it's just an amazing, amazing.
And then again, the explosive anger, the confrontational nature of the character, everything about it.
When he explodes and call someone a bitch, when he when him going, you bitch.
When the woman cuts him off in traffic and he goes, you bitch, you fat bitch.
You know, like he's he's and then putting that into a drama as they did with Blackberry.
Yes. He might he might have a career in that.
You know, he might be our our Giamatti.
You know, it's it's hard to see. Hard to hard to say.
Dennis was a character at the beginning of the show that I could have cared less about.
It was all about Charlie and it was all about Mac behind Charlie.
And then in the season around season four, all of a sudden it was like all about D.
And then all of a sudden.
Towards the end of four into five, this this Dennis character just blossomed into this thing
where he went from being like the Ambercrombie and Fitch dildo that was funny,
but it was like, oh, he's funny because he's like a snotty preppy to dear God, like he's a sociopath.
And they just started writing to that.
And, you know, the great speech, the one that that where I was like, oh, my God, I'm here.
I'm here for this for the rest of time.
When he's when he's pitching that movie back and forth, back and forth, we show it.
We show all of it anal or all the big ones, all the hits, that whole thing.
Like, I'm like, this guy's a fucking genius. Yeah.
I would when when he left the show and he was like they were he was going to be gone
and then came back immediately the next season.
I was like, right.
I was like, I'm not going to watch the show anymore.
I don't think like I can't.
It was one of the weakest seasons. Yeah.
I can't go on without him.
And he thankfully came right back.
They they I think they didn't even do a whole episode without him.
But and then and then he did AP bio and AP bio supporting the thesis of of my picks.
Is is a slightly lighter version of Dennis Reynolds,
but all the same qualities just scaled back a bit for NBC.
And it works perfectly.
It's it's he's equally as hilarious on that show because that's how strong this character is.
Dennis Reynolds, ladies and gentlemen, at number two, do yourself a favor.
If you haven't seen it, go check it out.
Yeah, no, he's he just missed my cut just because I didn't feel right.
It's all right. My number two was was David Brent.
And I'm not going to say anything you didn't accept.
As I was talking about earlier, getting a bootleg from the UK of the office is how I first watched it.
And I think it was my first introduction into the region free world and trying to figure all that out.
But because I had to I bought it twice.
I remember getting it and it wouldn't play and I was devastated.
But I kept hearing like, oh, my God, like if you if you can get your hands on this thing.
But if you go back and let's so let's say now somebody you go, oh, you got to see the British office.
Likely they've seen one of the 14 seasons of The American Office.
They've seen this style of awkward comedy done a billion times because of how influential the show was.
And most importantly, they now know Ricky Gervais as a sadly, but judging by his latest special,
hacky stand up who has been great and stand up before a guy who hosts award shows,
a guy who does other TV shows of varying quality, who's made movies.
You know, when I put in the office, I wasn't fooled.
I didn't think I'm watching a documentary here.
But you got to you got to realize I had never seen a single person on that show.
Yeah. So like, you know, it was written.
You're not like, you're not, oh, wow, is this a real paper company documentary?
But I didn't know who that man was.
Sure. That that to me is why he's got the number two spot.
I remember just like watching all of it, calling my friends and being like, come over.
We're watching this again. All of them come over.
We all were like, holy shit.
It's the best. He's the best.
You know, now he is what he is. But when he arrived on the scene, man, holy cow.
And again, a show, Martin Freeman's great on that show.
The whole cast is great, but he is the show. No question.
We had number one, Joe. Yeah, I guess you should.
It's your yeah, you go first because you went for so you do your number one first.
OK, I don't think mine will surprise too much.
It is the fictionalized version of Larry David.
George Costanza, as played by Jason Alexander.
He's everything that Larry David is on his show.
And obviously, George, you know, Jason Alexander famously asked him who would act this way.
And Larry David was like me. That's my story. I did that.
But Alexander brings something completely different to it.
Larry David, I called him unattractive earlier, but many, many women find Larry David very sexy.
And he's always dating, you know, beautiful women.
But in his early days, he's a guy who got better looking and more confident over time.
If you see him in the 70s when he was a writer on like SNL or Fridays or whatever, looks like a homeless person.
He looks insane. The hair.
He hadn't decided that like bald, high and tight was the right way to go.
So he's bald, but with like a weird Afro around the back that just looks terrible.
And George is that George is the Larry David who can't talk to women.
Who is beyond selfish, as all the Seinfeld characters were.
But I'll say I could have put anybody here from Seinfeld, but that's really not true.
Jerry Seinfeld is the best straight man for those people.
But, you know, he's a comedian.
A lot of times you catch him laughing at jokes on the show.
You know, it's not so much a performance, although I do think he's a lot better actor than he gets credit for.
Kramer, when I was a kid, I was like, holy shit, this is the best stuff ever.
You watch Kramer now.
He's very, very funny, but he's in a different show than everybody else.
He's playing a very broad kind of alien creature.
Very, very funny.
Don't get me wrong.
Elaine is arguably the second best character on that show.
That was at a time where if you were a woman in comedy, you were the long suffering wife.
You were, oh, God, did you eat my pizza again?
I was saving that, you know.
They made her every bit as funny as the men on that show.
And at the end, by the end when they started making her a bit of a loose, very sexually progressive woman, that's when her character really took off.
I actually love the later seasons of Seinfeld when they all get crazier, when they get bigger and broader.
I love that.
But it really does boil down to George.
There's no character I've loved more.
Maybe Curb at times is like a more modern, sometimes even funnier version.
But to be a young kind of insecure guy, to be kind of selfish, to be all these kind of negative qualities.
And I had never seen them on television in that way.
I had never seen a character act so despicably.
We all watch Seinfeld as a family.
But in the episode where his fiance dies, the season seven finale, Susan dies from licking the poison envelopes, and they all shrug and walk away.
They don't care at all about his fiance dying.
My mother, who has an amazing sense of humor, she was like, I'm not watching this show anymore.
She was like traumatized by it.
And that's what it's hard to remember.
Always Sunny obviously took the Seinfeld formula in a way more extreme direction.
But for network television, which was all we really had back then, something like that.
Your four lead characters shrugging about a woman who's been on the show for like two seasons dying, who he was going to marry.
Never seen anything like that before.
It's the sitcom of all time.
It's the best sitcom of all time.
It's not going to be defeated for me.
And George is the character.
George is the one.
He's the voice of the show.
He is Larry David.
I got basically got Larry David on here twice.
But Jason Alexander's performance is off the charts.
And again, I'd like to add that he has never won an Emmy for that performance.
Equally as unsurprising for my number one is my pick.
Of course, it's Frasier Crane.
I mean, who else was it?
He's not on my list.
Yes, just in my opinion, the greatest sitcom character of all time.
Not just for the fact that he's the character has sustained now for 30 years across three shows, two of them, which are considered all time classic sitcoms.
Cheers and Frasier.
And now is back in the third show that is not up to speed, but hopefully we'll get there and has a fighting chance.
But the fact that you could still watch this new show and go and go, I'm not too into it.
However, when he's on screen, I'm glued to it is that's what my whole list of picks was about.
This guy, no matter where you put him as this character, it works.
It's great.
It's hilarious.
And it's weirdly relatable to see a guy, a character that has this level of wealth and this level of intelligence display the level of everyday problems and insecurities and foibles that he does.
And you watch it and go, I relate to that.
Oh, like I've, you know, when Frasier flips out about this, I get it.
I get it. Oh, man.
You know, he makes it somehow.
Kelsey Grammer makes Frasier Crane in every man.
I don't understand how he just does.
And it couldn't be done.
The elitist snob every man.
It's it's it's an unbelievable task to pull off and then to make Niles even snootier.
It's really unbelievable.
Yeah, it's wild.
I will forever love Kelsey Grammer.
I will forever love Frasier Crane.
And, you know, for better or for worse, for Kelsey Grammer as an actor, I hate seeing him as anybody.
If I met Kelsey Grammer in real life, which I have a friend that just did, he was at a bar in Queens just like hanging out like for karaoke or something, this little shit like pub.
And she sent all these pictures.
He's taking pictures with everybody.
He's beaming.
He's so happy and smiling and taking pictures.
And I'm like, as as amazing as this looks to meet this man and to have him be this gracious, I would have been sad that he wasn't Frasier in real life.
I would be sad that he wasn't drinking Sherry and too snobby to come into this bar.
That's how much I love Frasier.
As I'm looking down my full list, here's the crazy because I left him off.
I knew he'd be your number one or two.
I figured it would be him or Archie Bunker.
But the crazy thing about Kelsey Grammer is that he is not funny at all.
He's a pompous blowhard.
He is, you know, he's like not he's not interesting.
He's kind of boring.
You look down this list.
If you watch an interview with Matthew Perry, with Larry David, with Jason Bateman, with Danny McBride, with almost any of these people, you'll be laughing.
Phil Hartman, whoever, because they were funny people playing funny characters.
Kelsey Grammer isn't funny.
So it's amazing that he knows where the funny is.
That's very rare.
A person who's not hilarious, who knows how to find the funny.
He's been doing it for ages.
Yeah, he seems to me like he'd be a very nice man and a very sweet man to talk to.
There were definitely in previous years.
He seems to have lost a lot of this.
He had a very arrogant air for many years, like when he'd gone stern and stuff.
He seems to have lost that and become a very humbled, emotional man.
And he seems like he'd be a delight to speak to or to be around or to work with.
But yeah, I agree.
He's probably not any.
He's not a funny dude.
He's not a quippy guy.
But that's the thing.
He's a real actor.
Not that these other people aren't.
But he's a true actor where it's like, well, I play a role and that's how you do it.
And he plays it so truthfully.
And that's why it's hilarious.
Like Kevin James, I bet is a funny guy in real life if you're joking around or whatever.
And you watch him on King.
And he's also a great sitcom actor in the sense that he knows how to do a sitcom thing.
But he's a guy that takes he does funny things that he knows are funny.
You know, he'll go, yeah, what's the situation on or, you know, that that all that.
That's a guy going like, I know that that's funny.
So I'm going to do a funny thing.
Kelsey Grammer, he does Frasier.
It's like it is played one thousand percent like a real person.
It's just that this real person has these peaks and valleys that are fucking hilarious.
And if you nail those emotional notes, it's going to be great, which is why I bet you Glenn Howard.
I've talked to Glenn Howard.
He was nice, but he wasn't funny.
You know, I'm not saying he's unfunny, but like he's not.
He can be pretty funny.
Yeah, but he's not.
But yeah, he actually takes himself pretty seriously.
Yeah, he was.
He was being very nice.
He was being very endearing and gracious.
We talked for a very long time about the Evil Dead movies.
He was very cool.
But he wasn't like cracking jokes or anything like that.
You know what I mean?
Where I've met McElhaney, both times I was with you, obviously.
I've met McElhaney a few times now.
McElhaney is like a funny guy.
Like you're talking, he'll be like, shut up, stop being a pussy.
You know what I mean?
Like he'll break your balls and stuff.
So I think the reason Howerton and Kelsey are my one and two is because I feel like they are like Julliard actors playing parts so convincingly
that these parts are iconic to me, like beyond anything else I've ever seen.
So anyway, Kelsey Grammar as Frasier Crane, that's my number one.
And that's our top ten list, people.
Ten each.
Yeah, that's our ten.
I mean, my just missed list is Hank Kinsley as said, Stephen Toast from Toast of London.
I think that character is fucking amazing.
I forgot.
Damn, yeah.
Basil Fawlty, back in the day.
I love Fawlty Towers, but I thought John Cleese has been funnier elsewhere.
Jack Donaghy on 30 Rock also could have gone with Tracy Morgan on 30 Rock.
I had Hank Kinsley.
I had Roseanne.
Yeah.
And also Dan Conner.
You know, I love both of those characters, but ultimately not there.
Michael Scott was amazing, but not in a world where we had Gervais first.
Cartman.
Used to crack the shit out of me.
And I also considered Frank Drebben, although I figured he's more a movie character than a TV character.
I saw Police Squad on a couple lists.
I looked up some lists while I was doing this to see if I was forgetting any shows or whatever.
And I saw, and I was like, I was tempted to take Drebben, but I was like, eh, it's not.
It's a movie character.
Yeah.
And it's sort of a sitcom.
It's more of a parody.
That's why I didn't, I'm not saying you shouldn't have picked cartoons, but I kept cartoons off the list.
Because I was like, is that a sitcom?
I couldn't tell.
It was a hard call.
I only picked one, but I hear you.
And Frazier, Dennis Reynolds, and Elaine all could have easily been on my top 10, but I just didn't put them.
Well, this was fun.
It was fun.
Thank you all for listening.
We'll be back in February with something.
You know we'll be back and we'll be back with something good.
We love you all.
Thank you for listening.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.