I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear reviews.
Of those films you may or may not have watched my name is Joe Derosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
How's everybody doing today?
Can't answer.
All right.
Joe, how are you doing?
Pat, I started a diet this week.
Okay.
Started to do some exercise.
Yeah.
And I've learned a lot about health and fitness in this last week, which is it doesn't work
if you still drink 11 tequila sodas every night.
Sure.
So that's where I'm at right now.
I was out last night with not to name drop, but SNL correspondent from the weekend update
desk, Michael Chey, we were all show together.
He had a big night last night, didn't he?
I eventually boiled down just me and him.
I repeatedly was trying to leave.
He kept saying have one more quick.
They'd put a full tequila in front of me.
I would pound it.
You would say, Jesus, Joe, slow down and I'd say, I'm trying to leave and you keep saying have
one more quick than that would happen again.
Yeah.
There's a real comedy of errors last night, came home about 4 a .m. eight, some leftover
chicken and pasta sauce that I had made.
I mean, I knew you were in a spot when the second I see your face on the zoom, you're like,
I know I look horrible.
I was like, oh boy, it's an alpha steam issue.
I've been doing this peloton every day and noticing no difference in my weight and then
I started doing 75 minute peloton rides that leave you shattered as a man afterwards.
You just limp to the shower.
It's hard to even get the clothes off.
They're so drenched.
If that's a sexy image, you're welcome.
But not losing a pound and in fact gaining and I talked to my fitness buddy.
I'm like, what the fuck is going on?
Am I just 40?
I mean, when you're 40, things shut down fast and hard.
I've learned that.
Yeah.
You know, it used to be, okay, I won't eat for an afternoon and I'll drop five.
And now it's like, if I don't eat for five weeks, I'll drop one or something.
So he said, well, you're probably just building muscle.
I'm like, I don't care.
I don't think I am building muscle.
You know, I mean, that was my thought when you said, I'm gaining weight, you might, yeah,
I mean, I don't, it's not like I look in the mirror and I'm like, who's this muscle bound
body?
You know, well, you're probably building it in your legs and probably not noticeable, you
know, that's, I would imagine legs aren't extremely noticeable muscles, you know.
My legs look good.
And if I do have to stand up during this recording, you will see that I am wearing a pair
of orange briefs, oh, balls to the wall.
Yeah.
So you'll be able to see my legs and all their glory.
I almost did a zoom yesterday in my underwear, a business zoom.
I just, I don't know, I feel like you could, you could do a business zoom when you're
underwear and people would be like, as long as you don't jack off, yeah, you could jack
off as long as you turn your camera off.
Yeah.
Keep it on, keep it out of frame.
I could, did you see the clip of that guy, Tuben, when he, when he went on the, the news and
they were like, so elephant in the room, you were caught jacking off on, or masturbating
on zoom.
And he's like, yep, yep, you know, it's embarrassing, but it is what it is.
And like, just kind of got his career back.
And I'm like, okay, and I get it.
If you want to jack off on day, you know, I don't think he was trying to make eye contact
with somebody in the zoom, however, you can't jack off during the work zoom.
It's not only.
If I did it, which is the title of OJ's book, if I did it, I would simply kill myself.
I wouldn't be able to face anyone ever again.
But the fact that he was able to just go on the news and be like, yep, you got me.
I sort of admire the balls and I didn't get to admire the balls on the initial zoom.
But now I admire it.
You're, you're dealing with a different deck of cards here, man.
A guy that's even doing that to begin with, he's, he's 10 ticks down the road of not being
embarrassed past you.
Like, it's like, that's true.
You know, you're not doing that if, if, if suicide is on the line, you know what I mean?
Like if I had to do that on a zoom, it'd be like a terrorist situation.
They'd have like a gun to my head, you know, I'd be terrible.
We're jerking off on camera.
They send it to your mom for some reason.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd be like some kind of black mirror episode or whatever.
But like that guy's doing it.
That's, that wasn't his first rodeo.
No, he knew I bet you wasn't the first time we got caught either.
It was the first time it came out.
I'm amazed by the sex drive of like a 60 year old man who one second after a meeting needs
to pound one out.
It's like, go, go lay down and, and, you know, tease yourself.
I thought it was like a lady.
I thought it was during the meeting.
It was after he thought his camera was off.
That's why I felt like there was a little bit of gray area to it.
It's like, oh, that's fine then.
I thought he was doing it during the meeting.
No, seriously, that's not his fault then.
Yeah, that's not his fault.
All right, that's fine.
Well, it is his fault.
I mean, there's a green light that tells you if the camera is on or not.
What that is, I never knew what that was.
You're actually supposed to tape over the camera because the government
apparently can watch you at any point.
Yeah.
I mean, look, at this point, God only know.
I'll tell you folks, speaking of the government,
I have fully now swung from a first person in line, strong believer in the Vax too.
Now, what did they put into my body?
These other people are starting to make sense to me.
Like, the narrative keeps changing every day.
Pfizer came out yesterday with they were like, or two days ago, they're like,
oh, we just figured out that if you take a third dose of our regular Vax,
it will protect you against this Delta variant.
You're like, guys, this is all two coincidental.
What is happening right now?
33 billion dollars in profit I found out they made.
When they were having financial troubles just before this Vax,
miraculously launched overnight with a 90 % efficiency.
I'm just like, I don't even know anymore, man.
I'm not going down the tunnel with it.
I'm just, I still believe everyone should get vaccinated.
And it's our only way out.
And the Delta variant is looking scarier and scarier.
I will say I have a couple of friends that work with the great Mr. Bob Odenkirk.
And I am ecstatic that the man is alive and well.
I know you as well work with Bob Odenkirk.
Yes, Bob, I got word that he is going to be okay.
And they seem to announce that also on Twitter and stuff that he's going to be okay.
So that's great, but that was very, I was like, Jesus Christ.
He's all good, heart incident, not quite a heart attack, but he's fine.
And, you know, I'm reading through some of the tweets about it.
And I start saying people say, when did he get the vaccine shot?
Perfectly healthy man, you know, who works out constantly, suddenly drops to his knees.
And I'm like, I don't want to engage with this, you know, I don't want to engage.
I mean, it's that's the problem is it's like it's blown.
Wide open in every direction now.
Yeah.
So, you know, am I happy I got vaccinated?
I am still, you know, but also it upsets me that the ad that the adverse opinion, not that
adverse opinion, but some of the adverse opinions are starting to make a little more sense to me.
And I'm like, oh boy, you know, like I watched a thing where these nurses were being interviewed
and they refused to get vaccinated.
Yeah.
And then the guy goes, the reporter goes, you don't trust the CDC and they're like, no.
And I was watching, I'm like, that's a perfectly fair opinion to have at this point.
Sure.
It's the CDC is all over the place.
Somebody tweeted the other day.
It was really funny.
The CDC just asked, what do you think we should do?
Yeah.
But yeah, it's just like so it just upsets me that there's this much ambiguity now.
And, you know, I don't even know.
I don't even know.
Yamanika Saunders, she's a very, very funny comedian.
She has a really, really funny bit about Fauci, about she's like, that motherfucker too happy
about this virus.
Anytime you see a man who's masked matches his suit, you were too prepared for this.
That's funny.
I mean, Fauci, you know, the fact that they're trying to like lock Fauci up, I mean,
it's, I feel like we did as well as, maybe not as well as we could, but we did what we could
in the emergency situation.
There was a bit of a rush to the vaccines.
I feel confident that they're not going to fuck with me in any way.
My health, I feel glad that I'm not going to die from the Delta variant.
But what I do have on my side is that I am prepared to die.
Yeah, and I also welcome it.
That's what, you know, I'm not saying that because my wife is an air shot, but yeah, it's time to die.
Fauci, at this point, it's like, this is like almost like an OJ scenario where it's like where he's
like, I know how it looks.
I know I have a clearance badge from the Wuhan facility on the day that the thing started and a
receipt from funds I gave them. I know how it looks. It's like turning into this like minority
report thing or the fugitive where it's like, you're on that that waterfall right now.
It's like, dude, you better find this one, our man.
And this is getting insane. But then the problem is is the other side of it is fucking lunatic
Rand Paul. It's like, it's, it's, I love when Fauci was like, can I tell you something?
You don't know what you're talking about. You don't know what you're talking about.
But that's that's politics now. Nobody knows what they're talking about. And everybody's an expert.
And I, for the first, maybe it's getting older, but for the first time in my life, I feel like
everyone who is talking to me is just as clueless as I am. And that's scary to say.
We are, we are about a week out from Trump coming out publicly and being like, oh, not so easy,
isn't it? Yeah. Yeah, for sure. I can't believe he hasn't done that yet. I can't believe.
Oh, I'm sure he has. I just don't think we see or hear from him anymore.
It is weird. I've never seen a president disappear so quickly from the spotlight.
Yeah, I think when he's, when he has that hill release of video, not so easy, is it? I think
he'll be doing those, those two balls in his hand, the bachy balls that you, you turn in circles.
Well, well, or maybe even a yo -yo, that level of like, maybe he's looking a lollipop. He needs
something where he's like, he's, he's doing great. But it's a shame you guys are struggling right now,
you know? Yeah. I would like him to go full Jerry Lewis
Losage, like legs crossed, like just the most arrogant. Yeah, he's keeping it clacking in his mouth.
Today's, all right, folks, hopefully, you know, we're not going to delve too deep into politics.
Today's movie is freaky, starring the great Vince Vaughn, looking forward to this. I think you're
thinking that is. They sang the song, I think you're freaky and I like you a lot. And then they,
they were in the movie Chappy. Oh, oh, the rap group. Yeah, like blonde hair lady rap,
rap's pushing it. But yeah, they both look like they're tank girl. Yes. Yeah. I know, like
tank girl and tank guy got together. You ever see tank girl iced tea, Lori Petty? No. I wanted to
see it. And then I was great film. I wanted to see it because I lifelong iced tea fan. And that
was like your third movie. And then when he was like a half kangaroo man in it, I didn't want to see
it anymore. Yeah, I want to see like New Jack city iced tea. I just heard iced tea for like two hours
on stern go through his career and boy, it was great. What a great interview. Oh, you're going to love
this job before we get to the bulk of the pod here. I was listening to Jim Carey last night on stern.
They're doing like a best of week. Sure. And it's Carey and that, you know, he's talking about all
that he's being a little bit of his annoying meditation self, you know, for sure. But they're talking
about all the hits and the old movies and and stern loves them and blah, blah, blah. And then
they go, what was your low point, Jim? What was your, what was the low point of your career where
you were like, I can't be in this fucking movie. I'd rather die. I got to get off this set. And he
goes, well, for me, that was Mr. Popper's Penguins, which co -starred our dear friend David Grimmels.
I never saw Mr. Popper's Penguins, but he was like, that was a real low and I that was a time
I had to look in the mirror and say, Jim, you can only do projects with some edge to them because if I
don't have that edge, I'm bored, I'm miserable, you know, I just got to have that edge. And he keeps
talking about it. And he's like, that's why, you know, with this project, and you never know on stern,
what time period you're listening to when he does a best of. So he goes, with this project, you know,
I was like, page two, okay, this definitely has that edge I'm looking for. It's very critical of
like the, the mechanization and the weaponization of our world today and very aligned with my political
beliefs at this time. And I know people don't love me speaking out about it, but I have to do projects
that align with my political belief. Like, okay, he's rambling, rambling. What movie are they talking
about? Sonic the hedgehog. Come on. No, I'm on. No, because then he goes, yeah, I mean, when I
when I stepped into that mechazoid suit or whatever and I'm like, tell me he's not talking about.
Sonic, he was, he was. That's the playing a character named Dr. Robotnik. Yeah, he was, he was,
you know, going into like, it had a lot to say about AI and our place in the world. And it had
that edge that I, you know, I was unbelievable, unbelievable. The lies people will tell themselves,
just say they offered me $20 million and I hadn't worked in five years. We get it.
We all get it. Quick news psycho. Yes.
The trailers, I'm just going to highlight a four trailers that dropped this week. Yeah,
all of them great. Every one of these trailers, I was like, wow, I got to do a catch up.
So day of the dead, the series based on the George Romero film, trailer dropped, couldn't
have cared less. I was like, oh, another fucking walking dead thing. And then I watched it. And it's
actually like a zombie comedy thing. And it actually looks super fun and cool. And it's a sci -fi series.
Sci -fi channel. Yeah. And I really like that the first one of the first things you see is a zombie
crawling out of the grave. And I was like, finally, give me the good fun old zombies again, you know?
Right enough with this rage virus bullshit. So it looks like a lot of fun. It's coming up when a
zombie's putting a brain between two pieces of bread and spreading mustard on the top. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Sci -fi also dropping Chuckie the series looks great. All I saw was a tweet from
black Twitter, the only reason to follow Twitter anymore is black Twitter, but they had a picture of
Chuckie with like the tag that caption was basically like, who the fuck doing Chuckie's hair? And he had like
the like almost like it is a new hairstyle for Chuckie. But it is, they make in each passing Chuckie
project. They make his hair look more and more like hanks in the Vinci code. It's the same hair.
I don't know why they're they keep doing that. Yeah. But they are. But Chuckie's ever looks stupider than
the instant Vinci code. Ridiculous. Ridiculous. The second Da Vinci code is one of the worst movies ever
made. Angels and demons or whatever the fuck it's called. Angels and arrows. That's the best one of
the three. There's three? Yeah. There's inferno. Angels and demons and the Vinci code. I never saw
it for no. I saw all three in the theater with my mom. Okay. Because they were good mom movies. They're
a fun mom movies. But like, yeah, they're not great flicks. And that's just two more Tom Hanks movies.
We didn't get because he had to do that stupid fucking franchise. And by the way, three Ron Howard
Flicks. Yeah. True. Well, he's on to Hillbilly. You won't work again for a while. Yeah. So
anyway, Chuckie the series about a kid in a small town buying a vintage Chuckie doll to flee at a yard
sale. Okay. And then the doll starts to wreak havoc. Everybody thinks it's the kid. And of course,
it's not the kid. It's the doll. And and characters from the series will start to appear in the town
to because they catch wind of it. And they're there to help try to stop or assist Chuckie,
depending on who the character is. But Jennifer Tilly's back. Brad Dorif is back as the voice of Chuckie.
Nice. Don is it Don Mancini? Is he the creator, I believe? He's at the home of the whole thing.
It's it's it's the it's the whole classic crew that the original kid is coming back that played the
the kid in the first two movies. I'm excited about it. I'm really excited about it. So that was great.
The chapel weight trailer dropped, which is the new vampire series starting Adrian Brody that
is based on Jerusalem's lot by Stephen King. And here's why I'm excited. Period piece takes place in
like the 1700s or 1800s or whatever, which is always way better like a gothic vampire piece is
always way cooler to me than a modern day one. And scary vampires again. The vampires look like
disgusting, awful monsters. I'm like, yeah, this is yeah, let's get back to it here, man.
So that was those three were our TV shows coming out. Chapel weight I think
I think is paramount plus the other two are sci -fi. But can I ask as you're talking about how much
you love the old style zombies and vampires and et cetera. Yeah. When are we getting
a classic old toilet paper mummy walking walking very slowly after you with his arms extended.
Maybe you step on one of the pieces of toilet paper and unwind him completely. Where are those
movies? I agree. I agree. The last like six mummy movies have been like a guy like a Persian gorgeous
beauty strolling around in broad daylight. You know, it's not my mummy. No, hashtag not my mummy.
I agree. I want to I want a good old rotting like, you know, we have to we had to do a ritual. Yeah,
it needs a bride. One of those even give him ruby eyes or something if you need CGI in there. But
keep the toilet paper base that we all know and love. I agree. And the big one this week for me,
I don't know if you'll agree Pat. I know you did see it was the official Ghostbusters after
a life trailer. I am so excited to see this movie. I loved the trailer. It did lean way more
serious than funny. But I think I think that's just a tonal choice for the trailer itself. But
and I think that it probably will be the most serious of any of the Ghostbusters movies. But I think
that's only because of all the emotional baggage coming along with the storyline at this point.
But that all said things starts you almost immediately see Annie Potts talking about Egon and
and what you're like, oh man, this is cool. Like, oh wow. It was cool. And I keep seeing with with
this renewed success of Jean Smart, a lot of people like, when are we getting pots back? And it's
like right on cue. There she is. She looks great. It's great to see her. She does a problem if she
didn't look great. I just love seeing her. It was awesome. It was awesome seeing her in that that
it looks great. Everybody's charismatic in the trailer. It's a fun trailer. The vibe is great.
And then the best part is the little button at the end. They keep showing the YouTube video
of the original Ghostbusters commercial from the first movie. We're ready to believe you that one.
Yeah. And you're like, come on. Give me just give me a taste. Just give me a taste of the boys.
I once did time in Bermuda for saying that. No, give me and then and then at the very end of
the trailer, yeah, you see a hand reach out and grab a bottle of crystal skull vodka and tilt it
back. Right. And then Danny act very into the trailer. I think Paul Rudd calls the number and you see
the phone in the original firehouse and you just see a hand come over and answer the phone.
And you hear Dan Akroy go, we're closed. And then it just says November. I just got chills
talking about it. That was like, that was as well done to me. I know I go back to Star Wars a lot,
but that was as well done to me as when I saw the Force Awakens trailer. And after the title card,
it's it showed Han Solo and Shoei and he goes, Shoei were home. And the audience went fucking
berserk. It was such a, it's just such an iconic character movie moment. I'm just,
there's only a few of these franchises left where they can still do, I mean, look, they're making
new ones now that kids now 30 years from now will be excited when they reboot it or do a 30 years later
sequel, whatever. But for my childhood and your childhood, we get that new new jungle cruise in
2052. Pat, I've got a, that's, I've got, I told you there was something I really wanted to get to
today. Is it JC related? I've got a big surprise for you. Okay. All right. Are you in Jungle Cruise too?
I am writing and directing Jungle Cruise too. I go see Jungle Cruise and it opens with like Joe's
ass just giving it to Emily Blunt. And I'm like, what the fuck Joe? Yeah. It's a different kind of
jungle cruise. Anyway, I, there are very few of these franchises left that could actually
be sparked up again. Masters of the universe was one for me. I won't be talking about that today.
I'll talk about that in the next episode. But anyway, Ghostbusters is one of them and I'm excited.
And I'd love to get to the movie corner because I got a big surprise for you is what I'm saying.
Uh, let's do it. And I, I agree. I, I didn't love the Ghostbusters trailer, but I felt like it's,
it felt like stranger things in the movie, which is kind of what I was expecting. And I'm excited to
know, I just want to know how much they're in it. You know, do they come in in the last battle to
join forces? Or are they a big part of the movie? Do we know? Uh, I think they're probably going to be
second half, you know, whatever. Because a lot of here's the thing. Jason Wrightman or the studio
or both are being very smart. It's like guys, we get one shot, right? To cash in on the reveal of
the original Ghostbusters. That's true. That's true. Like do not put them in the trailer.
You know, like, like we got one chance to do this right. And, and so far, they're doing it right.
But they released, you know, toy, if you look at like ads for the toy lines that accompany these
movies, that always kind of gives you a few clues. They've, they've already advertised full.
There's, there are three action figures of the original guys in the full suits with the past.
With white, with white hair, Rammus's dead. So Hudson's back too. Yeah, it's Hudson. Yeah, it's the
three of them. And there's heavy rumors that Moranis is going to pop up and daddy. Yeah, that'd be exciting.
The Dan Acroid, I just saw on, again, Twitter, but it was Jim Belushi, now owns a Marijuana farm
and his big pro marijuana. And he and Acroid were standing with their arms around each other. You
know, I was a cute little picture, whatever. And Acroid looked great. So I figured he was getting back
in fighting shape for something. I'm glad to hear that he's in there. Yeah, no, I'm excited.
Man, and I think Acro, Acroid is one of those guys when he pops up, it's seldomly, but he'll pop
up here in there. And when he does, he's still a great actor. And he's still very funny. Like he goes
back to SNL once in a while, he's still really funny. And we know that Murray is funny. And I have no
reason to doubt Ernie Hudson. So it's like, I think, I think we're, I think we're going to be in good shape. So
anyway, that was reviewing Ghostbusters. This piece is shit. Yeah, it will take us to the movie
corner, Joe. What's your, what's your surprise? I'm doing something a little different today
for the movie corner. All right. I get a text from our dear friend, Matt McCarthy today. Yeah.
And in that text is a link to something to do with the film Jungle Cruise. Okay. I'm like, why is he
sending me this? I don't care about Jungle Cruise. Right. And then right after it, he sends a link to
the Elton John song, The Bitches Back. And I realize he has sent me Rex Reed's full scathing review.
Oh nice. The film Jungle Cruise. So my movie corner today, a little something different. Thank you,
Mattie. We could even rename the segment The Bitches Back. But I'm not reviewing anything for the movie
corner today. I am just going to read Rex Reed's review of Jungle Cruise in its entirety because it
is worth it. Who is Rex Reed reviewing movies for at this point? What the observer? The observer.
You've got a liberal, I think, gay man, writing for a predominantly right wing outlet. I love it.
I love it. You can do your movies first. Then I'll do this or I'll do this and you do your movies,
whatever you want to do or I could break it up into pieces, however you want to do it. But I'm
this, this review is the guy he's back, baby. I thought we maybe lost him with COVID. I can't wait
to follow this guy. All right. Well, I'll do mine and then you can get to it. I watched
Francois Truffauts, The Bride War Black, which is an awesome title. I haven't seen a lot of
Truffauts. You know, he did the 400 blows in day for night and he's a very like acclaimed
400 director of course. But The Bride War Black is his like Hitchcock homage, his attempt at like a
genre movie and it's pretty dope. Also, the movie is clearly the inspiration for Kill Bill. It is a
bride whose husband is killed on her wedding day and she has a list of names that she goes through
killing everybody who was involved with the death of her husband. The murders are pretty sweet.
It's Truffauts. The movie looks great. It feels like Hitchcock. It's super entertaining. I look it up
and Tarantino, whose claim to fame as I have seen every movie ever made, was asked. So,
clearly, The Bride War Black is an inspiration for Kill Bill and Tarantino claims that he has never
seen the film. Now, I guess that's possible. But if he's on a podcast, he's brags about having
seen every movie ever made no matter how obscure. This is a Francois Truffaut Hitchcock style movie
that he just would have seen. Why not just say, yeah, it was kind of the jumping off point.
Kill Bill's a way better movie. Kill Bill 2 is a way better movie.
acknowledge your fucking influence. It drove me a little nuts.
But he's never really, I feel that he's never, I love Tarantino, but I feel he's never fully
given it up to the stuff that he clearly is doing a little prototypical use up. You know what I mean?
Like even with the Django thing, you know, in all the press for Django unchained and everything,
he never really talked about the Django series. You know what I mean?
That's true, yeah. So I feel like he doesn't ever address that stuff. I don't know, like, you know,
but anyway, I rewatched Fast Times at Ridgemont High, which I have seen numerous times, of course,
but there's the new Craterion Edition. It's never looked better. The movie is super entertaining.
I don't hold it up with the Hughes, you know, the 16 candles, classics, but I love Fast Times.
There's a lot to like, it really has less than zero plot. You know, but it's a great film.
It's of its time. Penn is great. Jennifer Jason Lee is great. It's fun to see, you know,
Forest Whitaker and a tiny role, Nick Cage and a tiny role. I love the film, but there's an extra
on it, which is Olivia Wilde interviewing Cameron Crowe and Amy Heckerling, the director of Fast Times.
And Olivia Wilde comes off like the biggest dunce. She talks the whole time about book smart.
It's a 30 minute interview with these two people who gave us like this pioneering teen classic.
She talks about her own movie. Can I just tell you guys, when we were doing book smart,
I had the entire cast and crew watch Fast Times. And you know that scene, like, she's referencing
scenes in her own movie. I mean, here's the thing. That's for your DVD, Olivia. The question sucked.
Here's a thing to me. Here's the thing. What a waste of a feature.
You know, it's how we would is so sick that it thinks that somebody is going to see Olivia Wilde's name
and the special features for a movie they wouldn't have otherwise bought and then buy the movie. Yeah.
Those commentaries are for the hardcore fans. Only the psycho fans like us would ever sit and listen
to it. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. You can't even hook the fans up there. Like, you got to,
I hate when they do this all the time now with these goddamn commentaries where it'll be like,
you'll buy like a blu -ray release of the burbs and they'll be like, you know,
Scorsese, he sits down with you. This doesn't make any sense. I just want to hear Tom Hanks talk
about it. Like, I want to hear the people that did the movie talk about it. Yeah. And Criterion's whole
thing is, I mean, sometimes to a fault too, but they'll have like these film historians come on and
get, you know, really academic commentaries and stuff. I hope they're not going to this direction
now that it's got that the fucking Criterion collection has to embrace celebrity culture and we have to,
I mean, I had, I liked book smart. I have no real issue with Olivia Wilde, but like, she was,
she seemed very unprepared. Also Criterion is putting Zoom interviews on their releases. And I
understand that we're in a pandemic, but God, it seems cheap and shitty to me, you know, they're putting
one of the releases zoom interviews. This was a zoom interview. Yeah, come on with that shit.
It's like, just wait, wait until it's over or get the three people in a fucking room and have them
sit six feet apart. But man, I mean, she might have camera crew out to to shoot them properly. Right.
In three different locations, like the news used to do. Don't you love how that all just went out
the window? They used to do live interviews with guys as bombs were raining down in like Afghanistan.
And the guy would be on like, it would look like he was in the room with the other guy. And the second
they didn't have to do that anymore. They're like, well, you know, we can't do that for John Goodman.
He's promoting the Conner's. So just have him do it from his iPhone. If he can get out of the car
great, if he can't, don't worry about it. Well, Carrie on on that stern was talking about what a
thrill it is now that he and other celebrities will be able to do the late night talk shows from their
home. He's like, I've been talking to my friends who are actors. He's like, believe me, no one's
hopping on a plane to go to found anymore. We're all going to just stick to the zoom. And it's like,
so this in a way will be sort of the end of all culture. You know, it's just like
so we have we have nothing anymore. I don't I don't watch any of these talk shows, but like the
thought of watching somebody on zoom when they don't have to be on zoom is like, what are you doing?
Get on the plane. You make $25 million to play Dr. Fucking Robotnik.
Yeah, it's it's pretty silly. And the fact that these celebs don't even have the decency
Yeah, to plug in ear buds.
Anything they literally just sit with the computer mic. I know. It's like, how fucking dare you?
Well, the shows should really send a little kit, a little AV kit or something, but like, I mean,
I've watched somebody on cold bear the other night and it was going in and out of
we have better recording on this. Yeah, I was going to say a podcast that now now our fans pay for
these new episodes. Yes. But before anybody paid for these new episodes, we still did the same
quality recording when the show was free because you give a shit. Yeah, you give a shit. It's like
it's just so gross, man. But um, all right, sorry, we said you got one more, right? Yes, my my
third title is the Jesus Rolls. Oh, boy. You know, I would imagine if you're like me, you heard
about this when it was coming out. You were extremely curious. And yet you just never got around to
seeing it because you sensed that it might be an abortion and it is. The Jesus Rolls is a I guess
Lebowski. Um, I adore the big Lebowski. Of course we all do. Terturo wrote and directed. He goes to
the Cohen brothers. He's like, can I use this character? I know you guys don't want to do a sequel.
They gave him permission and friends for a long time. The only character who returns is Terturo.
There's no nods to the there's no mention of the dude. There's no mention of anything to do with
uh, the big Lebowski. It is friends not in it either, right? Friends not in it. Which is the Liam?
Yeah, the the friend now is Bobby Canavale. Okay. Good to see him working as we discussed.
Um, you're not allowed to make anything anymore if Bobby Canavale is not in it. It's like Jesus
Christ. I'm a fan. But come on him and Sarah Paulson. It's like Jesus Christ guy. Yeah, take
a day off. It starts. Joe guessed it when I told him I was watching it. It opens with
immediately. Them saying he's not actually a peter ass because why else would you be watching a
two hour movie about the exploits of a petafile? But um, so there's this scene and I and when I say
it's the it might be the second scene, but it's very early on. Terturo was standing at a urinal.
There's a little boy standing at the urinal next to him. He looks over at Terturo's
cock and says, boy, that's really big. And then Terturo's like, yes, you know, thank you,
but it's not really the size of the the power of the cock is within not the size of the talking to the
boy. And that's how he got arrested for being a petafile, which doesn't make a whole lot of sense. Then
him, Kanavali and their friend, Audrey Terturo who played omely 25 years ago and still
maybe I do focus on looks too much, but she looks fantastic. She's very charming. The three of them
go on a road trip together. I look it up. It's now it's a remake of Going Places.
Have you seen Going Places? I've never seen it, but I read about Going Places. Going Places apparently
as one of the most defensive movies that's ever been made. It was extremely controversial. I think it
was it was made in France, right? In France, it's got Gerard Depardieu. It's on canopy and I guess
I'll probably watch it. I always have a I like watching controversial movies and seeing
why they're so controversial, but the movie yeah, Going Places is about two men who go around
France, sexually assaulting women and then having threesomes with women and the rapes are played
for gentle laughs kind of because what I heard about the movie, which makes me think that Terturo
probably I would assume initially didn't want to change. Yeah, the petafile element of the character
perhaps. I mean, look, when they said we're doing a Jesus solo movie, none of us were like I won't watch
that. It's about a petafile. I was like, I'll watch that. That character's really funny.
So I bet that I bet, but I bet some financier somebody was like, dude, you have to it can't be
yeah, you know, but I mean, the fact that he was trying to make this a remake of one of the most
defensive or controversial movies ever made, I was like, okay, he clearly lose, you know, anyway.
He clearly called it a lot of favors. You got one 20 -second scene with Christopher
walking where he's almost just doing a parody of himself, you know, with the way he's talking at this point.
You got John Hamm and a horrible cameo as a hairdresser that just does not work at all.
They go on this journey and the tattoo character reveals that she fucks anyone and everyone who
wants to fuck her basically. She keeps fucking Terturo and Cannibal both separately and together.
There's a 10 -minute scene where the two men are completely naked for 10 full minutes. You
don't see cock, but you see everything else. They're naked. They're a little out of shape, you know,
for actors and it's just, they just keep going in for turns with her and they'll like fuck her
and then the other one gets right in there and fox her and it's in this comedy. It's insane.
But she reveals that she's never come. Then they pick up Pete Davidson and he's the first
man to ever make her come and that's basically the plot of the film. Is it like he's Jesus' son or
something? No, they pick up Susan Sarandon and Davidson is, I believe, her son.
You don't care about the details. I assure you, but it's a really sexual graphic at times strange,
strange movie. I would almost recommend it just for the curiosity factor, but it's nuts. It makes
you wonder if Jon Terturo is okay mentally honest. I never in a million years thought they could have
made a movie that related to the Big Lebowski that I wouldn't care to see and I was so excited when
they announced this film and it took years and years to get made and then when I finally saw the trailer
I was like, I just don't, I'm not interested, man. Yeah, she don't work. The movie don't work.
All right, here we go, buddy. Let's hear it. Let's hear it. Rex Reed's review for the observer
of Jungle Cruise, courtesy of our buddy, Matt McCarthy, headline, Jungle Cruise is a waste of time,
money, Paul Giamatti, and scenes from better movies. So he's off to it. No, Giamatti was in it.
I might see this now. I didn't know he was in it either. And Jesse Plemons playing Warner
Herzog apparently. Oh, man, if that's what it is, hold on. I'm trying to get this so I can see it and
see you. Okay. I'm going to read the whole thing. It's not terribly long, but bear with me. Trust me,
it did, you know, in the exposition areas, we're always followed up by something really worthwhile.
Lusely based on a Disneyland amusement park ride, which in turn is based on a dozen other
Disney rides, Jungle Cruise is a numbingly overproduced family film unlikely to appeal to any family member
over eight years old. The ride itself has been entertaining people for decades as your boat tugs
through the Brazilian jungle alligator snap monkey scream and alleged thrills await behind every turn.
Kids of all ages love it and grownups find it amusing too. It is doubtful that the noisy,
predictable and woefully inspired movie version will produce the same reactions. A torturous waste
of time and money. Its mechanical contrivances are many and its entertainment values are few. He is back,
baby. The plot, which grows more convoluted and pointless by the minute begins in 1916,
London, at the start of World War One, when an adventurous name Lily Houghton played by Emily
Blunt, embarks on a dangerous expedition to the Amazon jungle to find a magic tree with that amazing
healing powers called tears of the moon. All right, that's just a plot point. It's making me laugh.
The petals of its legendary flowers are rumored to cure everything from shingles to syphilis.
What? There's no way that they say that in the movie. There's no way. I'm picturing
read writing this in a bathrobe and nothing else, by the way. Athrobe, cigarette in the holder.
By the way, I'm picturing a bathtub with the typewriter on a tray in front of him.
He's in a hotel and they're bringing him room service and like they they asked the room service guy
to tell Rex, we need you to pay your bill soon, Rex. You've been staying here for three months
and we haven't gotten the money. And by the way, typing like this with two fingers at that,
that, the ash keeps dropping into the keys. Yeah. Yeah. Anyway, apparently the petals of its legendary
flowers are rumored to cure everything from shingles to syphilis. So Lily and her brother McGregor,
played by Jack Whitehall, set out to pick, set out to pick some and take them home to the civilized
world. Reluctantly engaged to guide them is Frank Wolfdwayne Johnson, a big beefy buffoon of a
sea captain with a tramp steamer. They hate each other at first sight. Lily calls Frank Skippy to
annoy him. Frank annoys Lily and everyone else with gags like, we're we're heading into head hunter
territory. A terrible place to be headed. And then Pat, I swear to God in parentheses, Rex
Reed wrote, these are the jokes folks. He does a fly. You know, we would get along great with Rex
Reed. But we went drinking with Rex Reed. I was just going to say, I want to hang out and just drink
martinis with this guy like, yeah. If things get sexual, they get sexual. I mean, I against it.
We'll do a Jesus role situation where we take turns with Rex. Still they chug ahead
through typhoons, rapids, explosions, and countless distractions designed to make you forget that
there is no plot in the movie is going nowhere. The director, Wom Khaled Sarah, I think I'm saying
that correctly, seems to be making it up as he goes along. The villains are a 400 year old zombie
conquistador with snakes crawling out of every orifice. An evil German imitator of the Kaiser,
Jesse Plammans, who rules the Amazon from a submarine and a nasty thug with a talking cockatoo,
a wasted Paul Giamatti. I guess Giamatti is the cockatoo. I think, oh really? Yeah, I think he's
the voice of the cock. Well, maybe now maybe he's the thug. I don't know. I assumed he'd be the thug.
Otherwise, you'd say voiced by Giamatti. I know. That's a good point. Add an army of bees
and cannibals and you get the idea of how to drag a 20 minute theme park ride into nearly two hours of
cinematic tedium. Lily wants to use the two use the tears of the moon and its medicinal powers to
change the world. The German wants the flowers to help Germany rule the world. Everything is played for
laughs, including a ferocious computer generated tiger named proxima that turns out to be as timid as a
gingham cat. And even the cannibals who confess, they are really dress extras who hate their makeup and
complain about their costumes. This movie sounds insane, dude. I'm going to see it. Yeah.
Instead of thrills, this whole thing is played for laughs. Unfortunately, no one in the cast displays
any true sense of comedy timing, especially the roofily miscast, Dwayne Johnson, who is about as
funny as a knee replacement. All right. Go on. Go on. Last paragraph. Every scene in Jungle Cruz is
derived from another more original film. You'll spot familiar steals from Raiders of the Lost Ark to
pirates the Caribbean to the African Queen. But it took three writers to come up with the dismal jokes
from old Vegas nightclub X to its credit. Jungle Cruz has some admittedly watchable performances,
mainly Emily Blunt as the female Indiana Jones and a pitch helmet and safari jacket and by Jack
Whitehall, a rare gay character in a Walt Disney film. If you don't fall asleep, there's plenty to
look at, including action scenes, cram with special effects as well as lush rain forest played by Hawaii,
Australia, and wait for it at Lana, Georgia. As your review, that's a fucking review, man.
Ooh, I got to start reading more read. I'm going to follow him, man. I was like, why didn't I do this
before? I'm starting this. Yeah. Yeah, I'm going to go see the film. It sounds like maybe something I
got to watch. I didn't know Giamatti was involved. Why is he not always on billions? That's why. I
don't watch that show. So it seems like he hasn't been in a movie in years, but he's working steady. So
like, you know, that's that would have been a nice surprise. I think that's I guess what they were
trying to do. But anyway, all right. Freaky is the film today. Freaky is the film.
Joe, you want to walk us through the plot. The movie was written by Michael Kennedy and Christopher
Landon and directed by Landon, who did Happy Death Day, which was a similarly sort of
entertaining fun throwback to the days of like 90s horror. You want to walk us through, Joe,
there's an amulet. Of course, there's always an amulet. Well, it's a dagger. It's a dagger.
So the plot here is Vince von Plays. It plays a Jason type of serial killer. Michael Myers,
probably type of serial killer. Masked serial killer is the point. He prays on teenagers. It's classic.
You know, this is the 1980s and this is horror kind of stuff. Right. He ends up in the opening
and the cold open stealing a magic ritualistic dagger from the home of a collector of antiquities
where he murders the kids in that house and then steals a dagger and ends up using that dagger to
try and kill a new a new victim who's a young girl who's very sheepish and shy and very much
hasn't come out of her shell yet. And when he stabs her with it, they switch bodies and then
hence the title freaky. Obviously, a plan freaky Friday. The event of them switching bodies
happens on Friday the 13th in the movie. And it plays from there and it's Vince von
playing a 16 year old girl basically through the entire movie, which I loved. I
loved this movie. I thought it was fun from the jump. I thought they played every trope and every
cliche. It's a lot like scream to me. They're very aware of the tropes and cliches that happen in
these types of films. And they ham them up. And they're very self -effacing about them.
I liked the characters a lot. I cared about the characters a lot. You know, the basic plot
further, you know, past what I already said is obviously they've got to figure out how to get
the girl back into her own body before midnight of that night. Because if it passes midnight,
they're stuck in the other body forever. They learn. And the only way to do that is for her to get
the knife and stab her. It's kind of confusing, but it's for her inside Vince von's body to get
the knife and then stab the girl who the serial killer is occupying her body now. And that's the
only way they can switch. But it's a really, really funny film. Again, I cared about the characters.
I really, really like her. Her one male friend is a gay kid and he's the character is just so funny.
And they perfectly placed in a movie like this, by the way, because he got to say all the shit
that if you had a straight male saying it, he would have been an asshole. You know what I mean?
Right. But I love that the kid would be like, you know, you'd say pussy and the girl would be like,
don't say that word. And he go, girl, please, you know, like, is there any like almost like a pull in
kind of, right? I think her guy, he was really funny, man. And I cared about her friend to her
girlfriend. Like by the end of the movie, when those two kids were in danger, I was, I didn't want
to see them die. I was like, I'm going to be sad if these two kids get killed. It's hard to do that
in a horror movie. And it's not often done these days. You usually don't give a shit anymore
about it, you know, losing characters throughout the film. I thought it was a great, I thought it
presented a great commentary on gender. And it got it all kind of out in the open without being
what I thought was annoying or heavy -handed by wearing it on its sleeve. You know,
I love a message in a movie, but when the message is no matter what it is, it's too heavy -handed and too
transparent. It's annoying because you feel like you're just being lectured by a filmmaker at that
point. But this, I thought, did it really, really, really well? And I loved it. I loved it.
Yeah, I think I liked it a little less, but I had many of the same reactions. I thought it got
better as it went, steadily better and better, which is great. You know, don't get me wrong. But I
before Vince Vaughn comes on the scene, which, you know, he's got kind of a dialogueless performance
for the first half hour or so, and he's not in it very much. I was not that engaged. But Vince Vaughn
is completely invested in it in a way he hasn't been in a while. He seemed very bored recently
in his movies, and with good reason. They're pretty boring shitty movies. But he's having a blast
here when he gets to play The Teenage Girl. He does a similar thing to what Jack Black did in
Jumanji, which I thought was, I mean, he fucking stole the hell out of that movie. Jack Black is so
funny in that. And Vaughn is doing something similar. But he makes the right choice of not impersonating
a dumb teenage girl and just making fun of teenage girls in general. He's also not really impersonating
the girl from the movie. He's just, he picks a very specific way to play it. And it's a believable
character in a weird way you believe Vince Vaughn as a teenage girl. And he's got some really sweet
scenes too in particular that that I agree made you care way more about the characters than he normally
would in a slasher. The one is where he's in the changing room and he talks to his own mom, but he's
Vince Vaughn. Yeah. And the mom is, you know, going through a rough time and talk and she asks Vince Vaughn
out, but she's actually kind of asking her daughter out. And it's this very sweet moment where he kind of
tells her everything will be okay. That was a really touching movie. Our touch, sorry, touching scene
very well done. And then later kind of the highlight of the movie really is when he's in the back seat
of the car with the girl's crush. And the guy knows that Vince Vaughn is her. She's inside his body.
And they share this really sweet moment like he's able to kind of hit on, you know, tell tell tell
this crush how he feels because he's in this other body in a weird way. And they kiss and they actually
kiss, you know, they don't pull any punches. It is, you know, Michael Kennedy is a gay writer,
Christopher Lannon is a gay writer director. And you feel that too. They don't go for the cheap
jokes of guy and a girl's body. They don't go with like Vince Vaughn kisses him and then it's like,
you what am I doing in all this stuff? You know, it's a very sweet touching moment.
I think I thought they missed, I thought they missed a great joke opportunity there though. I like
that they kissed. It was really sweet. But then they stop. And they stop because Vince Vaughn's like,
let's maybe do this when my whole hand doesn't cover your face, whatever, which is funny. But I just
thought they missed an opportunity to make a joke there about like, this is technically illegal. Or
you know what I mean? Like something because of his age, whatever. But whatever. That's nitpicking.
But yeah, I agree. I think that a lot of actors could have taken this role and played it
disrespectfully in the sense of like, I'm just going to play it like, like some kind of airhead
teen, which the her character is not by any stretch. But I think that wouldn't have changed the
approach that a lot of actors would have taken to it because they wouldn't have known how to do it.
Vince Vaughn actually finds like the truth like the like the real essence of a teen. He finds innocence.
He finds the innocence in it. Yeah. And the and the figure that a teenager has. In turn,
she is great from going from this like sheepish nerdy innocent, wonderful kid to like this really
sinister like she plays dark really, really, what's her name? I'm sorry because this is the first
thing I ever saw her in. So I didn't know what her name was. Catherine Newton, it says she's in three
billboards. I don't really remember her blockers, which was a pretty funny movie. She's been in some
stuff, but no real breakout. But she's she's great. So they're both really, really good in this. And then
also what's his face? Alan Ruck. Alan Ruck from Ferris Pure playing up just a prick, which I've never
seen him play an asshole before, which was fun. He does on succession. He's a really great character
and he gets the best death in the movie, just a really gross. He gets slashed on the old
wood shop table saw. It's cut in half. There's good kills. You know, it this felt to me
and I think we're going to be seeing a lot more of these as we get older. It felt like an homage
to the 90s horror, you know, like the screen. I don't think it's anywhere near a scream level
personally, but there was that second tier of movies that were funny and scary. And, you know,
they weren't all perfect, but like the faculty, I know what you did last summer, that kind of stuff.
It has that sort of fun feeling to it. The comedy works, the horror works, the kills are good.
Kills are brutal. I got to I got to hand them the Vince, the cold open kills, yeah, are brutal.
Like they're really violent. They're intense. And I was like, this is cool that they're really
when it's got to be raw, it gets raw. And then when it's funny, it's really funny, but it's funny
in the way a good sitcom is funny, because the characters themselves have personalities and are
distinctive and are funny, not because of dumb gags and whatever. You know, so very well done. That's
and then there's I thought it was great that too, after they switch bodies back and all as well,
there's like another seven minutes, you know, twist again, ending where you find out Vince Vaughn's
not dead and he's still alive and he goes to the house and you get to see the girl. And I thought
this was actually really endearing and really sweet because when she's in the car, she says to the guy,
when she's in Vince's body, she says to the guy she loves is in love with. I, you know,
I, it's nice to feel strong for once. When everybody pushes you around your whole life,
whenever it feels good to be in a body where you're actually literally strong. Right. And the killer
and the girl's body at one point can't punch through a door to hurt somebody and she goes,
this body is fucking useless. And it's a very interesting commentary on literal strength versus
inner strength and all that sort of thing, which is a big topic these days. And I thought it
was really nice that at the very end of the movie, they let you, you got to see her face off in her own
body against the actual killer and his and she outwits him and wins. And you're like, they just
really did a nice job with it, man. And it's a Blumhouse movie. Blumhouse, you know, we've talked about
the Blumhouse is usually putting this shit so on the table in front of you. Yeah, we're like,
we get it guys, you know, uh, this was really, really, really well done, man. And I never saw
happy death day, but now I want to go back and watch it because I really liked what the writer and
director did with this. Happy death day is much like this. It's about five times better and more
clever than it needed to be. It's riffing on the standard Groundhog Day formula that Palm Springs did
and many, many movies do, but they're both really fun. I think this is almost guaranteed a sequel
as well. I think we'll be getting even freaky here at some point. And it's six million bucks, you know,
at a time where your average movie is a hundred and fifty million. It just goes to show that you can
make something infinitely more entertaining than your average big bloated summer action movie for
not much cash. And I hope that they return to making these kind of great little horror comedies
because they're fun and they make money. It tripled its budget. Good for them. I agree. And if for
nothing else, like I think, I think this might be like, this is kind of Vince Vaughn's third act he's
beginning now. Yeah. And he's had a great first two acts. But if I remember in fairness, if we're
going to say all these like, Annie Potts still looks great. Vince Vaughn doesn't look great.
No, he looks like he's been drinking for 35 years. That was the first thing I texted you.
I go, Vince Vaughn looks like dead. There's like a, there's an ashy quality to his face. Like,
it's like, yeah. And it's not just for the movie. If you see him in anything anymore, you're right.
He looked great and he looked, he looked pretty good in brawl and so block. And then after that,
it was like, that was it. Yeah. Well, he's like, he's like, you are I always barely keeping it
together. And yeah. And that's why we love him. You know, I love the guy. But he, I think this is
a third act because if you remember the end of Vince Vaughn's first act, he was doing some movies like
the cell and whatever that were very forgettable. And you were just kind of like, I don't know, man,
like. And then all of a sudden, he did old school. Yeah. And there he was, not in the lead,
supporting character where he got to do his Vince Vaughn thing and it was awesome.
And then that went for a while. And then it tapered off. Then it started to be like movies like
the internship. And you know, and you're like, all right, this is, you know, but now I feel like his
third act is relaunched, which started with these Craig Zahler flicks that are amazing.
And seeing him in this was like seeing him in old school. I was like, this is so cool. It was like
so great to see him again in a supporting role where he was really fucking funny again. Like,
I hadn't seen him be funny in so long, you know. And he's, yeah, funny. He's one of the, I would
argue that Vince Vaughn could be the funniest actor working right now. He's a period. He's just a
hilarious guy. So it was really nice to see him there. And again, like, I felt like it's his third
act now. He's doing a lot of these like indie low budget passion project movies that work for him.
And he's doing great with them, you know. Yeah, I would imagine his team saw what happened with
McConaughey. And we're like, that's got to be your path. You know, just just get in there, do the
work. You're going to make about one 20th of what you used to make, but you'll start getting the
respect back. And then you'll, you know, I would not be surprised if in five years time Vaughn is back
in the A list, you know, he's just that kind of guy that you're root for. And he's got the talent. Yeah.
Anyway, folks, two hogs up, right? For free. For sure. Yes. And that's our episode. Next episode,
we are going to be discussing the film old M Night Shyamalan's latest romp. Until then, we thank you
all for your support. We thank you all for listening. We thank you, Emily, for taking care of business as
you always do. Thanks for sticking with us through this journey. I'm Joe DeRosa, comedy at Instagram
and Twitter. You can hear me on my buddy Scott Weinberg's fantastic over hated podcast where he discusses
movies that are hated. And we decided, are they, are they deserving of that claim? And my favorite
segment of it was it goes through all the movies released the month of it. And you say, is it better or
worse than this? And with ours, Freddie got fingered, he's gone through all these movies of the time. And
I was like, God, yeah, that's a piece of shit. That's way worse than this. So even like he goes through
notoriously hated movies. And what you come away with is learning that there's way worse movies,
even just in the weeks surrounding its release, but movies get that like Ishtar, Ishtar is funny,
but it has this reputation and it sticks with it forever. Really cool podcast. Check it out,
Patreon only. And I also was on the Texas Forever podcast, which is a Friday night lights episode by
episode pod. Check that out as well. We will see you next time for old. And we will see you in hell.