Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Hello everybody and welcome to We'll see you in hell now proudly hosted on the head
gum network. What it is, folks, is a loose conversational, often heated accusatory podcast
between two dear friends, myself, Patrick Walsh, and over here to my right, Mr. Joe
DeRosa, say hello, Joe. Hello, Joe. That's starting real strong. And we talk about, generally,
a horror or a sci -fi movie each week. And it veers off into all kinds of different tangents
and also segments that we still don't quite understand what the rules of them are, even
though we created them.
Yes.
So now, without further ado, on with the show and on with the Joe.
How are you, Walsh?
I'm good.
I threw in kind of a disbelieving chuckle into that one.
Can you believe I'm doing this?
That was.
That was a very, it was almost a gargamelish delivery of the on with the Joe.
I enjoyed it though very much.
He's a big influence of mine, Gargamel.
I was about to say to Joe and I said, you know what, hit record and let's, let's talk about
it on the podcast.
I'm not going to get deep into this, folks, but Joe and I had not just tonight, but also earlier
in the week.
A couple homedingers of fights and these were not funny fights
This is in fact if I may say the second take of this episode
Because Joe and I really went at it and we're not gonna get into specifics because that may have been what led to the problem last time
But boy do the two of us go at it when I was gonna say to Joe is that I think
Much in the same way that if you've ever been out with a couple that hates each other and I have many many many times
Right, you know it's a I recently read that you know you're in a good relationship if your partner
Compliments you in public and to other people and I was like that makes sense. I was thinking about Heather
You know that's her to a tee and so you know I do it as well. Well, you know Heather's great at that. Heather does it
Whatever yeah
But the flip side of that and I've been in and observed these relationships is when there's so little communication in the relationship
that the second they go to dinner with another couple,
they use it to criticize the other to the couple.
Yeah, yeah.
So it'll be like, oh, that's so nice that Carol
makes your bed in the morning.
I mean, I can't get Heather to lift a fucking finger
around our house.
We get dinner and then it's usually
with a couple drinks in the mix.
And then on the way home, then you're driving
and it's like, oh, so I heard you didn't like the way
I make the bed or whatever.
And so it's a way, it's a very extremely passive
of aggressive way of getting out things.
And somehow, when we clicked on the podcast today,
it brought out a lot of like deep -seated little irritants
and aggressions, and they all just came tumbling out
because it's a safe space.
We always fight in the podcast, but today took a turn.
It took a dark turn.
It took a turn.
I will not get into it any deeper than you did.
We should.
Uh, I shouldn't. The one, the one detail that I think we can both laugh about right now is something I exclaimed at Pat, uh, after we stopped recording and Pat was leaving and I did, I did, I did exclaim the sentence to him, you walk out that door.
You're, you're making a statement about this show and our friendship. You're making, if you walk on that door, you're making a statement about not just this show, but also.
So this friendship to which even in the heat of anger, I almost laughed, but it was serious.
It was a serious exclamation.
But my hats off to my boy, Pat, my sweet boy is, uh, we often say, uh, he texted me.
He said, Hey, man, Olive branch.
I said, Olive branch right back at you.
He said, you want me to come back?
We'll do a J and we'll do the show and folks we've done a J.
We smoked a bit of something that Pat brought over here and I am I am I don't even know what's happening right now to be honest with you
He said be careful. It's strong. It's real strong. We'll be good and you know
I recently watched a video that almost moved me to tears of a of a gentleman an old gentleman middle -aged who had
Extreme I believe Parkinson's but like you know way beyond Michael J. Fox and he was he could not control his body and to me
that and any sort of mental disorder, nerve disorder,
Alzheimer's, et cetera, is my biggest fear.
I can't think about it, or I go and say it.
And this man is sitting there,
and he cannot control, like his arm is up over his head,
and you can just see in his face, he's like, kill me.
I don't want to live like this.
He takes one hit of a joint,
and his arm just kind of slowly comes down,
another puff, and then he's sitting there just like you were I.
Really?
And, you know, I went out and voted yesterday,
and L .A. had a lot of big things, I voted of course, one of the bills was, do we want to help the
homeless and you could vote yes or no? Really? And like, it was kind of close, you know?
There were a lot of crazy things, but I also went to just vote to support fucking marijuana
and the taxation and making money and the cities are all doing really well off it, but I was like,
this is an important fucking issue. And it helps, I never got on antidepressants, I probably should,
I've been told that by several people, including a licensed therapist, but for me, I'll tell you I'm on and I don't know that you need, you know, they can go in either direction. I'll be honest with you.
For me, and then I've been dominating and I'll turn it right over to you.
The weed, if I am mad or angry, if Heather and I get in a little tiff about something or whatever, because of the way I was raised where my dad would walk ten feet ahead of my family on vacations
because he would get angry with us right and then just not engage with us for
the remainder of the vacation. Griswold style. Oh that you know everybody says
oh that guy's my dad just because your dad's a nerd and so's Clark Griswold
no I it's my dad because of the anger and the screaming and fussing at the
family and the barely contained rage and etc. That's why that's one of my
all -time favorite movies right now for me I could be that and I recognize that
in myself. I can't talk about things sometimes. And even though I apologize without the influence
of drugs and we patched it up, the weed just helps you stop thinking about it. Because
I'll be like, he said this. I'll drive myself insane. And it's a big mental help. It
calms me down. There are times I get home from work and I'm so wound up, I'm just going
off, not going off on my girlfriend, but I'm yelling about my day and complaining. And she'll
but want to make love, make sweet love.
And I can't get my mind there
because I'm still in the angry place.
So even though we're sitting on the couch,
I'm going like something in my head.
I'm cursing to myself.
So then when she wants to get a little frisky
and who could blame her.
I don't blame her.
I can't get my mind there.
I know if I go downstairs
I'm gonna be like still in that other place.
One puff and it's worked like a charm now
since the day I first tried it.
I'm there, I'm in the zone.
I love it.
It's a beautiful substance.
I'd like to say that I'm glad that we have smoked it.
I'd hate to think our tips were anything to get
between you and some love -making.
And I agree with you.
I can't think about anything that happened today.
All I can do is try to convince myself
my chair's not moving right now.
And I know it's not moving, but it feels like it's moving.
I mean, it's good.
It helps kind of just wipe away the shit sometimes.
We, I absolutely agree.
And it's legal now until Trump takes it away.
Yeah.
We are talking today and we're not going to get into the movie just yet.
We're going to discuss Logan, everybody's new favorite comic book movie.
But the only reason I bring up what we're discussing or what movie we're discussing already
is because Pat and I saw this film last night in the theater together and a kind of a rare
occurrence.
It is. I would like you because we did we did get this story out on the first
Take it this podcast and it's a it this was a nice story. It was funny then as well, but uh, yes, Joe
Um
And I for whatever reason because we both love movies and we both live five minutes from a theater
Don't go to a lot of movies together. We go to a ton of movies. Just not always together
And I think it's been split recently and then
maybe the last one was spy, which is over a year ago.
So, yes, which is kind of,
without making a lot of fanfare,
a bit of a special occasion.
Yeah.
So we go up to see Logan, and I'm sitting there,
and I realize about five minutes in.
I don't know if I can go to any more movies with Joe.
I've sit in there, and he's heavily sighing,
almost from the word go, like a whew.
He's crossing and uncrossing his legs like there's no tomorrow.
Tell him what you ordered first, Joe.
Tell him what you ordered.
We got to the, Pat was nice enough to buy the tickets.
Thank you for that.
I owe you.
You don't.
You know, but next one's on me in nine months.
Yes, that sounds good.
Whenever we go to see the next movie, but we, so we, Joe, you entered in a bad place, which
might have led you to that concessions. We were, I was in a, well, yeah, we got in.
I padded paint for the tickets. I said, can I treat you to something at the concession
sand? Pat said, no, I don't want anything. And he said, are you going to get anything?
And I said, yeah. And he said, what? And I said, I'm going to go real, real hard at this
right now. I'm not in a good spot right now. I was not in a good way yesterday. So I ordered
a popcorn, a cherry coke, and a bag of peanut M &Ms that had the words share size on it.
That's beyond king. That's like the king's like, you know, let's put some of this away for tomorrow. I'm done.
But you're eating beyond the king's share.
Now, and he did not share, folks. I didn't get, I didn't get peanut M &M one.
Now tell me because we talked about this earlier the butter what happened with the butter because I sort of remember
But you described it better well Joe and I were having conversation like you do in line and then the guy behind the counters
Like sir, what can I get you and Joe's like yeah this this and a popcorn and Joe turns to talk to me
So he's got his back to the popcorn guy and the guy goes sir
Do you want butter and Joe without looking back over his shoulder at the man goes he had a lot of butter
I hope you got it. I hope it was a buttery bag. They did. They soaked it up. Uh, we sat
down in the, in the, uh, in the row there to watch the movie. Uh, I dumped the entire
sharing size bag of peanut M &M's into the popcorn, thinking they would blend because I've
heard of, you know, I saw him like whiplash, Paul Reiser mixes the raisin. That's what it,
with the popcorn. It seems delicious. Was it delicious? It was delicious. I like the salty
on a sweet. It was a perfect combination of salty and sweet. You had salty buttery popcorn
meeting the chocolate in the M &M meeting the peanut, which also was salty. It was wonderful.
But those candy coated shells, I mean, you get butter on them. It felt like it felt like
used anal beads in the bag there. They was disgusting. You really paint a picture? It was real nasty.
Yeah, but it was delicious. I mean, and yeah, this is like use anal beads in the
Look who amongst us hasn't pulled out a string and then maybe you clean it up before you put it back in the drawer
Am I wrong?
You're not rock you're not rock folks. I've never done that my favorite
I might have a string in right now one of my favorite David tell jokes of all time ever is when he goes
when he goes why do anal beads come in so many different colors when they always come out brown
Yeah, it's a great bit. I'll my mom. I love that one the
But this is how bad of a spot. I was in last night wash. I I had so much shit stuffed into this bag
Yeah, and I and then I also the extra butter that I asked were I was like
there's no way this bag can hold this mess and
and I didn't care.
I'm usually very OCD about spots on my shirt.
I get up, I'll scrub it something
in a bathroom in a restaurant.
If I spill it forever, I just didn't care.
I said, let me wear my mess like a scarlet letter.
And I got home and sure enough,
just stains all over my clothes,
didn't treat it, just threw it in the wash,
didn't give a shit at all.
I mean, Joe Kim walking up, it was like,
I'm parking down at the Del Taco,
So, which is probably a half mile away, it comes up just looking like just a man who had
just been beaten to shit by life waiting in the crosswalk.
But as he did yesterday, I mean he's sighing, the leg crossing, and it's called the Vista
Theater here in Los Filos.
It's a beautiful old -timey theater, and you couldn't find more legroom at a theater, like
it's a big stretch out place.
The one issue is that the seats while comfortable are all a join to each other so when there's movement you feel it
So especially sitting next to him Joe is rocking in his chair and leaning forward and leaning back and sign
Then at one point he starts bouncing his foot really furiously and it couldn't have been more than a minute or two
But it was driving me insane and as I'm about to say something to him the woman next to him leans over and is like would you stop doing that?
And afterwards Joe's like could you believe that bitch next to me?
And I was like, yeah, she was right.
She was absolutely right.
And then folks, where it really hit its pinnacle
and something I've never heard in a movie theater before,
certainly not for someone I'm sitting with,
at about the two -hour mark, Jogo's,
like a baby -blowing raspberries,
like an old man who's just like, had enough.
And I'm trying, I was into the fucking movie.
I was enjoying it, but it's like when somebody is hating something so visibly and audibly next to you
There's like a heat that was coming off of Joe and it didn't ruin my enjoyment, but I was like
We're gonna have a good conversation about this because I really liked it and you know spoiler alert Joe did not
But we'll get to that soon
I
Logan and and we will get to that soon Logan is one of the few movies that I have actually taken notes and
and put them into my phone.
Oh, okay.
When I was driving home from the theater last night,
I had so many thoughts racing through my head
that I was like, I have to put notes down,
because if I don't put notes down,
I'm gonna sound like I'm just being a hater on the movie.
I'm not being a hater like I have legitimate gripes.
All right, but we will get to it.
There was to it.
You told now, I'm trying to recapture
or some of the magic of the last take before it exploded.
The tragic, you told a story about a woman in a theater.
Oh, that's right, because I made a joke when I said,
if you thought the row was shaking when I was shaking my leg,
did you feel what was happening?
Oh yeah, the late next one started getting finger -banked
and you said, are you serious?
I said, no, and then you told a story about.
Yes, I was asking, you know, he said that lady
had no right to complain. It seemed like she was getting finger bang next to me and I said,
are you serious? He was like, what are you talking about? And I said within the last year
because the film was Jason Bourne. So the latest Jason Bourne, I'm sitting in the back row with my
buddy and there was nobody in the back row. Then about halfway through this young, and I mean young,
like 18, 19, a couple comes in and the girls wearing a full blanket, like a robe. And we're like,
this is weird. They sit next to us and then almost immediately we realize that she's getting
fingered. Her head is tilted all the way back in orgasmic pleasure. And my buddy hits
me and he's like, check this out. And he's like, oh, and like switches his seat, which is
a very different stance than I would take. I'm trying to watch what's happening. Sure.
So I'm looking down there. And then sure enough, once she gets hers, she disappears under
of that blanket. And she's down there sucking this kid off full BJ in the back row of Jason
born of BJ at J B Jason. And then I went back on a little reminiscent of a hand job
I received on a double feature of a mid -summer night stream. There's nothing better than it
starring Kevin Klein and 10 things I hate about you. There's nothing better than getting
a hand job in the theater especially when it's to a bad double feature like yeah yeah that makes it
all worthwhile it's right except that about the same with like you know roadhead or something
there they're hits a point where you're like well now I'm gonna just come all over her arm here
in a movie theater it's listen I and I don't mean to be crashed we're already there I just realized
what I just casually said I will say this and it's always been my complaint about uber culture LA is
New York is yellow cap culture.
Sure.
Still?
Well, at least there was about a year ago.
This was the difference.
And that was the big difference when I moved out here.
It wasn't a yellow cap culture, it was an Uber culture.
And Uber's great and it's convenient and Lyft is convenient and great and they're affordable
and all that stuff.
But my one gripe can't get a good fingering going on in the back of an Uber.
That's very true.
I've always said the back of a yellow cap is like international waters.
I mean, anything goes back there, you're getting hand jobs.
There's fingerings.
there's, there's PJs, there's, there's kind of lings, there's all kinds of shit happening
in those back seats.
I mean, I've seen taxi cab confessions, I think you could, you probably could do it in
a lift.
If I were a lift and Uber driver, I would be patiently waiting for somebody to get blown
in the back of my cab.
Well, the difference with it is your car, though, I guess that's what I was going to say.
The, the, the, the lifts guy got to put his groceries there tomorrow.
Yeah.
Whereas the other, the yellow cab guy just goes back like De Niro, I have to hose the come
them off the seat.
Right.
Or whatever.
I tweeted about this the other day, and it was no joke.
I was in an Uber to an Oscar party, and I'm sitting in the back seat with a car seat
with something in it, which I already felt kind of like, you don't bring your baby or whatever
it is in a cab.
It's weird.
And then put it in the back seat with the potentially creepy purvy passenger.
You know, it seemed very fucked up.
But I get in, and this thing is covered tightly with towels and blankets.
like there's no air getting in and what was coming from it was not a human baby sleeping it was like a
Like a snorty sort of flimmy weird sound coming from it and as he's about to drop me off
I was like I can't get out of this cab and not ask because then I could convince myself
Maybe it was a chihuahua or something right so I go hey man
I got to ask you is this a baby or a pet back here asleep and he looked up looked me in the eye in the rear view mirror
and then did not answer my question.
Oh, that's, that's, watch, I'm gonna be honest with you.
That's the worst ending to the story that it could have been.
I know.
I'm nervous now.
I was picturing like the eraser head baby.
Yeah, I'm almost like a warm type baby.
It's an unsettling story.
I hated it.
But like, what a great start to like a new David Lynch.
I mean, it freaked me out.
I went in this Oscar party for 30 minutes.
They were like, hey, you all right, man.
I was like, yeah, just a little shaken up about my,
my cab ride over here.
So yeah, yeah, yeah, you're, yeah, yeah.
Was Robert, I just keep picturing Robert Blake
as the cab driver.
Yeah, he's, well, it wasn't him driving it,
but then his eyes did appear in the rear view mirror.
Let's talk about him for a second and David Lynch
in the film, lost highway.
Watch 20 minutes of it last night.
Then I realized I wouldn't be able to sleep,
so I started off.
I don't understand how a man, David Lynch, makes another man, Robert Blake, looks so
terrible.
And this is Beretta for Christ's sake.
I know.
There's that scene at the end where he's walking towards the guy with the gun.
It's one of the scariest things I've ever seen, and you're seeing, they're going, it's just
Robert Blake.
Why am I so scared?
Yeah.
But something about white powder on his face and it, God damn, it's fucking freaky.
I love that movie, but Lynch has a way with that that like if only if only every horror movie had one tenth of like the
Dread that he can put into like a scene of just like going to the store. Yes, but that scene that we might have discussed this on here
Years ago or a couple years ago was at the Winkies
Diner in Mulholland Drive when they go out and that
Just a homeless man. I guess comes out from behind that dumpster to this day
Like talking about it now, I just felt my heart kind of skip a beat because that scared me so fucking much it is
My all -time number one scariest thing I've ever seen ever in a movie
Yeah, I think we'll ever top it as far as I know I agree and if you really look at it on the surface. It is a
stupidly dressed almost like in a bad play homeless man
Yeah stepping out from behind a dumpster in broad daylight and even if you saw it five feet for me
you'd be like, oh, excuse me, sir.
But something about Lynch and the sound and everything
is, it's terrifying.
Mahal and Drive is one of my favorite movies ever made.
The bill, I love Mahal and Drive.
It's in my top Lynch films without question
and number one for me.
It's, it might, you know what, I think you're right.
I think it is my number one Lynch film.
Blue Velvet is killer, but it doesn't stay with you.
And sometimes when I don't get a movie,
I'm like, I guess I'm stupid, I go to bed.
And I don't care.
I saw it and I was like I need to figure this out and I did and I could talk about it for like three days. I think it's a great movie. Yeah. In fact that in the last
Ty were the only two Lynch movies I own so uh oh and I own Firewall with me which I like very much love fire
Walk with me, but yeah, it's the build up in that scene. He shoots it Lars von Trier has an ability to do the same thing
Yeah, they just make this completely
Horrifying suspenseful build out of almost nothing that the even the slightest payoff is devastating
You know, and that that's what he does
It's just the guy and you know, it's funny like the guy that that is
really responsible for that scene working so well as the guy telling the story
about the dream and he's just so terrified. Oh, yeah. And it's just
Fishlor or something. Yeah, madman. I love that guy. I mean, you know, I
remember seeing him in old school and being like, oh, that's the guy from lost
Arbina from my home drive. Like he can't possibly be normal. And it's like,
no, he is. He's just a normal guy. He's just really good in that scene. No, I
felt the same thing. He's just one of those roles where you're like, well, I can
never see this guy. It's like that molester and happiness, which we always talk
about. I see him in like a Harrison Ford movie. I'm like, Harrison is guy's gonna
molest you. I can't shake it. Well, I knew he, here's what saved him for me, Dylan Baker. Yeah.
I knew Dylan Baker first and foremost from the film Delirious with John Candy. Of course,
he's, he's exposed to the toxic waste and he's falling apart. Yeah. Yeah. And he's really funny
in that. So he'll always be that guy to me first. Thankfully. That's a strange movie, Delirious.
I really like it but it's not good yeah, you know, I'd have to rewatch it. I recently rewatch
summer rental. It's terrible. Well, I love that so much as a kid. I mean, John Candy was all
that mattered to me when I was a kid. And there is some funny stuff in it. Most notably when he realizes
he's in the black family's cabin. Yes. So when he comes down with that like 200 pound bag of dog
Kibble right and then it as he's about to leave with it it breaks all over the floor
Then he slips in it and seems to genuinely fall and then the dog starts eating the Kibble
And they cut to the family staring at him and like his kind of fumbling explanation for it
What what can you did in almost all those movies your Uncle Buck your plans trying to et cetera is if you really think about it the
Office years later that kind of and it's become the dominant thing of like single -camera comedy is that stuttering like oh
I'm sorry, yeah, you know over explaining and right that was him to a tea like that scene was really funny
But the end of the movie is a 25 -minute boat race with no jokes. Yeah, I know
It's not a good movie. I looked it up. I watched it recently. I thought we you know last summer or whatever. Yeah
Because I was just tell you about it. I thought it's the summertime. It'll be fun to watch summer rental
Put it on. I was like
like, God damn, I don't think this is a good movie.
And then I looked it up and it had like a 30 % on Rotten Tomatoes
from the Retro reviews they pulled up or whatever.
And I was like, oh, I guess maybe it's a,
I do enjoy the scene that you talked about.
I also enjoy when he takes the two eggs on his drive to work
in the first one's hard boiled.
And then he breaks the second one and it's raw.
And he's like, it's my fault, it's my fault.
Should have said hard boiled, I didn't say it.
It's just two eggs, you know, that part's funny.
And let me tell you, especially knowing 80s scripts.
Here's what that said in the script.
He cracks one egg, it's a hard boiled egg.
He cracks the second egg, it puts the yolk on them.
Like I think back in those days, they were like,
John, what should you take this next scene?
Like he seems to be making up all of his dialogue
in almost everything.
Look, one of my favorite John Caini jokes ever
is in a movie we've discussed many times.
Who's Harry Crumb?
Sure.
And it's, there's nothing funny about it, at all, on paper, at all.
And I don't even know if it was on the paper because it's so odd.
But he's on the bus, he's got a bag of cherries and a diet coke.
Yeah.
I remember it well.
So odd that he's eating this as his snack.
Yeah.
And then he offers a lady of cherry and then a sip of coke and he goes, make some gau, yeah,
a cherry coke.
And he starts cackling like a lunatic.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean he's a guy who was like this script is terrible. I'm going to I'm going to make it funny. You know that was
Karen Kilgarif
Hate it much like I much like I hold tower highest over your head. Yes
She anytime I say anytime we disagree in a movie. She's like well, you did like who's Harry crumbs?
I don't understand how anybody doesn't like that film. It's hilarious
You know that was supposed I might have said this before in this pod if I did forgive me
but that was supposed to be like a big series.
That was supposed to be like an Austin Powers,
I sure wish it had been.
Series, you know, where he was solving crimes
in every movie or whatever.
That's the same.
I loved armed and dangerous as a kid.
Eugene Levy, baby.
When that part where like they dress up like the leather,
when Eugene Levy dressed up like the leather guy
and then John Candy gets in the drag,
I mean, that used to fucking devastate me.
I recently bought it for like two bucks and can't wait to watch. It's Harold Ramus and Levy and Meg Ryan and candy
I'm sure it's got some laughs in it. Yeah, and the guy from
Dune is in it the guy that plays Meg Ryan's dad is the guy in
The David Lynch Dune that plays the guy with the the postials all the way
Boydune would be my absolute least favorite David Lynch. I hated it. That's not that couldn't be further than my thing is Dune
One of the most insulting things that I've ever seen is I was watching up behind the scenes
on Dune recently on YouTube and Harlan Ellison, the writer, I'm a fan of, but he says stuff
that's, you know, hurtful, I would say to people.
Sure.
They're interviewing him and he goes, and he goes, he's raving about the cast.
He's raving about the cast.
And then he goes, Kyle McLaughlin, he was fine.
He was competent.
He did not have the chops that these other actors had and then he starts going through all the and he goes
He did a perfectly fine job
But he did not have the chops of and he starts rattling off every actor and then the last one he goes even sting
How wonderful is sting in this film stings terrible in that film and I was like what a kick in the goddamn teeth to somebody
I bet McLaughlin never got over that
but McLaughlin's lucky he's had a fucking 30 year career
saying that he's a middling talent at best.
I am a McLaughlin.
I'm a McLaughlin fit.
For Twin Peaks alone, the guy will have me.
He destroyed Twin Peaks.
He was so fucking funny in that first season of Twin Peaks.
I take it back.
I love him in the ad and, of course, Blue Mel,
but I take it back.
Yeah, I'll take those eggs over hard.
Yeah, I know what you're saying, but hard.
Yeah, hard.
Old habits die hard.
It is hard as I want those yolks.
Yeah, he's awesome.
I got really excited when they released that little teaser
of like the first reveal of handway and the new one.
Yeah, not wait.
Yeah, that was cool.
It's coming soon.
When, because they keep saying coming soon,
I feel like the Goddamn thing's been in production
for three fucking years.
I think it's coming this summer actually.
Like maybe May even.
It has literally been like three years since it was announced.
Yeah, but then he wanted more money
and he wanted to do 20 and he wanted this and that
and things got really held up.
I remember one of the first meetings I ever, ever, ever had
when I moved to L .A. was at showtime.
It was just a general.
And I remember in that meeting,
the person I was meeting with telling me about
twin peaks is even better than we thought it was gonna be.
And she didn't give me details, obviously.
But she was like,
and I believe it was right around the time
they were talking about how Lynch came back
and all that stuff.
So that's how fucking long it's been.
That she was talking to me in like,
like the time where he's back and it's going to be great.
That was three fucking years ago.
I mean, I just hope it's like a new awesome case or something.
I don't want to, I don't necessarily need more
of Laura Palmer because I get it, you know.
Well, she's in it.
So I think it's going to be more of Laura Palmer.
She's in the cast list in both roles.
Okay.
Well, the cousin's still alive, right?
Yeah, that's true.
So I guess she's going to play the cousin and write,
all right, who knows?
I mean, I'm very intrigued.
and it's got a cast of like 200 people.
There's some weird names in that cast.
Yeah, it's a very weird name.
My buddy is in it.
My buddy J. Larson is in it.
Yes.
That's what I'm saying.
He's in it and here's my one concern with the cast and these shows do this man and true detective
did it and I'm a fan of everybody that was in true detective season two.
I was not a fan of season two, but the orgy at the mansion was a good episode.
I didn't see that one that was a later one. It was really good. It was a very
Macatams heavy episode but they go the first season does well and it's a very
bare bones kind of thing and it's stripped out and then season two comes and
they go now we're gonna add all these people what scares me now they worked for
wet hot they did a good job with that and it all worked out but what scares me a
little bit about the new twin peaks is there's like a hundred new people that are
all famous. Well, but what's cool to me is that they're like, it's not like George Clooney's
dropping by Twin Peaks. You know, they're like weird names. It's not, it's not Adelisters.
Right. And everyone I saw was like probably some weird friend of David Linger.
I'll tell you what I'm excited about. Robert Forster. Love. I thought he's now playing the sheriff.
What's the sheriff's name? He's got a famous Miguel Ferrer. No, no, no, no. That guy died. He
He does.
Sadly enough, but I think he shot his stuff before he died.
Oh, okay.
Oh, he's playing the, uh, the other guy who died.
Who's the, no, no, no, no, who's the, the main sheriff in the show that works with
Comic -Gogg and then it's like a famous person's name.
And that's like one of the greatest.
There he is, Trim.
Yes.
Yeah.
He's playing him.
That role was originally offered to Farster.
Farster turned it down.
They gave it to the other guy.
They do the, the now sequel series.
They go back to the actor that played him.
He says, no, I don't want to do it.
Really, they go to Robert Forster. He's like, yeah, I'll do it. So now they have the guy in the role that was originally supposed to play the role
What a dream that would be to pass on Twin Peaks. It becomes this huge phenomenon
Forster did find for himself, but I bet part if he was me, that's all I do for 30 years is kick myself and then you get to play it
They come to you later. Yeah, it's great. It's great. It's great. I'm sure it's been discussed on this show so many so many times
but I watched
I watched my my movie that like if I see it's on on the TV guide
I don't even go to it because if I watch 30 seconds of Jackie Brown
I'm in till the end. Yeah, I think it's my favorite Tarantino. I think it's edge above pulp fiction
Heather my girlfriend comes out of the bedroom the other night and walks out
She's like sits down. She's there for an hour 30 past her bedtime. It's just like
It is so good and everything about it is perfect and the ending of it
But still makes me very, very sad, like in a way that you're not expecting watching
that movie.
It's a wonderful film.
I think that I would have a hard time choosing between those first three, you know,
Reservoir Dogs, Pulp Fiction and Jackie Brown to me are also captivating in very different
ways.
Yeah.
And they're wonderful, wonderful.
Jackie Brown is probably, in my opinion, the most quotable or the most fun to quote out
of all three of them.
and it's maybe my favorite Sam Jackson performance.
He's awesome in it.
Because you know what I love about Sam Jackson
on that movie?
It's exactly like the dynamic between
Pesci and Goodfellas to Casino.
Yeah.
It's, but to the narrow.
No, no, no, it's because like Sam Jackson
from Pulp Fiction to Jackie Brown to me
is like Joe Pesci from Goodfellas to Casino.
They're very similar characters,
but the second one is so much darker in such subtle ways
that like it's it sticks with you harder. You know what I mean? Yeah, I mean, especially
because at that time, De Niro was not the joke he's been for the last 20 years. Like you
never would have imagined De Niro doing a dirty grandpa back then. You just couldn't have
even dreamed it. Good Lord. Analyze this or meet the parents when he dips. He chose very
carefully with these comedies and he was amazing in the butt. At that time, he was still like
like the shit, he's coming off heat and he plays this like stupid, like high tempered guy
and Samuel Jackson is mopping up the floor with at that time the greatest actor alive.
Right.
And that's De Niro's choice.
De Niro's like, I'm going to let you have this scene, I'm playing a different character.
But Jackson, like, you imagine if the two fought, De Niro wouldn't stand a fucking chance.
That's how powerful Jackson comes up from that.
Jackson cuts glass through that whole movie facial hair is great
He's fantastic it. He's fantastic that that scene where he brings the nearer out and he's like and he opens the trunk
And he's like that's Beaumont. Yeah, now if you know Beaumont you know Beaumont ain't gonna do no 20 years
Yeah, you know what I mean that whole thing. Yes, but just when he shuts the trunk and he turns and he goes now Vincent
If you're gonna come in with me on that like he takes this tone of like a
a grade school teacher, it's awesome.
He's really the best with Tarantino's dialogue,
and I will say, I've always wondered about it,
Spike Lee called him out for it,
and perhaps rightfully so.
In writing a sitcom, I find myself feeling very strange
about writing African American characters,
talking in anything but perfect English,
like the other members of the cast.
And even though I know like, oh, this would be funny, this would be something different.
It feels uncomfortable to me because I don't want to say, you know, it could be something
as simple as ain't instead of, right, not whatever.
But you feel weird about it, even though your other characters might talk that way, white characters
might talk that way.
It's a strange feeling.
I feel the same in writing a Jewish character or in writing a Hispanic character or whatever
else.
It's a weird presumption to make.
Like, how does Tarantino sit down and write dialogue with 8 ,000 N words in it?
How does he do it and then present it to Samuel L. Jackson and just know that Samuel Jackson
is going to love it?
That would be terrifying to me.
It's a great question.
I know Tarantino grew up in Carson, which maybe that's what the thing is where it's just
like, you know, he came from certain neighborhoods where certain people talked in certain ways
or whatever.
But I don't know. I was surprised because I found I love all the Terrence Eon movies. Doesn't mean
I don't feel uncomfortable at points watching them, especially in a theater. I mean that true romance
scene. You're like, is the writer of this movie racist? What's going on here? Well, the the walk -in -hopper
scene. Yes. Yeah. That's a good. That's a great example. The in hateful eight hateful eight was
was I haven't had too many crazy uncomfortable times in a movie theater.
Hopefully it was one of the most uncomfortable times.
The other time was the movie Edmund with William H. Macy, David Bammett.
I mean, I was like looking over my shoulders during that movie was making me so uncomfortable.
So, but hopefully I would say was tense.
I mean, it's a very racially tense movie.
Yeah.
And then in the end, it seems that characters learn a lesson about progression and
and perspective and race and equality and all these things.
So that's nice, but getting to that point
is can be tough, which is the point of the movie.
But I did a, I was not surprised,
but I was, you know, I remember seeing an interview
with Samuel Jackson and he was like,
he was the one that said, you have to make this,
but when Tarantino wasn't gonna make it,
Samuel Jackson was like, you have to make this movie.
So I was like, oh, that's cool,
because like, he clearly sees the importance
of the message of the movie and all that's
stuff but it doesn't mean it doesn't didn't make me feel sure well especially having written it
I mean it just boggles the mind and then today I read to you know we're on episode two now
but on episode one of the season get out uh Samuel Jackson today was in the news because he was pretty
pissed off that the lead of get out uh Daniel Aluja I'm probably pronouncing that wrong I didn't look
up a pronunciation was British and not African American. He's like, you don't think any African
Americans here on a home soil might know a little something about that. Interracial
dating has been going on in the UK for a hundred years. Why not let somebody here with some
actual experience give it a shot? Why do they have a British guy play Martin Luther King in
Selma? Oh, wow. You know, wouldn't an American have a better
And I, you know, it's certainly not a point I would be making, but when I heard Samuel
Jackson say it, I was like, what a fucking interesting argument.
I was like, I am really fascinated by that.
And I love it.
And they asked Samuel Jackson why they always cast British actors, not just African Americans,
but, you know, a lot of your stars, your favorite shows are from other countries.
And he said, well, basically because they're cheaper.
Oh, really?
He's like, we get more money.
they do it cheaper. He's like, but, but straight up, he's like, I get out. He's like, he
didn't even say whether or not he liked it. But he was just kind of like, I think it's
fucked up that that role was not played by an African American. It was played by a British
person.
That's interesting because I know it's not the same thing. But that is, that is a, that
doesn't have a certain kinship to the whitewashing argument. And, and why are they always recasting
in these roles with races other than the ethnicity
that they were originated as being portrayed by or whatever.
So I feel like there's a certain kinship there
where it's like, okay, well, we're of the same ethnicity
technically, but social experience is very important
and you need to, you know, but then again, you know,
poor people play rich people, rich people play poor people,
et cetera, et cetera.
Yeah.
I was just kind of fascinated by the argument.
I mean, I think it's certainly less agree just than Emma Stone playing an Asian in a low -haw
Or till to switch playing an Asian or a Scarlett Johansson playing an Asian or whatever else
That yeah, although that goes in the show looks kind of cool
I got to say I never saw the anime one, but it looks pretty cool
Has there been any complaints yet about Scarlett Johansson tons? Oh there has yeah, yeah, okay
Cuz I I googled it the other day and I didn't see anything and I thought I'm surprised people aren't complaining about this
Yeah, that's a bad one
That's a real bad one. Yeah, I mean they're taking a straight up anime movie and I mean that's
You know the the the Emma Stone one to the till the entirety of voice that I didn't agree with the till the Swinton thing right on numerous
Levels on the podcast when we did Dr. Strange, but the the Emma Stone one is is straight up confusing to me because I'm like
She's not Asian. Yeah, I just don't get you got Emma Stone
I understand you wanted to be in your movie and that's great, but then change the character
The character doesn't have to be Asian. It's odd. Yeah
Pat we're 42 minutes in. We haven't even talked about Logan yet. All right. Well, that's crazy
We that that that are obviously counts as the movie corner. We talked about about 40 movies there in a 20 -minute span and
As long as you approve, I don't think we need to get into Joe's scary stuff. No, no, we can keep moving
We covered a, we covered a, an ethnicity corner there.
Oh, we covered a lot.
It was like a hair and all Jackson race corner.
I mean, that's the thing.
Like, you know, I have a great deal of respect
for Lena Dunham and what she does.
But if Lena Dunham is complaining about something
being racist or whatever it may be,
my eyes are already half -rolled before I read the article.
Yeah.
When Samuel Jackson makes a point, I listen.
Like, I was like, I really, for some reason was like,
Fix it on this article and thought about it all day because I just love I love being
Challenge and being forced or asked to think about things I wouldn't have thought about I agree with that. I agree with that
I agree with everything you just said. I'm sorry to shut on lean it down. I
I have no problem with it. It's fine with me. Yeah
Folks here we are
Logan the movie
about let's let's do an accurate count here. You had six six X -Men movies, two
Wolverine movies. So this is number nine in the X -Men series. It's only been
nine. Well I'm not counting Deadpool. Oh yeah. Yeah because there were two solo
Wolverine movies and then six X -Men movies or three solo. So this is a
Roughly part nine to show you where I'm coming from I thought X -Men 1 and X2 were okay. I
Like actually liked an X2. They kind of took the
Homosexuality theme a little further like they were outcast and all that the other right bit of a theme there Brian singer
No comment on Brian singer
But everything that came after it was kind of boring except the time travel one days of
future past I believe which I would say is the best ex -man movie. That's one of the
best superhero movies ever seen. I love that film. That's fair. I thought the Wolverine
movies were terrible. The first one was an abomination. It played like a made for sci -fi movie or something.
The second one was an attempt at a samurai film, it was painfully boring, it was a much
more passable film than the first one, but it's still sucked.
And were they both James Mangold?
I know Mangold was the second one, I don't know if he's the first one.
Maybe he's not the first one.
But I will tell you this, the leaps and bounds that Mangold made in the second film were,
I mean, they were just that above the first film was a fucking atrocity on numerous levels
the most, you know, offensive of which I would say is when they did the thing with Deadpool
where they sowed his mouth shut and then they made him a mute like mute. Oh my God, I was like,
what the fuck are you doing? This is terrible. So he write it some of the wrongs in the second Wolverine
movie. There was a good little teaser scene at the end with Patrick Stewart, you know,
secret scene, credits scene, whatever you want to call it, which tipped off that this next
one was going to be potentially interesting for everybody. And, you know, in the Canada
of X -Men films, I thought this was an interesting step. You know, it's based on the old man Logan
story, basically. We meet up with Wolverine. He's an older man now. He's clearly sick. He's
living in Mexico as a limo driver for higher, right?
Yeah, it seemed to me like he was driving people
over the border.
He had those fracas chanting USA at the roof.
Okay.
And then, oh, I guess, yeah, they're pretty close to Vegas.
I mean, I would say the border makes the most sense, yeah.
Yeah, they were going over the border, yes.
So that was this whole gig was,
I'll take you through into Mexico.
There's gonna be a lot of spoilers in this apologies,
But anyway, well, I think let's let's not spoil them until the end when we just say what if we want to discuss the end
We don't need to spoil it two and a half hour move. Sure. There's much to talk about before like the two things that would spoil the move
So the basics are we pick up with Logan
He's further along in his life all the you you find out all the mutants have been exterminated or are now extinct
and
And he's living with Professor X in hiding essentially.
They're hiding their identities as mutants.
And then I'm also living with a albino butler
played by Stephen Merchant.
Yes.
Which was an interesting character
that I felt was not handled in maybe the best way.
That was my only real grievance.
And I love Stephen Merchant,
but it was a strange addition to the mix.
The Caliban, and I know he's in the comics.
I don't know much about the Caliband character. Oh, he is a comic character. He is in the comics. So that turned to Joe's
I guess he is roommate. Does he is lover? Is he is nurse? What's going on here? That part I couldn't answer. I just knew the Caliband was in the comics and
Anyway, they're all living in Mexico and
Not unlike a vacation
Sex in the city kind of way. They're all they're all down there hiding because if people find out
but these are the last of the mutants, they'll be killed.
Yes.
And then there is a discovery of a new mutant
that in so many ways is the daughter of Wolverine.
Yeah, and that's no big twist.
But her opening scene, I thought was fucking awesome.
Yes.
She's got kind of like junior claws.
And the girl that played her is mute
for the bulk of the movie, it says absolutely nothing.
And I just thought she had such an extremely expressive, interesting face.
I liked her a lot.
She was not your standard kind of movie kid.
I love her relationship with Wolverine.
And even though nothing that happened in the movie was particularly surprising, I guess.
For me, the tone of it was just like really, really cool.
And I thought it was shot incredibly well.
And I love James Mangold, who was, I think, obsessed with Westerns.
we differed on this earlier.
But he said his writers and him as a director
was out to make a modern western.
They watched Shane on television.
Mangold made 310 to Yuma, which I think is pretty good.
And also Copland, which is maybe in my top 10,
top 20 movies of all time.
And it's a modern western for sure.
Yes.
It's basically high noon with Stallone as Gary Cooper
as Gandalfine used to say.
But for me, I just thought it was a very sort of thematically, if I can bring my old
film school roots back, interesting movie.
And I found myself really thinking about it a lot today, and my biggest grievance about
these movies, Marvel movies for the most part, is that I, when wishing I was dead while
they're on, and then I leave and never think about them again, and I'm angered myself for
being fooled into seeing another one.
this I thought had a lot to say a lot going on. There's an amazing article I
recommend reading on a site called Birth Movies Death. Reviewing Logan, it's
one of my favorite movie reviews I've ever read. I wish I had the guy's name I
can look it up that wrote it but it really gave me a deeper appreciation of the
movie but for me for a two and a half hour superhero movie to not be bored I got
to give a coup d 'oeuvres. I loved it. I have a different opinion. Yes. Well, I want to hear it
because we didn't get into last night why you didn't like it. You just clearly didn't like it.
Yeah. And then I said, let's just save it for the show. Yeah. So they fun. This is where, like,
I'm going to try my best not to spoil things, but if you don't want to know how the plot unfolds,
You might not want to listen to this
But here's the thing they find this new mutant. I agree with everything Pat said about her performance
She was really good in it. I mean the kid can't be more than six or something or eight or something right
I have a hard time with kids ages, but I think she was 10
10 12 look 14 16 tops. Yeah
But she was great
She was she really played the role with it with it with a strange depth where I was like
It's kid this kid seen some shit out there in the world or something. Yeah
And the whole plot of the movie is is they got to get this girl to the safe haven to the the sort of Valhalla for the for the new
generation of mutants
Where where they can sort of be reborn again or whatever
So I didn't, I know the attempt was to be a Western, to me it felt more like a national
ampune's vacation or something, like it was a road trip, they're, they're cooped up
in the car the whole time, they're meeting different people along the way, yeah, there's
a road trip.
It was a road trip.
I think if you replace like a stage coach with the truck that he buys, you know, and then
he, they actually knock that horse carriage over and the horse is break free and he helps
rustle them up and then goes and stays with the family on their farm and then there's rustlers on
the farm and I think that family being black and the girl being Mexican, you know, a Mexican
mother caretaker who was scared about going over the border and all this stuff. I think all that
stuff was in there pretty intentionally and a lot of that comes from this article which I found
because I don't want to take credit for some of these theories because they all kind of come from
that's but right the guy's name is
G's I'm sorry
Sid Ant
ad lacca and
The article is called Logan the things we leave behind on birth movies death. It's a fantastic article, but
I thought it had about 10 killer action sequences car chase was like
almost mad Maxian with the
The the train when they're going alongside it. Yeah, that part was cool
I had been prepped for extreme violence and really to me, it was just kind of a lot of
claws going through heads, which we'd never seen before, but it wasn't crazy.
There were some beheadings and shit.
Can we stop?
Can we pause on the extreme violence for a minute, please?
Because that was when my gripes to the movie.
It was so...
Look, I'm not offended by violence, obviously, and I'm not offended by language, obviously.
but it was it was it was so they they said fuck so much it was almost like they
were showing off it was almost like they were being like we made an
R -rated movie I mean Professor X was saying fuck frequently well I thought
the Deadpool was showing off the at the R -rated and this was just like a
fucking gritty adult drama and a cool way to me that I was not expecting it's
It's in character for Deadpool to make jerk off jokes and come jokes or whatever.
It's not in character to me for Professor X to be saying fuck frequently.
That was odd.
And I also thought there were lines with Wolverine where I was like, every time he got mad,
he would just go, fuck, fuck.
Often to the little girl.
Yeah.
And I'm like, throwing a shit once in a while, just to break it.
It's just better writing.
it's you know like so so that was one thing but the second thing is the violence
right off the bat in the opening scene he he gets into it with like five dudes
and immediately it's like claws through fucking eye sockets and stuff so they blow the they blow
the violence load so quickly there's so many dismemberments and decapitations by 25 minutes into
of the movie, I was just like, okay, well that part's done now.
And then for the tone of the film to be so somber,
it was so goddamn depressing and everybody was so hopeless
and everything was gonna be the worst.
And I was like, it just felt like a not fun John Wick to me.
I was like, it didn't have the fun that John Wick had to me
with the violence and the craziness and the action
in the... John Wick, to me, is dark, but it's not hopeless if that makes it, you know.
Well, I thought... I mean, I thought it fit the times. I related to it very much. I thought...
Kind of the coolest thing about it, and this is probably discussed in that article,
but also just something I walked away from it with, which I thought was a very cool theme.
Of this guy is, you know, everyone points out to him how much he's drinking, and etc.
he's just kind of fuck everyone, he doesn't want to make new friends, he doesn't want a family, he doesn't want to fall in love, etc.
And what's chasing him throughout the end of the movie is this just pure animal clone of Wolverine basically.
He's like alter ego.
And I think that's really saying, well you take that too far.
If you go too far with not attaching yourself, not making human connections, et cetera, this is the
Monster you could become. I thought there was a very interesting theme. I liked the
however brief redemption that Wolverine has by the end of the movie and
Heather, my girlfriend and several other people have talked to me about crying at the end of it and I was nowhere near that point
But I sort of got it. I thought it was strangely moving, especially considering I have never given a
Fuck about Wolverine or any superhero, but I really gave a shit and I really cared about the story
I got a site in a big way. I'm gonna set off a couple major spoilers here
All right
Before you do
Because we should put that near the end of the podcast
So let people listen and then at the end say we're gonna discuss the ending for a minute right I think
Let me ask you Joe
not to, you know, put you on the spot, but if you hate the joky, um, whip a minute tone
of Marvel movies, but now you also do not like the somber, jokeless tone of Wolverine.
What do you want?
You're not going to like the answer pack.
Don't, please don't say it.
Please don't say it.
You're not going to like the answer.
I like a somber tone, but I like there to be a little hopeful
Whatever at the end of it, which I felt that man versus Superman had I felt like we saw a redemption of that man
And a door opened for him to do a new thing in the next movie to be a better man in the next movie
But I enjoyed that what I didn't like about I'll be seeing those movies
What I didn't like about this and we are almost at 60 minutes
So I feel like we're close enough to the go ahead that I can tell how I don't like that he died at the end
Wolverine. Yeah. I think that I thought it was poetic in a certain way, but would
I last shot of the cross? That was very cool. The the cross being set down as
the X was very cool. I thought it would have been look I don't know maybe I'm
soft, but I just thought it would have been nicer to see him become the new
Professor X and lead these kids. Especially when we're being left with a
a group of 100 % generic mutant kids,
like there was nothing memorable
about any one of those kids except for the girl
who was a girl Wolverine.
Right.
Which she was, I think whatever power that girl had,
she would have been pretty riveting in the role.
But it's like, you take her and they defined her so well.
And then behind her are 12 other kids
that literally except for one look completely physically normal and then like
one of them like at one point shoots a little lightning and one of them does
this other thing where he lifts a thing in the air and then one grows cold
breath and when it and I'm like all right well I'm not saying they were setting up a
new Marvel universe but I'm saying if you want to leave a Marvel a comic book
movie saying I'm excited that that world still exists and right now that world
world has been left to 12 of the most boring versions of the lost boys I've ever seen.
And there's and Wolverine's dead and it's just like not a great, it's not a great like
feeling at the end of the whole thing.
The kids, the kids were really nothing to me, you know, they're kind of cute or whatever,
but yeah, the powers were nothing.
And I wonder if it wasn't just like, I don't know, but Scott Frank co -wrote it who wrote
like out of sight and the look out, he's a, he's a fantastic writer, one of my favorite
screenwriters with Mangold and some other dude who I should look up but I'm not going to.
I just, I think what they probably thought to themselves is, do we really make these 12 kids
like cast amazing actors, give them all crazy new awesome mutant powers. But if they do that,
then you're watching it and it's not the end to Wolverine, a character that many people have held
deer for 20 years, then it becomes like, ooh, what's this new? What's the next X -Men going to be? Are
to keep the focus on Wolverine if I had to guess but I don't know I think they didn't want people going
I want to see more of those kids. I'm gonna bring up another movie that's gonna make people angry. All right
Probably you too and I'm not saying it's a better movie than this movie all right uh
But I think this is a good example
When I watched the last Indiana Jones movie there was no part of me. Yes, there was no part of me that thought at
at the end, it was going to lead to a mutt Williams son of Indiana Jones story, right?
A perfect ending to me was the kid, shy, above picking up the hat, and you as an audience
and we're going, oh, fuck you.
And then Harrison Ford takes it back and you know, he's probably retired, but he's still
out there.
You know, it's like the end of the last season, a Sherlock.
talk. It ends on like, please don't tell me. Okay, I won't tell you. But it's, it speaks
to what we're talking about. So it's like, it's, it's, it's, it's, you know, I felt like,
I felt like they, this movie was a very, very good effort. But I also felt like there was
a lot of, we have fucked up so royally with the first two. Now we've got to make it all
account in this last one at the expense even of the character himself where it's like,
okay, don't make any more Wolverine movies, that's fine.
But it doesn't mean he has to die at the end and he has to be completely fucking selfish
and hard at it until literally his last dying breath almost.
It's just like, this is just depressing to me after a while, I don't know who I'm supposed
to feel good about.
I don't know who.
Well to me, that's what differentiated it from all of these other shitty movies.
And I, you know, it's the kind of thing I look for in like a drama.
I like a blue Valentine or a Manchester by the sea or these miserable movies, the wrestler
or whatever it may be.
And the wrestler I actually read was one of the main influences of Logan.
He said it was like Logan in these different westerns and that made sense to me.
Well, here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
Can I say this?
Please?
The ending of the wrestler I love.
I like the wrestler.
Yeah, I would I would have I would have loved to have seen Logan
Running off into the okay. They made such a big deal about the drug right right the green drug
Don't take it all at once be careful. You better not take it all once. He takes it all at once at the end big surprise
Right
That's not what kills him
That's not what ends him. He gets killed because he's fighting and he gets fucking thrown into a branch and it stabs him through the chest
whatever
or give me the ending where they're like,
you're gonna die from that serum,
and he runs, and he's running off into the woods,
and you're like, is he gonna die,
or is he fucking Wolverine?
Give me something where I'm like,
maybe he's still out, just a tiny bit of fucking hope.
I get it, I think people just get tired
of being jerked around, so that in five years time,
oh, guess what we found Hugh Jackman living in Antarctica,
now we're gonna make another shitty Wolverine.
I think it was like, I want to just end this fucking character
They're gonna do Son of Wolverine in five years anyway, but for me a character
I did not care about suddenly cared about it a lot and it became probably my two
It's only March, but my two -fair moves of the year probably the two we've talked about get out in Logan
Like I going into Logan. I never would have dreamed I would love the movie as much as I did
But I thought it was a very
Kind of special movie. I liked it along. I will say this
Because you brought up closure at the end with his death. Yes
There was another thing that bothered me about the movie was, again, we're in major spoiler
territory right now.
I didn't give a shit when Professor X died because they killed him in X -Men 3, they killed
him in X -Men 3 and then they just pretended like that never happened in days of future past.
And then now here we have another movie where I'm like, but what about days of future past
when Professor X comes in in the floating wheelchair.
That is clearly not this future that we're in, right?
They just kind of disregard that stuff, okay fine,
come and books do that too, there's this storyline,
there's that storyline, whatever.
But my point is, is when Professor X died,
I didn't care, I wasn't choked up.
After nine fucking movies, I should give a lot more
of a shit about that character.
And also, but they have never liked them as much
I did in this movie.
They have both already said Patrick Stewart and Hugh Jackman have already said that they're
open to reprising the role again.
We'll see then in a Deadpool movie, which would take place before this, but it's still
like, it's not over.
It's not over.
Yeah.
I mean, look, and this, at this moment in time, I thought that this was a extremely well -done
movie.
I thought that Hugh Jackman, who's an actor I can give or take, I love him in prisoners, thought
really good in this. And I thought Patrick Stewart was really good in this. And I just
I love the movie. They were both good in it. I just I just had my gripes. Pat enough.
I mean, maybe it was, you know, look, I was sitting in a puddle of oil butter. Yeah.
God knows how many horse noises getting shushed. God knows how many calories was in that bag
alone. I don't even think about it. But, uh, but in any case, uh, that's Logan
folks, uh, and that's the podcast. I think this may be the longest episode we've
ever done. We heard an hour and well, no, that's not true. Those commentary ones
that were endless, but we're at an hour and six, seven minutes here. So that's
pretty good. Uh, let's wrap it up. I mean, for me, I got nothing particularly to
plug. Uh, you know, I was a writer producer on crashing, which was airing on HBO
now, Judd Apatow, Pete Holmes, check that out. Hope you like it. And that's that's about all I got.
It's like I'm touring or something. Well, I don't have much either. I don't want you to feel bad about
this. I don't. This comes out Monday, March, whatever it is. I'll be I know this much. I'll be in
Australia for the Melbourne Comedy Festival in April. So if you live down under, come out to
show, be part of the headliner showcase, which features myself and I guess I think
four of their American comedians. And the album is out. You let me down. The
special is out. You let me down. It's on iTunes. And if any of our fans can
go and give me five star reviews to offset these goddamn trolls, you did that
for the podcast. We're so grateful. If you could do that for some of my albums, God
we'd be grateful. That'd be so nice of you. Absolutely. And also now that we are on head
gum in a new network, our reviews did carry over. It appears, but it would look great to get us off
on a good foot over there. I think people are going to see us on the main head gum page and go,
what's this? So if you get a chance to give us the stars, give it the ratings. We'd love it. We
appreciate it. You guys always do. There's a, we'll see you in health Facebook page. I love checking in
on that. You guys discuss the episodes. Please feel free to do it more. I'm going to start
commenting more when I get a little free time. I am at the Patrick Walsh. Joe is at Joderosa
Comedy on Twitter and Instagram. And we love you guys. Thank you very much. Keep your
comments, questions, stars, tweets, likes, a comment, and we'll see you next time.
Thank you.
That was a hit gun podcast.