I'll see you at the podcast you turn to when you want to talk movies and such, my name
Mr. Joe DeRose, my name is Patrick Walsh. There's a new update to zoom where they make you consent
to being recorded. It's very interesting. But probably very wise. I mean, how many times have
you been recorded without your knowledge? Who knows? Who knows? I'm waiting for those videos
to surface. I actually lived for a couple of years when I moved out to LA in the sliver apartment.
The movie Sliver, where Billy Baldwin would watch every room, including mine. I didn't find this
out until years later after I had made love to him many times. But yeah, he had a whole wall
of black and white TVs, and he would just watch it all. He loved to watch. I used to like visiting
that apartment and teasing Billy. I knew the cameras were there. Show a little cheek in the bathroom.
Doing the licking the thumb and then circling your nipple with it kind of thing.
Yeah. Today's movie is Wrath of Man.
And just now, we've said more than Jason Statham says in the entire film.
This, I'm excited to talk about this movie, but not yet, obviously.
As of my Wrath of Man, I think just became available to purchase as well. We always like to say where
you can get them. We don't, you know, Joe and I are going to try to do for the most part stick with
streaming stuff, classic stuff that you can get on shutter, et cetera. But this just felt like
why not if the theaters are back opening? Joe and I are hitting the shows. Why not talk about a
couple new releases like we used to, you know, back on the big screen. Yeah. And I got the regal
what the hell is it called? The regal points car, whatever the fuck it is. I got the regal card.
You're a regal vehicle. The regal vehicle. Me and Larry go to a movie every week together.
That's a threes company joke, folks. The second we did Drack Dripper on the last
up. Yeah. What was the other one we used to do? Pizza Hut Dracula. That's something people always
were more always comment to me was what? That we discussed on the podcast and I'd have to go dig up
the actual clip because I don't remember specifics. But we did a whole bit on Pizza Hut Dracula that's
become one of our most popular bits. And I don't remember specifics on it. I got nothing on that.
That doesn't even make sense. What the hell is that? I mean, look, in a year we'll say Drack
Dripper and more understand why that was funny either. But at least it's a, it's like a play on
words or a pun or whatever. It's like Pizza Hut Dracula. There's no, what is the reference? I don't
even get what? Well, somebody, somebody please tell me via a DM or tell Emily and she can tell me
what Pizza Hut Dracula was or at least tell me what the episode was so I can give it a listen.
I actually, I don't do it often, but when I was at my most, you know, like just a loan during
the pandemic, I love throwing on old episodes and listening to the riffs, listening to how depressed
we were at any given time. It is funny how many times throughout the last five years we've been like,
well, this is obviously the lowest star depression can go. And then it just kept getting lower.
I did three podcasts yesterday that I guessed it on and all three brought up, we'll see you in
hell. I had nice things to say and said that all three shows, so the the one was called the trash and
another was called the power play. And then another was called the Val Kilmer cast where you just
talk about Val Kilmer. But they all had very nice things to say about we'll see you in hell.
Well, that's very nice. Did the Val Kilmer cast you each go through? You go through a movie each
week or what? Just reminiscing about them. You pick them. You do an interview about yourself and
then you pick a movie of Val Kilmer's that you want to discuss. And the host reads some passages from
the Val Kilmer autobiography. It fills you in on some stuff you may have not known about Val Kilmer
and then you you discuss the movie you picked. I picked Spartan, David Mammoth, Val Kilmer film.
Um, it was fun. It was a fun time. I had a good time. I remember seeing at first sight in the theater,
a love story where Kilmer was blind. God, it sucked. Was it him in Sorvino?
Yeah. And it was when he gets sighted at the end he realizes it's Paul Sorvino and that's the big
gag at the end of the film. Bitch gets out of the car looking more like Paul Sorvino.
It's a Friday line, Freddie Jackson, Janet checks. Um, did I ever discuss the upshaws on this show?
You didn't. But before we get off Val, did you share my story about him and Peter Gallagher
hating each other on the set of Conan? I don't remember the story. I can't remember my own
gags from this show. I can't remember anything anymore. It's gone. They have a documentary coming out
where just like that weird, um, punky Brewster documentary on Hulu, apparently Val Kilmer has been
filming his life for the past 60 years and he, the documentary is like collection of him on set
for all of his movies and blah, blah, blah. I'm sure it doesn't, it doesn't include all the times where
he would scream at somebody because he's supposed to be an unhinged psycho. But, um, I've always liked
Kilmer fine. You know, when they were pushing him to be a star in the late 90s, you know, like if you
remember the saint, uh, and, and at first sight in all those kind of movies, he just, he's not a leading man.
He's just, he works in supporting his best role as tombstone. He's incredible in it. But, um, for some
reason, there's something that's not super compelling about him in a lead. He's great as Jim Morrison.
He looks the part, sounds the part, you know, but he's a character actor. He's not a leading man. Yeah.
He's weird when he's quirky. That's what I like about Spartan is he's, he's convincing as a tough
mercenary, but then he's also so odd and quirky. Yeah, he gives like this weird life to the mammoth
dialogue that I really enjoy. Um, but also yesterday in discussions about we'll see you and how I was
out with some of my buddies from a little TV show called the impractical jokers.
And I've been talking to Brian Quinn of the Joker show about how he is in Victor Crowley,
the fourth hatchet movie. Okay. Yeah. And he, he goes, did you watch Crowley yet? And I go, I didn't.
I'm still on hatchet too. I got to get through three. I want to watch him in order. And just he goes,
you, we're viewing it on your podcast. And I go, I don't know, maybe, maybe we will. And he goes,
you know, I'll come on. So I go, we'd love to have you on sometime. We never have guests,
but it'd be fun to have you on. And then Sal was there too. And I go, Sal, would you also be a guest?
And we'll see you in hell. And he goes, of course. So two guests that we could have come on. It would
be a lot of fun for us to talk to about movies and whatever. I would love it. I mean, maybe that's the
move. Many, many a time we brought up having a guest and it never, it never comes together outside
of Crumbholtz on the live show. Right. But especially in this time of zoom, I mean, it couldn't be
any easier. Why not? It could be so easy. So we should in some way shape or form get them on at some
point. I got a couple other guys in the in the pipeline that I think would be interesting guests
that would come on to. Same, same. Yeah. So, you know, um, the, uh, well, we, we shit. You know who I
love to have on as my buddy, Scott Weinberg, who is one of the most knowledgeable people about horror in
the world. And yeah, and did my favorite podcast that apparently unfortunately didn't
continue the 80s all over where they reviewed every movie released in the 80s. Any relation to Max
Weinberg? He is not, uh, thankfully, Max Weinberg, not the nicest, but Scott is awesome. Yeah,
we should. We should do like a month of, uh, you know, bringing people in for 15 and, and let them
get on with their live. It'd be fun. I agree. I agree. Well, and let's ask the fans, what do you
get? Would you guys like the guest episodes to be sort of a separated thing where maybe it's an
ad? Another yet another tier on the Patreon? Or do you, or would you mind if we incorporated guests
into some of the regular episodes? You know, sometimes people are like, I don't want you to
botch it up the, sure, the magic. So I mean, I can't imagine feeling that way about any two people.
No, but some people do. But, you know, as long as the guests aren't, uh, you know, hate mongers or
something, I think it'd be a fun little ad. I tend to ask the hard -hidden questions.
I'm going to give on compromising interviews and I don't know which direction they're going to go in.
Folks, I would like to say, uh, you know, I guess you could call it a new psycho, but, uh,
RIP to a real one. One of my very favorite comedic actors of all time, Mr. Chuck
Groden. Charles Groden, unfortunately, rarely got perfect parts for him because Hollywood didn't
really know what to do with him. He was a very strange comedic presence. I've been watching some of his
late -night bits, Carson and Letterman, and stuff where he just goes on and is an asshole.
He, he made as part of his like real -life persona just this like bitter, angry guy who hated Hollywood
and hated phoniness. And man, it's a thrill. There was nothing else like him in those days. Uh,
a genuinely popular comedic star who went out of his way to just be an asshole in these interviews.
And you never knew if it was real or fake. And I think now we know that it was largely fake.
But some of the tension that came out of those interviews was real. Sure. Super funny does not get
the credit he deserves. Uh, his best movie unquestionably is Midnight Run with Bobby DeNiro. The chemistry
those two have is off the charts. That's one of the great action comedies, an amazing script,
a great film. I like him as the fucking dad in Beethoven. Not my shoes, Beethoven, not my shoe.
I was a little depressed that the headline I read was Charles Grote and Star of Beethoven dead.
And I was like, do not reduce this man to Beethoven was, you know, heartbreak kid for God's sakes.
The heartbreak kid, uh, yeah, is, is a masterpiece. It is not available anywhere. It's just not
available to watch. So I'm hoping there is having to bring me in. Neither is heaven can wait. I like
heaven can wait fine. I watched it recently on TCM or something. And I thought it was fine.
Heartbreak kid is really something a really painful uncomfortable movie ahead of its time.
Very in the curb school. It's a guy who you saw the remake maybe with Ben Stiller, but uh,
it's a guy who goes with his honeymoon. He realizes he's not really in love with his wife because he
sees Chibble Shepherd and he wants to fuck her. So we just kind of like abandons his wife who has a
sunburn. It's a cruel mean character. And he plays it beautifully. But it's also from another time
when you could, they make the wife so annoying. Yeah. You're like, you kind of get why he's doing it,
but you know, it's not right. Like, right. It's just, it's, it's one of those movies that walked,
you know, that walks a fine line. And then very dark ending. But some of Grodon's funniest.
He's awesome. And funny stuff. It was always cool to see him show up like he was in this movie.
The X with Zach Braff and stuff. But like later on, he was mostly a cameo guy. His cameo and
so I married an axe murderer steals the fucking movie. It is absolutely hilarious. I used to love
him. He's just a guy who drives a or a lapaglia says, I'm commandeering your vehicle. And Grodon goes,
no, because you have to. I'm a police officer. You have to give me your card.
Oh, no. It's really funny. And then Phil Hartman as the tour guide of Alcatraz is, is also hilarious.
And that's just a grand. That is Hartman in that could be the greatest cameo of all time. It is,
might be the funniest cameo I've ever seen anything. God, I still think about if we had another,
we would have had now 25 additional years of those little Phil Hartman cameos and things,
you know, like God, just him popping up and shit would have been amazing.
It's, it's my top two or that and Farley and Dirty work. The, the, I got a new made old Jack.
Yeah. Dracks and odd speed bleed. Yeah, hilarious movie. Yeah. Sometimes he stares at me while I'm
sleeping, which is off pudding. Yeah. He, man, the stuff done in those early Sandler, Farley,
McDonald movies that you hear so much of that in comedy today. And none of these old people would
ever give credit to them because they're not, that's not all comedy, but it was. It was, you
asked. Real life. Albert Brooks first movie. You know, it's basically the reality show following
Broden and his family. And Albert Brooks is the reality show director. That is a real gem,
hilarious movie. And you're getting, you're getting Broden and Brooks. Broden and Broden to
form, I mean, Brooks is out of control in that movie. He is asshole. Like it's perfect. Albert
Brooks. Broden, you know, playing a very difficult role where he's like trying to, he's clearly a bad
father and husband, but he's trying to play that he's a good one for the cameras, it's hilarious.
And then if I got to pick a sentimental favorite, it's definitely the first time I saw the man
is great Muppet Caper. And Charles Broden's commitment to Miss Piggy is so funny to this day. I showed
it to Heather recently and we were just cracking up because he looks Miss Piggy like dead in the eyes
like I'll give any whatever you want Miss Piggy. Like anything to fuck you got like he's so locked
into the scenes with Miss Piggy. He sings a song to her. He's funny as shit. We're just one of my
favorite guys Clifford with Martin Short has become a cult classic. It's not perfect, but what's funny
in it is very, very funny. My favorite, uh, Broden line of all time is in Clifford. You got to,
you got to meet him. He's a great kid. He's a great nephew. You'll see. What's his name? I want to
say Mason. What do I say Mason? Yes, hilarious. That's a, that's a, that's a good line. Yeah, him
and him and Short together were great combo. I'm just a fan. Uh, news psycho. This week we'd be remiss
if we did not discuss two things. We got two big news stories. The first is that yet again,
Evil Dead is having a sort of sequel continuation type thing. It's going to HBO Max
is being produced by Raimi and Campbell, but they're not involved beyond that.
Um, I don't know what to make of this. It's going to be written and directed by Lee Cronin who
was an Irish filmmaker, not familiar with him. Uh, the hole in the ground is his movie.
I know the movie. I've never seen it, but it was very well received. The hole in the ground. Uh, I
really did not like. I will just say, but, you know, okay, let's, uh, I'm going to check it out. It's
look, I'm never going to be mad in the city. I'm never going to be mad at more evil dead,
just like I'm never mad at more Star Wars. Right. But I'm also aware that they could do it very wrong.
I thought Ash versus evil dead really jumped the shark in the third season, uh, and became just a flat
out absurd comedy. Uh, it started teetering that on that in the second season. Um, but they
reel it back in towards the end with a great finale. And then third season, they got his daughter
coming in and it's like, what is this? Like so, yeah. So, um, I just, uh, evil dead doesn't take
place in a high rise. I just don't think that is interesting. And I think every time you say high
rise, horror movie, all anybody can think of his poltergeist three. And it's like, yeah, or the movie
high rise, which I did not like either. Yeah. It's just, it's just, my head is immediately, it
look, it's just not scary to see demons and ghosts in, uh, an elegant setting, uh, or, or well -kept setting.
It's just not, it's, you know, you don't want to see them in a polished arena. You want to see
them in a creepy, dark, there's no way to get help, you know, whatever. And you know, look, I'm sure
they're going to fix those questions or, or answer those questions by they get the building,
get sealed off or whatever they do to trap people, you know, like they always do in the evil dead movies.
The elevators broken. Yeah, I mean, I don't know. I just don't, I'm just not interested. Like, I
mean, I look, I, I will be excited to see the trailer, I guess, and see if maybe I'm wrong. But
do we think they ever go out on the windshield wiper, uh, cart that goes on the side of the building?
Does that get used as an escape? I'm sure at some point, they're on that thing. I'm sure there's
some kind of ledge suspense. You're never going to do better side of the building ledge suspense
than the naked gun, where he's, he's going from statue cock to statue cock grabs the woman's tits
and then he actually gets to a real woman's tits in the window. Well, and in all seriousness too,
the scariest, one of the scariest horror shorts I've ever seen is the ledge in cat's eye when he's
got a walk all the guy from airplane has to walk all the way around the building because I'm terrified
of heights. That makes my fucking skin crawl that short. It's so scary. But, um, you know, man, I don't
know, like it's just, look, like I said, it's more evil dead. Great. But, you know, this is like
when they announced like, we're doing a rogue one prequel where we're going to get into the roots of the
the six characters from that. I'm like, I don't give a shit, but make it. Maybe I'm wrong, you know,
and maybe I'll like it. I just would rather something in the vein of what interest me in that universe.
Uh, of course, we'll check it out. We'll probably do it on this show.
But, um, it's, it's, it's coming to HBO Max, you know, we'll, we'll see what, we'll see what happens.
I don't know what to tell you. But yeah, the fact that they're calling their shot as it being an
HBO Max only released is a little odd, you know, it doesn't show a lot of faith in it, but who knows?
So it's not going to be the dual theater thing that they're doing. Well, they said there's a possibility.
But I, I think what they do now, honestly, and it really sucks is they're not, they won't say it
explicitly, but I think that they only release movies theatrally that everybody agrees are great.
I think because I keep seeing in, in like the, the Hollywood Reporter articles and stuff announcing
movies, they'll be like, it's going to be a Netflix release. Although they're leaving the possibility
open for theatrical, it's like, then they're just waiting to see how good it is, which as soon as people
start realizing that, then that sucks, you know? Yeah, another news psycho, the,
oh boy, wow, did I just go blank there? Oh, Hellraiser is going straight to Hulu.
This Hellraiser reboot reimagining whatever the fuck it's been, whatever this latest iteration is,
it's TV show, then it's a movie, then it's a TV show again. I don't know what the fuck they're doing.
You know, they could have done this goddamn thing with Clive Barker 12 years ago.
And of course, all this development hell bullshit, you know, it's like these people can't get
their shit together to get anything out on time or whatever. But again, I'm a sucker for Hellraiser,
90 % of the movie suck. But I'll always go back and watch another one. So I'm curious to see
what they'll do with it. Maybe it'll be cool. Maybe it won't, again, not really feeling like it's
extremely promising when it's the direct to Hulu direct to Hulu. I mean, yeah, Hulu's original horror
slate has not been stellar to say the least. Not at all. And you gotta, you gotta wonder why they wouldn't
go to shutter or somewhere where the fans really appreciate it. You know, very rare when one of these
troubled productions eventually gets turd it out. Is it great? But we'll see.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So it's a remake. Let me just get some of the facts here. David Bruckner and
spy glasses in development film reboot. So they're saying remake in the fucking thing. They're saying
reboot in the thing. I don't know. Uh, I heard it was a reboot where it's got like a country
tinge to it. Country music theme. It's Hellraiser in the country world. And Reba McIntyre plays a key
supporting role. Yeah, it's, uh, yeah, hell is gone with that one. You have to listen to their
her latest record. I actually thought Joe, uh, Joe's laptop froze. That's how little reaction I got
from my Reba bit. It's only because I'm looking at the Hellraiser article. Okay. Not to mention creative
trio. Okay. Well, this here. Here we go. The trio behind it. Bruckner and screenwriter Ben
Collins and Luke Piotrowski, whose previous efforts include super dark times. Loved super dark times.
So like that. I like that. They're also doing the nighthouse starring Rebecca Hall, which looks like
about her 13th who gives a shit horror movie. Uh, Rebecca Hall is, man, she stays working.
Nobody in the world knows her name. I like her. I think she's pretty and a good actress, but, uh,
man, she, what a, what a lucky lady. She's been around a long time. There's a lot of actresses like
she does these horror flex. Sometimes you're like, who cares? She does that one where she's got to like
disprove hauntings or something. Yeah. It's like the dry. Remember when a haunting disprover,
the haunting disprover. Yeah. Uh, it was like when what's her face started doing some horror movies.
Boys can't boys don't cry. Um, Hillary swank. Yeah. You're just like, oh, for God's sake,
this looks so boring. Like, yeah. Because they're not horror people. They don't, they don't have,
they don't pick a good script. They just see they're like, they go, well, look, Patrick Wilson and
all those Wilson and Vera doing great over that conjuring thing. Like I should get into this horror
game and then they should just pick these doozy's, man. Get me my conjuring. What was that one a
couple years out from, uh, from the boys don't cry, Oscar where they were still trying to make her
a leading woman. First, she played the femme fatale and black dollia, which no one has ever been
warmest cast. But she was in this movie where she played like a Creole fortune teller. Yeah,
yeah. It was called like the, the reckoning or some, you know, some generic. Yeah. I mean,
that movie was so bad. That's what I'm talking about. They, they, they, they drift over, but they
don't pick the right shit. Cause yeah. And that was right. Like when, when, um, uh, they're
reaping my, the reaping. Yeah. There you go. That's right. When, uh, what's her face? Did the ring?
Not the ring. Yeah. The ring. What's your mommy wants? Amy Watts. Yeah. So they see that. It's a big
hit. But Amy ought to pick a script. So she picked a, you know, or she just got lucky with the ring.
I don't know. But, um, you know, it was awesome. Of course. But it was like, man, oh, man. That was
just the swank did boys don't cry. And she did the, uh, uh, uh, boxing pretty baby. What was it
called? Melody baby. Melody baby. It was called brown eyed baby. It was one best picture, but it was
called brown eyed baby. She was killing it, dude. And then she does the reaping. I've never ever
said I know. She popped up in the hunt, which is one of my least favorite movies of recent years. I
whenever she pops up in anything now, it's she is wrong for the part. She is miscast. And
the truth is, it's just what she does well is a butch tough woman. She needs to do like a GI
Jane or something. But people, people like her in million dollar baby because she's playing a tough
boxer and boys don't cry. She was literally playing, you know, a trans person. So it's, it's hard to buy
her like in a ballroom gown for some reason. I don't know why, but it is. Um, the biggest news psycho
that that I've been sitting on here and I shared this with Joe earlier this week.
Kevin Spacey, always a favorite. Here it will see you in hell. He is preparing to return to the
big screen, playing the role of a detective investigating the case of a man wrongly accused
of pedophilia. Kevin, what in God's name? Are you the the stones on this man? The sheer audacity.
Um, I'm almost back rooting for Spacey just based on the ball size alone. I mean, this is Cahoney's
like I've never seen like it's just nothing. It'd be like OJ returning to acting and he's playing a guy
who murders his wife. It's, it's absolute madness. Yeah, it's wild. It's wild stuff. The
Nestle Redgrave was circling the film when they cast Spacey. She dropped out. Uh, the movie is called
The Man Who Drew God, which sounds like a terrible title. But uh, the director is just like, I cast him
because he's a good actor. And they're like, what about the accusations? I think they're false.
Okay. He's allowed to think that. I mean, it's a ball's stance, but you know, yeah, it's like,
they're right. Yeah, it's, um, is the director known for anything?
His name's, it's an Italian director, uh, Franco, Nero, oh no, star is Franco, Nero.
Um, and it was directed by Lewis Nero. No, she's got how many Nero's are involved in the production
of this thing. Uh, directed by an all star's Franco, Nero, I don't know that he's done anything,
but that sounds like an old school like Bertolucci style Italian director, but I'm, yeah, I'm wrong. No,
yeah, he's 79 years old. Okay. He did, uh, Django, but not Django on chain, but Django, the, uh, the
original that kind of inspired it. So I mean, he's an Italian director. It's like, Spacey's going to
have to do that definitely work in, uh, the overseas markets for a while. The movie I assume
will get a release, but it's not like, who wants to watch that out of curiosity? You know, like,
I think people are just done looking at the man. All right, let's, let's slide to the movie corner.
You want to kick it off? I got to plug my phone in. I will. Um, and as I do folks, if this means we
don't get any more of those Frank Underwood Christmas videos, I'm going to be very upset because
they really keep me going through the holiday season. I love them so much. I have been watching
many a thing. I, I hope you're watching Mary of East town. It's a good little show on HBO with Kate
Winslet and it's really picking up the mysteries are good. I'm not going to say recommend fully
yet because I haven't finished it, but I've, I've really been enjoying it. I watched
on jibab shutter ginger snaps. I've been loving this season of joe bob. Everybody just seems
in better spirits than they did on those pandemic episodes. And ginger snaps is a movie I saw years
ago. It's a Canadian horror movie about two young girls, uh, sisters, their outcasts. It's a Canadian
horror movie. Uh, and on the night of one of the sister's first period, she gets attacked by a creature
and becomes sort of like a werewolf. So it's a, there's a feminist, uh, slant to it. It uses
menstruation and kind of coming into your own as as symbolism. And it does it very nicely. A
joe bob, you know, as he does sometimes goes way too over the top about this being like one of the
all -time best werewolf movies and etc. It's not that, but it's really well put together. Um,
you know, it's, it's very fun. It's a high school movie. So there's lots of like kind of high school
action and, and bullies and stuff like that. And it does, it handles all that stuff better than
its American counterparts, like the faculty and all those movies that came out around the same time.
It's very solid. Ginger snaps worth a watch. I haven't seen the sequels, but um, definitely a good
cult horror to check out. It's on shutter at the moment. I, uh, mentioned Spartan earlier. Uh, I
rewatched, uh, heist. Another David mammoth film. I just love this movie so much. Gene Hackman,
Delroy Lindo, Sam Rockwell, Dana DeVito, Rebecca Pigeon, uh, Patty Lapone. Patty Lapone. Ricky J.
Yeah, just a stellar stellar stellar cast of some mammoth regulars and some new people
to his crew. Uh, it's a heist movie, obviously. It is the most overloaded with mammoth dialogue
movie I've ever seen, like mammoth speak. Every line is flashy and snappy and whatever it is. So
if you like that, which I do, it's a lot of fun. Uh, still remember from the trailer, everybody
wants money. That's why they call it money. Right. That's not a good line. No, but it's very mammity.
It is, but it doesn't make sense. Yeah. So some of the lines are a little, a little much, but I love
the movie. If you're in the mood for a, again, just a fun heist thriller and you want to see Gene Hackman
in one of his final roles, by the way. Uh, and my favorite Delroy Lindo role that I've ever seen.
Uh, check it out. It's worth a watch. I, uh, I, I know I saw it, but I don't remember a thing about
it. So I'd have to rewatch. My favorite Lindo is Crooklin. Love that movie. Spike Lee's Crooklin.
Uh, you didn't ask, but I'm telling. I saw folks, Billy Eilish, Colin, the world's a little blurry.
Why would you watch that? You know, sometimes in a marriage, you, you have it pointed out to you
that your wife watches pretty much anything you want to watch and you often don't watch what she wants
to watch. And then she picks something like this and you go, here's why. Well, you know, look, I,
I like what I've heard of Billy Eilish. I, I, I, I'm not a fan per se, but she seems cool and seems
to have her shit together and be talented. And I always like a documentary about a musician or an
actor or whatever, about a making of a movie, even a movie I don't like. I'll just sit and watch them.
This was punishingly long at 140 minutes. Um, and was definitely awards and all kind of thing. You
know, it's, it's, uh, she has a really shitty boyfriend that you follow throughout and you're like,
God, why is she with this loser, you know, and you kind of swept up in the, in the drama of it,
but it's for big fans of Billy Eilish. And that's not me. It's, uh, a decent music documentary. And
if you're a fan of hers, you'll probably love it. I think I'm out. I mean, maybe she's doing it
ironically. Um, I'm not sure. I don't think she is given the tone of her songs. But that new fucking
record she's got out where it's called like, what the fuck is it called? I don't know. Uh,
her new record is called, hold on a second. Oh, happier than ever. And it's like her crying on the
cover. I'm like, uh, for Christ's sakes. I just can't with this shit. She said they've been. Yeah.
Yeah. That's all. That's what, that's what do you listen to? You're emotional at that age. I know.
Well, I'm sure this is going to end well. Eilish. Yeah. Take an 18 year old splitter depression
and darker emotions blow it up all over. Make her superstar with it. I don't wait. She's going to go
great. Drake, the rapper, uh, has, has been controversial for like, he celebrated when Billy
Eilish turned 18. Drake is like 38 years old, but he publicly was like, Billy Eilish is 18. I love it
whatever. And then he's been getting a lot of flak for DMing with 11 from Stranger Things. Now 11
looks like a child. She, she's, she's, she's claimed they're just good friends. That's what she's
claimed they're just good friends. Yes. But then he released a song this week.
And there's a lyric in it that said, on a private jet with 11, I'm on my Epstein shit.
Drake, what are you doing? What are, what are you in Kevin space? You doing Drake? I don't,
I don't think Drake's fucking 11, okay? But why are you putting that in your song?
That's a really disturbing thing to put on your in it for numerous reasons. How we what is
disgusting? It's disgusting. All right. I rewatched, I'm going to stick with rewatches for this one. I
rewatched only the lonely starring John Candy. Oh, I love it. I love it so much. Anthony Quinn. Uh,
uh, uh, uh, of course, you know, Hara, Moreno, Hara, and Ali sheety, Jim Belouch, Jim
Belouch, and a young boy like Lincoln in a cameo. Yeah, surprisingly fun role with Belouch.
I love being a, and a romantic comedy called Return to Me with David DeCovny and Bonnie Hunt. He's
really funny in it. And that's an underrated romcom. Uh, I, I love the movie only the lonely. It's
an early Chris Columbus picture, I believe. I'm not mistaken. Um, it's just a sweet, sweet film.
I watched it with my mom and dad the first time I was able to visit after we were all vaccinated.
Uh, and it was just a great thing to watch with your folks, especially if you have the kind of
relationship with your folks that I do where they worry about you constantly and you worry about them
constantly. Uh, it was very relatable. It's very funny. Um, and hats off to Chris Columbus and as a
director, he shoots some of it legitimately like horror movie style when like candy has some
fantasy sequences. Yeah. Yeah. But his mom getting killed and stuff and he's worried and Columbus
actually does shoot it in a way where it like, I'm like, Columbus could probably shoot a horror movie.
Um, in fact, when they bring the dead guy into the bar for his last drink, like, which ends up
being a funny scene, he sets that up very like creepily. And then it becomes funny, but he does a good
job of kind of playing with your emotions a bit. But, uh, if you want to see a sweet, sweet film,
uh, with just two, two wonderfully endearing people in sheety and candy, uh, check this film out.
And Marino Harrah is great in it. Well, she's, yeah, current Quinter great. They're all everybody's
great. I just mean, but you're there for the, you're there for the romance and some great Chicago
feel to it. I'm a big fan of that movie. I like it a lot. Um, I watched on Easter Sunday, Joe,
little movie called Soul Plane. Oh, Jesus. Have you ever seen Soul Plane?
I, uh, I believed I was served a legal document saying that I was not as an open -minded man allowed
to watch the film. It's a, it's a problematic movie. It's holy shit. I got friends in it.
I got friends in it. I didn't watch it. I was like, I can't do this, man.
I mean, it was, uh, it, it's written by a white guy and a black guy, which makes me think, maybe
they put a black eye on it. So the NAACP didn't, you know, shut the production down or something.
I don't know that. I'm just guessing, but it, man, it's, uh, a really troubling and racist movie.
Uh, as I said on, uh, letterbox making this movie today would get you the death penalty.
It is outrageous. At, at, at one point, I mean, the cast is Tom Arnold.
Uh, is, I guess the lead sort of, and he's on the plane with his wife, Missy Pyle.
And he spends the entire movie worried that black men are going to have sex with his wife with
their giant penises. That's his entire plot. Um, it goes beyond like stereotype humor and just like,
oh, boy, you know, she gets on the plane. She finds a, a nudie magazine where the guy has like a 12 -inch
cock. Then she happens to be on the same flight as the, the model who has the 12 -inch cock and
then she becomes determined to fuck him and cheat on Tom Arnold. So that's Tom Arnold's whole plot
trying to keep black men from fucking his wife. Um, by the way, and my reason, my, my main reason,
my primary reason for not ever seeing this film is Tom Arnold. I refuse to watch anything he's in
anymore. You watch Austin Powers. I know. I'm just kidding. I just hate Tom Arnold. God damn it. I
can't stand him. Anyway, go ahead. Sorry. He sucks. Um, they, I heard once from an executive that Tom
Arnold gave a full pitch with a bloody scab hanging off of his hand. And they all, like, couldn't stop
staring at it. And it's apparently talked about to this day. Tom Arnold has a violent, uh, diarrhea
scene in this movie. Mm -hmm. Just as he did in Austin Powers, like, when I'm, when I'm sitting down
on that toilet for my second, that I know of five -minute diarrhea scene in a movie, I might call my agent
and be like, hey, buddy, that's it on the diarrhea for me. Um, he doesn't do the diarrhea in powers.
He comes in with the line, Jesus, boy, what did you eat? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, light a match on it.
Um, you know, there are people who show up and get laughs clearly out of improv lines. Those
people are Monique and John Whiterspoon. It's hard to argue with those two. Uh, they get some laughs,
but like, I mean, there are jokes in this thing. Like, when they get to the sole plane terminal,
the black terminal, uh, instead of the usual food court, they have like the 99 cent store.
You know, like, it's that kind of joke. Like, malt liquor in a paper bag store, you know, like,
it's that kind of movie. It's, it's pretty rough. Yeah, you know, we have Michael Jackson,
fucking kids, jokes and just it's, it's part of that period of time where it's like, all right,
you know, it's, it's very good thing that we cleaned some of this bottom barrel stuff up. You know,
I think we all agree. Things are getting too pure. It's antical, but you watch this movie and it's like,
boy, the fact that this was a theatrical release is deeply troubling and that it was popular in
the black community as baffling to me, you know, because it's, it's, it's certainly beyond gone with
the wind or something like that. It's, it's, you got to look at it this way. And I, and you know,
I, every, every race of people has the thing like that. Yeah, yeah, where you look at them and you go,
how could you think this is funny? ours is Larry the cable guy. You know what I mean? Like, yeah,
like everybody's got this thing where you're like, when you go overseas to non -English speaking
countries and you see who like their biggest comedy stars are sometimes you're like, are you
fucking kidding me? Yeah. So it's, it's just, it's just a people thing. People like whoever they are
just seem to like dumb shit, I guess, you know, so sure. Yeah, it's a shame because that movie's packed
with talented people and it's like, that could have been like with like a little, a little nuance,
a little grace, a little extra effort. It could have been like a Friday or something like that.
You know what I mean? And it's just like, when you look at the assemblage of, of hilarious black
actors in this movie, I mean, there, there are, it's a stacked bench and man, they try, but like,
I think I, I guess I was listening to Kevin Hart on Marin or something, but he said that the movie
derailed the start of his career by five full years. He was like, it was the kind of failure and like,
people were so appalled by it that like, he had to just kind of sit, sit in the dugout for a while
and wait before he got his big break again. He had to start over. All right. My last rewatch,
and then we'll move on to today's feature is a hilarious picture called Doubt,
starring Philip Seymour Hoffman as a boy fucking priest allegedly. I'm getting movie.
Amazing. Yeah, that's not funny. I'm just joking. It's an amazing film. I bring it up just to say
that exactly that. You want to talk about home run grand slam performances by Philip Seymour Hoffman,
Merrill Streep, Viola Davis, Amy Adams. This thing is impeccable. I envy it. I watch it and I envy it
for two reasons. Number one, I grew up in the Catholic church. I went to Catholic school for
12 years. I grew up in a very Catholic family and a Catholic neighborhood. I have always wanted to
write something about the Catholic church. It's why I love heaven help us so much. It's why I love this
movie so much or one of the reasons. So I envy it for that. And I envy it because this is a writer's
dream is to write something that is this simple and this direct that can somehow keep you on
the edge of your seat. It's uncanny writing. It's really brilliant. You know, while never getting
into the sorted details of the molestation and stuff, it's not it never really tells you much of
anything, but it just kind of holds you completely locked in the whole time. It keeps you guessing the
entire time. I read Patrick Flannery or whatever's name is the guy that wrote it. Patrick Shanley.
Yeah, I read an interview with yeah, I read an interview with him where he was like, my intention
was so you never were quite sure whether he did it or not. And I was like, that was such a relief
because I was scared I was going to read it. And he's going to be like, no, I know that he did it.
And like, the point is that and he was like, no, that's not the point. The point is is you're not supposed
to know. And it's the title. It's just an amazing, amazing film. I would love to see the play. I hope
to God they revive it on Broadway at some point. I always heard about Cherry Jones in that movie was
or in that play. Played the Meryl Streep part and was supposed to be just incredible, but I never saw
it either. So check it out if you haven't seen it. Riveting film. Do you think you did it?
No. And I read it. Well, I don't know. I don't know. I remember thinking you did it. I've seen it
three times. I think you did it. I've seen it about six times at this point. The first few I definitely
didn't think you did it. Then I started to think he might have. But I mean, dude, it's like it's like
so it's like layer overlay, like detail, panel detail of it that you just don't know what to do.
The kids mom says leave the priest alone. Yeah. He's good for the kid. And then you find
then she reveals that she's saying that because the her son is gay and her the father can't deal with it
so the father beats on the kid. So then you don't know if the mom thinks it happened. But she just wants
her son to have some relationship with a man that's normal. Or if she really doesn't think anything
it's fucking nuts, dude. It like it hits you from every angle. The kid that the kid that pulls back
and scowls at Phil Psymer Hoffman and almost seems scared of him like something has happened
is the bad kid that starts shit through the entire movie. Right. It continually gets in trouble.
It's like there's just no direct. None of the every road is a potential dead end that you could
explore. And I think it's a brilliant movie. And Phil Psymer Hoffman said in an interview he goes,
I'll never say whether I think he did it or not because that ruins it. But what I can tell you is
I grew I wrote an entire backstory for that character. So I knew how to play it. So I'm
God, I would love to know like what he thought. But we'll never know, obviously. So
they're really it's and those are some of the best actors of all time. And all three of them give
like some of their best performances. Phil Psymer Hoffman, Meryl Streep, Theola Davis. I maybe had seen
her a couple times, but not much. That's seen with her man. You see why she was like an immediate huge
star. She got nominated. Yeah. She wins or just nominated. I know nominated. I don't know about one.
I don't think she's in it for like five minutes. It's crazy. It's like it's like up there with the
with the Baldwin Glengar, Glenn Rossine. Right. Yeah. No, it's it's it's a hell of a hell of a movie.
And John Patrick Shanley also did Moonstruck, one of the best romantic comedies ever. And Joe versus
the volcano, a very underrated comedy with Hank's and Ryan. I might tune into Joe versus the volcano
because I I long for some classic hanks. You seen it? No, you'd love it, especially the first half
is amazing. Is it funny like classic hanks? It's very funny, but he plays a guy who at the beginning
has a brain cloud, which is what the doctor tells him. And he's just like unbelievably depressed and
miserable. And he works in this horrible office where his boss is Dan Hadea. And he sits next to him
and all day, Dan Hadea is on the phone. And he goes, I'm not arguing that with you.
Madam, I'm not arguing that with you. It goes on and on. And he says it the same way every time.
There's a light, a fluorescent light that just keeps like in the corner. It's sort of a pre -office
space. And then when they get to the volcano, it gets very, very silly and goofy and aid the goadas
in there. And I don't know. I love them. It's very good. I'll check it out.
Today's film, The Wrath of Man, starring Jason Statham, the latest from writer director,
Guy Richie, Star Trek 2, The Wrath of Man. Good to see these two back together. They usually do
some fine work together. Richie's been a little hit and miss over the last few years as is Statham,
but I was happy to see the reunion between two of them. This is your, you know, in the vein of
the John Wicks and all these things. You know, Jason Statham plays a guy who gets hired
to work at a security truck depot banking. You know, they collect the money from the banks and bring
it back to the depot, keep it safe, armored trucks. He gets the job by the skin of his teeth,
barely passes his exam, but they do hire him. And upon his first excursion, they are robbed,
Josh Hartnett back in action. Great to see him again. And I don't know.
Tiny role. I mean, tiny role looks exactly the same, annoyingly the same.
He was the star of that penny dreadful. He's not like had no career sense. I don't know what
led him to take this six line part, but he's good in it. He's great. In this scene where they're
going to have to get Rob Josh Hartnett is freaking out. He's like, we got to get out of here. That's
protocol. Statham says, we're not leaving because they've abducted one of the guards. We're going to,
we're going to go in there and save him. Hartnett is like, you're crazy. And then of course, as you
would expect and hope for desperately, Statham gets out of the truck and murders everybody in five
seconds. And then it becomes a, what is this guy doing here? Who is he really? What is his plan?
And then through a very, very creative storytelling mode of timeline jumps,
he, you learn the backstory why he's there, who he's up against, the whole thing. And
for a movie that starts in with the first 20 minutes being almost so the first 20 minutes of this
thing are so absurd. The lines they're saying the only way I could describe it is it seemed,
it seemed as if it was written by a woman who hated men who was forced to write a movie about what
she thought men were like. They're absurd the lines. It's the ridiculous. And I think when they're
when they're in like the locker room at the precinct, yeah, my name's bullet. We're going to call
you H, you know, there's a scene where they come out of a bank and they're like, how's old Stacey
Dylan or whatever name is? And this bullet guy is like, she's hot to trot today. And then
hot heart and it goes, there's still some juice in that raisin. The lines are absurd. I said to a
friend last night and we were like, I do think that's what it is. I was like, I think I richie is
used to writing for Cockney Englishman. So when he writes for American, like if it was all
the Cockney cast doing those lines, you'd be like kind of laughing and they'd be kind of funny.
But when it's the Americans doing them, it's it just seems weird. It seems meat -heavy. It's like not
funny. But once you hit that point where Statham does the, takes down the robbers, from there on out,
I was like glued to the fucking screen. I was like, I can't wait to see how this ends.
Like I was I loved it. But you got to get through that first 20.
Yeah, and I didn't even mind the first 20. I mean, it's it's really, really well done. I did
I got kind of tired of the guy Richie style movie that he's been doing. I didn't like the gentleman.
I didn't like the man from Uncle or whatever. Like he just he'd been losing me for years. And this
is a really, really solid action movie. It reminded me a bit of Den of Thieves, which is a very similar
underrated action movie that's just way better than you'd expect, way better than it had in your
right to be. What was the one with Schwarzenegger? Sabotage is another one. They're they'd be an amazing
triple feature because they're very similar movies with a lot of twists and big, big action and
macho guys. But like it's just a real solid movie that the plot is sort of overly complicated and go,
you know, plays with time and stuff. But in a time where almost movies are so lazy, I love that.
It felt like they really put, you know, put some time into it. It's a remake of a foreign movie. So
but it's a lot of fun. I actually, I'm sure I've seen him in something but didn't realize it.
Scott Eastwood steals the movie. Clint Eastwood's son. He's a great villain. And he looks so much like a
young Clint, but he's just got this like disgust in his eyes that he really, you really hate him. He's
so good in it. Yeah, he's such a fucking prick. Like he's great. The guy that plays bullet is great.
Like doing like a John candy level of likability in that role. Like, you know, that's a, yeah,
Holt McElenny. I looked his name up, spelled differently than Rob McElenny. But he was so incredible
in mind hunters. The Fincher show on Netflix. And me and Heather were always like, who is this guy?
Turns out he's been in a bunch of Fincher movies and a bunch of movies in little parks, but he's a
great actor. And I loved him. Yes. Hartnett is great. Who plays a prick for once? Hartnett,
you know, doesn't play a prick, but he plays a prick in this whose nickname is boy sweat, which is
such an odd. But uh, um, and then one of the rich, Dave, actually. Yeah. And then one of the rich,
he's another rich, he's staples in there. I forget his name. He's an English actor. He plays the boss
of the depot at any Marathon. Yeah. So, um, I really, I really liked this film a lot. And I liked,
I'll say this about the direction. I feel like this is a movie where Richie really came into his own
as a director and showed that, you know, because Guy Richie was known for one thing. It was like that
music video style, crazy edit, bank ice style thing. It was a lot of fast zooms and snap zooms. And
you know, that was his thing. And he's great at it. And he, you know, I, I think he's the inventor of
that style. It's been mimic many times. But I do see why people kind of start to write him off after
while because it does seem like it's a lot of flash. And if the script isn't there or whatever,
he does none of that and literally none of that in this movie. And he shoots scenes in this that are
so interesting. The opening scene, the camera is in the back of a bank truck as two guys who are driving
the truck or talking and you can't fucking see them. Yeah. And it just, and, and then that truck,
spoiler, this is spoilers, that truck gets robbed. And you see the robbery take place from the
perspective of sitting where the money is in the truck. And it just speaks so much to how caught off
guard these guys are. No pun intended. You know, the blind spot. They don't see it coming. And it just
makes this scene so interesting because it's not, it's not a Michael man style thing where there's
like 360 degree shots going, which I love Michael man, but it's not that thing. And then they zoom in
on the guy with the rifle and, you know, and then it cuts to this guy with the bombs and what it,
it's you just sit in the back of this truck and watch it all happen barely through the windshield.
Yeah. And it's awesome. It's just awesome. And he does a lot of that in this. He really uses
the way he pays off statham in the end of this thing is like, I mean, you get, it's like you
want a cheer, dude, like you know it's coming and he makes you wait for it, dude. He doesn't exhaust
statham through this thing. He sets him up awesomely. And then he makes you wait and you just wait and
wait. And then like in that final sequence, man, when he's on the ground, I'll tie it up and he
finally flips over and gets the guys gun from him. I guess got chills and I'll talk about it.
My friend I was with, she started clapping like it was like, it was awesome. It was just awesome.
Yeah. And it's it's weird. You know, the review, I've seen some reviews that are like like Matt
Zoller -Sites, who's an amazing writer at the New York Times, who I've always loved. He gave this
thing a four out of four and raved about it. And I was like, oh, wow. This must, but then you look at
the other reviews and everybody else was like, hey, typical Jason Statham guy, Rich. No, it isn't.
Yeah. Even if you don't like it, like just try a little harder. If you compare this to all the
Jason Statham movies, they have very little in common. And they, sorry, go ahead. They go out of their
way to show you halfway through this film. This is not the whore with a heart of gold story.
Yeah. Statham is not what Statham is. This is like, yeah, I love the line at the end. Like right
when you're expecting him to finally have this like breakthrough with Josh Hartnitz character,
because they're at odds through the entire film. When you're waiting for him to have this breakthrough
as they're up against the same common enemy at the end of the film. And Josh Hartnitz is like,
and Statham gets his gun and he's going to go after these guys who are trying to take over the depot
and rob everything. And Josh Hartnitz goes, what do you want us to do, man? And you know, at this
moment, we're in every other movie, the guy would be like, now we work together and Statham just goes,
you can do whatever to fuck you like. And just leave some, just watch. And I'm like, I love that they
never fucking compromise on that thing. Also, by the way, uncredited Andy Garcia shows up in this thing.
Crazy. Yeah. Actually, for a second there, I was like, did Andy Garcia pop up for 30 seconds
in Saw Spiral or in Wrath of Man because it's so unexpected. Yeah, he's not credited in the beginning
at all. He just pops up in the middle of the movie. Yeah. It's really, really a cool movie. You
know, it's like a, it's just the action is so well done. I really, really liked that the suspense
works, the story works. And this just as we were talking about with Saw Spiral, this felt to me
like an updated dirty Harry or a 70s Clint Eastwood movie. Yes. Man, maybe it's just Scott Eastwood
being in it, of course, but I got to say I did not expect to come out of this thing saying,
Scott Eastwood is going to be a huge actor, you know, but like, man, he's, I really love the minute.
I really did. And Jeffrey Donovan, the guy from Burn Notice or whatever that show as it was on
for 40 years that no one ever, they were that whole crew of guys was great. Like that whole crew of
the like the expat. I love, I love that detail that this main heist crew that this depot is protecting
themselves from are a bunch of soldiers who can't get work and aren't being taken care of by the
government financially that when you meet these guys, they introduce you to them from out of nowhere.
Dude, you're like an hour into the movie. Yeah. And you're like, who the fuck are these guys?
And it's, it's a bunch of soldiers talking about like how they work at the mall now and stuff like
that. Right. And they're broke and they turn to crime as a way to finally like kind of set things
straight. And then you're like, well, obviously these guys don't have any problem if they have to kill
somebody. They've already had to kill people. Yeah. In the military. And they're, they're squad.
This is their, this is their sergeant. Like they're going to follow him. And they know how to
execute plans and strategies and stuff. So I thought that that was a really, really cool little detail
that allowed you to have some empathy for these crooks. It was just a great flick, man. It's a good,
like nasty little movie. And like, you know, with my action, I would always watch every,
every Schwarzenegger, every Stallone, but I'd never go for the Seagull. When you'd go for the 70s movies,
I'd always go Eastwood, you know, whoever, but I would never go watch a Bronson. But now going
through all these Charles Bronson movies, I'm like, a lot of these are great and fun. And I think
I've got that waiting for me with Statham too. I never checked in with Statham. I love the two
cranks. And I always liked them when he popped up in a, in a fast and the furious or whatever.
But now I've got 20 Jason, Statham movies to go back and hopefully enjoy. I never saw
a transporter. I never saw any of those. Yeah. And I never saw a transporter supposed to be,
he's supposed to be awesome. Yeah, I'm excited to check him out. I mean, he's a, he's got a presence,
you know, and he, I bet he goes through every script and crosses out 99 % of the dialogues. He
doesn't want to say it. I've heard Gosling does that too. But you don't need it when you've got
that much presence and you, and you can convey what you want. Like you know what Jason Statham
wants and needs out of this movie. And you don't need him to flap his gums the whole time. But when
he does, it's, it's always a funny, great line. I'm a, I'm a fan. I was, I was surprised. And it's,
we're in this weird time where, when something has 100 % rotten tomatoes score, you can almost
guarantee you're going to watch it and go, what? Yeah. Everyone thought this was great. Bill and
Ted three or whatever. And then Wrath of Man will have like a 42 and you're like, what? You know,
it seems like people don't even know what's good anymore. Yeah. I agree. I agree. Two hugs up firmly
for the Wrath of Man. I loved it. Upcoming shows. I think next we're going to do Quiet Place 2
an army of the dead. And that will be followed by conjuring three and potentially the dentist
unless something else steps in in front of it. But I finally saw the dentist. And that's a ride worth
talking about. I've always wanted to see the dentist. And what else do we got? We got conjuring two,
we're conjuring three in the coming months. Yeah. So we got some.
Conjuring three will be early. It'll be like first week of July. We could do it in June,
but let's get army of the dead out of the way with Quiet Place 2 since they came out first. All right,
folks. Joe, there was a comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Check out the Taste Buds pod. That's it for
me. Thank you for listening. Thank you for your support. Thank you, Emily, for all you do for us.
We love all you guys. Love you very much. Thank you for coming on this Patreon journey with us.
I just stumbled upon a treasure trove of Instagram DMs that I had never noticed and a lot of you
have sent great stuff. We see your messages on the Patreon. It might take a bit, but we do see them.
Thank you, spread the word. If we got new fans, welcome aboard. I was wrong about Rathamann. It
has a 66 % on tomato meter. But here's just one random review. I saw the first one wrestling just
enough stakes out of its thin plot. It doesn't have a thin plot. It has an incredibly complicated plot.
It's because it's yeah, it's just it's dumb. Anyway, yeah, it's dumb. I think they're having a hard time
getting good critics because it pays like $5 a review. I mean, I understand. It's not a it's not a
way to make a good living, unfortunately. Anyway, we're living in like a peyola level of Hollywood
crit. Anyway, yeah, we will be back. We've got some big horror titles coming up. We will see you
next time and we'll see you in hell.