I see you in hell.
Hey, when the shine of your screens,
there comes a thing on the dream.
You know I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I see you in hell.
You the fucker.
Folks, welcome to.
We'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear
a review of the monsters. We've got today for you. Cut to our subscriber list going down
like in a sitcom when somebody says something bad on a telephone, the numbers start dropping.
I just looked at myself here. I look particularly Irish today. Jesus Christ.
Yeah, you do. And it's a good thing. You look, it looks good. Yeah, it looks, it looks like I'd be like
part of Dennis Leary's entourage. Dennis, wait up, buddy. Dennis, wait up. That's all I do. I tell
them to wait up if he's going too fast. Dennis, Dennis, we got, we got to go the car.
You're the guy. The car, Dennis, we got to go. Yeah. Yeah. Joe, uh, what's going on is I had,
I had so almost an emergency therapy session yesterday. You know, I don't believe in God,
but I'm sitting there like something is wrong. I've had a flutter in my chest for like a week,
not a heart thing at all. It's an anxiety thing and I recognize it because it flares up occasionally
or before a show or something, but it's been permanent and it's like, I'll be watching a movie
and I'll get the anxiety flare up. And I'm like, what am I even thinking about that's causing
this? And it was becoming a bit of a problem, to be honest. And it's just a lot of stuff. Joe and I were
trying to say yesterday, it's like, okay, is this me stopping drinking and weed, Joe was stopping
drinking for health reasons. I'm doing it for a variety of reasons. Is it, I'm stopping for a little
bit. I'm not permanent. Yeah. Is it PTSD from COVID? Is it, is it immediate after effects from my
COVID that I just had? My therapist said she has a patient who started having severe panic attacks
out of the blue right after he got COVID. I said, I got to tell you, I feel like I'm circling severe
panic attacks. And she said, well, in researching it for him, she found out that COVID can exacerbate
the worst parts of your mind. So like if you're a, you know, if you're somebody who obsesses
over things, it makes you triply obsess over things. And I said, well, when does that go away? I'm
nobody knows. So I woke up yesterday. And again, haven't drank anything with a splitting headache,
my heart going a mile a minute. And I was like, something's got to give here. I was going to call
the therapist. She happened to text me like a the exact moment. It was a beautiful thing. I went
over there. We had a very nice talk, kind of calm me down. And then last night, this story is a little
personal, but too good not to share. And then I'll turn the floor to you, Jim. Please.
Last night, I was like, okay, I'm not going to sit in this house bouncing off the walls again.
I go out with a young lady, come back to the house. We have just a fantastic evening. Girl,
girl brings over. Get again, a little personal, but girl brings over. We've hung out a few times.
A board game called sex, Jenga, where each block that you pull out either has a certain side of
yourself. Each block either has a sexually provocative question for your partner, or it has a
sexually provocative dare for your partner. And these things, I mean, this game was 20,
but this was not on all ages, Milton Bradley. Like, I pull out the first thing. I'm thinking it's
going to be like Eskimo kiss your partner. Rob noses or something. The first thing is like,
my butt fucking your partner. I was like, what? It was graphic. I got way more graphic from there.
Great night. A lot of fun. Just what I needed. And because it was such, that's kind of a wild
night for me. And it took my mind off everything completely. I was just having a lot of fun.
So we go downstairs to the bedroom. And we're making out. And she goes, can you turn on some music?
And I go, absolutely. What kind of music do you like? I go, do you like, you bang into a
Metallica? Or you like something a little smooth? You know, jazz? What are we talking? And I go,
I don't know. The latest Santana record. I go, I go, because I like to bring comedy into the bedroom,
too, Joe. I don't think it doesn't have a place there. I go, I know what I'll do. I go, give
me a song that you love that you would like to have sex to. And then I'll click one of the,
you can do on Spotify. You click the song and it gives you an immediate playlist off of that song,
like similar vibe songs. Yeah, yeah. A little feature. So she's thinking and she goes,
hmm, and she goes, you know what song? I have always wanted to fuck to. I go, what?
All right. Because make it which you by the Queens of the Stone Age. Oh, jeez.
I go, you like the Queens of the Stone Age? I blow it off and kind of laugh and I play the song
and we do the, we do the D. Okay. But Joe, what you're forgetting.
And what you have no penis. Well, you're forgetting and what these people don't know is that my
wedding song was make it which you by the Queens of the Stone Age. Oh, boy. There, there are 50
billion songs in the world. When this girl said that, I looked her in the eye and I was like,
this girl's fucking with me or this is a friend of a, something's going on. Yeah, here I go. And I
almost just laughed and said that this is so crazy, but that was my wedding song. And I knew that
would kill the mood. So I just played it. And honestly, it was kind of cathartic to be making out with
somebody to this song, you know, but I'm not as up on my Queens as you are. Make it which you is
is like a, that's like a fast one, isn't it? For a wedding song, I mean, is it not? Our first dance
was to make it which you and you can dance to it. It's kind of, it's, you could, you can definitely
dance to it. But I'm saying it's kind of a grinded to it. You know, it's a sexy song. It's a song about
fucking. And it's a song about fucking for all time. You know, that's the point of the song. But I told
her this morning, took her to the house of pies because I'm a gentleman. And luckily, she thought
it was funny, but she was kind of mortified. She was like, I wish she'd said something. I was like,
I guarantee that would have ended in you and a lift going home.
Me cranking it out on the deck, howling at the full moon.
Coming on the neighbors below. Jesus. God almighty. All right, take it over, Joe. I've been,
I've been flapping my gums. I just thought that story. Like if I was doing stand -up, I'd be like,
oh, that's a good one. You know, the new girl requesting the wedding song.
Oh, boy. Well, I got nothing. I got nothing to follow that. I'm dealing with some health issues.
You know, I don't want to get too into it. Dear listeners, but there's some stuff going on.
It's, it's, it's, it's treatable. But it's nothing. It's rickets, rickets, it's rickets,
it's crickets. Oh, it's the old gamut. I'm suddenly haunted by the video of when Adam Yacht announced
that he had cancer with Mike D and they were laughing. And Adam Yacht goes, I probably should be laughing.
It's not funny. And then he died. I don't have cancer. But I am making light of a, of a health thing.
That again, it's treatable. But some major changes need to happen. Primarily dietary and,
and booze related, which is not easy. Not easy. I had a little incident today that set me off.
And I just, you know, you just want to go to the nearest bar and have maybe the one you own.
And half a shoe, tune out for a minute. And I couldn't, which I guess overall was healthy.
You know, it's going to be a real challenge this weekend. I'm doing Skankfest in Vegas,
which is a fucking four day party. And I'm only going to be there for two and a half days.
But that's going to be a tough one. So, so I don't know, man. But where do they do the shows there at
what hotel? They're at, they got a venue. I don't know the name of the venue of Tommy Heppard. It's
an old Vegas. It's worst case scenario for not trying to drink. Comedy festival, all your friends
downtown Vegas all under one roof. It's worst case fucking scenario. The, the most you'll spend for
a drink in downtown Vegas is one dollar. Yeah. My plan right now is to do my sets and immediately go
to a black jack table and god, you're making me honestly just got me hard. Grip the edges of it.
Well, a shake trying not to drink. And then, you know, the waitress comes over and I'm because I'm
losing. I'm like, whatever, two lines.
Sucking the juice out of the line. Oh, boy. I've been off six about a year.
That's not helping right now. You know, it is what it is, man. But, but it's been a hard, admittedly,
a hard, I still have to get some other tests done. And again, it'll probably be okay, but it's
really nerve wracking. And that's not me being dramatic. Like there are things that hopefully won't
be wrong, but could be. And it's fucking freaky. And, you know, and I know I haven't been the easiest
person to deal with. Walsh, I apologize. I've been very on edge lately. I know you and I have had a
text tip or two. I'm sorry about that. I mean, that's a place.
Walsh and I yesterday were talking about the incidents we've had in the last few days where we've
cried for no reason. Yeah, I was telling my therapist about how I've gone to house and paused several
times. I don't get pause. I just sit there like I can have coffee and write and have a little breakfast
at the time. It's fun. It's where Pat runs his real estate side hustle, which is why nobody takes
it seriously. Pat, you can't do it at house of pies. I hold a folded up newspaper that kind of like
shields my plans. Can I? I put the coffee on it to circle the the the ad that I want to cross
for me to look at. Client sits down. You go, do you like pie? So do I. You know what else I like?
Houses. And that's how you start every every. Yeah, two slices of pie. What are you going to have,
sir? By the way, that little laugh I did was John Candy, of course, but he, Colin Hanks, who was a
I guess a little more than on a acquaintance of mine, the nicest guy. He used to like me on mine and
that we kept in touch, but he did a Queens of the Stone Age documentary. He did an Eagles of death metal
documentary. Both were fantastic. And now he and Ryan Reynolds are making a John Candy documentary.
That's very exciting. I read about that and I feel like it's a perfect pair because I feel like
hey, I never met Colin Hanks. He seems like the nicest guy, but also there's connection,
connective tissue through through his dad, you know, his dad and Candy didn't stuff together.
And then Ryan Reynolds, I feel like is like and Rita Wilson, by the way, that's very cool.
And I think Ryan will volunteers. Yeah, Rita Wilson for all the same reasons. And then
and then Ryan Reynolds, I feel like there's almost like a new type of John Candy. Like, you know,
I feel like if John Candy was alive and young, he'd be doing like some of the movies Ryan Reynolds does,
the comedies, I mean, sort of meant not dead. I'm going to go ahead and I don't see the connection
there at all, but, but okay, you don't think you'd see a Ryan Reynolds, I mean, a John Candy and a
just married were, or no, I'm sorry, not just married. Yes, friends and cut your mixed up.
Yeah, you could see him maybe in a just maybe, you know, Reynolds. I'm excited to see a holiday movie
out with Will Ferrell. Like, I don't know, I don't think it's that. Okay. All right.
Well, they got access through the Candy family and kids to all the vaults, all the home movies,
all the everything. You know, it's going to be a tearjerker. You know, it's going to be amazing.
You know, they're going to talk to all the top folks. And also huge news. Thank you to all the
hellians who sent me this link. Text to me this link. Obviously, I've already pre -ordered it. They
are releasing a 4k plans, trans automobiles on November 8th. And the big news is there's over
an hour of deleted scenes. So the three hour cut that has always been rumored,
this thing's got pretty much all the cut footage. I'm excited to see it. Yeah. I wish it was an
assembled three hour cut. Sure. But I am excited to see it. And I'm curious to see how it
pairs up to the small amount of deleted footage we've already seen. But the one major deleted,
we've talked about it here, the one major deleted scene. The brownie scene. Yeah. It's amazing.
That scene is incredible. That had to hurt him to cut that. Like just, I mean, the whole thing
is just start to finish. Well, the trailer for plans, trans, contains several, several things
that are not in the movie. So I'm excited to see this. Yeah. That's good scary stuff news.
I got to scary stuff here. Where the hell is my document? There it is.
No, I'm sorry. That's news psycho. I have a news psycho. I can't believe I'm saying this.
The trailer for Super Mario Bros. movie came out and it looks good. I cannot believe it.
It looks good. Wait, now I didn't watch this thing, but the entire internet spent three days
talking shit about this thing. Well, the biggest gripe, and it's very, very justified,
is the guy, I forget his name, the voice actor that did Mario, that's done Mario in all the games
for the last, yeah, over 20 years, was booted out. Like they just replaced him with Chris Pratt.
The guy is Mario, he's the voice. So I agree with the backlash about this fucking guy helped
you sell a product and helped bring your character to life and you just throw them aside
because you want to put a name on the poster. When at the end of the day, as you've mentioned,
it's John Malini's joke. Nobody's watching the movie and going, oh, that's Chris Pratt, no kid
gives shit. And the super fans of Nintendo certainly are the ones that are going to get offended.
So I think that was a bad move. I maybe even Nintendo doesn't have the clout to get a movie made
without putting a celebrity in first position, but who knows anymore? I think they strayed from it
because they're in this, or potentially strayed from it because in this climate with everything,
they're getting away with fire by having a blonde -haired white guy from America doing what's basically
a stereotypical Italian man's voice, but they just did that in house of Gucci and it was fine.
So I don't know. Like, you know, maybe the guys are telling the actor. I don't know, but you know,
I don't know. I don't really know what the reason is for that. I got to admit,
I was a fan. Is he looking for the princess? Is that the plant?
They don't really tell you what the plot is, is that King Koopa is clearly taking over worlds and
Mario's got to save the mushroom. Okay, I mean, that's basically what it is. But Kendrick Lamar will
re -record King Koonta as King Koopa. I wouldn't doubt it. There will definitely be some sampled wrap
Mario Brothers theme thing connected to this. They do the thing in the trailer. Oh,
God, I hate this so much though. Like, when Mario pops up, by the way, what I was going to say was
I was always a fan of the like Brooklyn version of Mario versus the like, sure.
I never really cared for that voice, but it's the voice and it did well and maybe they should
honor it. Anyway, I um, they did this thing in the trail. I hate this so much.
Like, it's the first time he pops out into the mushroom kingdom. It's the first time you're seeing
Mario. It's like the lone piano that goes, Bing, Bing, Bing. And you're like,
just play the fucking music for Christ's sake. Like every fucking trailer has to be the
Oh, you mean like them? They're going to go. Ding, ding, ding, ding. Yeah. And then the
orchestral version comes in. They did it. I saw a leaked version of the new, this is another
news cycle. Actually, I saw a leaked version of the new Indiana Jones trailer. And even through the
foggy iPhone footage that I saw it on. Holy shit. It is a, it is fucking awesome. It is. All right.
Awesome. Did it go. Yes. Yes, it does that. And it and it sort of works a little better for Indiana
Jones because it's Indiana Jones. But like, but like God damn it, man. Anyway, let's go to the movie
corner. Let's go to that movie corner. I then watching some shit. A lot of Halloween shit
coming out. A lot of scary shit. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. You know, I won. I'd love to talk about,
Joe, did you ever talk about this? I feel like you did dark night of the scarecrow
with Chuck Durning. I don't think I have. I don't know if I've talked about it. I don't remember.
But it's a, it's a fun one. It's a, it's a made for TV harm movie that actually is kind of scary.
Yeah. I love, well, I didn't love it. I liked it. And I guess it aired on CBS the year of my birth
1981. They got Larry Drake playing a mentally handicapped man, which he has done 10 times. How
do you, how are you the go -to guy to play? I mean, it's so strange. He's a mentally handicapped man
or a lunatic. Right. It's Dr. Giggles. It's a deranded dark man or the guy on LA law or the scarecrow.
So at the beginning, Larry Drake is hanging out with this young girl. Larry Drake's, you know, 35,
40 years old. He takes the girl home and a dog attacks her. But the neighborhood is always
suspicious of him, especially Charles Durning, who's like the neighborhood asshole and steals the movie.
Without Durning, you don't have the movie, am I? He's amazing in it. By the way, like, and it's like
modern day, like it's, it takes place in 1970, whatever it was made. Yeah. And Durning is leading a
full -on Lynch mob. Right. Yeah. Yeah. He immediately latches on to this handicapped guy must have
killed this young girl and gathers up some townsfolk. They tie him to a scarecrow pole and they all
shoot him a thousand times. That's like the first act break of a CBS TV movie. And from there, Larry
Drake, like I guess it's never really explained, which is kind of cool. And habits the scarecrow.
And you never see the scarecrow running around. You never see the scarecrow at all. But
what you gather, I guess they didn't have the money for effects, is that the scarecrow is
taking out the people who committed vengeance against him one by one. And it's very fun and very
well done. And I enjoyed it. The kills are cool. Durning steals the show. And it's one of those
where the real evil is of course within human beings. It's great. Where did you see it? Did you buy it?
They have a flawless, beautiful print of it on shutter right now. They'd put up a brand new
revised like 4k version of it. Man, to be in shutter right now, really hitting home runs with the
horror. I shutter has seven new movies a day. Yeah, it's pretty, it's pretty amazing. I,
I'm going to do everything from this box set, which I don't remember if I plugged the box set yet,
but this is scary stuff if I haven't. And if I have, it's a scary stuff again. I got the all the
Haunt's BR's box set, which is Severance Compendium of Folcar. It is so worth the money if you can get
the sale price on it. The sale price is still steep. You're going to pay 150 bucks for this thing
when it's on sale, but you're getting like 19 movies, including the amazing folk horror documentary
that they released on shutter. There's crazy amounts of bonus footage, all kinds of foreign
silent movies. Half of these movies on here have been restored. They were lost for years. They were
dead. But I've watched three of these so far. The first being Eyes of Fire, which is the first movie
on the set. It's from 1983, I believe it was an American released movie. It was written and directed
by a guy that never wrote and directed ever again. He was a fairly renowned photographer. I forget his name.
And it starts sort of like the witch. It takes place like on the American Frontier.
There's a clergyman who's come to a village to lead it spiritually. He is
adultering with women. They go to hang him and his sort of not daughter by blood, but a girl
that he's the caretaker for because he saved her when her mother was burned at the stake.
He has magic powers and she saves him when they try to hang him. So as a result of that,
they are sort of banished like the family in the witch and they go and start their own colony and
the terror ensues. A lot of fun. Not as artsy -farty as the witch, but you certainly see way more.
You get a lot of good witch time on screen. It was fun. It was just really fun. It was a great
way to start the box set. It let you kind of let you know we're out of the bat. Hey, this is a serious
box set, but we're not taking ourselves too seriously. We're going to put some fun movies in here
along with some really wild foreign films and experimental stuff and it's a great box set.
So that's a chamber. No, that's eyes of fire. I'll review which. Oh, you'll get to witch.
I want to sing which hammer when we get to it. Okay. I would love. I'm thrilled to be able to shout out
a genuinely funny program that genuinely lifted my spirits for four straight hours the other night.
I watched all eight episodes did not leave the couch and I'm honored to say I know the men
responsible for it. John Gabriel is one of my dearest friends. We go hiking a couple of times
a week. Love the man. He's a dream. You've probably heard him on podcasts and shit. He's a
comedian comedy actor. It's him and Adam Pally who I know a bit and you might recognize from
happy endings and he does stand up and stuff as well. Very funny man. These two are very old friends.
They have amazing chemistry and they travel the glow. I mean, Joe, it's the dream. You know,
we get to they basically would end in the show or real life. They do this. They pitch like the trip.
Basically, they were like, we want to go to eight kind of cheap places in America because they're
a picture of true TV. So you got to be kind of cheap and we go there and drink and smoke weed and
black out and have fun and get an adventures. It's basically insomniac. Let's be real. What is
the show called? It is. Oh, sorry. I thought I had said it. It's called 101 Places to Party before
you die. Oh, wow. And it was on true TV. It is currently on HBO Max, which means they could be
thrown in the ocean any day now. Who knows? But it's so fun. They are two extremely funny
quick guys who are very, very funny together. Yes. And to watch them enjoy each other is part of the fun.
And it's just them. You know, it's a foodie show. They eat amazing shit. They drink a lot.
And you get to see cool parts of cool cities. I love the Atlanta one, of course.
That's one you could start with, but you can't go wrong. Great show.
I'll check it out. I like both of them. And I like the idea of traveling and eating and drinking.
Yeah, we got to get our own show. It would be nice, wouldn't it? Yeah.
We both die halfway through season two of a shared heart attack. I don't get my hopes up.
Anyway, um, which show got the head of true TV on set? Yeah. Yeah. I think I'll be a harsh
dragger across the floor. Uh, which hammer? I want to be your witch hammer.
Go ahead. Uh, which hammer? This is the second movie I watched in this box set.
Uh, which hammer is from 1968. And it was made in the Czech Republic as a black and white film.
That is about a witch trial that's happening during the inquisition. Uh, and a witch master general.
That is sort of brought out of retirement, uh, by a indignant priest
to solve the witch issue in the priest village, the witch you wish you. Yeah. Make it with you.
And needless to say things go awry. Uh, it's, I don't want to give away too much because Pat
is going to be purchasing this box that I believe. So it's one thing for me to spoil things on the show
and you can fast forward through it. But I don't want to spoil it to you in real time where you have to
hear it. Um, to you, Pat, I mean, thank you. But, um, this movie is almost not, it's not even really a
horror movie this one. It's just sort of a drama about how the shit went and it's bleak.
It's fucking hopeless. And I loved every minute of it.
Uh, amazing performances, not a lick of English. That's one of the things
that I'm enjoying about this box that it's sort of breaking my
adversity to subtitles, not that I wouldn't watch some type of movies before.
But I always sort of roll my eyes like god damn it. I gotta read it.
I don't want to read it. Have the meaning dinner when I watch a movie. It's like I want to look down
at my plate if I need to. But this, these movies have really been kind of breaking me out of that
and making that sort of a second sense when watching the movie. So, well, it's good too because then
your nose isn't on your phone. You got to pay attention the whole time. Yeah, true. But which hammer was
great. Uh, and just gorgeously shot and brilliantly acted and poetically written the dialogue
in it is just wonderful. So check her out. I'm getting it. I would love to recommend to horror fans
this Halloween season. Another show that kind of for the four or five hours I watched it was just
like a great distraction. Uh, it is called the 101 scariest horror movie moments of all time.
It's a great companion piece or update to that old bravo show that I must have watched 5 ,000 times
which was the same thing basically. Remember that Joe the bravo it was easy to show it every Halloween.
I love it. I love it. And it's and it's a kin to Eli Roth's program too. Yeah.
Yeah. This I would say is a just a perfect update of the old bravo model. They make really great
smart choices. They have for the most part, um, if not huge names, they have really intelligent
commentators. I will say the one that baffles me beyond belief is Kevin U -Banks the bassist
for the tonight show with Leno. I don't know. I don't know how he wound up on this panel. The man
has never scored a movie. He I don't know that he's seen a movie. But, um, our boy Dana Gould is one
of the commentators. Dana's Dana and Mick Ganty of course. Yeah. Garrison Dana in particular. I'm
just like every time I watch them on one of these things, I'm just like, I don't understand how you
know so much. It's like wild. Dante too. It's wild. They've they've seen like there's the one.
Now I watched the first episode of this and then I stopped watching it because I was like there's
too many movies in this that I haven't seen yet that I want to see and they're showing me some of the
coolest parts. One of them was was Black Sabbath with Boris Carlisle which I've never seen for whatever
reason. Uh, it's pretty good. It's pretty good. So I backed away from it, but but it's a very well done
show. But like like when they were talking about like the old RKO movies and like Dana was just like
the whole thing about like everybody goes to Universal and Universal's great. But there was a whole other
studio RKO on these. It's like an encyclopedic knowledge of this stuff. It's really impressive.
Especially for a guy who doesn't work in horror. I mean, sort of does, but you know what I mean?
He's more of a comedy guy. Mick Garrison, at least I'm like, well, that's your field. Right. You
That's a good show. Yeah, I dig it. It's a great sort of mindless Saturday entertainment. Love it.
Last one I'll talk about from the box set is called V or VIA as they pronounce it in the movie.
This is a horror movie from I think the 60s earlier 60s it seems.
Or maybe it's even the 70s. I don't know. But this is from Russia.
This is a film about a fairy tale or an old folktale that they tell you on a title card at the
beginning of the film that the folktale has just been committed to film. The writer didn't change
anything. He's like, this is how it was told to me. And this is how it's told. And I'm going to show
to you. It's about a seminarian who spends a night when he's on his leave spends a night in a
witch's shack. Okay. And finds out that the woman the old woman there is a witch.
And then through a series of circumstances is eventually charged to pray over a young woman who is
dying for three days. And it goes from there. Again, I don't want to really spoil anything.
This thing is so visually stunning. It looks like one of the old techno color movies from the 40s
or 50s. It's so bright and beautiful. It looks like one of those old.
Here's so the trailer for like the Dr. Sus movie they made in the 50s that looks terrifying.
Oh, yeah, I never saw that. It's just got that look to it. There are visuals in this thing
throughout where I was like, how the fuck did they just do that? It feels like you're watching
a fairy tale. And man is the payoff amazing in the third act. It's just awesome. It's awesome.
I've just this box set is showing me stuff I never would have seen in a million years.
Hats off to Severin, man. Good work. And an underdog in comparison to like screen factory or
or criterion or whoever. Yeah, you know, but they're another one of these like, you know, sort of
label is the wrong word, but I don't know what you'd call it. You know, they're a part of shout.
I aren't there. Am I wrong? I don't think so. I think. Okay. They're out there. All right. All right.
But Severin put out, I think the angry is the angry dwarf Severin. Hold on. I'm going to get
this book. Yeah. Severin puts out really interesting stuff. Like they put out the sinful
dwarf. Excuse me, which I own, which is a batshit movie. Bright name. They put out anthro
ho fegos, which the cover is a man. Terrible. You've seen it. Joe Bob did it. It was awful. Yeah.
Awful. I thought I bought it on blind faith because the man is eating his own intestines on the cover.
I mean, look, this just was not not for me. I didn't even Joe Bob was like, this one sucks, folks.
All right. But Severin, you know, I got the sinful dwarf years and years and years ago,
and the bonus features were just two guys being interviewed about the movie.
Right. And I was like, I think these guys are Severin. Yeah. And I think they've sort of grown
into a much bigger operation at this point. Right. So anyway, check, check it out. Check out the box
at all the hotspr. If you can, that brings us whether we want to or not to our movie this week,
the monsters directed by Rob Zombie. More human than human.
Funny bit we used to do on the bonfire pat. You'll appreciate this. When the bonfire radio show,
we used a bit about how every Rob Zombie, every Rob Zombie song title sounds like
he's ordering a special limited time burger at the best food drive through it. I'll have the
Thundercast 65 psycho drag. Uh -huh. With mayo. Can you get it with onions? It's always like turbo
charge 5000 or whatever. Yeah. I mean, boy, they played that song in every action movie trailer for
so long. He must have gotten so rich. And look, if this is what he wants to do with his money, I mean,
this movie feels like a child who had a dream who grew up to do it. And he doesn't care if anyone
likes it or not. I don't know if he thought people would enjoy this. I don't know if the actors
thought people would enjoy this on set. But you know, this is a travesty. It's a god damn travesty.
I was I'm stumped by this. I got to say you knew from the trailer. You knew it was off.
But it's off for here's what I don't okay. So there's there's a lot of ground to cover. Here's
what I don't understand. Excuse me for a man that understands
the product. He understands the product. His Halloween remix sucked. But he understood Halloween
like to an extent. Right. Visually, you know, it's suspenseful. Whatever you want to call it,
you could watch his remake of Halloween and go, I don't care for this interpretation. I don't like
it. But it's a Halloween movie more or less. Yeah. This thing. And to me, more of a
flavor, more of a personality than the latest ones. I would say it's hard to say I prefer them,
but I guess I prefer rob zombies to the new ones because just because they're more of a movie.
They tried more. I think I would agree. I don't know if I would agree with that. I don't know.
But it's a tough one. That's just real. Yeah. But anyway, this monster's man.
I'm like, this seems like he never even saw the show before. Like, I don't understand.
Well, he is supposed to be a TV pilot. Why is it an orange origin story that never comes to fruition?
Like, I don't understand. You really feel it. The only character that really kind of sort of
barely works is Herman because the guy is kind of funny actor. Not that I laughed, but he's kind
of a funny actor. And he's not in the first half hour. That the first half hour to me was just
punishing. And I'm not saying it got much better. I'm just saying it starts out in this graveyard
with the fact guy from lost and their Robin graves or whatever. Then they're switching stories
every 30 seconds. You can't even get your bearings. You don't even know what you're watching.
The title, the title card reveal is a bad payoff for something that should be built and built
and built with this huge reveal. It's a terrible payoff. The graphics they use for the credits are
terrible, which that's the first head scratch to me where I'm like, what is happening here?
I disagree with you. I think the only redeeming quality in the whole film is Daniel Robuck as
grandpa. There were like a few moments where I kind of chuckled a little bit at something he said.
And the actor playing the grave robber, the scientist who makes Herman has a moment or two that are
kind of funny. I don't, I mean, the guy playing Herman is, look, everybody else is passable. It's
like Sherry Moon Zombie. Sherry Moon Zombie. Yeah. She's like passable as Lily and monster, but
she's like, but she's like, it's like a mad TV sketch and it's like if they just did a sketch and
you're like, you're, you're Lily monster. You could do it. You could pull it off for four minutes
in this sketch. Right. It's, it's, and that's how I thought about Herman where he's not even,
that's the other confusing thing. Daniel Robuck is doing like a rendition of grandpa from the show
sometimes and then other times he's not at all. Sherry Moon Zombie is doing a straight up impersonation
of Lily monster from the sitcom. Herman is nothing like the, the Fred Gwyn portrayal. Yeah, he's
doing like a real broad comedy kind of voice, like a comedian voice, because they, I don't know if
that was part of Herman monster's lore, but this guy gets a stand -up comedian's brain.
Brackenstein. Yeah. No, it's not part of the original lore, but I, I thought that was kind of an
interesting funny idea like, oh, he's a comedian that's so bad, the audience murders him. Right.
And that's the brain that goes in Herman, which is why Herman always makes these terrible jokes.
But then they show the, they showed the comedian who is killed, who the brain comes from. And he's
like depressed, dejected and monotone. And then when his brain goes into Herman, he's like big and
blestress and animated and he laughs all the time. It doesn't make any sense. What's none of the dots
connect in this movie at all? It's crazy. It's crazy. It's, it really is. It really, really is. And
also he makes these terrible jokes the whole time. He pretty much all his dialogue is terrible
jokes. But then everybody else makes terrible jokes too. It's not like it's just Herman's thing.
They're all grandpa, everybody are making bad jokes, winks to camera kind of shit,
goes on and on. So how long would you think that a like neon, neon movie that looks like something
that would air on Nickelodeon at night? How long would you think like a monster's with no real
story outside of like a bear, a bear sketch? How long do you think it would last?
80 minutes tops. This thing is 150. 150. That's why I was on and on and on. They take a trip to
Paris that looks so bad. The set is made of like cardboard. It looks so horrible. And the graphics are
like Microsoft paint, like sub Austin powers, which was supposed to look bad. They like spin this
sign that's like gay parry. And now you're supposed to be in Paris. How about the cartoon where
they're like traveling? Well, that's what I'm getting to when they go to New York and Rockefeller center
and shit, they do that in a black and white cartoon. And I get that it was COVID and you probably
ran out of money. Everybody in the movie is playing dual roles and they can't play them. They're
they can't back that up. The witch and the month, what is her name? Sherry Moon. No, I mean the
lily monster, the witch and Lily, she doesn't distinguish them enough. Who's the witch?
The witch with the green face? No, that's not that's not Lily. The witch. Oh, that wasn't her. The
witch is Elvira. It must made me spit out my water. The witch is the real estate agent played by Elvira,
the lady that plays Elvira. I thought she was doing both because they kept doing the camera like when
Michael J. Fox talks to himself and back the future to Sherry is also the newscaster woman that's like,
this is the news. It's like it is the it's terrible. How about her born date at the beginning with
the guy who keeps showing her pictures of his, whoa, I thought that point was kind of, I thought that
part was kind of funny. Like I was like, oh, that's kind of funny. Like, no, she's on a blind day with
no, that's right. And he's like proud of all of his rats. Right. That's kind of funny. Okay, you're
okay. You're right. It's not a bad idea. I just wasn't executed. Yeah. And like that's the thing.
Like they'll do a bit like that. And I'm like, okay. And then like, but then like every other joke,
not every other joke, but mostly every other joke. And I guess it's Rob Zombie, kind of again,
winking to cameras, you said. But it's these the laziest jokes like like everything just has the word
ghoul substituted for it. So it'll be like it'll be like cold ghoul creamery. You know what I mean?
You're just like, how many times you're going to inject the word ghoul into something? Yeah.
Long ghoul silvers, Rob, really? Really? Really, really, Rob, long ghoul silvers. But the craziest part
is there's a third type of joke in this movie. And this is where I was scratching my head. Yeah.
There are flat out Randy sex jokes throughout the movie. And I'm like, Rob, what are you doing here?
Is this like a Disney movie for kids or not? Because you got like sex jokes in this, which is weird
to just have them in this. It's just weird. And then, and then also some of the visuals like when the
grave, when the scientist guy gets leprosy, and he turns to reveal his face that has leprosy,
it is disturbing looking. Yeah, it was. Rob, this is like, I thought this was like for like
nine -year -olds. What the fuck is going on here, man? Well, I don't know how dumb kids are, but I can't
imagine kids liking this either. They have no ties to the monsters. They might like looking at
monsters or something walk around. I like monsters when I was a kid. But it's not entertaining for adults.
Maybe a dumb child would like it, a really dumb child. He thought that out said it is family
humor. I'm like, okay. Okay, so you're watching this with the kids. And there's a joke in there about
how the guy down the street is trying to hire a pool boy, even though he doesn't have a pool.
That's a weird joke to put into a kid's move, a family movie. Sure. You know, it's weird to put
when the tomb is rock and don't come and knock it. It's a weird thing to inject into a family movie.
It's just odd. I will say, though, you look back at some of those 80s movies. They got questionable jokes
as well, you know. Yeah, I mean, these stuff are penis breath and ET, that kind of stuff. It's always
been around. Sure. I for some reason, I am particularly square when it comes to sex humor in a family
movie. I don't understand it. I think it's weird. There's nothing. There's nothing
weirder to me than encountering anything that's to do with sex when you're with your parents.
Right. No, it's fine for some reason. But anyway, the plot of the movie is lily lily needs a husband.
She can't find one grandpa offers to make her one. She says no. And instead ends updating a man
that was made by a different scientist, which just convolutes everything. Yeah. They move. They get
married. They move to the States from a guest Transylvania. For some reason, only a few people on their
journey see them or notice them in all faint and scream. Yeah. There's a terrible gag in the middle of
this thing when they're flying to the States where the entire crew of the plane, the stewardesses on
the plane are jumping off the plane with parachutes because they're so horrified by the monsters.
But then when they land, the pilots are helping them down the stairs and the pilots aren't freaked out.
It's like, it doesn't make any fucking sense. Right. If it makes any sense, anyway,
Herman, because he's naive and stupid, signs a very bad business deal with lily's brother who's a
werewolf. I don't know if that's from the show or not. But that's what it is in the movie. Yeah,
that's the one black guy on the entire film is the werewolf. Yes. Yeah. And then at the, this is how the
movie ends. They move to their new neighborhood in the last 20 minutes. Yeah. Mockingbird line. Right.
They're terrified by they move there on Halloween. So everybody thinks they're in a costume and they
think and everybody's in costumes. So they think that everybody looks like them. The next day,
they are horrified when they realize none of their neighbors look like them. They all look like normal
people. Again, they've encountered normal people throughout the entire movie. It doesn't make any sense
that now they're freaked out by nor none of this adds up. And then here's the end. Here's the end.
The brother comes back and goes, congrats. That deal you sign with me paid off and Herman goes,
we're rich. And that's where the movie ends. Well, not before some of the oddest shots I've ever seen
in a film when they do like slow zooms on each person celebrating the money. And then the credit's
role, that was one of the worst shot and edited sequences I have ever seen. The final shots of this
movie. Yeah. And just a baffling ending, it almost seemed like a fuck you who cares kind of ending.
I don't know if they're trying to set up a sequel on Mockingbird Lane. God, I hope not.
It sort of feels like a pilot. Like here at the end, they get money. And then that explains why
they never work for the rest of the series. And then at the end of season one, they'll, she'll be pregnant
and they have Eddie and all that. Like, I guess that's what this was supposed to be.
Oh, yeah. Eddie wasn't even in it. So he's clearly trying to set it up for a sequel.
Yeah. Or Rob, I mean, look, I got, I got no, I'll make no bones, but I think Rob Zombie is
a terrible filmmaker. He really is. I think he's a bad writer. Yeah. So I think unless he's being
steered by some good crew of people, he's terrible. And this to me looked like he wasn't steered at all.
I think the studio was like, holy shit, we got a problem on our hands here. This guy doesn't know
what the fuck he's doing. Yeah. And they cobbled together what they could. He probably had
five hours, a five hour cut of this thing where they were probably like, it felt like COVID cut like
40 mil off the budget or something. I mean, something went wrong. So I think what wrong is he
doesn't know what he's doing. I don't think it understands like, dude, I think Rob Zombie is like,
oh, and then it'll be fun because we'll make it look like Halloween adventure because it'll be neon.
And then also we'll do this. And then also we'll do this and nobody is going and then he's married
to his wife who he's putting in everything. So you know she's not going Rob. What the fuck are you
talking about? You know what I mean? Another gem, Rob. Yeah. That's a wine. Love it, Robby.
You know, so I think like he got the rights of the monsters, he had enough money to buy it.
The rights, he got the rights. He got this project Greenlit in some way.
You know, they probably saw that his last few indie features that he made from like the ground up
made some money and thought, let's take a chance. Yeah. Because he did a Shyamalan thing. He
like kind of got banished to the go make your own movie region for a while. And then those movies did
pretty well. So they invited him back. It's kind of what happened with Kevin Smith. It's what happened
with Shyamalan. They kind of, you know, you get a couple box office bombs and they go, hey,
dude, you're done. And then they go prove themselves on their own terms. And then they go, okay, you
can come back. And I think that's what happened here. They Greenlit a thing. And it was very obvious.
He was in over his head or just had no guidance. Yeah. And you end up with this piece of fucking shit.
And not the studios are any good at reading fucking scripts or giving notes to anything. They're
probably a cocktail of reasons. This was an abomination. But I mean, Rob Zombie's never made a
great movie. I think people, most people would say his best. And I would agree his devil's rejects.
I didn't hate lords of Salem. But they're terrible. It's better than any end on fumes always.
They never have a story to the end. The end of this thing is so crazy and confusing and abrupt.
When I turned it on, I said, okay, the big payoff is going to be this movie is going to end with
the theme music finally kicking in. And it's going to recreate the intro to the show, which was the
teaser trailer. Right. And it's going to go black and white. And it's going to be, look, they're the
monsters. They've become the monsters. I got a little chill just talking about it. That's a pretty
cool payoff. That, when that music hit and that sequence happened, I was like, oh, that's weird.
They're doing this in like the middle of the third act. And then I was like, oh, no, the movie ended
there. What is happening? Yeah. Yeah. It's just a piece of shit. And as I was talking about on the
solo corner that I was trying to record earlier, the Netflix, which I reinstated to watch the monsters in
a few other things. I haven't seen Jeffrey Dahmer. I couldn't watch this. How many movies we're
going to make about this? Yeah. I don't know. I guess I don't know much about them, but it's supposed
to be a rough ride. Yeah. There is nothing on Netflix. There's nothing. It's I had been gone for six
months. I come back. There's nothing. There's still nothing. Ryan Murphy strikes again with his
horse shit. I can't stand Ryan. I've been trying to get through. I didn't even do it on movie
corner. I've been trying to get through American horror stories. What's that anthology thing?
Again, here's another thing where it's like, you got like a 14 year old kid hanging out with his
mom. And they're watching like a fuck scene on something. It's like, it's weird. Ryan, he's just
shocked at this point. Yeah. It's like, come on, dude. Like, but you know, another, you know, it's just
another Dahmer thing. And I love that now these think pieces are coming out like, perhaps it's bad
are obsession with serial. Oh, you think so? You fucking Nimrods. Yeah. Christ. You think that could
have went too far eventually? I'm not knocking all of it. I'm not like, you know, I'm not I promise,
I'm not just saying this because of our friends. I like my favorite murder. I like some things that
deal with true crime. I think it has a place. But this thing where it's like, there's no plug in the
sink for it. You know, it's like Jesus Christ, man. Like how many time, how many fucking Dahmer
things are we going to do here? How many like sick, twisted ways do we have to see his life? It's crazy.
I'm with you. I'm with you. No, you don't get it. When I say I'm with you, I don't mean I understand.
I mean, I'm with you. What would you say the most act? Well, I don't know what movie actually.
God, I'm under cover. I'm an agent. Finnie, you can't just make yourself an agent.
Would you say the more accurate portrayal of the mob is my blue heaven? Or would you say it's
Mickey blue eyes? I see Mickey blue eyes. Mickey blue eyes, a sex. It came out right. It was like a mob
comedy boom. Analyze this corky Romano. Hey, folks, wait, wait, before I forget that, can I slip in a
news, a last news cycle? Of course. Just so you know, looks like 20 years later, after it bombed
at the box office, Rob Schneider is making a sequel to the animal, directing, writing, starring, triple
big old threat. Why would you just make a third do his thing? Yeah, the only funny thing you've
done is do his big love. I mean, that's it. And I honestly, your opinion had some laughs.
But yeah, this is not going to not going to be good. I never even saw the animal. I saw the hot
chick. Right. Yeah, you're often that was obsessed with the hot chick. I was like, are you stupid?
I didn't say that to her. I let people enjoy what they want to enjoy. That's not true. I know for
a fact that that's not true. But I believe that you didn't call her stupid. Folks, I am the Patrick
Walsh at Twitter and Instagram. That's about all I got. We got our Florida show coming up. Joe
can give you a little more specifics and take it away, Joe. Yeah, Florida hit us up or people
coming. Have we heard anything? I don't know. Are the tickets for sale? Yeah. You can get tickets.
I'll put it on my Insta. You can get tickets. And joderosainfo .com. We got December 8th in St. Petersburg,
Florida. Coastal Creative Live is the venue. We'll see you in Hell podcast live. 7 30 p .m.
in Florida. St. Petersburg, Florida. December 8th. Coastal Creative Live. Get tickets at joderosainfo .com.
And you can get tickets to all my upcoming shows at joderosainfo .com.
November 8th, New York, New York. I'm back at the black cat doing the new one man show. I never promised
you a Rose Garden. And then 9th and 10th in St. Petersburg. I'll be doing it that those nights as
well. One show each night. Austin, Texas, January 13th, 14th at the Vulcan. And Levittown, New York
Governor's Comedy Club, January 20th, 21st. Come on out to some stuff and come to Joey Roses in New
York. Joey Roses NYC .com. We're open seven days a week now. So come see us. That's it folks. We'll
see you in Hell.