I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's another episode of We'll See You In Hell, episode 2 of The Final Four, The
Dreaded Final Four.
We are talking today, speaking of number 2s, in many senses, Happy Gilmore 2.
More like Crappy Gilmore number 2.
Oh yeah, Jack Estes, I was going to say, why is no movie called the sequel number 2, and
I think Jack Estes did that.
Yeah.
I love Jack Estes.
You know, I talked a little bit in the last episode about this new Larry Charles book,
which I enjoyed about 100 times more than the Michael Richards book, and everything
I complained about, it's like Larry Charles listened to my notes, he gives you one minute
of backstory into his childhood, and then he's on the set of Seinfeld.
I mean, he doesn't, you don't learn about his mom, his dad, his upbringing, where he
grew up, it's like, you guys are probably here to learn about my insanely successful
comedy career.
Yes, you're absolutely right Larry, you're right, we didn't come for your army stories.
So it's a really good book, I enjoyed it, but he talks of course at length about Borat,
and how groundbreaking it was, and I was kind of like, well now hang on, Jackass, because
of how stupid it is, and all the nudity, and all that, that is a movie, a phenomenon, whatever,
that has never gotten the respect it deserves.
That's a major movement in film, as far as I'm concerned.
Well, it made it to criterion, I mean, it's, you know.
Well, it hasn't happened yet, I hope it happened.
I think the channel streamed it.
No, no, they made the announcement, they said they were going to release the MTV movies,
they said they were going to do Election, Jackass.
They've done Election, I hope we get Jackass.
And there was a third, not Joe's Apartment, which I wouldn't be surprised if criterion
put out, because as I've said many times, sometimes I think they're just fucking with me.
Yeah, well, I mean, the original Jackass came out in 02, and then Borat was like 06, 07,
like, you can't tell me there's not a direct line from Jackass to Borat.
By the way, I'm not shitting on Borat by any means, but it's like that got Oscar attention
and stuff, and Jackass is like this dirty secret of the film industry.
It's always, it gets some respect now behind closed doors.
But a lot of the new people, like Rachel, Rachel from the last movie is a good friend of mine.
And I knew her before the movie because she's a comic.
A lot of that crew lives in Austin, like, like, Jackass.
And I think that guy poopies and they're kind of all around the comedy scene.
Like, it's cool, like, kind of getting to sort of know some of them.
Well, another really awesome thing about the book is that Larry Charles is essentially
like, look, I'm probably retired.
I make edgy in your face, like, we're going to get arrested comedy and I'm almost 70 years old.
So he names names and he takes swings at people I would not have expected, including Mr. Larry David.
Really?
Really.
I mean, he's got, he understands that Larry David gave him everything in his life and
he thinks he's a genius and he speaks very, very highly and reverentially of him.
But one of the final anecdotes he tells in the book is that he started getting more into
doing stuff on his own because, mostly because of Army of One, that Nicolas Cage movie that
was a huge bomb.
And he's put the full length version of that on his website and I'm excited to watch it.
But he knows he's not going to get another big shot.
He made Dix the musical, which was unwatchable.
And he says they took that away from him in the editing room and he hates it and changed
the title and everything.
So he's done.
But he's like, he had made this, he wanted to interview Larry David and he interviewed
him for like four hours.
And Larry David was like, that's the best interview I've ever done.
Thank you so much.
That was amazing.
And then Larry Charles starts adding in a bunch of video components and he's like, I made
this thing that I'm like, I was really proud of this and I thought I could have a new career
late in life as a documentarian.
And he shows it to some people and then somebody slips it to HBO and HBO says, we want to air
this.
We love this.
This is beautiful work.
And Larry is saying, I love it.
I think this documentary is incredible.
Because he had heard the audio, but then he sees it and apparently Larry David is a very
sane man.
He doesn't like how he looks in it.
He sends in his high powered managers who are like calling and threatening Larry Charles
to not release this.
So HBO has ads out for the documentary.
This was the thing that was going to happen.
They made ads for it.
Larry Charles was getting paid for it and Larry David killed it even though he'd been
fully supporting it the entire time.
There's no benefit to Larry Charles to making up that story.
It just makes him look like an asshole.
He's like, I wasted a year and a half of my life and he's like, I never talked to Larry
again.
I'll probably never talk to him again.
I get the idea that Larry David is a lot of fun to watch.
Yep.
Oh yeah.
But up close, you're probably, you know, somebody told me a story about him somewhere.
What the hell was it?
It was like, they just, you know, it was a curb thing.
They said like he, like recently, like, you know, he was in some coffee place, you know,
and just being like, I don't understand.
Why can't you, why do you do it that way?
Why did you do it this way?
It doesn't make any sense.
And I was like, was he being like funny?
And he's like, they were like, no, he's just, no, he was like irritated.
It's like, yeah, I think he just kind of lives in that.
I'm not one to talk, I mean, but you know, I've had a few ladies in my life be like,
it's funny when you're on stage.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it's, it was a really great comedy book.
You know, you sort of forget how much Larry Charles has been involved in.
That was really good.
And so many good Borat and Bruno stories, because you forget that like they were risking
their life basically making those movies.
What's going on, Joe?
Are you in Austin now?
I'm just, yeah, I'm still here.
Nothing's going on.
The thing I failed to mention last episode was I met your old friend, Fred Savage.
Love that guy.
And he was in the audience at the Chapelle thing, and he came backstage and I met him.
I go, hey, dude, I got to tell you, the first thing I said to him, I said, it's nice to
meet you.
I go, I'm really good friends with Pat Walsh.
Yeah.
And he was like, oh my God, I love Pat.
Does he live in Atlanta?
Is he in Atlanta?
And I was like, no, he goes back and forth.
And he's like, that's so great, man.
Well, how do you guys know each other?
And I was just like, you know, well, we met and we're friends.
We have a podcast.
And then like seven minutes in the conversation, he goes, how do I not know that you have a
pod?
He has a podcast.
And I said, well, because it's not very popular, more of a cult.
You know, we had a chuckle.
And he told me about his new watch company thing that he's doing.
And yeah, I don't know.
He was super nice.
By the way, very good looking guy, man.
Like, it's weird that you don't people don't know that about.
He's definitely improved.
Handsome fucking dude, like semi retirement from the business.
But yeah, he's he looks no different than he did sitting with Peter Falk and the Princess
Bride, really.
Except he's got a little Jack now.
Yeah, he looked very fit and he was very nice.
And then hours and hours later at an after party.
I was pretty shit house at this point.
This guy is like, hey, it was nice to meet you.
And I was like, oh, shit, that's Fred Savage again.
Yeah, he's very nice to say goodbye.
And I said, yeah, man, I hope to see you around.
And he was very cool.
I wish that there's not really a good story to this.
No, you've met a famous person.
Now, Dave Chappelle, when they walked into the green room, said, hey, everybody, it's
Fred Sanford from the Wonder Years.
And I I swear to God, I don't I couldn't tell if he was fucking with him, joking or
if he accidentally actually said Fred Sanford.
It was Sanford and son, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
And I was like, I think he's joking.
I think he's making fun of Fred Savage's name and calling him Fred Sanford.
Now, Joe, you have not we just recorded for an hour and you either didn't notice or
didn't mention that I have a giant facial patch.
I didn't notice.
I thought your forehead was just a little bit red.
What the hell is that now?
I now I can see it.
It's called a frowny, you know, other than blue chew.
We don't really advertise on this show, but yeah, it's called a frowny.
I saw it advertised on Instagram.
They're very cheap.
They're similar in theory to like the Biore nose pad.
I am going to do a genuine ad here, an unpaid ad.
They it's like they're like the Biore's that you use to take the pores out.
What it is, is you put a sheet on your forehead, relax your face, kind of stretch
it so that those forehead wrinkles evaporate.
OK.
And you slap it on ideally at bedtime, but I'm staying in doing some work today.
So I put mine on.
You wake up in the morning, take it off.
It's not a, it's somehow not a scam.
These patches work similar to like a Botox.
I've never done Botox.
I could never imagine injecting botulism into my face.
Obviously every woman I've ever dated has done it and it's more of a lady thing.
But, um, ladies, if you're, if you're uneasy about it, if it's too expensive,
look into these frownies.
You know, it's like you take it off and it's what these, these products and
these creams claim to do and never do.
Not eliminate, but reduces the appearance of your fine lines and
wrinkles is exactly what it does.
I always have three big lines in my forehead.
Just the, the, the being a stressed out man my whole life.
And they're little by little going away.
I love these things.
Check them out.
Frownies.
They're, they're really cheap and good.
Okay.
Frownies.
Yes.
God bless.
I mean, if you find anything that works, it's like, why not share it
with people for God's sake?
Um, all right.
Well, hey, I, uh, I wish I had some beauty tips to share here.
You look like a bunch of beauty tips, Joe.
You'll notice my face is sort of red and, uh, that's probably a result of the drinking.
The, I, I'm trying to quit smoking.
Uh, I've severely cut back and I think I'm almost at a place where every
time I smoke, it makes me feel just sick enough that I don't want to do it.
Okay.
I'm praying to God that sticks.
Um, I got to get back into a routine here, man.
Oh yeah.
Yay.
And that's the bummer that my apartment is in such disarray because I
thought I'll go down to Austin.
I'll be in the new pad.
You know, I don't have to do any standup if I don't want, I'll relax.
And then I walked into a fucking, it looks like a bomb went off in here.
And I'm just like, completely stressed out.
You know, you can't cook cause there's no, you know, I'm like, God damn it, man.
So anyway, um, I, uh, uh, yeah.
So anyway, I, I'm just trying to get back on a routine.
It's not, again, not, not very interesting talk folks.
This is as Pat said, last episode, why this show is coming to an end.
We told you we're out of gas.
Joe told Joe's told two stories this episode.
One was about meeting a man and the other was about considering smoking less.
We're dry.
Okay.
Oh, I wrote a perfect Dennis Miller joke.
Oh, let me hear it.
I put it on my Instagram.
I, uh, I did a video in legal seafood.
I said, I'm sitting here in legal seafood.
Uh, I've never been the only place I've eaten is illegal seafood.
None of the shrimp had a fucking green card.
You know, how was that received?
I don't know.
Nobody said anything.
The other punchline I thought you were going to say, uh, illegal seafood.
What is this?
Jeff Epstein side business.
Okay.
My other punchline was, uh, uh, I've only eaten that illegal seafood.
Great place until ice raids the fucking crab cakes.
I, uh, I it's so weird that you mentioned this because I had not thought of Dennis
Miller since I rewatched bordello of blood seven years ago, but he popped up on
my Instagram and I was like, why did I accidentally follow him?
No, but sometimes it'll just show you people that they think you might care
about and he's doing a whole Instagram post about how upset he is that John
Voight isn't a more awarded actor.
I did see that.
I did see that dude.
How much of this Kool -Aid are you going to guzzle it?
I don't care at all that you're fucking right wing.
You don't have to suck John Voight's dick.
Well, I mean, what's next?
The Dean Kane appreciation post stop.
It was, it was strangely.
I was, but I, and I also felt like I felt like John Voight is appreciated.
Is he not?
He's appreciated quite enough.
Yeah.
Wasn't it like, but wasn't it like, it's a crime that he hasn't gotten
the Kennedy center or it was like something really specific.
Yeah.
And you're just picturing Dennis Miller sitting at home like, oh, wait a minute.
Has he ever won this Kennedy award before?
Googling it angry.
What do you care?
Now in, now in, in Dennis Miller's defense, once you give one to Sandler,
you're probably sitting there going, guys, come on.
And I like Adam Sandler.
He's a great actor, but you know, I'm sure there are people like.
Pacino doesn't have one.
Well, they're probably going to revoke Sandler's after they watch today's film.
They'll just take it back.
Oh boy.
Uh, if you want to go to the movie corner, I got a, well, actually, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
I got a, I got a, one of these ramp things.
I don't even remember what this was, but I bookmarked it.
Nope.
Stop it.
Okay.
Um, Oh, it has to do with today's movie.
All right.
Uh, this was a post on, uh, I guess this is, yeah, this was an Instagram post.
All 62 celebrity cameos we spotted and happy Gilmore.
I'm surprised it was that few.
And I mean that.
Um, I, you know, this, this is troubling to me because this has become
now a selling point of a movie.
This has become something in lieu of plot.
Yeah.
People, somebody told me that their, their son was telling them how good
happy Gilmore and their son is 16 or something, how good happy Gilmore too
was and the dad, this friend of mine was like, I don't know, I'm, I'm skeptical.
And the son goes, no, no, all the cameos.
You got to see it.
All the cameos are so great.
And I'm like, this is starting to become a thing that certain people, I guess
younger think, bring quality to something.
And it's just so odd to me because we just got out of this, stopped doing
the fan service bullshit, right?
Which started initially with the star Wars force awakens stuff.
And people cried slight foul then.
And then as the years went on that followed, people started to say all the
time, this sucks because all this is his fan service and fuck this.
And it makes something different.
And we're just now getting to a place where that's sort of happening and we're
finding the right balance yet.
We still have all these movies coming out that are just littered with cameos
and people think it's great.
Yeah.
And of all the movies that doesn't need it, the happy Gilmore, no reason.
The only thing you quote need is a couple of famous golfer cameos to get
the dads hard, then you just move on.
The original has no cameos has no cameos.
By the way, the cable guy has no cameo.
All these classics that we love, no cameos.
So still are unhappy.
Gilmore is the cameo.
Ready for this?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm going to read through some of these.
Cause so many of these are not even for young people.
So I don't get it.
Some of them are so Eminem spans generations, I guess, right?
Post Malone, obviously for the younger crowd, Kid Cudi, obviously for the
younger crowd, number four, Sarah Sarandos, daughter of Netflix, CEO.
Imagine that call coming in.
You're the director of the movie.
You got a million dollars in the bank.
Problems and Ted Sarandos wants you to cast his daughter.
Here's three, Rob Schneider, Nick Swartz and John Lovitz.
All very funny dudes.
Guys, maybe give them funny, substantial parts in the movie and not just these
weird cameo, the Schneider cameo.
I'm like, what the fuck is this is literally just a callback.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yeah.
Again, I, so I was talking about pop star last episode cause it's a similar
vibe to naked gun done better, at least than the modern naked gun.
And pop star is too cameo heavy.
It's probably got as many cameos as happy Gilmore too, but it's a movie about a pop star.
So you, you, you need cameos from pink and Usher and all these people in RZA.
They start, they make a point.
Every single famous person that appears in pop star gets a laugh out loud line.
Otherwise, why are you having this person come down to set to hang out?
It doesn't make any sense.
Every cameo in happy Gilmore too, is the person just showing up and being there.
And then my friends, John and Alison, who have two little daughters, they go to
the Midwest every year for a month in the summer and hang out with their
nieces who are 15, 16, same thing.
They were like, you guys got to see happy Gilmore too.
Everybody famous is in it.
God, it's so gross.
What?
Now, now here's the thing.
This article, this number is inflated because this article, some of this is
just casting, Benny Safdie is not a cameo.
He plays major character in the movie, but that speaks to a different problem.
Why the fuck is Benny Safdie outside of friendship playing the lead
villain in happy Gilmore too?
Why is that not Rob Schneider or Nick Swartzen or John Lovitz or any, nobody
knows Benny Safdie or an up and coming funny person.
Yeah, there there's he's, he's terrible in the film and I love the
work of the Safdie brothers.
They're great.
It's terrible.
He's, he's, he's passable.
You know, he, he gets the job done.
I just don't get it.
Oh jeez, there's music on that.
Sorry.
Um, well, we'll, we'll get to HG too anyway.
Um, for the, well, speaking of terrible, I watched, uh, this is the, is
this the movie corner?
I'm sorry.
Yeah, we're there.
We're there.
I watched it, baby.
Ice cubes, war of the world.
Wow.
I've been hearing the clips I've seen are, are jaw on the floor stuff.
Now they shot it during COVID.
So that's part of the problem.
Yeah.
And part of why I'm like, eh, it's not their fault.
They did their best.
Um, ice cube goes, he's, he's the whole movie.
Um, and he swings between, you know, believable and, and good in the, in,
you know, decent and conveying the truth of the role or whatever into
areas of absurdity at times, but the absurd areas are not his fault.
The dialogue is so bad that you can almost hear him just like, Jesus Christ.
I'm just, I'm going to just, I guess I'll just read this.
It's so stupid, you know?
Um, so in the, in the areas that he's laughably bad, it's almost like he's,
you can just hear him lose his committing to, because he knows this is
probably not going to be a good movie.
Um, you know, it's all, it's all screens.
That's the, that's the gimmick of the movie is it's war of the worlds, but
you're seeing it through like everybody's computer screen or whatever.
So it's like that, uh, what's that?
That online movie, the horror movie that maybe we did on this show, we
did unfriended or whatever.
Yeah.
Um, and that's it, man.
It's war of the worlds.
It's the, it's the, you know, it's the same story.
Like it's the guy trying to reconnect with his kid and his kids out there in
the madness and this guy can't get to them and, uh, you know, they,
they do create a good device to tell the story, which is that ice cube is this
like national security specialist who has to be at this desk because so much
is riding on what he is monitoring and everything.
So, so that, that works.
That's why he can't go to his family.
Um, and that also is why he is so shut off from them because his job has, has
made him a sort of paranoid and somewhat callous human being.
But God, man, the movie sucks.
This is what I'll say though.
If you're thinking about watching it, don't, because here's the thing.
Does it suck?
Yeah.
Is it laugh out loud?
Bad?
No, it just sucks.
The worst, the worst.
Yeah.
It just sounds like, yeah, it sucks the way like a movie by the asylum would suck.
You're just like, yeah, this sucks, man.
Like it's, this is a piece of shit.
This is like a made for sci -fi piece of shit.
Like that, that, so whatever, but poor Ava Longoria, cause she's been away for a
long time and she just came back and she's in this and the pickup, which we
will be reviewing and these movies were not well received, I feel really bad for
her that these are her two swings back into the public eye.
Hey, she, she made that flaming hot Cheetos picture too.
Yeah.
She also, she, uh, you heard about her and John wick, right?
Wait, what?
Wait, lower your mic a little bit towards your mouth a little more.
Her and John, uh, John wick, they were getting ready to start shooting.
They lost 6 million in funding.
So they're like, we can't do it.
And somehow Eva Longoria was asked one of those deals that agencies have where
they're like, could you ask your big actors if they want to produce a movie?
So she gave $6 million to John wick and it made her like, you know, 200 million.
I didn't know that.
That's great.
She's doing okay.
All right.
Well, good for her.
Um, I went to the American cinema tech and saw, uh, of which I am a member,
ladies and gentlemen, and saw may a movie that I always recommend to people when
they're like, what's a horror movie that I've never seen that's really good that
I should check out may is usually my recommendation.
Have you seen it, Joe?
I don't think so.
Not many have, uh, came out in 2002.
It's somehow more than 20 years old.
I saw it right around the same time.
I saw wet out American summer and Donnie Darko.
And I was just like, this is an amazing time for independent movies
that nobody has heard of or seen.
I kept seeing these great little movies at the video store and may really holds
up.
It's a psychological horror movie.
It's got some, you know, some sort of similarities to Frankenstein, but not
really, uh, it's about a very lonely young woman with a lazy eye.
She had a difficult childhood.
She keeps what seems to be the ghost of her mother in a doll.
Um, and she works at, at a veterinarian's office.
Uh, she starts dating, hooking up with people.
Uh, Jeremy Sisto, who's an actor I've always liked Anna Faris, who I always
love playing like a predatory lesbian.
Some of her scenes are not going to feel great in 2025, but she's a very
slutty predatory lesbian in this.
And basically we're talking here about a very, very sad character study with
some great horror elements about a woman who keeps getting seduced.
She's, she's attractive and people keep coming onto her, but then
treating her like shit.
It's basically what dating is now.
You know, you go on a date, you start to like somebody and then they ghost you or
something weird happens and they fuck you over.
You never hear from them again.
It's like how dating goes for most people.
She just can't take it.
It's driving her crazy.
And eventually she snaps.
There's some Carrie elements to it as well, but you know, near the end of this
thing, she basically screams, see me.
Like somebody see me.
It's like, like somebody stopped me from the mask, but it's a, it
got gasps in the theater.
I mean, it, it's such an emotional moment in this movie.
You'll, you'll know it when you see it, but, um, that's where the movie really
thrives is it's got a lot of heart to it.
You really care about and love May who was played by Angela Bettis, who's an
actress I never really saw much of again, even though she's incredible.
Um, and it's written and directed by Lucky McKee, who does a lot of really
good kind of B horror, but this is still his best, still probably his most popular
movie, kind of a cult classic, a lot of breeders on the soundtrack, one of my
favorite bands, um, highly recommended if you've never seen May.
I did see this actually.
I'm looking it up now.
I forgot about this.
Uh, we might have done it on the show.
I don't know.
I don't remember it though, for some reason, but I did see it because I
remember when I saw Angela Bettis on masters of horror, I was like, Oh,
that's that lady from May.
Um, yeah.
And I remember Jeremy's sister.
Yeah, that's it's, yeah, I got to rewatch this, but I, I do remember
being good, I think, um, well, I talked about it a little bit on the last
episode, but I'll review it properly.
Now I did watch the new Superman.
Um, I already voiced my opinion about the, you know, the passive use of
nostalgia, you know, I think if you're going to go nostalgic, do it, don't
just sort of do it, um, and I'm referring, you know, to me, the John Williams
theme and that, Oh, this is what kills me.
They, they use the font from the Richard Donner Superman for the credits.
They use the John Williams theme, but they don't just do the thing that gets
you up and out of your seat and excited, which is stupid.
I don't understand that.
Uh, you know, the, and then you think they, maybe they're going to do it at
the end of the movie, the way naked gun did, and they don't instead Superman
ends with this like new wave pop band song.
I'm like, what guys, this is, I saw that it ends with the teddy bears.
I used to really love that album and I was like, this wasn't even a hit album.
This, this song is closing Superman.
I'm so confused by that.
It's, it's, uh, it's a bad way to close the movie in my opinion.
Now, did I like the movie?
Well, it's got it where it counts.
Uh, I will say James gun brought fun and it's not overly comedic, uh, but
brought fun and comic bookiness back to Superman.
Yeah.
We haven't seen that in a while.
You know, Superman returns was a sort of drab attempt at rehashing and
sequelizing the, the Donner stuff.
And it didn't really work.
Um, man of steel was, was a well put together movie, but, but very
grim, um, and quite joyless.
This, this feels crazy and comic booky and you know, the version of green
lantern played by Nathan Fillion, the guy Gardner version, who's an
asshole and looks ridiculous.
And, uh, but it's kind of awesome.
Like they, they really committed to a lot of interesting choices in this,
which I thought was cool.
Um, overall, I found the movie to be overstuffed and overcomplicated.
You know, my biggest gripe with these superhero movies anymore is the first
one out of the gate feels like the last one guys.
When your first movie hinges on the destruction of the city, the superhero
lives in, there's not really much to go to after that.
There's not much to go to.
So they've got him in the middle of this international conflict, um, and this
war happening overseas that's completely clearly supposed to be Israel and
Palestine.
They've got him in the middle of that.
They've got this other plot line where the American public has lost their
faith in him because, and I really hated this, and this is a big spoiler,
but his message from his parents, um, they, they, they play half of the
message and they say the message was corrupted in, in his journey as a baby.
So he only has the first half of the message and the first half of the
messages, his parents are played by Bradley Cooper and I forget who plays
the mom and they're the first half of the messages, like them saying, like,
you are special, our son, and we are sending you to a place where you will
be able to be safe and influence the people there.
It's the typical Superman thing.
It's the thing that Marlon Brando says to Christopher Reeve in the
Donna version, Lex Luther manages to uncorrupt the message and get the
entire message in the movie.
And the rest of the message is then his parents telling him to lord over the
earthlings because they're weak and stupid and to sire children and, and,
and rule the planet.
And you're, you're going, that can't be real.
This has to be whatever.
And then in the end of the movie, it's like, no, no, no, it's real.
That is what his parents message.
I fucking hated that change so much.
And of course, Superman does not do it.
He's against it.
And that's sort of built on this idea or builds on this idea that he is one of us.
He is not an alien.
He is an earthling, but just different and whatever.
Doesn't matter.
I really didn't like that change.
Um, but my point is, is that change sparks a plot line where now the
American people hate him.
So you're like, okay, the American people hate him.
He's in the middle of the Israeli Palestine conflict.
Uh, he's dealing with Lex Luthor who has created a clone of Superman that
is able to beat up Superman.
Also, there's this thing happening where Lex Luthor has caused an interdimensional
rift and now that rift is going to swallow.
It's, it's too fucking much.
Yeah.
It's too much like guys, Oh my God, man.
This is, I don't know why they keep doing this.
Was this was the problem in Beetlejuice?
Uh, it was the problem in the last Jedi.
It was, uh, and, and in, uh, uh, rise of Skywalker.
Um, it was the problem in, um, what else did I just see where I was like,
this is all this had to be.
This is why is this so, Oh, I would happy Gilmore too.
Yeah.
You're just like, guys, it's, it's, it's simple shit here.
It's simple shit.
Play the music, show us the bad guy.
Let's go.
Yeah.
That's it.
Um, but, but, but was the cast good?
Yes.
The cast is very good.
He's a very good Superman.
He's a great Clark Kent.
Uh, Ms.
Maisel is an awesome Lois Lane.
She really is, uh, about a boy.
I think I've never seen her act in anything.
I've seen her in a, well, I've seen her in Ms.
Maisel obviously, but I think I've seen her in one or two other things.
I haven't seen that.
About a boy is an awesome Lex Luthor.
Okay.
Cool.
I like him.
So the cast is great.
The guy that plays Mr.
Terrific is awesome.
Um, Nathan Fillion is great.
Uh, Hawk Girl is a cool character.
Like it's got it where it needs it.
And Gunn knows how to direct a movie.
Now, of course there's sequences in this where you're going, everything
I'm looking at right now was made by a computer and none of this is real.
Um, which is funny because after I finished this, I turned on the
original Donner Superman and you are sitting there going, this movie, the
Donner one was made, is it 40 years ago?
Almost 50, 78.
So that's what 20, 45, almost 50 years ago, 47 years ago, and you're watching
it going, all of this was made practically this scene in the beginning
where Zod and his minions are in the, in the, they're going to be sentenced
to the phantom zone and there's all the weird lighting and the faces up
talking over them and every, you're like, this was all lit and created
and put together and it's, it's, it's real.
I'm watching something visceral here.
And it's so much more enthralling than when you watch Superman crash
land to earth and then his dog comes and his dog pulls him by the cape
and whatever, and it's fun and everything, but you, you're going
these dogs, that dog's probably not real.
Right.
Clearly not real when it's dragging him.
Um, you know, it's, it's spectacle.
It's all spectacle, but this is kind of what big studio moviemaking
is these days.
It's, it's not going to go back in the other direction and especially
with everything fledgling and failing as it is, like, you know, these,
these studios do not know how to go smaller to fix problems.
They only know how to go bigger.
So, you know, completely different topic, but yeah, on the subject
of only know how to go bigger.
I keep seeing the trailers for the roses.
Oh boy.
Now war of the roses is one of my favorite black comedies ever.
And post my own divorce, it only grew in my estimation.
I fucking love that movie and this new one already, you know, you've got
Andy Samberg and, uh, what's her face.
Hillary Clinton from SNL, Kate McKinnon as like the friends.
And then, you know, instead of the, you know, did, did, did she, or
did she not kill his cat there?
They're scraping a bunion off of his, off of his foot into the meal.
And you're like, well, that's disgusting.
So like somehow that's worse than killing an animal.
Like every choice they're making is wrong.
None of the lines seem funny to me.
I don't know why they think Benedict Cumberbatch and Olivia Coleman
are going to open a comedy.
None of it makes sense.
But what really bothers me more than anything is making the title, the roses.
The war of the roses says, Oh, that sounds exciting.
That sounds like something I want to see.
There's a conflict.
The roses is nothing.
If you don't know that's the couple's name, you know nothing.
I know.
And it's not like the movie is something that the kids today are talking about.
It just, none of it makes any sense.
That's all I got to make your own movie about divorce.
That's all I got for the quarter.
Did you do one or two?
I only did one.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I rewatched Romeo and Michelle's high school reunion.
What a great fucking comedy that is 90 minutes in and out, laugh out loud, funny.
Kudrow is hilarious, but Sorvino kills in this movie.
She's funnier than she was in mighty Aphrodite, which won her the Oscar.
Really, really fucked up.
Obviously everything Harvey Weinstein did is fucked up, but killing Mira
Sorvino's career is really shitty because she was a really great comedy actress.
She really was.
And, um, I wish Paul Sorvino had killed Harvey Weinstein as he often threatened
to do because what a great way to go out.
Anyway, this movie really makes me laugh.
I saw it in theaters when I was in high school and it just holds up really well.
The structure is off.
It's, it's two girls who were losers in high school.
They decide they're going to pretend that they invented post -it notes and act like
they're really successful and go back to their reunion.
I also just watched gross point blank.
They did a double feature of these at the new Beverly gross point.
Blank is an incredibly well -written and structured movie in addition to being
very funny and having an amazing soundtrack, Romeo and Michelle, very
similar to gross point blank eighties high school reunion, the soundtrack
is fucking on point.
There's a lot of laughs where it's lacking is in it's plotting.
There's no real story here to speak of.
There's no real reason for them to go to their reunion.
So that's not ideal, but it's a 90 minute comedy.
So it winds up not really mattering.
The great Cameron Mannheim from living biblically, uh, is really
funny in, in a, in a supporting role.
Jeanine Garofalo steals the movie.
I forgot how funny she is when she is on.
She plays like Daria basically, like the girl who hates everyone and
everything about high school and just shits on every book.
They ask her to like go, you know, Hey, you know, we're about to do such and such.
And she's like, I'd rather put this cigarette out in my right eye.
Like that's her vibe the whole time.
Uh, Alan Cumming is very, very funny in this movie.
They have a dance sequence at the end, a three -way dance sequence
between Romy, Michelle and Alan Cumming that I absolutely love.
Great dialogue.
It's the female dumb and dumber.
If you've never seen it, check it out.
Joe, have you seen it?
No, I recommend it.
You'd laugh a lot.
It's so funny.
Yeah, there I have friends from over the years that have always said like, you
know, that's a very funny movie and you need to see, and I just, you know,
I just never, I don't think I've ever seen it like on streaming or anything.
So I never, I never tapped into it.
Well, it was directed by David Merkin, who was a Simpson's guy who also did
get a life with Chris Elliott, one of the craziest sitcoms ever made.
And his directing career consists of two movies, Romy and Michelle and
Heartbeats with Sigourney Weaver and Jennifer Love Hewitt and Jean Hackman
and Ray Liotta, and these are two perfect, double female led comedies,
like A level, two women doing all the funny and heavy lifting comedies.
Why has this guy not worked again?
The movies were not huge, but they were moderately successful.
I don't know.
I never, I never, maybe he didn't want to, maybe he got sick of work.
I always just speculate what happened to these great careers where here's a
guy who actually knows how to make a cool looking, laugh out loud, funny
movie, and then we just never hear from him again, but oh well, that's,
that's the nature of the beast.
Well, speaking of the comedies.
Yeah, man.
The perfect comedy.
I rewatched Happy Gilmore in anticipation for this.
I didn't need to.
Happy Gilmore lives in my blood.
You know, I've seen it 40 times.
It's a great, great comedy.
It is very funny.
And what I really love about Happy Gilmore and Dirty Work, I just rewatched
the dirtier cut, the new 4k that came out, which was cool to see.
I can't say buy it for 50 bucks to see the dirtier cut.
It winds up not being that much new material.
But, um, wait, where was I?
Dirty Work?
Happy, you rewatched Happy Gilmore?
Sorry, sorry.
The plot of both of these movies is somebody's, somebody sweet and old
is in trouble basically, and our hero is going to help them.
Happy Gilmore needs to get the money to get his grandmother out of tax debt.
So anything he does over the course of this movie, you still love him.
That is what today's executives, and I've dealt with people on these issues
before, likability is such a major thing.
And you're like, the whole movie is him trying to get money for his grandma.
He can run someone over.
We don't care.
You're all in for him and his journey.
And, and nowadays he's doing something nice for his grandma.
They go, there's no stakes.
Why do I care?
And you wind up creating these Lebrinthian plots in comedies.
That get more and more complex.
You leave feeling nothing at the end of Happy Gilmore.
You go, oh, awesome.
In addition to having this great time and all these great laughs,
he got his grandma the money.
What a nice guy.
His grandma's going to be okay.
And you're happy and you leave.
When Happy Gilmore 2 ends, you've had no emotional experience, no laughter.
You've wasted two hours and some change and you don't even really know what
you're supposed to take away from it.
No, it's, I agree with everything you just said.
Um, you know, back to this concept that all you need to do is fill in the blank.
All this needed to be was a return to form for Adam Sandler.
Yeah.
He's a guy that needs to get back into golf because he is down on his luck.
Uh, you know, the plot point of my daughter wants to go to ballerina
school in France is not strong enough.
Those stakes are not high enough.
Um, so then the whole family's in this thing.
He's making plot decisions based on how much screen time his
fucking daughters can get.
Then he gives, then there's this whole second plot of they're going to lose
the house or whatever the hell it is.
I don't remember, but so there's like the double money plot.
Yeah.
He's got four son characters in this that have nothing to do with anything.
I don't understand why they're in there at all because it's only
focused on him and his daughter.
They kill the wife, which is an unnecessary.
Well, let's pause there.
But if you can't, if, if I totally get making a movie and then when you see
the edit, you go, okay, these little boy characters make no sense.
Let's get them the fuck out of there.
We made a mistake.
What were we thinking?
You can write stuff into a movie script.
And then when you see it on its feet, you're like, Oh no, that doesn't work.
Let's get out of here.
Why aren't we editing movies anymore?
Well, why is a two hour, five minute comedy?
Why isn't somebody going make it an hour 40?
Because there's too many cooks.
And when you're dealing with somebody and no disrespect, I have a great
admiration for the guy and I've met him and he's very nice, but Adam Sandler
you're dealing with an Adam Sandler.
He's going to have final cut.
He wrote the thing.
You know, he wrote it.
Yeah.
It's like, it's like his company's putting it out.
It's, it's, it's these movies now, again, you know, these movies, these TV
shows, when you get to a certain level, they're treated like podcasts.
It's like, let them do whatever they want to do and whatever.
And I hate execs and I hate studio notes, but sometimes you need a few
just to kind of reel things in.
But then you see something like this and you can tell the studio is saying,
let's overload it with cameos and let's do this and let's do whatever the fuck, man.
It's, it's, it's a mess of a movie.
There's too many plot lines going on.
It is very, almost confusing.
And then extraordinarily lazy to the point that they're showing you callbacks,
literally showing you callbacks to the first film by showing you footage of the
first film, just so they can then justify that Eminem is playing Joe Flattery's
character's son or whatever.
It makes no sense.
But my biggest gripe with it is there was no need for them to kill his wife and
make it sad and somber for the first 20 minutes of this movie.
It's a legitimately sad movie.
There are no laughs.
She does a whole press tour for this movie, Julie Bowen, who seems delightful.
You know, I like her a lot.
She's, she's doing a whole press tour going, I really thought they were going to
and Sidney Sweeney or Megan Fox.
I was so thrilled when they brought me back and you see the movie and she's
hit by a golf ball by her husband and killed five minutes in and it's done it.
The CGI is so shitty.
I had to rewind it to confirm that it was his wife because for some reason,
every shot in the movie is done on a green screen.
And then on top of it, on top of it.
They bring her back throughout the movie in ghost dreams.
Yeah.
Like it's Arthur too.
And it's Arthur too.
Guys, for the love of God, have her just be alive.
What is the, this is insane.
Why are you killing her off?
What is the upside?
It doesn't make you like Sandler anymore in the movie.
It doesn't, you'd root for him more if there was a woman in his corner.
And what, what humanized both Billy Madison and a happy Gilmore, and by the
way, characters in many of his early movies was that a woman liked him.
You know, like you watch Billy Madison, you're like, is this guy mentally
handicapped if you didn't, you know, and then a woman likes him and you're
like, oh, okay, like he's got some game.
He's a human being.
We don't have that here.
So he's down on his luck.
He's a widower.
He's an alcoholic.
He's out of money.
Nobody remembers him, of course, until he golfs one time.
And then all of a sudden, everybody remembers him, which is another
thing they do with these things.
They're doing that in the new spinal tap.
They've got like the spinal tap guys driving Ubers, and then they're
intercutting it in the trailer with them playing a sold out stadium.
And it's like, guys, if they can fill an arena, they wouldn't be driving Ubers.
That's not how that works.
So anyway, here's a 10 times better version of this plot
streamlined off the top of my head.
Uh, he and his wife got divorced because of his temper.
Yeah, he's now an alcoholic.
Uh, his wife contacts him and says, your daughter and I are going to be homeless
because your money was completely mismanaged.
Uh, you have to do something to save us.
He has to start golfing again.
The problem is he's an alcoholic, but the reason he's an alcoholic is
because when he drinks, it's the only time he doesn't freak out and is calm.
He has to get off the sauce and start golfing again.
And immediately he's happy Gilmore again.
And it's, and then we're off to the races and that would be so
funny and so fun to watch.
And then he wins his wife back at the end and he gets his
family and you're, you're, and it's beautiful.
And instead she's dead.
The daughter wants to go to dance school.
He freaks out one time in the movie, one time he freaks out.
That's it.
That there's that sequence where that's got quality and Eric Andre in it.
And it's, it's another set of needless cameos in this film.
And pointless.
Who are these people?
You, there are three people with a, with 10 years between their
ages, hanging out on a golf course for some reason, and they, and they
golf with him and they don't know who he is.
And by the way, this is after they've, they've done a gag where they show,
they show on Jeopardy, this golfer was known for his crazy temper.
And people go, who is Hanky Gilbert?
Like, so on Jeopardy, keep this in mind, the three contestants on
Jeopardy don't remember his name.
Now the point of that joke is he is such a has been three geniuses
don't remember his name.
He then goes to golf for the first time with three people that he just
clumped together with as, as that happens, I guess, at a golf course.
And the three people are, two of them are Zillennials.
Yeah.
And one is Eric Andre.
It's the little boy, the Nepo boy from SNL.
Margaret Qualley.
Qualley and Eric Andre.
Why are, why are they together?
What is the, you don't even, when a scene starts, you don't even know
what you're looking at at the time.
Yeah.
And here's the thing, they recognize him.
You, you go, guys, you just showed us that nobody remembers who he is.
The Gen Z kid knows who he is.
What are we doing?
This is no, no Gen Z person knows any golfer.
Yes.
That's never happened.
Anyway, unless you're a golfer.
Anyway, much to my surprise, much to my surprise, this scene that I'm
initially rolling my eyes at and we're at about the 20 minute mark when this
happens, he does the Sandler shit that you want.
He's, he's hitting a ball.
It ricochets off a tree.
It hits him in the nuts and he's going crazy screams.
I laughed out loud when the kid, when he's in the woods looking for his
ball and the kid goes, you find your ball back yet?
And he goes, yeah, I found it.
I just like walking in Poison Ivy.
You stupid piece of shit.
Like all that.
I was like, here we go.
This is awesome.
That is happy Gilmore.
Yeah.
This is what we want.
Right.
Then the scene after that, they reintroduce Stiller and Stiller's
run in the AA meeting and he's talking to the members of the meeting and he's
going, yeah, cause you're a degenerate and you're a scumbag and whatever.
I was like, this is very funny.
Great.
And then the scene after that is Chris McDonald, shoot him again.
I'm like, he's reading the Shining laughing.
Like, I'm like, we are off to the races and then when they put shooter
in the insane asylum, I, that was the first time in the movie where I
relaxed a lot of movies, especially legacy sequels have a real awkward
beginning where it's like, let's reset the table and clearly the resetting
of this table did not work, but when I saw a shooter in an insane asylum, I
literally put my hands behind my head and was like, here we go.
Here's the movie.
I was wrong.
No, the movie nose dives from there.
Shooter gets out, shooter becomes a good guy immediately, even though
he's illegally escaped an insane asylum and nobody seems to folks there.
There is no finer and more quoted and more beloved comedy villain, at
least from our generation, then shooter McGavin when, when Chris
McDonald played, uh, my dad, essentially on living biblically, we went out
afterwards and he was sober, but he was white knuckling it.
He kept, he just kept talking about how badly he wanted to fucking drink.
And he was great in every single person, people from across the restaurant,
people walking by outside shooter, shooter, they love him.
And to, to, to get this script and be so excited.
He, I mean, I'm sure he, he just lied to everyone that asked him, but he
must've been devastated.
He doesn't get anything funny to do.
He's not the villain.
And here's, here's what I'm saying.
I would get it.
If the villain was bad bunny, I'd hate it.
Bad bunny plays Adam Sandler's caddy in this movie for no reason.
Yeah.
Instead of this, which it was supposed to be.
If they said, Chris McDonald, you're out bad bunnies in, okay.
I would hate that.
It would make me sad, but I would also understand it.
This is 2025.
Happy Gilmore is not as relevant.
They want to get the new audience.
Okay.
To, to replace Chris McDonald with Safdie, essentially he's the villain.
He's a not, not funny character.
And by the way, not a comedic performer.
So what, what are we doing?
That to me was, you can't come back from this.
You've got this great villain and you've lost him.
Why not have Sandler, you know, very similar to what you pitched some sort
of anger management thing where he's been living like a monk, he's been living
Zen, he finally got his anger under control, you know, he's in Tibet, whatever
you want to do, then all of a sudden shooter gets out and it brings back the
anger, you know, like there's a million ways to go.
I bet if you ask any two guys like me and Joe sitting in any bar across
America before this movie came out, what would be your dream?
Happy Gilmore sequel.
You'd hear 500 points of view, but you would never hear what we got.
You would never hear anything close.
You'd never hear somebody go.
I think he should kill his wife with a golf ball.
Then shooter gets out of an insane asylum, but he's not the bad guy.
We got this douche that's kind of an Elon Musk satire, but we're not
going to have the balls to go there.
Also too, and also too, to your point that you made about the naked gun,
or similar at least to the point that you made about the naked gun.
The bad guy is a competitor where he's going to make golf cool and relevant
again with this like X game style golf thing.
Yeah.
And the whole thing is more absurd than the shit they did in Caddyshack 2.
With Jackie Mason having like laser golf clubs and all that shit.
Guys, the first movie was grounded.
That's what made it hilarious that you put this psycho in the middle of a
grounded sport and watched him just be a bull in a china shop.
This thing is so unbelievable and so stupid and so over the top, the final
putt is the course is now spinning and they're getting dizzy and they have to
switch clubs, but they can't touch each other, so they've got to throw the
clubs to one, it's just like, guys, what the fuck is this, man?
Like, Jesus Christ, man.
It's just nuts.
And then again, this thing that everybody keeps doing and look, much
love to Kevin Smith and to Adam Sandler and all these guys, please stop making
these movies where it's like, I'm supposed to feel sorry for this
character that I love because of his relationship with his daughter.
It's like, stop doing this.
Like, it's just, it's depressing, man.
They went to the same well for Paul Blart Mall Cop too.
They've got all these sequences between him and his daughter and she's
worried about her body and so forth.
It's like, somebody, did somebody come in and say like, okay, we know dads
are going to watch Happy Gilmore too.
How do we get the kids to watch?
Who did that?
Who, you know, cause Sandler doesn't take notes anymore.
Why would he have to?
It's like, it seems like Sandler was like, I want to hang with my family.
But this is what we get.
I think that's what it is.
And these guys, these guys have kids and they go, you just changed my life.
You know, I'm a different man now and I'm a deaf and it's like, okay, guess what?
Guess who you're not playing in the movie yourself.
Yeah.
Like, like I understand things change and you go, I don't want to make that record
again, the band already did that one.
We want to make a new kind of thing.
That's fine.
So do that, but what you don't do is go, this is like the thing, like when rappers,
like, like when Eminem did the Marshall Mathers LP too, and you're like, there's
no almost zero connective tissue to the first step, the first Marshall, if you're
going to do it, do the stuff that we were happy Gilmore to star Eminem.
What's that?
You mean Happy Gilmore to star Eminem.
Happy Gilmore to star Eminem with face tape pulled back like Dennis Reynolds
style, where I'm like, what is going on here, man?
Eminem, Eminem playing Joe Flaherty's son is one of the strangest
senses I will ever say.
Now, the Flaherty character in Happy Gilmore is like, you, you're not
wondering what happened to him.
You're not, you get updates.
That's the other insane thing about this movie.
Every single character outside of the grandma who's dead from Happy
Gilmore 1 returns to no avail for no reason.
You get the guy, the little kid that he chokes, he's back.
Everyone that has one line in the original is back for no reason.
Well, what is the, does Eminem look like that because he's had plastic surgery
or do you think they put makeup on him so he would look more like Joe Flaherty?
No, he, he, he's had plastic surgery and the, the drugs.
I think really did a number on him and he got some sort
of reconstructive situation.
But he didn't look like that two years ago and he's been sober
for like 15 fucking years.
I don't know.
I think he just got old in vain and got his face pulled back.
I don't know, man.
Um, look, there's not much more we can say.
Does the movie have a laugh here or there?
Sure.
Does it have a few out loud laughs?
Absolutely.
Does the movie suck?
100%.
It kills me to say it.
Uh, Sandler now said, let's go.
Let's make Billy Madison two.
He might've just been being, you know, uh, uh, humorous, but I, I, I mean,
I mean, it's come, I will predict it now.
We will get an Ace Ventura three.
Yeah.
And it is going to be some goddamn heartfelt fucking, please Jim Carrey,
if you're listening, if you make Ace Ventura three, just make Ace Ventura
three.
That's it.
Don't he's the only guy I think that got it with the sequel.
He's like, no, I'm going to make it even stupider.
I remember sitting in Ace Ventura too.
And I was like, thank God he didn't learn anything from like the first one.
You know, it's like just a stupid collection of laughs.
Uh, Billy Madison too is insane.
That wouldn't make any sense and it wouldn't work.
So naturally I assume they'll make it at some point.
We'd all much rather have perhaps a wedding singer sequel, something
like that makes sense.
I guess they go back for their reunion, do another reunion movie.
But, um, yeah, I, I going into this, this was not the kind of legacy
sequel where I went in arms folded.
Like, this is going to fucking suck.
And how are they going to, how are they going to duplicate the original?
I think me and pretty much everyone I know was like, this is really
going to be a special moment.
And it was, I mean, the opposite of a special moment or a special movie.
There's so many other things we could even mention.
I mean, the amount of times they do a montage at the beginning of what his
life looked like after the original movie and they show him hosting SNL
numerous times and that I think honestly is the worst CGI I've ever seen in a
mainstream movie and it's like, just use footage of him on SNL he was on SNL.
You don't have to do anything.
It looked worse than the Irishman, which was like the test of that technology.
It's insane.
And the amount of money Netflix has, the amount of money Sandler has, the
amount of money this movie had in my opinion, in my opinion, that's, it's
not fair to say it looked worse than the Irishman because the Irishman
was a little jarring at first.
Then you got used to it and you're like, okay, I can go with it.
This looked insane.
It looked like a kid did it on his phone.
Well, then Joe starts pointing out to me and then eventually Joe and I just stopped
texting each other because it was like, we were pointing out everything that
happened in the movie, but there are scenes of like a guy yelling in his front
yard that are CGI and you're like, what, what is happening in what world was
this cheaper, was this a better option?
Like, I don't know what's happened to the movies, but they, they could
certainly be improved by it, by at least trying at the script stage.
If all movies are going to become this bloated cameo fest, no laugh disaster,
at least try to get the script right.
Then at least you're starting from a good place.
This, you got to point the blame at Sandler.
He, he took his own iconic character and drowned him.
It was him and Tim Hurley.
He, who wrote the original Hurley.
He's a big SNL writer, wrote a lot of very famous sketches, but are
they past their prime?
Is it time to turn it over?
I don't know.
But there's almost nothing to recommend about happy Gilmore too.
It's depressing.
Yeah.
Hogs down for happy Gilmore too, right into that hole.
Yeah, same here.
As I said on letterboxed, it's like running into an old friend who sucks now.
You're like, Hey, it's, it's happy Gilmore.
What's up?
And then two minutes into talking to him, you're like, Oh boy, this guy ain't the
same.
Um, we'll be back, be back with the pickup, uh, I haven't seen that one
yet and Pete Davidson's the pickup.
Um, just some quick plugs.
Please go watch my special.
If you haven't yet, I never promised you a Rose garden on my YouTube, which
is at Joe DeRosa comedy, subscribe to that YouTube, please.
Uh, I'm on the road.
Next stops coming up.
Uh, you'll see me live in September.
Uh, I am going to Tampa, Florida side splitters, and then I've got, uh, a
headlining weekend at the mothership here in Austin, Texas.
Uh, after that early October, I will be at the punchline in San Francisco.
And then there's some other dates into this year and then neck into the
early of next year, go to Joe DeRosa .com, please for tickets.
Folks, I'm the Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
We are see you in hell pod on Instagram.
Um, please remember to get in there, do your downloading, do your recording,
uh, get, get whatever you want to take from this show that you want to have as
yours and keep do that in the next month and do it now because you're going to
forget, we all forget, um, the new season of the miss Pat show premieres October
24th on BET plus, make sure you watch it there on edited.
Um, I recorded a commentary track for airplane to the sequel that releases, I
believe September 23rd on 4k and Blu ray from Keno Lorber.
You can pre -order now there or at Amazon.
We will be back with a discussion of the pickup, which is now streaming on Amazon
prime and then a fourth true final episode of the we'll see you in hell show.
Thank you everybody for all your love and support.
We love you.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.