I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see
you in hell. You know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell. It's the month of Halloween, and we're here with some
big old horror talk for you. Today, reviewing a little film called The Mist. Black and White.
The Mist. 4K.
This is one of those, this is one of those title announcements where it's news to me
as well when Joe says what we're reviewing. I'm like, what are we doing? I completely
forgot.
I forgot too. That's why I said it so slowly. And then the next episode is Insidious Five.
Insidious Five. The door of the night. What is it called?
The Red Door. It's about sex work in Amsterdam. Well, more on that later. But yeah, we're
here to, we've talked a lot about The Mist on the show, but we've never officially reviewed
it, and we felt that reviewing the, specifically the black and white version was means enough
for it to justify its own episode, which is going to be interesting to talk about.
Yeah, we kind of, on the last episode, we're like, you know, there's 10 or so movies that
have these weird alternate black and white cuts, and I haven't really done any of them.
But yeah, I think it's an interesting enough topic. I think I'd love to see some black
and white cuts of things where it would be cool. And Darabont says it's his preferred
version, but oftentimes I disagree with him. Sometimes in the movie I do agree with him.
We'll talk later. We'll talk later.
You know what I'd like to see a black and white of is The Shining. I think could be
very interesting.
For sure, for sure. I mean, it's an odd thing. To me, it's like doing an IMAX movie that
wasn't shot with IMAX cameras. Like, does it look cool in spots? Yeah, but it's never
going to be the same as if you lit a set or lit a house or lit a woman's face for black
and white as opposed to color. Like The Mist at the end of the day is a color movie with
the color removed. It's not a movie lit for black and white. So it's interesting that
a director would feel that was the preferred version since it's not unlike using a filter
or something. I don't know.
And genre -wise, it doesn't always make sense. It's like when they do like Terms of Endearment
anniversary re -release in 3D and you're like, what?
She really wants them to give her daughter those drugs. She's coming out of the screen
at me.
You know something? I'm embarrassed to admit it. I've never seen Terms of Endearment.
Oh, it's an excellent movie. That actually comes out on 4K in a couple of weeks, I believe.
But oh man, put that number one on your list. That'll be one of your favorite movies. It's
incredible.
So funny, funny story. Ture Gordon, who is my mentor in comedy. He was the guy that got
me up and on my feet in Philadelphia and took me under his wing when I was one of the
only white comics in an all -black comedy club. And he's a black comic. But he used to take
me on the road.
Ture is a black comic?
Yes, yeah, yeah. He used to take me on the road and we were in the room one day. We got
stoned and we were talking and he was like talking about the color purple. And embarrassingly
enough, I've never seen the color purple either. And I said, and I hadn't seen it then. And
I said, I've never seen the color purple. And he really like started like laying into
me like, how have you never seen the color? It's a classic. And I was like, I go, well,
Ture, I go, it's, you know, I don't know. It wasn't like a movie I grew up with. I was
like, this is be like me yelling at you that you've never seen Terms of Endearment. And
he goes, Terms of Endearment is the shit.
And you hadn't seen it. You hypocrite.
I had.
No, it's the best. It's, it's McClain, Nicholson, DeVito, Lithgow, Jeff Daniels, Debra Winger,
everybody in their absolute prime, James L. Brooks, you know.
DeVito? Who's DeVito playing? I didn't know he was in it.
He, well, he was always bumming around with Nicholson. He was in Cuckoo's Nest and Hoffa,
of course, which he directed and stuff. But he plays a suitor of Shirley McClain, who,
you know, comes by with flowers and a suit and everything. And it's a small part, not a joke,
but it is a small part. And a small actor, Mr. Danny DeVito, the great. That'll be a,
that'll be a loss, DeVito. He's 80 now. He still seems sharp.
He's about 75. I, I, I, I think about it sometimes when you, you can see that he's
getting a bit older, like on the new, It's Always Sunnies and stuff. And I'm like,
but that's a tough show. And I get very upset when I think about losing him. But then that,
he's a tough one to judge because you see him mostly on It's Always Sunny. And the goal of
It's Always Sunny with that character is to make him look as putrid as possible. So you're like,
oh my God, he's doing terrible. And then you see him on a talk show and you're like, oh no, he's
still. Yeah, that's true. I mean, I love that they lean into, you know, one of his first lines
in Always Sunny is like, I don't know how much, how many years I got left. So I'm going to get
real weird with it. And then they just embrace that as the character's vibe for 20 years now.
But he's short. He is very short. That's my concern. You know, I, I worry like Simon Birch
and Warwick Davis, and he's not that short, but the shorter you are, it seems like your heart's
got to work a little harder because it takes up more of your body. I think he is technically a,
a dwarf because he's four, nine, 11. Okay. He does have, I forget what his condition is called.
That makes him so short. Or he might just, he might just make the cutoff. I don't remember,
but he's like the lady and she devil. Yeah. Oh, Linda Hunt. Yeah. Yeah. She's great.
In talking to him face to face or face to chest or whatever you want to call it. He doesn't read
as a dwarf. He reads almost like talking to a woman you're dating or something. So it,
it wasn't jarring, but they also might've had him on lifts and stuff too for the show. I don't know.
Any who the hell are we talking about? Black and white. Yeah. Yeah. I want to check out Logan.
You said the Mad Max is not that great an experience, but I don't know. It's certainly
something that didn't really catch on. There's only a few movies that did it.
Did you not watch? So wait, I thought on the last, oh, you haven't seen the Mad Max. I thought you
had, sorry. No, I haven't. I just haven't watched. Got it. Did you hit this? By the way, I haven't had
a drink since Skankfest. So October 1st. Okay. I'm not drinking until the end of the event on the
28th. So almost a month. Yeah. I'm sleeping better. My anxiety is better. I'm able to handle
and manage my emotions better. I'm living better. I'm feeling better. That said, I can't wait
to have a drink. Yeah. Yeah. I, I've been good about the drinking for sure. I think I will
definitely drink at this festival. And I hope you guys are all coming out. What's the seat
count in there? I remember going to Arlene's Grocery for shows and it seemed kind of like
your standard rock venue, right? It is, I think it was 110 tickets total. Love it. Love it. Plus,
and then there's another 15 people coming in, guestless people or whatever. So yeah.
Um, I have a, I have a bit of an announcement. Um,
I have been dating the lovely Jada Pinkett Smith. Um, I learned she was single and thought, well,
shoot, you know, let me shoot my shot and reached out. I love the way she's handled that relationship.
It seems like she's done great things for that man and that career. And I'm hoping she can do
same for me. By the way, I'm going to own everything I'm about to say. No offense to
anybody out there with alopecia. I know people that have alopecia and they don't have any hair
because of it. Yeah. I'm watching these Jada Pinkett things. She's got, she's got eyebrows
and hair. Like what am I, what am I missing here? What am like the, like alopecia means
the hair falls out completely unless there's procedures. I get that also too. It's, it's
progressive. Yeah. But I mean, the people I know that have alopecia, it was like,
it's, it's gone, man. Like that's it. Like they're, you don't have, I don't know, maybe I'm wrong, but
I only bring this up because she has become so, I mean, I have never seen a woman who was
being, I've never seen a woman go from celebrated to pariah this quickly in my fucking life. I don't
think like, holy. Yeah. I mean, she's, she's impossible to like at this point. I don't know
what else to say. I doubt Will's innocent and all of it. And I think he's unhinged as well, but
you really just want to shake them both and be like, you guys could do better elsewhere.
You can find happiness somewhere else and still talk to each other. You can still reach out and
co -parent and be pals, but let's not sneak off and fuck like 20 year olds and act like 20.
I think he was 20 is generous. I think he was, I think it was arguable about whether or not,
you know, of age. I don't want to talk out of school here, but I think that that was one of
criticisms that she got was that the kid was like 17 or something. Then there's those picks of Will
Smith and Margot Robbie where she's like showing off her cans and stuff. And it's like, guys,
look at the lives you could be living. You could be fucking Margot Robbie and children.
It bums me out because, you know, uh, I got to kill a bug on my wall,
Pat, talk for one moment while I do this. If you don't mind. Absolutely.
Maybe I'll sing Miley Cyrus's fly on the wall as a soundtrack to Joe and you know, that song fly
on the wall. Miley Cyrus is a, I think even her most ardent haters would admit that she has a
good voice. It's hard to deny. She's not like some of these other pop starlets, but fly on the wall
off one of her very early, maybe even first albums is a hell of a banger. It's a rocker.
I urge you to check it out. Did you get the bug, Joe?
Oh, he's not listening to me. I got these goddamn elder bugs all over my house. What are elder bugs?
I don't know. I looked it up today. They're, they're, they're innocuous. I mean, they're not
like, it's not like having termites or something. Like they don't really do anything, but
tell you stories about the old times and bore you. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. They, they, they, they,
yeah, they judge the furniture you're purchasing and what you're willing to spend on a lamp.
The, no, they, they just like, like all over my front window and I just found one in the house.
Like there, there's clearly a nest. I got to go after we record today to get some,
you know, I don't know. Here we go. Home ownership. I got to go buy like some kind of like
barrier bug shit that you put down so they can't come back again. But it's really a pain in the
fucking ass. That's the worst part of owning a home is you're like, Oh God, something has gone
horribly awry. Somebody should take care of that. And then a few days later, you're like, well,
I think it's got to be me. Think there's nobody else here and I got to do it. Yeah. It's, that was
a lesson I learned with when we opened the bar and shop was, I was like, this is it. I'm the end
of the line. Like there is no, yeah. Somebody else will deal with it. Somebody will pick up the
slack. Yeah. You know, and that's, so that kind of prepared me for this. Cause I was like the, this,
the owning a house was going to be like the bar where it's like, no, that's my problem now. I have
to pay for that and figure it out. So whatever. I'm not complaining. Just, you know,
maybe I am. Who knows. I made some orders this week from the, I got from the arrow sale,
the criteria on sale. Let's talk. I went into the arrow UK store and sometimes I do that by mistake
and I, for the four K's are region free. I have this top of the line 4k player that's still for
some reason is region specific, but any 4k will play. So I feel good buying from them, but I hate
that British blue rays have that giant red 15 circle on them. Yeah. I hate it. Yeah. You know,
like they put the age thing. I got the psycho collection, which I'm most excited about. I've
only seen psycho one and two, but it's all for a 4k, a book. It's like a beautiful looking set,
limited a dish. And then it's got this giant, it's like putting a giant R rating on the box.
Why do you need to do that? Which would look cool. The, at least the R, the, the, the classic
R rating stamp would look cool. That 15 thing looks like, you know, it looks like some sort of like
a warning sticker or something like, like it's on every one of them 15 or then I got Robin Hood,
Prince of thieves. It's got a 12 on it. Like that's even worse. A big green 12. You, you got
re Robin Hood, Prince of thieves. Who's going for 999 and 4k or 999 pounds. I love Robin Hood,
Prince of thieves. I mean, I saw it in the theater when I was 10, the drug dream.
I don't know if it holds up, but I fucking loved it when I was a kid.
I got from the arrow sale. I got the psycho box set. I love psycho too. I think psycho three is
serviceable and I think. Psycho four is interesting. I like the flashbacks,
but, but the thing that compelled me more than just having part two and three and 4k
was that the, there is the uncut version
of which one the original psycho has the original cycle has the R rated
and the uncut. So you get both versions of that, which is pretty fucking cool.
I have an Alfred Hitchcock box set. Which one do I have? They've released so many,
God, they've released so many Hitchcock box sets, but the box that I have is like the masterpiece
color or some shit, whatever. Anyway, it didn't have the uncut. So I got that.
I also got demons one and two 4k. Those, those were 18 pounds a piece, which translated to like
21 American. I was like, yeah, that's worth it. And then from criterion,
I got some real good ones from criterion. I got a, I got, I finally got that Malcolm X 4k.
Uh, yeah, they're really up in their 4k game. They're doing video drone, princess bride,
lots of great stuff coming out. I got devil and Daniel Webster. Finally,
I got the Todd Browning Blu ray set. They did, which is freaks, the unknown and the mystic.
Same. Uh, and then I got these box sets. Uh, one is called monsters and mad men.
Yes. Uh, and what's on this? It's like sci -fi shit. It's the atomic submarine,
first man into space, the haunted strangler and corridors of blood.
And then I got, these are only on DVD. I don't, I guess they just haven't done them on Blu ray yet.
Uh, and then I got another one called, uh, uh, when horror came to Shahi Shahi.
I got it. Yeah. So that's got goke body snatcher from hell, the living skeleton genocide
and the X from outer space. Very curious and excited about those sets.
I would also like to showcase this little beauty. Wicker man 4k steel book 50th anniversary.
Oh, I thought for sure it was the it's not beyond Walsh to have purchased the Nicholas cage wicker
man on 4k. I wouldn't have been that surprised if you wouldn't go over 10 bucks for it, but,
but not a post. I remember enjoying it. Um, this is the final cut reborn in glorious 4k.
I absolutely love the wicker man. I watched it yesterday. We can talk about that later, but, um,
it's a best buy exclusive and I think it's already wiped out. So I'm hoping this becomes one of those
hard to find gyms. I'm a little upset with best buy. I bought the, uh, Texas chainsaw massacre
4k finally from them and they had it advertised on the website as the steel book. And then I got it
and it wasn't, but it was also only like 22 bucks. And I'm like, I don't know if I feel like calling
them and they're going to make me return it. And then I got to wait and I'm like, Oh, who cares?
That's every time. And Amazon now, if you get a vinyl record from them, it looks as if they
rolled it down the highway to your house. And I'm returning. So I write in the reason like,
could somebody please, and every, every time you send a response to Amazon, nobody reads that,
but I'm like, please start checking before you send out stuff. Like, what are you doing? I'm,
I'm at whole foods now five times a week, cause that's where you have to go to return a fucking
package to Amazon. No, boy. Anyway, um, I'm excited for these, for these things to show up.
I got them shipped to the house. This is the first things like fun things I get. Actually,
I did get the mortal combat one arcade one -up arcade cocktail table in the mail today.
Okay. It's killing me that I am recording with you right now. I'm not assembling this in my
living room. Oh, it's not even up yet. I said you have to assemble the one, the arcade one -ups.
That's the price you pay for getting such an affordable version of an arcade cabinet. But
you know, it's sad. I actually love when I have something to assemble like this bookcase. I just
put together it because that sort of work finally quiets my brain. Um, I usually love it until this,
these last three weeks where I've had to do it every day. And you know, it's like 11 45 PM. I'm
in my living room going like the sucker won't fit the way it fucking says it's okay. You know,
I'm like, my neighbors probably think I'm a lunatic. Yeah. Sweating in your eyes and everything. Yeah.
Um, well let's, let me take us to the movie corner for the wicker, man, the ridge, 50 years old.
Um, feels super fresh really just because of how fucking weird it is. This final cut version has
like 10 musical numbers in it that I, I mean, I remembered there being a couple in the original,
but not this. Um, including wild, there's this Brit Eklund sequence where she's like dry humping
the air completely naked, trying to seduce this cop in the next room. And she's like just fucking
the wall. Like come get it, bitch. Man, it was hot, but the entire time she's singing, singing this
siren song, the whole movie's got crazy vibes. Uh, what's his face? Ari Aster should definitely
have to send these guys 5 % of his midsummer earnings. Um, it's essentially the same.
Another chink in the Aster armor. Gotta love it. No, it isn't. I mean, I actually,
and this is probably sacrilege, I probably prefer midsummer, but I just think he
took a lot from this movie, especially in terms of set design and horror by day and all that. Um,
I would imagine it was pitched as a modern wicker man. Um, but it's just great. It,
it's earned its classic rep reputation. I think a lot of times when people watch
a 50 year old movie, especially the younger generation, their arms are folded and they're
like, let's just see if this is really the scariest movie ever. And then when the wicker
man is not saw 10, they're like, what the fuck? It wasn't scary at all. That seems to be the,
the underlying attitude of most of the, uh, the young generation regarding movies. Um,
and you're just stupid because those movies wouldn't exist without the pioneers. Now,
if you want to say, okay, I love Jim Carrey. That doesn't mean I got to watch Charlie Chaplin.
Fine. I get that comedy changes, but to go in expecting it to be scary in the same way
50 years ago is kind of silly in my opinion. They also just released the Rosemary's baby 50th,
which I'm excited to watch in 4k, but like, you know, movies had different paces, different cuts,
different edits, you know, everything, every shot lasts about 10 times longer in a movie from 50
years ago. And, uh, you either get on that wavelength or you don't, but I have very little
patience for people who don't watch a movie in the context that they should, you know what I mean?
I really liked the Wicker Man. It's nothing. It's a great movie and, um,
highly influential, obviously on horror, even if it's not terrifying to this day,
it is very intense, especially the ending. Uh, you, you can do three in a row. I have,
I have a new psycho that I want to focus on and I'm going to send say, excuse me,
I'm going to save my movie corners for the next episode. I haven't had time to watch a ton of
stuff, given the, uh, the, the not construction, but the readying of the house.
Yes. Um, well, sure. I will talk about what I saw just last night, brand new movie called
Anatomy of a Fall. Um, it was foreign, but, uh, largely in English. I'm going to make sure I know
where it takes place because often I am dumb about that shit. Um, Anatomy of a Fall French.
Yeah. Okay. Makes sense. Um, this was essentially a courtroom drama.
And honestly, you could feel in like the crowded theater I was in
that people just love that genre. William Friedkin's last movie is an, is a yet another
remake of the Kane mutiny court martial. And I'm very excited to see it and it's getting good
reviews, but like it wasn't out yet. It's just came out. Um, it's just once this movie, you know,
there's about an hour of setup and then it just becomes a real great courtroom drama with like a
douchey lawyer on the bad side being like, Oh, is that right? Mrs. You know, and that genre is
just such a treat because I was realizing as I was watching it, you know, people are clapping
and getting, you know, leaning forward in their seats and getting really into the movie,
which at its core is a pretty average courtroom thriller, but I was just realizing how much we
are not even being given the basic genres of movies anymore. You know, like there aren't
courtroom dramas. There, there aren't romantic comedies, you know, there really aren't, um,
thrillers, you know, so much, you have to really kind of go out of your way to find them and they're
low budget. And I don't get that because I think the public is dying for just a return to solid
classic filmmaking or in those genres that have worked for a hundred years. So, um, it was a
treat. I think it's getting a lot better reviews than it deserves just because people miss the
trappings of this kind of movie, but, um, it's about a woman. She has a young son who was blind.
She has a husband who is depressed and struggling to write. He has writer's block.
She has cheated on him in the past and now she has an interview about her new book,
which she has stolen some aspects of from her husband's failed book. And it's a big success.
So while she is being interviewed, he is upstairs blasting loud music and trying to distract her.
And at some point he falls out the window or did he kill himself or did he push her is the
just of the movie basically. Um, and with her cheating and having possible lesbian tendencies
and kind of stealing from his book and all these things, there are motives and it's, it's, you know,
you get it. It's like a presumed innocent or something like that. My biggest issue with the
movie is that once I figured out it was a ripoff of the staircase, the maybe best true crime
documentary ever, it started to bother me how much of a ripoff it was. Um, if you've never seen the
staircase, the original 10 part series is probably the best true crime thing ever made. And this
steals the entire story from it. The, they just changed the sexes in the staircase. The wife falls
down the stairs. Um, the husband is secretly bisexual and has cheated on her. Um, it's the
exact same story. Um, that's a little weird to me. Like I feel like they owed them an inspired by
credit or something because it made the movie less surprising once I figured that out. Um, but a good
movie nonetheless, check it out. And the best part of it is the lead performance, which I think will
be Oscar nominated by a woman named Sandra Huler, who I loved in another movie called Tony Erdman a
few years back that they announced a re it was a three hour comedy. It was hilarious. I loved it.
And they announced a remake with Jack Nicholson and Kristen Wiig. And I was like, perfect. Never
came to pass. Yeah, I know. We haven't seen Nicholson since. Yeah, that was going to be it.
I bet he bailed and they just never made it unfortunately. But, uh, oh well. All right.
And then, uh, you know, one quick one after pet cemetery bloodlines, which was an F minus. Um,
I watched the original pet cemetery again and it looks killer in 4k, especially after the
exorcist 4k, which was a bit of a letdown. That's another 50 year old movie that, um,
weirdly the exorcist 4k looks best when they're outside. So I didn't need to get that 4k. I
already have the blue ray. No, it's the best the movies ever looked, but it's just not night and
day because it's, you know, just the nature of the beast. You know, the movie, when they're in Iraq,
it looks like a movie that was made yesterday, but some of the inside stuff is not as amazing.
It's just the source materials, you know, they're 50 years old. So it's like you get what you get.
The pet cemetery one really blew my mind, especially considering how badly Paramount
has done on some major releases like plans, trains, automobiles. But, um, yeah, it looks great.
The movie is so weird in a lot of ways and it's so fast. Like, I don't know if that Stephen King
screenplay is the reason, or if they just edit it to shit because Mary Lambert was a music video
director, but God, it hits. It's like a greatest, greatest hits of the book pet cemetery.
And it's so effective, but it's one of the few movies where I'm just like, man,
I could have gone for another 10 minutes in here. I'm shocked. You're, you're changing your tune.
When we reviewed it, uh, two years, whatever the hell it was, when the remake came out, you,
you were not very kind to it. And, uh, I'm glad to hear you're coming around to get on it.
I did. I realized I had given it three out of five on letterbox when I watched it last time.
And this time I added a half a star and on a good day, I could even go four with it.
But I mean number three and Stephen King adaptations. Uh, it's, it's pretty damn good.
It's just, it's weird in kind of the best way. It's like off the wall. I think where it suffers
is in its performances. Um, even Fred Gwynn, I'm sorry, his accent is ludicrous. Um,
he's playing it way too broad for me. I think he's great at it. I don't, I don't,
yeah, I'm surprised to hear you say that. I think the worst of the bunch is the wife is,
is not good at it. The wife stinks. The daughter is really annoying after a while.
The daughter is awful. The kid is one of the best kids of men movie history. Of course,
he's great. The kid's fantastic. The dad is fine. Uh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Watch it again.
The dad is, the dad is in another movie. Like there's a reason that guy never worked again.
I mean, he is fucking terrible. Gwynn works in a campy way. Gwynn works in it,
honestly, in the way the movie works. I mean, I laughed out loud every time they would cut to
cat with glowing yellow eyes and just like chilling with the family on the couch. I'm like,
nobody, nobody's raising an eye here. Uh, an eyebrow. Um, it's a little campier than I
remembered. And that, in that aspect, I think Gwynn's performance works, but it's a little
bit much. I loved it though. It's fun. It's, uh, it's what horror should be. I liked it a lot.
It has a sense of humor and it's mean as fuck. The best performances in the movie are by the
players. Um, you know, it's, uh, oh, the, the daughter. Yeah. The, uh, spinal bifida sister.
Yeah. We get played by a young man. Yes. And, uh, what's her face? The, the, the maid,
the one that's like that hangs herself. Like those are like the best performances in the movie.
Yeah. And then Pascal is great. Who's Pascal? The, the, the like zombie ghost that keeps appearing.
Now look, another issue. We should have cut Pascal from the film in my opinion. Why?
I would have cut Pascal from the film. I like Pascal. I enjoyed Pascal. Uh, it's a weird name
for the character, but I, he should have a scarier name, but, um, yes. Uh, my, my, my, uh,
two quick, uh, news psychos. So Netflix, you gotta love this. So Hulu I got rid of because Hulu
announced they were raising their prices, I believe to now 1799. For what Hulu? For the
commercial free privilege of having Hulu. And then Netflix. I mean, for what in terms of shows,
Hulu? What are you giving us? That's what I'm saying there because they're giving that that's
their, and then Netflix is 20 is going now to 2199 for the premium. Now here's what's happening.
Yeah. And you know, we could have seen it coming from a mile away. They're like, okay, you guys
want to strike? You want to give? Okay. Yeah. We're going to fuck the consumers now. And this is why
I keep saying they needed to call for a consumer ban of these services. And I know why that was a
complicated thing. And I understand theoretically why you don't ask the average Joe to, um,
to not have, uh, you know, his, his subscription service that he gets to sort of unwind with
after work every day. But, you know, I've had, again, I've ultimately, I stand for the concept,
uh, and the principles behind these strikes. I've got a lot of issues with them. I'd like to read
something that Bill Dawes wrote. Uh, Bill Dawes is a friend of mine. He's an actor and a comedian,
and he's a working actor. He's been on Broadway a bunch and he's been on TV. I just found this
interesting. Uh, he posted this, he posted a screenshot of an email he got from sag after.
Dear bill in this time of adversity and hardship, our unwavering solidarity along with that of our
sister union members is truly inspiring for 98 days. We've stood strong, united in our pursuit
justice, fairness, and the value we bring to the industry. The WGA triumphed after 148 hard fought
days, proof that perseverance will break the toughest barriers and result in the transformative
change we need to justify everyone's sacrifices. That's the screenshot he posted his response
underneath barf. There is zero solidarity with the union. 90 % of the people on picket lines don't
actually work. And 1 % of the union is making this go until 2024 because they are annoyed. They are
making less millions and are terrified of becoming irrelevant because of content creators and the
media landscape. Meanwhile, sag lawyers don't give a fuck because they get paid more millions
the longer this lasts. And ultimately, nobody knows where AI will be in two years. It might be
fucking your mom in 2026. Plus the world is ending in 2029 anyway, according to AOC and the climate
countdown clock in Manhattan. He, some of his, this is just his own politics, but, but whatever.
The fact that producers came back to the table with less shows. I'm sorry. The fact that producers
came back to the table with less shows that sag has no leverage. However, a bunch of part -time
performers are cosplaying activism and are being hoodwinked into believing there's some sort of
magical fairy dust, unicorn poop solidarity amongst a bunch of self -serving narcissists
who tripped on the Piaget. What is that word? P -I -A -G -E -T.
That I, I don't know that word. All right. Who tripped on the, whatever that word is,
cognitive developmental stairs growing up and now have to pretend acting as some noble craft
instead of an unfortunate byproduct out of a fucked up childhood. Finally, get over yourself,
the nanny and sag multimillionaires. You're tricking a bunch of Uber each drivers that
they're soldiers on the front lines of justice. Somebody needs to get kicked in the balls. The
people picketing are the same Lemmings wearing masks in 2022. Stop it, grow up, take the L,
work harder, create your own shit. Also, I love you all. Now, it's harsh, but, and whether you
actor saying one thing that I've, holy fucking agree with, go create your own shit. These people
are going to come back to the table and fuck you in a, just in a new way, which we are now seeing
with the price hikes of these streaming services. These other way, when the, when the deal is
settled and when they, when we do come to an agreement as the writers have, and the actors
will, they will exploit that contract. They are already doing it. I told you last week about how
I got a job and then the job was taken away because, oh no, we're not paying for you to replace
that rider. You guys went on strike, so fuck you. You know, it's very, I agree with quite a bit of
what he said. I would never talk about that publicly perhaps. And I disagree with a few things he said
but what are the comments? Are they ripping him apart?
It's funny. I didn't even look at the comments. I guarantee you there's some people there who are
like, yes, you're exactly right. But there's also probably some, some ruffled feathers. I mean,
I agree with him and Joe, like creating your own shit and breaking away from this system of having
to do the song and dance for these mutants and monsters that run these corporations.
You're definitely going to be happier. I mean, I don't know if you're going to be richer in the
long run, but you're going to be happier. No, most of the comments are like, you know, preach, brother,
you know, that kind of shit. Yeah. One guy wrote, you're such a tool. If you want to work, go work
for Drew Barrymore. I don't know. I guess did she cross the, I don't know. She had the saddest story
really because I, of course, I liked Drew Barrymore like everybody else, but she just, she announces
she's coming back, no riders. Everyone flips out and then four days later the strike ends.
Same thing happens to Bill Maher. It's like, if you had just been decent for another week.
Well, let me ask you this though. What happened to this whole, we're not going to go back to work
till SAG settles and they all went back to work. It's just bullshit. No, I was told across the board
that we would not be returning to work until SAG settles. And that's just not the case. Everyone I
know who's a writer is frantically trying to get a job. So I don't know what happened there, but I
accept on a positive note with all this with your, cause it's relates to your job. I'm excited to
announce Ms. Pat is co -hosting an episode of Taste Buds with me because she's, yeah, her publicist,
who's a friend of mine hit me up and she said, Pat's promoting some stuff. Could you have her on
Taste Buds? She's going to be in New York. And I said, sure. When she said early November, I said,
well, on the 6th, Sal is out. I actually need a co -host. And she said, oh, she'll do it. And I
was like, great. That'll be really fun. Like just, she will be hilarious on that show. Yeah. She's,
she's great. I love her. Give her my best as always. I'd love to get you in there, Patty,
if we're ever recording when you're on the East coast. Well, you know, I'll be there Thursday.
So we record Wednesday. What are you going to do? Um, all right, let's get to the flick, I guess.
Let's do it. Uh, let's talk. We're talking about the mist brand new 4k a dish hovering right around
20 bucks, 22 bucks or something on Amazon. And it gets you, um, a 4k edition of the original picture,
a 4k edition of the black and white picture, a couple of blue rays and a nice host of extras.
It's good little package if you like the film and Joe, would you put the mist below pet cemetery
and your all time Steve Kings? Cause to me it's in the top five. I don't know where it go, but it's
in the top five. No mist and misery are the top. Misery is number one. Yes. Mist. I would put it
number two pet cemetery rounding out the final three. I would put the original pet cemetery.
I would put the TV mini series of it. And I would put, um,
for me, probably Christine would be my fifth. Sure. Uh, I got Shawshank and Carrie above
some of your choices. I forgot about Carrie for a guy. They talk so much shit about how like he,
you know, they've made so many bad versions. They made a lot of good versions of his stuff too.
Let's be real. I'll tell you an amazing Stephen King, uh, uh, not book, uh, the, the, the TV mini
series of a storm of the century, but it's not an adaptation. King wrote the script as a,
he called it a novel for television, but, but storm of the century is one of the greatest and
freakiest and scariest Stephen King things ever. In my opinion, sweet. I own it. I never even think
about watching it. I'll watch it tonight, man. Awesome. It's perfect for monsters in the storm
or what, like the mist. No, it's about a major storm happens or I'm sorry, as a major storm is
approaching a man shows up in this small new England town who is quite evil and sinister.
And it just kind of goes from there. Um, but no, that's bag of bones bag of bones sucks. Uh, no
storm of the century is the main guy from wings. Tim Daly. Yes. Yeah. Uh, the guy those wings guys
were in all the Stephen Kings. We had, we had a Steven Weber shining like why was, why was wings
the pipeline to the Steven King universe? You know, who else is in this is the guy, the, the,
the guy that he's from walking dead and he's in the midst, the, the, the older man in the midst,
the gray hair guy, he's in this and he plays, he plays like a fucking prick in storm of the century.
He's awesome in it. Uh, it's great. It's a perfect rainy day. Like, you know, it's four
fucking hours cause it's two. Yeah. Whatever. Anyway. Um, all right. So the mist.
Yeah. Tell him, give it, give us the gist of the mist.
Uh, I mean, it's, it's as simple as it gets. It's a major storm happens. A major,
a massive mist is coming in, uh, over the water as a result of the storm. And
on a trip to the grocery store, you know, we're in a, again, we're in a small
new England town on a trip to the local market. I should say, uh, the mist takes over the town
and a father and his son gets stuck there with their neighbor who they're at odds with
others. Thomas Jane townies, the neighbor is Andre Brower, the great who does not act enough.
He's awesome. God, he's awesome. He's so good. I love that scene cause it opens with the
establishment that they've had these property disputes and stuff in the past. And in a, in a
gesture of goodwill, Thomas Jane takes Andre Brower into town to like be neighborly. Yeah. And
they're getting along and it's like, wow, like they're healing. And then this mist gets them
trapped. And then when Thomas Jane goes to Andre Brower in confidence, it's just like, I don't
want to scare anybody, but like there's, there are like monsters in the mist. We just witnessed
somebody die. Andre Brower thinks they're, that they're lying to make a fool out of him. Right.
And then also calls out the town's racism that he's the only black resident. And he's like,
and just the way he's doing that thing where he's like, I'm, you know, you know something,
I'm glad that tree fell on the boat. I'm glad it's so spiteful. It's just fucking great. It's
really, really great. He's incredible. Like I used to watch him on homicide life on the street,
one of, you know, one of the all time, great loss shows like Robin Williams would come on
and do a guest spot on that show. Cause the parts were so amazing, but he never really, you know,
unless I'm missing something, I don't remember him having like a classic role in a film ever.
Maybe he prefers stage and TV. I don't know, but he was in, you know, he was in that Ray Romano
show, men of a certain age. Yeah. I guess more of a TV guy. So, but he's, he's excellent.
Anyway, he's awesome. He's in a, Oh, you know what he's in? He's in a glory.
Yes. But he's like, he's, he's so young in it. I almost, I was watching clips of glory the other
day. Cause I was on a Denzel kick and I was like, Holy shit, that's Andre. But I didn't even
recognize him. He looks so young. Yeah. Anyway, the mist takes over. They can't leave. Why? Because
people are, they witness people walking into it and get killed and they don't know what's going on.
They just hear them screaming. And then the reveal of what's going on, that there are monsters in
the mist happens when they go to the back of the store to try to get a generator working.
Uh, the kid, as Pat pointed out, the Sherman Ader in a rare dramatic turn from a prior dramatic
turn for the Sherman Ader, he says, I'll go out there and, um, and fix the generator. And, uh,
Thomas is like, you can't go out there. You'll, you'll die. And the kid's like, you're a pussy.
Get out of my way. And, uh, of course, when they opened the door, these tentacles come in and
he is killed. And, uh, and, uh, as you, it's, it's funny that I watched this when I did,
because I re I, I just coincidentally, that day before I watched it, I was watching a clip of
Quentin Tarantino, uh, talking about how his major influence for reservoir dogs was the thing,
the carpenter version. And he said, I feel like I achieved what I was trying to achieve with
reservoir dogs. And it was the thing they did in the thing where it's a bunch of men trapped.
And because of them being trapped in the situation, they start turning on one another and,
and going against one another and whatever. And I was watching the mist and I was like, oh,
the mist is another one of these movies. I love to do a box set of these movies. Like people trapped
Dawn of the Dead is another great example. People are trapped. They're in a desperate situation.
How are they going to start turning on each other? And the mist is one of the best examples,
because the sadness Lord of the flaws. Yeah, there's a lot of the factions that,
that happen here are just, you know, and, and the most interesting of which is the one led by
the town religious cook played by Marsha Gay Hardin, Hardin, Hardin, Hardin.
Quick pause though, to the thing point in the opening scene, we learn that Thomas Jane is a
painter of movie posters. Yes. And he is worried that they will just do a Photoshop version of the
movie poster, a great little inside bit. But he appears to be painting the poster for the thing
in that opening scene. How about fucking when he said that on this watch, I was like,
it's one of those moments where you go, look, we're all freaked out about AI, but you're like,
it's just history repeating itself. Yeah. 10 years, 15 years ago, it was a guy worried about
Photoshop and people could just be out of a job because of that. And he's like, they'll just put
two giant heads on a poster and call it a movie poster, which is most movie posters, two giant
heads on a poster. Marsha Gay Hardin is the way she starts to systematically like form a religious
cult and end of days, a religious cult within the confines of the supermarket. And you see people
that doubt her and think she's an idiot and a lunatic convert over to her as they become
more and more desperate. It's really great. It's really, really well done. Stephen King's writing
and, you know, and Darabont, because I think he is a master adapter of Stephen King.
They write the best, most hateable, hissable villains. They really do. You look at Shawshank,
the assholes in that prison from the warden on down, the amount that you hate those people,
the sick fucks in the green mile, like half of that cast are monsters. I've talked at length
about how the bullies in Stephen King books and movies feel real because they're trying to murder
you. They're not trying to trip you. They feel like they want you to die. Pinkstone, I've talked
about it. He writes the best bullies. There's nobody scarier than the Stephen King bully.
And I mentioned Christine. Christine is probably the best example and it, those are the two where
like, my God, they're just monsters. It's the only time I feel like that reminds me of being
bullied, you know, because I always felt like I was going to be killed and not because I was a
pussy. I had horrific encounters with bullies. So I love that. And then this woman is really one of
his great characters. And as I was starting it, when she first appeared on screen, because I
actually forgot about the Marshall Gay Harden character, I thought, oh yeah, this is why I
don't love watching this movie because I hate this woman so much, but it's just so satisfying.
It's so satisfying. And to see, it's exactly how it would go down in this small town.
You know, she appeals to their religious side and starts swaying them over and uses fear to do so.
And that's just a tale as old as time, you know, no matter when you're reviewing the mist,
you would say this reminds me of what's going on right now in America.
Um, and it doesn't do it heavy -handed, you know, the only thing the movie does heavy -handed,
that's my issue with it, is the sheer amount of times characters say that there's something
in the mist. That to me, the amount of times they're like, you know, I think there might be
something inside the myth. That line is said 55 times for some reason. Um, beyond that,
I don't really have any issues with the thing. I think Marcia Gay Harden is awful, but that's
what makes her come up and so sweet. And I applaud it alone in my home, um, when she meets her fate
and the little guy, Toby Jones, who does it says, I killed her and Thomas Jane goes,
thank you, Wally. I laughed out loud. I applauded. It's such a great line.
Cause it's exactly what the audience wants. You're dying for her to be killed.
This is, uh, Toby Jones is great in this. This is before he was a household name. Um, and, uh, he,
he's great. Well, they give him that moment too, where, where he, uh, snaps at his boss.
Cause I think if he just came out shooting the gun, like Rambo, you'd be like, what,
where did that come from? But he also earlier on his boss is like, now listen, you're going to do
it. And he goes, Hey, shut the fuck up. Which he's probably wanted to say to his boss for 15 years,
but you sense inside, like there's this guy waiting to get out. Who's not this meek little
guy. It's tons of great little character moments in this movie for sure. I think, um,
that's my only criticism is I think they give Toby Jones, his character has some really dumb
lines in my opinion. Uh, when you talk about like, I'm blanking on the lines now, but you know,
he'll be like, you know, religious fundamentalism and, and political lunatics,
just another day in the office on planet earth. Like, you know, he has like lines.
That is heavy. I was wrong. That is heavy. You forgot about that.
Um, but, but those were the only lines that, that, that, that bothered me the seat. My other one
criticism would be, and somebody wrote this to me on Instagram, I posted a picture of some movies
I'm watching and somebody said, I hope in black and white that CGI has aged a bit better. And I
said, well, it hasn't, it's a little bit better, but the tentacles, it, it just, it just never
looks right. It just never, it didn't look good when it came out. Doesn't look good now, but
at the same time, you know, it's like, if I'm watching, like the empire strikes back,
I can tell that the ad acts are, are stop motion. It's, you know, it's just, you can tell it's in
effect. That's all. It doesn't ruin the movie for me. It just doesn't look real. That's all.
I think the black and white did help a bit. Um, I actually forgot that there was such a variety of
monsters in the mist. I remembered it just being like tentacles and stuff. I forgot that we see
like that there's a long sequence where they look like pterodactyls dinosaurs. There's a long
sequence where they look like bugs. Like there's just all kinds of monsters in the mist. And I
thought they all looked pretty awesome and would all look different and cool. And the only times I
felt it looked shitty was when like a, one of those big slug things was crawling on somebody's
face. And like the woman was like, ah, you know, it looked like not any better than something out
of the fifties really, but I'd say 80 to 90 % of these effects look pretty sweet. I don't remember
them looking shitty in color. Maybe black and white helps. I'm not sure, but, um, the black and
white really made it look sort of more like night of the living dead or like an old black and white
indie, as opposed to something like Mank or Schindler's list where it's like, you know,
incredibly well art directed. I think the living dead was, was, I might be mistaken. I think that's
the reason he wanted to do a black and white of this was that it was. Yeah. Yeah. Well, yeah. So
found out through reading up on it a little bit that basically the, the producers who are by the
way, America's sweethearts, Harvey and Bob Weinstein, they said, speaking of monsters in
the mist folks, they said you can either end the movie the way the movie ends with the most cruel,
mean, nasty ending in the history of horror and maybe movies at large outside of seven perhaps.
Um, just a sick ending to this movie. And they were like, you can end it that way and shoot it
in color or you can shoot it in black and white and give it a happier ending. And he said, it's
more important to me to do the ending. And thank God, because I don't think the mist would be as
well loved if it had been released in black and white. And I think that the reason it sticks in
people's craw 20 years later is the ending. I think the rest of it is a great movie, but the
story ends in the book on a very hopeful note. Uh, the, uh, the, um, I saw this in the theater
with my parents and I remember, yeah, I remember going into the theater, having seen a blurb in
the newspaper about it, you know, when they put the poster up with the testimonials and it just
said an ending, you won't believe. And I remember thinking like, you know, this is post usual
suspects. Yeah. At the time everyone was like, it's going to have a six cents ending. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm like, what is, what is this? Come on. How crazy could the ending be? And then we saw,
I remember the whole ride home. My mom was going, Oh my God. Yeah. I can't get over the way it ended.
I was like, yeah, that, that really, that stuck with me for a while. Like she saw it on a date
on Thanksgiving night. And my girlfriend was like, you ruined my Thanksgiving.
Like she just kept saying, you ruined, that ruined my Thanksgiving. I had nothing to say about it.
Um, but it's great, you know, it's brutal and it keeps getting more brutal as it goes. Um,
yeah, I just love it. I love it. And it's a Twilight Zone ending. Really. It's just not a way
that a two hour movie generally ends with like a fuck you, you know, which is really what it is.
Fuck you to the lead character and fuck you to us. Um, fantastic. Uh, what would you say over
all? Would you rewatch it in black and white Joe? Or when you put this on next, would it be a color
for me? It'd be a color viewing the next time I ever turn. It was a fun experiment, very cool.
And I enjoyed it. I just, for me, it's not the preferred version of the movie. It's, it was a fun
alt. Um, I would, uh, I would, um, I would suggest, I would personally recommend the black and white
actually, as I was watching it in black and white, I was envisioning, well, actually I can do one
better. After I watched it in black and white, I went to watch the bonus features, which for some
ungodly fucking reason, uh, you have to go to the third disc of the collection. They don't tell you
where anything is located. I'll tell you why, uh, it's because 4k can only handle so much information.
So they often put it off to the blueprint, but go ahead. Maybe you make a note of that in the box
somewhere. But anyway, so in going to the, all the other discs to find the special features I
wanted to watch, it was, I was seeing color snippets in the menu and, uh, and I was like,
oh, it doesn't, it's not as intriguing in color now that I've seen it in the black and white,
but there was something really, uh, there was something very desperate and, uh, cold about the,
the black and white version. It worked. It also made the mist look cool. Like it did the opposite.
The mad max was tough because like I said, you're just out in a desert and you're like,
I don't even know what the hell I'm looking at here with this. It worked. It made that the
mist come alive more. I agree that the shadows of the things moving in it a little more ominous.
I liked it. I agree for the, for the mist scenes for sure. Uh, yes. The early scenes where it's
like a tree fall that fell on the car and all that, that felt like desolate night of the living dead
to me. Um, and then the mist, and like I said, I think the effects were helped by the black and
white. Uh, let me get a little more, uh, metaphoric here. Uh, you know, the, the, the themes of the
film, some of the themes of the film are dealing with things in black and white. It's like, it's
the, the people think this is the end of days and you're either on the religious side or you're not
the people not on the religious side or like those people are absolutely crazy and a hundred percent
wrong. And this is scientific in some way. And that, so like everybody's approach to this whole
situation in the film is pretty, uh, cut and dry. So I liked it. It just worked for me.
I hear you. Um, I think either way you slice it, it's a fantastic movie. The stuff that I
not remember really hit the most, like really, I, I really loved the variety of monsters we got.
I love that they took the time to give them, you know, faces, personalities almost,
where at least they were differentiated and not just a big amorphous blob punching our heroes,
you know? Um, I liked the character design quite a bit. And when we see what has happened to these
people that left it to go explore the mist and they are like, it's similar to an aliens actually
when they're like frozen to the wall by, I don't know, pods eggs or something like that.
So disturbing, you know, that guy like shaking going like, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You know,
there's so many just really effective moments in this movie and, um, great to see Francis
Sternhagen from so many King classics as well. Um, I actually thought when he's going to kill his
son there at the end, I was like, did Francis Sternhagen say to the state of Darabont, like,
you're not going to kill that boy. I just couldn't imagine her agreeing to do that scene without
saying like, please don't do this, please. Then again, I don't know the woman and she's dead,
but, uh, I always loved her as an actress. Great film, easily a top five King for me.
Sounds like it's even higher for Joe, uh, and a really just a perfect movie for Halloween.
Why? I'm, I'm not, I can't believe I'm blanking on this, but why the decision
for him to, I guess he just chooses to live because he's like, I'll suffer the most.
You can all have a quick death and then I'll be the one that gets literally
eaten alive by these guys. I'll figure, I'll figure something out,
which I love that line too. I'll figure something out.
Um, I just assumed he was going to kill himself, but yeah, so jumping into a monster or whatever.
Folks, we'll be back with insidious, the red door, uh, quick plugs. We'll see in New York
on the 28th for Arlene's grocery, the festival.
Yeah, we're only about a week out everybody. So, uh, are there any tickets left Joe?
If, if any, very few. So yeah, uh, go get them if you want, but I think very, very limited.
Um, November 9th, I'm at KGB bar for the New York comedy festival doing, uh, readings from my
audio book, not standup comedy, but it'll be a fun show. Come out to that November 11th, Philadelphia
PA, uh, theater, the living arts, uh, doing the hour November, uh, 18th Buffalo, New York,
doing the hour in a theater at Seneca one 30th of November, Denver at the summit doing the hour,
December 1st and 3rd, Phoenix, Arizona, then Salt Lake city doing the hour. And then January 13th,
just announced Gramercy theater in New York doing the hour. Uh, go to what joderosa .com
for all tickets and info and all that stuff.
I am the Patrick Walsh on Instagram. We are at CU and hell pod on Instagram.
We sell merch at the Etsy store and we will see you next week in New York
and we will see you next time and we will see you in hell.