I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
It's your favorite podcast talking movies, what kind of movies, genre movies, most of the time,
but sometimes in a day like today we deviate a little bit from the course, talk about a comedy movie,
but a fantastic comedy movie, meeting its fantastical, and do we think it's fantastic?
We are going to have to wait and see.
Yeah, we're talking about we went to a double -feed the other night of Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back,
which I had not seen since its original theatrical release.
I ain't heard that song since it was big.
Exactly. You know what they're talking about? Biggie Lawrence.
Biggie Lawrence, the night the lights went out in Georgia.
Residogs.
And this is the first time I realized it's the husband killed the whatever the fuck the woman is.
Anyway, we also saw the brand new Jay and Silent Bob reboot, and if you're wondering,
hey, we're not going to spoil anything for you, but if there's nothing to spoil,
if you're wondering how to see it, this was a I think a two -night only theatrical event,
and now Kevin Smith is going to be going around the country with it as a roadshow,
where he'll talk to you for like three hours and then show you the movie and probably a $50
night package kind of thing. We will tell you if that's worth your time.
In the meantime, Pat, how are you doing?
I'm doing pretty well. I know you were saying you went off your meds.
Me, just the small 10 milligram dose has truly changed my life.
The obsessive thinking I had, I'm able to shut off with the flip of a switch.
I've been feeling better than I have in quite some time.
What do you want again, Lexi?
A 10 milligram Lexi pro, yeah.
I might need to try Lexi pro because I was on pro -zek for a long time and pro -zek's an old med.
Yeah. I learned that basically, you know, that I've been torturing myself since I was born
with my own brain, and I still have the tendency to go to those places, but I'm able to say,
my therapist would always say, just say out loud, cancel the thought, and then you'll stop thinking
about it. And I was like, you don't know me at all that will never work for me, but it does
with this. I'm able to go stop thinking about it and I do. It's helped my relationship, I'm more
present, I'm happier. It's a good thing. And, you know, there's always doing these national days
of destigmatizing this or whatever. I'm happy to speak freely about it. If you've got a question
about Lexi pro or whatever, if you've been putting it off, you know, it's not the 180 that a lot of
people say these meds are for people, but for me, it has made my life almost a measurably better.
And I appreciate it. Now, is it wrong? Is this a stigma if I think of you as a dirty, sick psychopath?
Because I take pills? Yeah. Is that a stigma? It's a stigma. I'll stop doing that. You're not wrong,
but it's a stigma. I'll stop doing that. No, I'm doing well. Good. Glad to hear it. I went to the
Desert Days festival, which for year DAZ for years was in. Oh, I shan't know. I get it.
Joshua tree. And now it is at marano beach, which is about an hour and a half out of L .A. Folks,
if you're in and around the area and you see the lineup, this is what Coachella should be. I've
been to two Coachella's. It's that without the douche factor. A, drugs are encouraged. It's not like
everybody's acting like you have drugs at Coachella and searching you thoroughly and everything.
They encourage drugs. The main stage has mushrooms on either side of it, giant inflatable mushrooms.
It was a huge wide open area. You were able to be alone at a music festival like I did mushrooms.
I went out and like looked at this beautiful water and you know, they have all these incredible art
exhibits and neon shit that you want to look at when you're on drugs and my buddy of mine, Ryan
Murphy from Missouri came out. We had an amazing time. Greater. Greater. I had no idea. You know,
a man who I once saw wearing a floor length almost like a robe slash cloak like a king would wear
out in public in Los Angeles. You know, they say it's gone to a set. I say he's still just the guy
from next door. Anyway, we had such a nice time. We saw Wu Tang. We saw Wien. We saw animal collective.
We saw one of my favorite new bands always with two V's instead of the W. Let me jump in. How was
Wien after all these years? Wien was great. They played chocolate and cheese in its entirety.
Oh, wow. That's a treat. And some others. Wu Tang played 36 chambers in its entirety along with a few
other tracks. Love it. Flaming lips were there. They fucking sucked. The man can't sing anymore or else he
was having an off night. But they were supposed to be doing the soft bullet, which is a beloved classic
album. And man, he couldn't sing. What is the big one after the soft bullet and did everyone?
Yoshimi battles the pink robot. Those are the two best probably. Yeah, I like, you know, I like
Flaming lips just fine. They don't necessarily do it for me. But I dig what they do. But some of the
other band you're man, I mean, I love to have seen Wu Tang again. I've seen them. But I'll always
go in for another round. And Wien is the one I was most curious about because there was a time.
Wien is from not far from where I'm from. Yeah. And when they split, it was like, it was like
David Lee Roth, Eddie Van Halen, and split was like, this is done forever. Yeah. So
I'm shocked to see them back together. And it's just weird seeing Wien with like gray hair. I mean,
they look like dads. They look like 60 year old dads. Yeah, for sure.
They were very cool. The highlight of the fest, believe it or not, because I thought they might
be past their prime was an amazing set by Devo that may be their last ever live performance.
They fucking killed it. They still wore the outfits and everything. But they were awesome.
Now the hats double as diapers folks. Stereo lab, you know,
witch, which is a you would love witch bunch of witches. The drummer is Jay Mascus.
Oh, okay. They were, they had two albums in the 90s, but they are a few men's shoes style,
riff, stoner rock, bonanza. I was right up front for them. Oh, baby. Now we're going to a
me, but we're going to a meba today. You're going to want to pick up that witch.
I'm going to pick up that witch. Also, I'm going to get the record folks folks.
And another highlight for me, a band that you should check out, they got three amazing albums,
Div, DIIV, great stoner, indie or rock, a little, a little more indie as opposed to the,
the riff rock of, of witch. But I love Div. They played their new album in order. It killed.
Anyway, my point is this festival is what you always expect and hope a music festival will
be. And then you find yourself mashing to some hippies armpit and watching everyone take pictures
of themselves. I watched full sets of bands. It didn't see a single cell phone and there's no rules.
You know, there's no like put your phone away. I'm just saying this thing brought out the kind of people
who are there to be nice to see good music. There wasn't one fist fight. It was just people
enjoying the show. Go see it. I'm going next year for sure. I had a brother. I love it. Maybe
I'll go next year. You should. You should. I saw I was I diced at three shows at the stand in New
York. Really? Yeah. He plays Vegas all the time. Yeah. In a very small room, it's about 150 seats.
And I got to see one of the shows, which was awesome. I laughed literally so hard. I was crying.
Okay. And then after the show, they had a regular show. And I went on corner of my eye,
I see dice watching my entire set. Nice. Yeah. And I walk out. You nervous. A little bit. But I hung,
you know, I kept it together, which felt good. And I did. I had a great set. And then it was awesome.
I went outside afterwards. And he's and I met him. And he's like, oh, you're fucking funny, man.
You know, like that's pretty cool. Do you remember when he gave you the cold shoulder at his
book signing that we would remember this was must have been nice? I didn't bring that up. Of course.
But there was also a line of 300 people waiting to tell him that, you know, which nursery rhyme
was their favorite, of course. And he did in classic like rock band style. He did his closing
joke and his closing joke was about how it sucks to get old. Yeah. And he goes, but you know,
people maybe old stuff ain't so bad. And then he turned, pulled out the cigarette, started doing all
the things. Yeah. Little Miss Muffet sat in like close with that. And it was like, you know,
it was like Pearl Jam coming out and doing Jeremy at the end. Sure. It was a lot of fun, man.
Have you ever listened to Dice's podcast? I haven't. I still do it. I didn't even know we had one.
He has one. I've never heard of it. You know, when I always wanted to listen to, and I never,
I don't know why I don't listen to iced tea's podcast. I feel like that is probably loaded
with gems. Probably he's the best Twitter follow. It's the funny. I mean,
everyone I have tagged his tweets. I mean, we've quoted them so many times each other.
He, I mean, he gives me a shit that I'm like, that's going to be a new motto for me in my life.
Yeah. I love it. Yeah. The daily game tweets, you know, like all that stuff. Yeah. He's awesome.
The other thing, you know, my buddy and I got this really nice Airbnb, which because it was in
Redlands, California, we got like a four, you know, four bedroom house for $90 a night.
But we had a hot tub and everything that we're having fun. But every time we would come back from
the festival, we fired up a little show called 90 day fiance. And I told Joe about it. I know you're
might be surprised to hear that from me. The last reality show I watched religiously was the original
incarnation of Jersey Shore at least 10 years ago. I gotta tell you folks, 90 day fiance is a treat
in these dark times. A bright, bright light. The easiest way to get into is watch the first season.
It's six 40 minute episodes. They're all on Hulu. The new season starts November 3rd, which might be
in your rear view by the time you hear this premise is simple. A man or woman here in the states
comes in contact with a foreign love interest in one of three ways usually. It's either they're on a
trip abroad and they meet somebody. They're on a dating site or they're being targeted basically as a
patsy by a gold digging whore. I mean man or woman when I say gold digging whore. But there's six
basically, you know, like there's six stories in each. And they go back and forth so you never get
bored. It's like, you know, like Magnolia where you keep jumping back and forth between all these
stories. That's probably the first time anyone's compared 90 day fiance to Magnolia. But you're jumping
around. There's always the best one that you look for that I look for is the sad, disgusting looking
guy who either lives with his mother or lives in shambles or his poor who has convinced this insanely hot
gold digging whore to come to America by saying he's got money. She gets there. She's devastated. You wait
to see are these two going to have sex? How far are they going to go with this? There's always one
attractive couple that you're actually rooting for. You know, they actually met when the guy was,
you know, overseas and you know, that's always sort of a fun romantic thing. But there's always a few
where it's just like, holy shit, this woman is going to ruin this man's life and she does.
The most popular people they carry overseas into season, it's on TLC. I don't know what you're
learning from it, except maybe don't meet someone on the internet. TLC, you, I mean, they're
hearing a lesson on that channel anymore. No, no, absolutely not. But for me personally,
I am always looking for that next like binge. It's been, you know, even the prestige shows,
you know, I really liked Russian doll, for example, but it wasn't a show where the one would end
and I'm like, I got to watch the next one. You know, it just wasn't that kind of thing.
This show I'm watching for a night with a giant smile on my face. My buddy Ryan got hooked on it.
I showed Heather one. She's hooked on it. And there's so many waiting for you. I urge you to check it out.
That's all right. Was that your first movie corner, by the way? It could be. Sure.
All right. Well, let's, let's do it. All right. Let's reverse engineer a trip to movie
corner. My first is 90 day fiance. I checked out finally, uh, NOS 4a2 pronounced NOS 4a2,
which is the new Joe Hill. That's a rough title, man. Yeah. The adaptation of the Joe Hill book.
I guess AMC adapted it. Shutter is now streaming it because AMC runs shutter.
Uh, man, the premise of this thing is so fucking cool. This creepy old man kidnaps kids and
takes them to a place called Christmas town. Okay. Which is some bizzara weird twisted Christmas land
that he run. Like interesting. You know, it's like, this is such a creepy cool concept. Yeah.
And I was really excited to check it out because I was like, yeah, this, this looks cool.
Uh, the kid that played Spock and the new Star Trek movies is the plays the old man.
Uh, you know, he's on American horror story as well.
You know, I'm talking about Zach Riquinta. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Uh, and he plays him because the
guy has to be young and old. Yeah. So he's great. But I, I just didn't enjoy the show. I couldn't
get into it. It's what these shows often do, which is they take whether it's from other source
material or not. Every show doesn't have to be a 55 minute 10 episode slog. Right. It's just too
long. Yeah. Just get to the meat. Like get us going here. Let's do it. I love a half hour drama
these days. Yeah. It's what I'm doing for TBS. Yeah. I mean, it's, it's just, it was just, it was,
there was just too much other crap in it that I just didn't care about. Yeah. You know, when,
when you've got to premise like Christmas land and an old man who's got like, who's like the devil
or a vampire or whatever the hell he is, that's enough, man. That's what you want to see. Right.
And then they're doing this like, you know, it's really tough. How this girl wants to be an artist,
but can't get into art school. It's like, Oh, God, guys, I don't care. Yeah. In the book, this might
carry. But in a TV show, this is just really counting, counting down the minutes here or eating up the
minutes rather instead of, you know, a great example of that is Dexter, which the Dexter material
was, I mean, man, yeah, I couldn't get enough of that show when it first started. And then it,
it found new life with the lift cow season. But they would cut to the dating exploits of like his
partner. And you just be like, what are you doing? Like it would be a half hour of the show was not
Dexter material. It was the other people that he worked with and their struggles. And man,
it brought the show to a grinding hauled every time. Well, I've said it before. It was my problem with
the psycho series. Bates Motel. Bates Motel. It was just like, guys, I don't need a subplot where there's
an a crime syndicate underground growing and selling marijuana in this. For Christ's sakes, guys,
give me Norma and Norman Bates. That's what we're here for. Not everything is an hour show. And
everyone always, you know, for the longest time, a drama's got to be an hour comedy's got to be a
half hour. That's changing now to some degree. Yeah. So anyway, that's not for a two. So how many do
you watch? Maybe three. You're done. I watched like two or three. And then I skipped ahead because I
was like, just, let me see that they get to Christmas town or whatever it's called. Finally,
in like episode eight and a half. You're like, yeah, for God's sakes, guys. Yeah. Give me the goods. Sure.
Anyway, I watched a Oscars for my consideration screening of the film, The Laundromat, which will also
be on Netflix by the time you watch this or hear this. Laundromat is a new film from Steven.
Soderbergh and I saw it with my buddy and I was like, you know, there are some I like less than
others for sure, but I don't think I've ever disliked a Soderbergh movie. I took a course on him in
college and whether he goes super low budget like that bubble movie or huge like Ocean's 11,
I just think he's one of our best directors. I know I'm not alone in that. But The Laundromat was the
first where I just felt it did not connect in any way. But I have to do a rewatch because get this,
Joe. I go to see it in Burbank after I hung out with you on Sunday. And we walk in. The movie starts.
It's Antonio Banderas and Gary Oldman, bizarre combination right there in white suits narrating the
film. Oldman is doing like a Warner Herzog voice. You mean like introducing the film? No, they're in
the movie. They're like, oh, they're in it. They're talking to the camera narrating it. Oh,
Jesus. And they're on the beach and these white suits. They look at the back street boys and the I
want it that way. It's open and who? Oldman and Banderas. They do, they are not the best couple. They
have no chemistry of any kind. And Oldman is doing a Warner Herzog accent. They're narrating it and
you know, I was getting so frustrated because I'm like, why is this so confusing? And
it made me feel stupid. And I'm like, I'm not getting this. Then after they talk for a few minutes,
it jumps into this fascinating story of this African family, a very wealthy African family,
where the dad is fucking his daughter's best friend. Okay. You know, she's probably 19 or something.
The this was such a juicy, great story. And it goes on for 20 minutes. And I'm like, what did Banderas
and Oldman have to do with this? Isn't Meryl Streep in this movie? I'm thinking. And I'm watching this. And
the story was great. Basically, the guy says, I'll give you my daughter, this huge
company and all these millions of dollars if you don't tell your mother about me, fucking your friend.
And I'm like, all right, whatever happened here, I'm very into this story now. Then that story
just immediately ends. They never go back to it. This Oldman behind me almost in my ear goes,
this is the weirdest movie I've ever seen in my life. I laughed out loud. Then it jumps to like
Jeffrey Wright. You know, the Jeffrey Wright. Yeah, now the big fan. The great actor. And his story is
completely disconnected. Then there's Meryl Streep and James Cromwell. You know, it's jumping
around in such a way I have no idea what's going on. You can feel the audience getting more and more
restless. And then the movie ends, credits start rolling and it's been 45 minutes. And I realized
that what happened is this movie that was already extremely complicated. They started it on like
the second reel. Oh God. And because the second reel starts with this narration, it felt normal.
And because Soderbergh is a man who always does his movies out of order, the Lyme and etc. No one
thought to say anything. We're like, okay, this all makes sense. So basically we watched the end of
the movie first. So my opinion of it is not really fair. When we did all watch the beginning and then
watch it in order, which I intend to do, it's kind of a mess. And it got away from Soderbergh.
Basically, the story, which I had to piece together like I was in fucking memento, was that Meryl Streep
and her husband James Cromwell are on a little fun boat cruise. Uh -huh. The cruise ship flips over
in a very terrifying scene and almost everybody but Meryl dies. She's trying to get much. She's playing
kind of a Midwestern woman. Meryl is incredible as she always is. She's always fucking great. Yeah.
Big little lies this season. I mean, what a great addition she was. And she's kind of in that
in that role again. She is, except she's nice in this one. She's trying to get her husband's
insurance money and just keeps getting told no. And basically these other side stories are ways of
showing how corrupt the system is. But when you're watching it out of order, man, it's an impossible
thing. And I would have immediately cut Banderas and old men. I think their stuff just absolutely
doesn't work. There are scenes and bits in this movie that are great. But by and large,
it didn't quite work for me. Maybe it'll work for you. There is enough to recommend. But definitely
watch it in order because otherwise it's impossible to follow. Imagine Soderbergh was not happy about
that. Probably not. Probably not. I'll do another television one. Sorry. You want to talk about LA,
though. We walk out and tell the people running the screening like, hey, we watched the last 45
minutes of this movie. I'll tell you what I didn't hear for five full minutes as they stumbled to try
to get this thing back on track. The words, I'm sorry. No, no, of course not. Wasn't there fault?
They said it was sent to us as a digital file. And they must have just messed it up. And it's like
yeah, but you're supposed to test it before you show it to a room full of people. No, it's not
their fault. Of course not. Of course not. Yeah, I understood. They sent it to you. Cut up to the wrong
thing. Test it. Yeah, don't get me started. Anyway, carry on. I'll do another TV one. I actually paid
to watch to rent the or I bought rather the season premiere of it's always sunny. Yes.
Newest season. It was back on before I even knew it was back on. I had watched season 12
when it hit Hulu a few months ago. I had seen some of it prior. I got to catch all the Dennis episodes.
I hadn't seen yet. Loved it, but was a little worried at the end of the season because it ended
with that huge dance interpretive dance thing that was to be taken very seriously that they were
going to somehow maybe go in a different direction this year. No, they just act like it didn't happen.
Act like it didn't happen. Came right back, tasteless humor. They're right back in the saddle again.
Dennis seems to be back in full swing. It's the only episode I've seen so far, but it was a strong opening
to the season. The plot is that Charlie and Frank and Dennis and Mack decide to rent out their
apartments to as an Airbnb under the stipulation that they get to stay in the apartment with the
person and this is a means for them to get laid. The Mack and Dennis storyline has Mack.
Well, the Charlie and Frank storyline is they're trying to get you like European co -eds to stay with
them who are backpacking because their place looks like a hostel. Pretty easy to understand.
The Mack and Dennis storyline is Dennis is trying to get laid, but Mack is trying to orchestrate this
romantic comedy scenario. This is the one criticism I have, not just of this show, but of many shows that
have established a cult following at this point. You see this more and more frequently now,
they never really completely explain that part of it very well. So the next thing you know,
you're in like the fifth scene of Act 1 or whatever it is, and Mack is going on about like now the
protagonist will be D and you're like, wait, what? Oh, oh, oh, he's doing a romantic comedy,
isn't it? Yeah. And it's literally a thing that they could establish in a very funny way with a few
lines of dialogue in the very first scene. So you're certainly wondering like this happened with
the Golden Girls in like the seventh season, like you'll be watching an episode and it will just end
on like Sophia crying or something and you're like, did they overshoot and were they in a jam with
edit? Did they, were they rewriting this on show night? Like what the fuck has happening here? This
is all very fixable stuff, but shows, TV shows, particularly comedies, I find tend to start doing that
where they're just like, they'll get it. They'll get it. And the movies we're talking about today do
that quite a fucking bit. That being said, found the episode to be very funny. I'm relieved to see
them being their old, you know, shady character selves again. And that's it. It's a positive review.
I hope to see more of this season sooner than later. Yeah, I mean, I've had a couple working
relationships with Charlie. So, you know, it is what it is. I have seen every episode this season.
The episode you're mentioning I thought would have been literally a million times better without
that romantic comedy element. I didn't understand it. I think, or just explain why Dennis would go along
with this. Right. They were making him too amiable in the whole thing. Why and why was Mac doing it?
That was never. Yeah, it just never made any sense. It's a show that is, it's the nature of a show that
takes as big as swings. And that's a huge compliment in this day and age, a show taking that
biggest wings. But it's hit and miss, you know, and, and of the ones I've seen, there's been hits and
there's been misses. But how is the season overall so far of the other ones you've seen? Pretty good.
It falls in lines with the others. There was one that was just sort of, I was baffled by it to
be honest with you, but that's, you know, that's the beauty of the show. Right. My last one will be,
it had been years, but it's because I had a friend in town. I went to one of the synospias screenings where
they do the movie in a Hollywood forever cemetery. How the people with family buried in these
cemeteries don't revolt. I'll never understand. They broadcast it on the side of a mausoleum,
but the sound and picture somehow is amazing. I've been to a lot of these 10 years ago. My old
riding partner and I thought we got a job on this show and we didn't, we each drank a bottle of
two buck chuck and I threw up on a grave. What the hell is two buck chuck? $2 .1. $2 .1. It's a
trader Joe. Still to this day for $2. Is it disgusting? Nauseating. You almost can't drink a
whole bottle without throwing up, but I threw up on a grave and I was so ashamed that I ran from the
the cemetery. But if you're in LA, you know, is it, is it trendy? Is it something that everyone does?
Yes, but being in that cemetery at night when they got it all lit up and the stars and the neon lights
and everything, it's so beautiful. And I was there for, you know, a special movie. The sixth
sense 20th anniversary came out in 99. When I saw it, I had a fever of 105 .7 and I almost blacked out.
But you still went to the theater with it. I didn't realize how bad it was until after the movie when
my friends were like, you don't look in five. Dude, that's, you die from that. It's like impotence, yeah.
I had to make sure my jizz still worked. It does. And at the theater. We said wait till you get home.
The theater, yes. I asked the usher to test it. But it was the sixth sense introduced by M Night
Shyamalan himself. Very good. And man, this guy comes out. He was as humble and charming. I don't
know why, but you always think the director is going to be a bit of a douche. He was a delight
and he brings out who else, but Haley Joel, Haley Joel 31 years old now, even more humble and delightful.
The two of them give a sweet introduction. And then after the movie, an interview by Jordan Peele.
Now, how much would you have respected the shit out of Shyamalan? If he Shyamalan, you guys
and played the happening instead of the sixth sense after you were all there? That would have been
really. I just, I remember despising that movie, but I would have, I would have stayed and watched.
Of course, but it just would have been an epic fucking move on the guy. For sure. Yeah. I've
been really wanting to revisit Lady in the water because I read that book about the making of it.
That is a fascinating night. I saw that opening weekend. Oh, my God. Oh, mighty rough stuff. Anyway,
go ahead. Um, you know, Shyamalan is one of the most inspiring stories in Hollywood. The man
came out swinging with just classic after classic, lost his career entirely, but they kept making it,
looked up letting him make shit until it got too bad. And then he found out how to come back.
You know, he's a fascinating figure. He came back in a low budget way. He's probably making more
money than he ever did before because he's investing his own money. He's doing it his way.
And it was, it was a great evening. They had great stories. They talked about how Haley Joel as a 10
year old boy would be slamming his body against a wooden door to try to get into the emotional state
he needed to for the scenes. And Shyamalan would say to his dad, like, Hey, is he okay in his
day. Oh, that's his process. Let him go sounded weird. But you look at Haley Joel. Now you couldn't find
him or well adjusted guy, at least on the surface who knows. But the sixth sense in a cemetery on a
beautiful crisp Hollywood night. It was a wonderful thing. The movie holds up like gangbusters.
You do feel stupid for not recognizing the twist because Willis is wearing the same clothes
throughout. He never talks to anybody. They're a scene after scene, you know, organized in such a way
that I can't believe I didn't think why isn't this person answering you? Right. But somehow it worked
on America. And I think that's a great accomplishment. Well, the real giveaways are that the many
moments where Willis yells, what am I a ghost to his wife? Yeah, exactly. I can't believe nobody picked
him. Exactly. No, but it's a it's a great movie. It still holds up beautifully and, you know,
the twist works, everything works. And really Shyamalan intended the last scene of the movie to be
that scene between Tony Collette and Haley Joel in the car where the mom, he reports basically to his
mom that he's spoken to her mom, the grandmother, and that she was always proud of her, you know,
and she came to see this dance recital that the mom didn't think that her mom was at. And I tell you,
I mean, my buddy was crying. I thought I was going to start crying. I don't even remember it being
that emotional movie. I guess it's just that I'm an older guy. But what up? It's a perfect scene.
It's a perfect scene. The two of them in the car where he reveals to his mom that he communicated with the
dad. There's an almost I'm not kidding. There's an almost identical Golden Girls plot line. Really?
Where Sophia passes out goes to heaven, sees her old husband, Sal, he tells her to, he's like, it's not
your time, Sophia, tells her to say hi to Dorothy with a goofy nickname that only he called her. They
entire episode I died and saw your father. Dorothy never believes her until she at the very end,
she says the nickname thing. Okay. And Dorothy's like, how do you know that mom?
Should we go to heaven with Sophia or just here? Yeah, you see her goal. That's, well that is,
do we or don't we? No, you do. Because that's where the Golden Girls, when I was rewatching it,
really fucked up, whenever they do a fantasy sequence. Yeah, it's like the Cosby Show where he eats the
big sandwich in there. I mean, that's the worst episode of that. There are two that go crazy
with fantasy. That's one of them. The other one actually works. I think it's when Blanche's dead husband
comes back. Yeah. And the whole episode you're like, how is this possible? Right. But they actually
make it very funny. And there's a storyline where Sonny Bono is, is desperately after Dorothy.
Okay. And it's very funny. And then at the end, Blanche wakes up and then Dorothy, she tells Dorothy,
I had the George Dream again. And she's like, who did I pick this time? She's like, you pick Sonny Bono
and she's like, oh good, you know, yeah. They actually do pull it off, but that heaven one is,
I ain't no good. Sure. Well, I mean, for me, I always thought his two best were six cents and
unbreakable. I rewatched Unbreakable very recently. The six cents is a far superior movie.
Unbreakable is great, but it can't hold a candle. It's a much more narrow film than six cents,
you know, but it's it's a good one. I'll end with one more TV related one. And I'm going to
make it make it last. Why don't you top yourself off while you're in there? Can it? All right, you just,
I'm not going to get you into having a drink or two, am I? It's just it's all right. Well, you know,
folks, this is what a what it sounds like when a lonely man tries to convince another man to be
lonely with him. I'm on my second glass of wine, which I don't think is too bad. But, you know,
Pat's had one whiskey coke here, and he even that one was a real struggle to get him to have it.
Anyway, I'll close with a, as I said, another TV related one for mine to keep my theme going.
We've talked stranger things at length on this show, and we reviewed the seasons.
But here is a movie that clearly influenced stranger things. One of the many,
but one of the far lesser known ones, and it's never gotten a nod on the show. So I have no proof
that it was an influence, but I would be hard pressed to believe it wasn't. And that's a little
1980s piece of magic called the gate. I just rewatched this movie. It stars a young,
what's his face? I was going to say Ethan Hawks, son of a bitch. I go to pieces when he's gone,
when Pat's gone. A young Stephen Dorf, cute as could be. He didn't have that sinister look back then.
Anyway, it's about a young Stephen Dorf and his best friend discover a hole in the backyard
of Stephen Dorf's house, his parents house. He's not like a richy rich kid. The hole opens up into
some sort of deep pit in the ground. And eventually all these weird things start happening.
And eventually you learn that the pit is a gateway to hell. And these demons start coming out of it.
And because it's the, I guess it's mid to mid, like 86 -ish. Because it's that time period, they use
some, it's all practical effects. But it's a lot of claymation effects for the demons, which actually
really works and is really cool. And then there's some on put on green screen effects and stuff
like that. But the movie is super fun. It's super sinister, especially for a movie starring children.
The entire movie the parents are gone because they've left the kids home alone for the weekend.
But it's about three or four kids coming together to fight monsters from another dimension.
It's great. It's super fun. It looks cool. It's very well directed. It's well written.
And it is absolutely worth a watch if you've never seen it. And it's worth a rewatch if you have seen
it. Because in rewatching it last night, I had forgotten just how menacing the movie gets. I
think it never really gets, well, at all, whims ago at any point. It's not ever played for comedy.
And they pull it off. Surprisingly, for that time period, with the effects and everything, it's,
you know, not to say that many movies didn't back then, but this one really, really does pull
it off. And it's great. It's great. And it really captures that fun mid to late 80s.
I keep saying late. It's really not late. It's mid -80s. It's pre -87. It captures that mid -80s
fun, horror adventure feel that, you know, I find those movies to truly be gems.
They're not hard to come by, but it's hard to come by one that hits it on the nose as well as
say a Gremlins does. And this certainly does. So give it a watch if you've never seen it. Give it a
rewatch if you have, I've never seen it. It's great. You should do yourself a favor. I'm surprised
Scream Factory hasn't done a re -release yet. It just played Beyond Fest too. It's an awesome movie.
I'll check it out. And now to our picture of the day, the double feature, Jay and Silent Bob Strike
back. And Jay and Silent Bob reboot. Sure. Let me give you my intro to Kevin Smith. You know,
I'm probably a junior in high school. I couldn't see our rated movies and had a big drama cast
party. I was wild. Somebody had clerks. I watched clerks. I was blown away by the language and I
could believe how filthy it was. I didn't know what some of it meant. I was very sheltered.
But I loved clerks. I loved mall rats. I first one I saw on the theater was chasing Amy because I was
finally 17. I loved chasing Amy. I loved dogma. And I used to be very, very excited about a new Kevin
Smith film. The man was a master of dialogue. Especially I think to a young, unformed mind. He is,
you know, like, you're like, oh my god, I love this shit because it's filthy. It's fun. It's funny.
I had a great time with his movies really up until I saw Jay and Silent Bob in the theater. I
remember seeing it. I remember my disappointment throughout. And I thought it was just because I
loved his other movies so much. Seeing it again the other night, I realized, no, that was the beginning
of the end for Smith. I don't think he made another good movie after Jay and Silent Bob.
You said you like clerks too. I did like clerks too. I did like clerks too. You're correct. Thank you.
But I said dog. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's thought I was before. I'm getting my timeline
screwed up here. I just feel like, and I know he got introduced to weed by Seth Rogan on Zach and Mary,
but I'd feel like the guy's not trying anymore. Let me sort of my overall. How did you come in
in contact with Kevin Smith, Joe? I went to see Pulp Fiction. Sure. With Jim and Bill Pinkstone.
And Bill had already seen it. We had all seen Reservoir Dogs. We were all excited to see Pulp Fiction.
And we were going to see it. Bill was seeing it like the second day in a row. Like he was one of
those guys. Jim's older brother Bill. If he liked a movie, he'd go five days in a row and see it
every day. Sounds like a prime candidate for AMC Stubbs, A list. Yeah. Well, he's got kids now. So he
doesn't hold on. My phone is buzzing and it's very distracting. Sounds like a fly. What do they call
those? Fly buzzer, zapper. So he had seen Pulp Fiction. He demanded we all go see it immediately.
We were all excited to see it anyway. So that was it wasn't a hard sell. On the way to the theater,
he said, I'm not going to say a word to you about this movie trailer. But they're going to play a trailer
for this movie. And it looks like one of the coolest movies of all time. It was a trailer for Clarks.
Jim and Bill were very excited about Clarks. I was not. It did not. It didn't look like the kind of
movie I would enjoy. I eventually saw it. I didn't like it, but I loved Jay and Silent Bob
so much. And I was like, I love the Star Wars talk. I like the Star Wars argument. It had
moments I enjoyed, but overall, I didn't even though it spoke to me in certain, like the street hockey,
like all that stuff, like I was very relatable to me. But I just didn't. It wasn't my kind of movie
at the time. But I love Jay and Silent Bob so much. Yeah. I saw ball rats opening weekend because it
was basically going to be a Jay and Silent. I fucking loved ball rats. Then everybody was like,
this movie is shit. Like Clarks is a good movie. This is shit. I was like, I loved it. I loved dogma.
Upon rewatching clerks, I appreciated it much more when I got a little bit older. I saw Jay and
Silent Bob strike back in the theater. I fucking loved it. And then after that is when it started to
go downhill for me as well. I was I hated chasing Amy. Okay. To this day, I hated it. And honestly,
not for the reasons that everybody hates it. You know, it never set me off that this is a white
cis male perspective on a, you know, right? That's not what set me off about it. I thought the dialogue
in that movie was so fucking contrived. And it reminded me of why I hated the TV show Weeds.
It's why I don't like a lot of Cameron Crow stuff. It's way too fucking quirky. It's I couldn't
fucking chasing Amy to me was. I actually liked the movie singles. Yeah. But singles is fucking
cringe worthy at times. And chasing Amy to me felt like he was trying to make singles or one of
those kinds of movies. Yeah. Yeah. Just and just the lines just didn't they're not what anything at
somebody would really say. You know, like when like the line that always sticks out to me is when he
goes when Jay and Silent Bob finally come into the movie and like and then Jay even that got ruined
for me because Jay goes, you know, I didn't know you were such and such or whatever. And you know,
and Silent Bob goes, bitch, what you don't know about me could just about fill the fucking grand. And
like, oh God, this is horrible. Anyway, there's a big practitioner of that. I mean, some people are
like dialogue should be flowery because it's not how people talk and other people want dialogue to sound
like real human being talking. And it's it's I think it people are pretty much evenly split down
them. And I got to be honest, it's what what you just said is what I always loved about Jay and
Silent Bob. Yeah. Jay to me is an absurd character. Right. But I knew guys like that. I knew guys like
that in college that were always on and so crazy. Yeah. And you're like, there's something wrong
with this guy. But it's his perspective on everything is so incorrect. It's fucking hilarious. Right.
Like and I found that palatable. I did anyway. I was pissed off after Jay and Silent Bob strike back
because he he had announced I'm ending the view of skewniverse. And now I'm going to make these
other movies. And I didn't want to see him do learn his lesson real quick. Yeah. And I remember seeing
clerks too. I liked clerks too. I when I find superior to the Star Wars argument in clerks
is the Lord of the Rings versus Star Wars argument in clerks too. I mean that the line when Randall goes
there's only one return and it's of the fucking Jedi. I was like, that's one of the funniest fucking
that should have been the review of the movie like or an actual review of the movie. Anyway,
um, it's uh, I uh, I loved, uh, well, that was it. I didn't love anything after that. Um, I mean,
there's Jersey girl. Terrible. Zach and Mary. I mean, Zach and Mary is, is, you know, passable on a
drunken evening. Exactly. Jersey girl is not. And then well, you love tusk. So I love tusk. Actually,
I'm sorry. I forgot about Tusk and I really like, uh, I look, I think Smith is at his best when he's
doing red state and tusk and shit like that. He knows how to stay. It was fine. You know,
the hosers I didn't say every movie he shoots already looks like a horror movie except with comedy in
it. Right. Yeah. So when he shoots a horror movie, you're like, finally, you're, you're unlit scenes
are appropriate. Yeah. You know, like it is amazing to me that he didn't find a cinematographer or
somebody to help elevate his shit because man, I mean, he's on movie 15, whatever it is. And this
J inside Bob reboot looks like fucking dogs, especially on a big screen. I mean, then came
the clerks cartoon, which cartoon is hilarious? The episode with, we didn't get into this the other
night. The episode with Baldwin, which is the episode one is hilarious. He's in the whole show,
isn't it? No, he's only in that one episode. He might come back. He comes back, but yes, very
briefly. Yeah. But he is the other episodes are not good. They did a J inside went Bob cartoon. It is
terrible. Okay. I like all six episodes of the clerks cartoon. I want you ran by the guy who ran
Veep, by the way. David Mandel, Anna Seinfeld, right? Other, you know, he's Kevin Smith has done
some shorts and some anthology things and whatnot. He's been off his mark for a long time in my opinion,
except I didn't like the harm. I can't say, but that to me was a different venture for him. Anyway,
I was excited by the announcement of Jay and Silent Bob reboot. I was apprehensive for very
obvious reasons. These guys are much older now. Can they recapture the stone or slacker humor again?
I thought it was an interesting barometer or sorry, it was an interesting litmus test to go see the
original leading right into this one, right? Seeing the original again in the theater, I laughed my
balls off. It is not a good movie by any stretch. It is not well made by any stretch, but in the
air of C before we're half banked, it very much to me holds up as a very funny stoner comedy.
And that's about it. I gotta say, I didn't like it then and now as a stoner, I didn't laugh.
I thought it was just a shambles really. The occasionally a great Lionel sneak out don't get
me wrong, but I mean, the story is ludicrous. The jokes are kind of not there for me, but it plays
like a Scooby -Doo cartoon undoubtedly. It's a masterpiece compared to reboot. It's clearly him saying
fuck you back to the mall rats people too. He did get angry. He was apologizing for mall rats,
and then he made chasing Amy and he was the indie darling again. And then after that, he was like,
why am I apologizing for mall rats? I thought it was funny. And Jay and Silent Bob was clearly him
going back to that. Yeah. You got the Batman gadgets coming out. It's fucking absurd. Well,
in all rats. No, I remember he dedicated to John Hughes and John Landis and all those 80s
comedies. And that's really what it was. I thought it mall rats in terms of pure comedy is probably
his funniest movie. But for some reason, Jay and Silent Bob has never worked for me. And I like the
characters too. It's as I said, it's an absurd. It's first of all, it's a 90 minute gay joke. Yeah.
The reason I think it can still work and not come off as homophobic, in my opinion, is
it's all being perpetuated through the Jay character who clearly is a repressed homosexual.
Right. They made it very obvious many times. Yeah. So I find the film very, very funny,
but is it a good movie? No. You know, you know, you know, just like when I watch, you know,
there are a lot of episodes of Nightcourt where I go, I laugh my balls off. It was absurd.
Bull talk to Martian's halfway through it. You know what I mean?
Needless to say, it got me amped up for Jay and Silent Bob reboot. I was excited to see where they
go, where they were going to go, if they could recapture this. And I was quite frankly ready for them
to do a frame -for -frame remake with new jokes inserted. The movie began, started off rocky. Then Fred
Armiston comes in as an Uber driver. Highlight. Very, it starts to get really, really funny. Yeah.
And then Fred Armiston's character leaves. And it becomes a fucking shit storm. It's terrible.
Armiston into, they meet up with Jason Lee as Bankie or whatever.
Him talking about reboot culture, reboots all that with Jay and Silent Bob is very funny.
And really the only time the dialogue comes to life in a way that Kevin Smith used to do all the time.
Right. Because the whole time I'm like, okay, this is funny. The idea is funny. We're doing a reboot,
a remake of sorts. And in the style of Jay and Silent Bob, we're going to be commenting the whole
time on how this is America now. Everything's being rebooted. All they really do, aside from the
looking into the camera bit, which they do a million times in this movie, like they say something
and everyone looks at the camera again and again and again. But this one two, three minute scene with
Jason Lee, Scientologist Jason Lee, he left. Okay. Yeah. When they're talking about reboot culture
and how it sucks and etc, all rings of so true and is so funny and coming on the heels roughly of
this really funny Armiston car scene, you're like, okay, here we go. It's going somewhere. And just like
you say, it comes alive for roughly five minutes and then goes right back to shit until the climax,
which is where it reaches its absolute worst point. Okay. So the big plot line in this movie,
or plot point in this movie is they want to go stop the reboot obviously. But the reason it's
going to be harder for them to do it now is they accidentally sign these contracts with the studio
putting the movie out that say they're not allowed to use their real names anymore because now
their names are owned by the movie company. So they're not allowed to say to anybody. My name is
where I'm Jay and Silent Bob. They're not allowed to say that anymore. It's a stupid hook.
But it gets to a point where this movie is so the original movie in the original film that they're
trying to stop from being made, that they fail from being made, has become so popular over the last 20
years. There's a character who's an Asian girl. She came all the way from China because it's her dream
to meet the stars of the remake of this movie. It's her favorite movie of all time. Yet every,
this is a popular movie is yet nobody in the movie is going, are you Jay and Silent Bob?
Right. You're awfully a lot like these characters in the movie, you know. Right. Which is unbelievable.
They introduced this plot line with where Jay has a daughter, which in the trailer I thought was
really funny because I was like, oh, that's such a great fuck you to reboot. They always bring in the
daughter. You didn't know you had a daughter. Here she is. And I was like, oh, that's so funny.
But then, and this is when I knew we were in travel, folks, before they played the movie,
they played a five minute video introduction with Kevin Smith and Jason Mews, where Kevin Smith
talked ad nauseam about making this movie and about how y 'all are going to cry when you watch this.
Not cry like, oh, they fucked it up. Cry because this guy, Jason Mews, is so good in the emotional
scenes. You didn't know he was this good of an actor. So that tells you right there, any emotional part in
this movie is being played for real. It's not being played to make fun of genre stereotypes.
So Jason Mews, Jay halfway through the movie, the quarter of the way through the movie meets his daughter
played by Kevin Smith's daughter. Played by Kevin Smith's daughter. And it becomes very apparent,
apparent immediately through scene after schmaltcy fucking scene. I mean, these things would have
made Robin Williams fucking puke. These scenes make bicentennial man look like the thorn birds.
You know what I mean? These things are so fucking schmaltcy.
And it's so apparent immediately, oh, this movie is Kevin Smith's apology for every dick joke he's
ever made in his life. Right. This is him saying, my daughter made me a better man. See?
I'm going to make a movie about it where even the dumbest guy on earth, Jay, somehow learns the value
of love. It's like, God damn it. You don't want to see Jay get grounded. You don't ever want to see it.
You don't want this literally feels like if you were watching a three stooge is short,
and Mo turned to Larry and Curly and goes, guys, I really care about you. I'm sorry. I beat up on
you all the time. Yeah. Nobody wants to see that. You want to see the guy be a dumbass, especially now
that muse has had facial reconstructive surgery or whatever he's had done. He doesn't even look the same.
So everything has this like bizarre quality to it. So now it scares me for, I mean, there's this scene with
Affleck and Joey Lauren Adams playing the characters from chasing Amy. We're Joey Lauren Adams
is talking about how she's running a Netflix TV show about their story and it's called chasing Amy
and she lead Ben Affleck goes, I guess it would be better to hear it through a lesbians perspective,
huh? And Joey Lauren Adams leans into him and literally says, anybody's, it besides a straight white
cis male. And I'm like, what are you doing, dude? What are you doing? Like stop. Like this is terrible,
dude. This is fucking terrible. And there are ways to make up for if you if you really want to make
up for some missteps, there are ways to do it without just saying it to the audience. Baldly stating,
like, I mean, it was everything was so on the nose. It was disgusting. He's literally taking like
criticisms out of reviews and just putting them in his dialogue. Yeah. And this whole movie just
becomes about Jay trying to bond with his daughter. It's not a reboot. It's not in any way a remake.
They lose complete sight of trying to stop the movie from being made. At no point do they get to
any point of anything of stopping the movie from being remade. And then it ends with this climactic
scene where the Chinese girl who is obsessed with them. Well, we haven't mentioned the group of
girls. There's the Indian girl. Well, she's one of them. Yeah. Sorry. With her story. I mean,
let me mention that. Oh, oh, yeah. Okay. So so Kevin Smith's daughter who plays Jay's daughter in
the movie. She has a support group. She meets up with girls from a support group of men who of
women who never knew their father. And they're playing this fucking thing like this is a fucking
breast cancer support group or some shit. Look, I'm sure she's in a stoner comedy. Yeah. I'm
pro. And by the way, I'm not saying it's not traumatic to not know a parent. But there you want to talk
fucking white privilege. You know, this is a girl. They introduced her. She's living in a fucking
million dollar house in Jersey. Right. And she's talking about how she never knew her dad. And she's
she's acting like she's she's got to have a leg amputated or something. And it's just not viable.
It's just not heavy enough of a device at all to have her be this fucking emotional about it.
Especially when they play her character as being fucking tough as nails the entire time. And they
don't play it as she's tough as nails because she's making up for something or overcompensating.
They just play it like she's a tough kid. So she's got a support group made up by the Chinese girl
who's obsessed with the Jane Soundbomb movie. Another girl who's oh, a deaf black girl who
is only deaf so they can make literally one joke about it at the very end of the movie that
it never plays any other part. I'm not exaggerating. And then another girl who's Arab,
whose name is Jihad, which I guess is Kevin Smith's way of being like, I didn't get two PC guys.
And it's just a dumb joke. And she tells a story about a guy grabbing her breast in in at her high
school and then proceeds to talk about how her brother tried to suffocate her and her sleep with
a pillow for bringing shame to her family. You're like, guys, what the fuck is this right now?
In a movie that like starts and ends with fart jokes, they have mues with his dick tuck between his
legs doing the silence of the lambs thing from a movie that at this point is 30 years old.
And thinking that we also are now going to go on this journey with him, the tonal switches
would give you whiplash in this fucking thing. Yeah, it's they don't make sense, they don't work.
I'm shocked at how few reviews are mentioning these things. Most of the reviews I'm reading are just
saying like, hey man, if you like Kevin Smith, you'll like it. It's a stoner comedy I guess for the
ages. It's not great. It's like, why is nobody talking about how bad these, this is Tyler Perry level
bad of like one, one moment they're making a fart joke and the next moment somebody's getting
diagnosed with like aids or something like what is happening right now? And the criticism is so
fucking lazy of like, if you like Kevin Smith, shit, you like the it's not true. No, like it's not
acknowledging that this is a man who has completely lost his gifts. There is not aside from one
Matt Damon monologue that's funny and the Jason Lee scene and maybe the armistice and shit.
There is no sign that this guy was somebody who once wrote great dialogue or once knew his way
around a comedic set piece or anything. It is a mess. And to me, the most embarrassing character was
Kevin Smith as Silent Bob. He talks not he talks as much as Kevin Smith does in this fucking movie.
Oh yeah, because he also plays Kevin Smith in the movie too. He plays both parts. They they've got him
making like making these mugging fake. At some point his Silent Bob started being this like
always doing like a little cartoon face for the camera. I always hated that. And now that he's
leaning into it so much, I almost had to look away from the screen. But if you remember at the end
of Jan Silent Bob, strike back, it's Mark Hamill. They're doing a scene from the movie and Mark
Hamill means a lot to them in that universe. And this one, it's Melissa Benoist from Supergirl. They
have to put her name in the screen because they know nobody will know who she is. Kevin Smith
directed a few episodes of Supergirls so he can call on that favor. Melissa Benoist is in it and then
Val Kilmer playing Silent Bob because I believe that Val Kilmer has lost the ability to speak because
he had cancer in his salivary glands. Yeah, and Kevin Smith said that. He was like, I asked him to be in
and he goes, I can't talk because of my tongue. Yeah, he goes, great. I got to bet you can play me.
You're it is you can play me in the movie version of me in the movie. I'm making it starts to get
so up its own ass. So sad. And they miss. There are missed. Here's a thing. And this is why I think
the guys walk it through life. High 24 hours a day. Yeah, he has this heart attack. I'm glad he's
okay. He seems to have gotten into good shape. He seems to be hiking and eating right. He's not fat
anymore good for him. But he's replaced all of it with a 24 hour weed regimen. Right. And
he's missing things because he's burnt the fuck out. So it's like, dude, you know what would have been
funny in the movie where you have to play Silent Bob and then you as a character Kevin Smith is
also in the movie have somebody else play Kevin Smith. That would be really funny. Right. Nobody would
be expecting it. Right. And he's just missing these fucking and then this also bugged me for some
reason. And I think it speaks to what we're talking about with his work and weed ethic.
When Kevin's, when the real Kevin Smith shows up in the movie, he's directing a scene for the
Jay and Silent Bob reboot. And he's like, all right, man, he says the crowd of extras. He's like,
all right, man, I'll be right back. And we're going to make some movie magic, man. And then he walks
backstage and he's like, oh, alone, finally, and pulls out a joint. And it's like, hey, bro,
are you directing shit high all the time? Is that what you're doing? Because it's not fucking work
and dude. Right. We know you like weed. He does like, it's like this gross scene of like, you
know when somebody really loves weed and they got to be like, all right, man, hear it? It's for 20,
whatever. He's doing that in a feature film. And it's like, we know you like weed, Kevin.
And you know you're cool, man. Let me say this publicly. I said it on Twitter the other day.
I've said it on stage. I'm going to say it here. Weed culture is so fucking dumb and boring and
safe and stupid. It is so fucking dumb. Everybody that's like, yeah, man, but so and so was a weed artist.
They had talent too. If you take the weed away from Cypress Hill, there's still an awesome rap group.
If you take the whiskey away from Ron White, he's still a hilarious comment. Comic, the substance alone
is not a personality. Fucking stop it. It's so stupid. I found it insulting to both Kevin Smith
fans and stoners to be like, you like Kevin Smith or if you're high, you'll probably like this movie.
I was both quite high and once a fan of Kevin Smith. And I am intelligent enough to realize that this
movie sucked dick. And I think stoner, I've had some of the most fascinating conversations of my life
with people who were high like people know shit when it's shit. And even though the audience was
laughing, you know, Smith's got his fans and supporters. If you pull them aside and say, come on, man,
you know, he's he's not even coasting. I mean, this was bad. It was embarrassing. I hate to say it,
but it's also not surprising to me. The man's been on a downward spiral forever with a slight peek
for clerks too. For me, Joe's like a couple more of his things, but he just, he's gotten too many tries.
I gotta tell you this, if I was high and watch this as a Kevin Smith man, I would have gotten paranoid
and confused by the whole thing. Yeah, it would have settling. It would have thrown me off.
There's got to be the substance has to be there before the fucking alter ego altering or
reality altering substance comes in to play. It can't just be the substance by itself. You know,
it can't just be the drug. It's it just doesn't fucking work. And then also to
for a guy that is going to call back every fucking thing ever that he's ever put in a movie
and expect you to remember every reference and whatever. How about this, dude? How about a stitch
of continuity? Clerks too was all about with Jane Silent Bob was all about how they had to get sober.
Yeah. That took place after Jane Silent Bob strike back. So maybe you put a thing in this movie
where they go off the fucking, bro, we got to go back to Hollywood. Well, I can't do it sober.
All right, we're going back on the weed. These are such simple fucking things to do.
I do a montage of them getting high for the first time, like an evil dead style thing. Would have been fun.
You know, oh my god. What it felt like, and this was a few years back when Smith was like,
we're going to do mall rats too. Then we're going to do clerks three. Then we're going to do that.
I think that he goes in our room for two hours. The room is so smoky that him and his
collaborators can't see each other. They come out two hours later with a completed script.
That's what it really does feel like. And what I've always done with my scripts is write them
completely sober. Do a joke pass stoned, which is always really fun. But I do it stone. And then the
next morning I read it again sober and go, wow, this is really funny. I'm glad I let my mind access
this other part, whatever. And then some of you are like, pet, that's fucking stupid. And you fix it.
I don't think he's doing that fix pass. I don't think he's doing a pass where he makes sure that
it makes sense because this was just a collection of scenes. And I was again let down by strike back.
But reboot is just a goddamn mess. Now he has confirmed clerks three. He and Jeff Anderson,
Squash, whatever beef they had. So Randall will be back. They are going to do it. I am going to
see it. I will be excited about it. But I'll tell you this much. If this fucking movie is suddenly
Jay and Silent Bob and the daughter hanging out in front of the fucking quickstop. I bet it will be
and and and it's going to turn into some fucking schmaltzer thine about, you know,
what Jersey means to us or whatever the fuck it's going to be. I'm out, dude.
Yeah. Well, clerks too, which is, you know, 15 years old at this point,
it did get a little schmaltz at the very end. They played that that solo silent song frustrated
and cooperated. But it was like it meant something. It was these guys and they never really they never
leaned into the schmaltz aspect. They were just like, we got to grow up. We got to do some with
their life. It felt like what Kevin Smith was going through at that time. It felt like real to how
that his fans are in their lives. And this just felt like, hey, let's take a sitcom plot from 1986.
And also to a turn into sincerity works nicely when it's a character like Randall, who's always a
loudmouth in an asshole. Right. Finally saying like, you don't fucking get why I'm this way because
I love the fucking quick. You don't you get it? This is you're like my partner, dude. I love you.
That was beautifully acted by a guy who's like barely an actor. Yeah. That works when you do it
once in a while. Right. This whole thing from from the 25 minute mark that's fucking happening. Also too,
there's this whole thing where they go out of their way to, okay, so at the end of Jay and Silent
Bob, after Elizabeth, Shannon Elizabeth tells Jay she loves him. And all they've had a chance to do
is make out. They make that very clear in the movie. She goes, she's immediately taken away from the
FBI for the diamond heist thing. They make it clear in this movie that he has not seen her since she's
been in prison. Right. Because the first thing she says is, why did you never visit me? And he says
because we couldn't fuck. Then she says, here's your daughter. Yeah. So when did this pregnancy take play?
I mean, this is just very valid question. It's just it's just it's just sucked. You throw in a
conjugal visit joke and you understand it for the love of God. Yeah. Jay, you don't remember you came
and we had sex a bunch of times. Oh shit. I was fucked up. Sorry. Right. Anything. Anyway, there's no
quality control anymore. And it's kind of sad. Now that all being said, I appreciate that Kevin Smith
is a guy operating with complete autonomy at this point. I appreciate that he's a guy finding a
new way to release movies that shaking shit up in the industry. I think that's awesome. I just
hope that he starts doing it with delivering a better product because it doesn't mean anything
if all you're delivering is like a stoned podcast on tape. Yeah. I don't care. He's by all accounts
a nice guy, but there is something about this that smacks of I have my fans who will turn out for
everything I do and at least get me to a point where I'm breaking even financially. So I will keep
doing the absolute bare minimum because I know they'll come. And at some point, he's got to say
I'd like to surprise them and give them something better than they're expecting, which is at this
point the bare minimum. I think it's it's not a great attitude to have. Yeah. Two hugs down
for this movie for this movie that spoiler alert. This is the ending spoiler alert ends with Jay
telling his daughter a story in front of the quick stop as that fades to black and the song
daughter by Pearl Jam plays don't call me daughter, which is a scene I would have written when I was 19
years old and thought that it was touching. And anybody who has any experience ever in anything
writing wise in TV or film knows it's two on the nose, dude. Come on. And this guy and that 100 grand
for daughter put a little money on the screen. So it doesn't look like somebody dropped oil on the
on the lens. Two hugs way down. Joderosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter Joderosa comedian on Facebook
wouldn't be funny if we got beat up by Jay and Silent Bob like they go after the critics in the movie.
I think seeing them in this one we could have we could take them. And I've got tours coming up
January look for dates on Joderosa info .com. I'll be in Pittsburgh. I will be in
Lancaster PA amongst other places that I can't remember off the top of my head. I'll be
announcing another short tour through the Chicago area soon in February. One of the shows will be a
taping. And then Skankfest in March in Houston. The Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram
check out our Patreon page where I am doing a new solo Pat's movie corner segment at least once a
month. Thank you to all of you for coming along with us on the Patreon. And that's it. Also go to
the the hog house on Etsy if you want merch. Thank you to Emily Florence for handling our online
shenanigans and activities. We're on see you in hell pod on Instagram and we'll see you in hell
page on Facebook. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.