Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
Hey folks, welcome to we'll see you on how your favorite horror movie sci -fi and fantasy film podcasts.
My name is Joe DeRose. I'm sitting here with the illustrious Patrick Wall.
Oh, thank you. You're welcome.
Illustrious, I guess, is like what a man about town.
I don't know what it means. I always thought it was a term for a nicely decorated apartment,
but then I heard it used for a human being.
Yeah, usually it's like an illustrious evening. Maybe I'll look it up.
Like we're gonna do it like a word of the day calendar now the podcast is just gonna be teaching you new words and
Folks, we apologize in advance if there's any sound
quality issues
We got a new recording device
and we're
Kind of just figuring it out and I think I think I did it right
But you know if it gets a little
Distorted at times or whatever. It's only because we're just still working through these level issues
reported about 40 minutes the other day lost to the world. Yeah, just gone. Boy, it was good too.
You'll never know. Sorry. Yeah. Illustrious, uh, you were right to call me illustrious. It means
well -known, respected, and admired for past achievements. Oh, okay. Like an illustrious career would be
the right way to use it. Okay. So it doesn't mean a nice apartment. No, it doesn't. Now, I'll be hog tied.
Now, Joe, I feel like I need to remind people from time to time that that's you right performing
and wrote our theme song, but I've been seeing questions lately.
It says, I'll see you in hell, but our podcast is We'll See You In Hell.
Was this recorded before I was added to the mix?
Take us behind the scene, behind the music.
No, it was recorded after you were added to the mix, but originally it was the show was just going to be me, and it was going to be called I'll see you in hell.
Okay.
And a friend of mine pointed out that only a raving lunatic would be able to talk for 90 minutes during a film by himself.
You'd be like an Alex Jones.
Yeah, yeah.
That's too much.
So then I asked my dear friend Pat, movie lover, illustrious man about time.
Yeah, to be a part of it. He said yes, but I still thought the theme song so we changed the title the pod to we'll see you now
But the lyrically I still thought the song worked better. Yes. I'll see you in hell and it was also a little wink
I like to give little winks to like my favorite bands and like bands. I love will do that
You know the title of the song one word will be different in the chorus from the actual title sure
I like those a little give me one example
I can't right now, but it's one of those things how like Queen has an album called Sheer Heart
Attack, which is my favorite Queen album, but then the song Sheer Heart Attack is on Queen
2 or whatever.
I bought the Queen catalog recently on vinyl and I noticed that it's very odd that you bring
that up.
The entire catalog?
I, but you know, I bought for their four kind of
Yeah, you can go. Yeah, there's there's I think I think you could go a little deeper. There's probably about six goodies. Yeah
But I thought you were saying you bought a box at and I was like man after
After the game you're getting into dicey waters
Bohemian Rhapsody never those words never appear in the song
They no, they don't they don't that's another example
It's an odd title for that song, what about it is Bohemian?
I think they probably were inspired by some sort of opera thing, and I'm sure we can
easily find that out.
I like how very often on the show we pose questions, don't answer them and move on.
I got to be honest Pat, I asked the question and I don't give a rat's ass what the answer
is.
Yeah.
Dead inside.
All the way to the middle.
hashtag same. I've added two new video game consoles. Okay. To the collection since we last spoke
which we're just going straight into Joe's scary stuff. No, no, I'm just telling you where I'm
at mentally in life. Okay. That if you thought this wasn't enough. Yeah. Two have been added since
the last time. Okay. Not since the, not since the botched recording. Right. But since the last time
we actually recorded, which was well over, it was like a month, two months ago at this point. Yeah,
You guys have been listening to a backlog collection
because Joe went out of town for a while.
So now we're up to day to gain.
We're recording this the day before you hear it.
So you're getting us right now
at our absolute lowest as Joe and I just discussed
over breakfast.
But it is a pleasure to be coming to you live
from the hog house.
It is.
You were supposed to do that.
Oh.
I was too busy thinking about what I will say
for today's on with the show and also on with a Joe who with a flow don't say
it doesn't matter with a Joe I can't believe that one took that long well we're
just talking about Queens of Stone Age but on with the show it's a great one with
the Joe that one was an interesting one that's a good one folks all I've been
What I'm listening to is those, the second and third Queens of Stone Age album, rated
R and songs for the death.
I think both are in my top ten albums of all time.
I can understand that.
I really do.
They're not in mine, but they're great albums.
And I was just telling Joe, make it with you by Queens of the Stone Age, maybe my wedding
song.
I love that.
It's a beautiful song.
Great song.
I love that.
Sexy mama.
What were you gonna say?
I cut you off because I didn't want to forget all with the, all with the Joe.
My buddy was like, you stopped doing all with the Joe.
I was like, no, I didn't.
But maybe I missed a few weeks.
I don't want one here and there.
Everybody needs to calm down.
And I'll be honest with you, Pat, any friend that's going to tell you something like
that isn't a friend at all.
That's true.
Well, I mean, you realize each day you have less and less friends than you think.
I don't even like myself anymore.
No, who does the, uh,
I was going to say, I was just going to talk about how whenever Pat sings the Joe song,
he covers his face while he's singing it, it's a deep shame.
Yeah, it seems to be just sheer embarrassment, it just covers his face, but I had something
else to say at the time and I can't remember what it was now.
And you're sitting, you know, five feet away from another man singing often a love song
with his name in it, there's a great deal of shame that goes along with it, an embarrassment.
Sure. Even in this, even in 2018. Yeah. Even in 2018. Yeah. I've got to be me.
Yeah, I've always been that way. You don't want to, I don't like people looking at me, you know?
I'm a very hard time being funny with my parents. My parents do not know or think I'm funny. Definitely. I have a hard time making jokes with them
Yeah, I mean then they make jokes with me all the time. Yeah
My whole thing now with my dad is he'll text
Something I write back a response and he goes I was joking
I guess I'm not funny anymore in my old age. This is every single time
So he's like what kind of food are you gonna have at the wedding? I tell him and he's like well, I hope you have some hamburgers
And I go, no, it's not like exotic food, you'll be fine.
And he's like, I was just kidding.
Every conversation is like painful, intense.
And then there's like weird random emoji use
because he doesn't know what they mean
and it'll be like a crying smiley face.
And I'm like, are you laughing till you cry?
Right.
It's just a mess.
I dare won't eat anything but pure American food.
He's never had sushi.
He's never had Chinese food.
He's never had anything.
He's never a Chinese food he came out here, which I would be almost consider American food at this point
Yeah, of course he like even a panda express I
Was gonna take him when he came out of here a few years back to a Thai restaurant and he was like I don't eat things that float
So he doesn't eat fish. I was like what what do you think Thai food is? I think he thinks it's all like a stew
That I mean I don't know what he thinks so would he not eat a beef stew a hearty beef stew
He'd eat a beef stew, but I think he'd much like people who have never had sushi think like you're eating like a fish
Eye right if you're old and dumb
But Thai food to him was like something floating in a in a vat and I was like I'm not even gonna try to correct you on this
Jesus God
That's that's in that's intense. I don't get so fucking close minded and I really hope I don't go that route
But it's just like, well, you did be fair, Pat, when we were in the diner this morning during breakfast, you were complaining that they were letting Asians in.
Not true, not true. Of course that's not true.
Yeah, it's, you know, like, I asked my dad, I go, oh, you said, I'm watching the Grammys tonight. And I was like, oh, you enjoyed it and he's like, I had to turn it off because of the wrap.
up, which is, you know, there's some race qualities there too, but it's just like everything
that you did not grow up with is suddenly terrifying and awful, and you can't understand,
and don't even make an effort to understand it.
That just seems to be everyone over a certain age, and the reason our country is where it
is, frankly.
Yeah, we're, we've been asking for this for a long time, and we're here today.
I had been off Twitter for like a week, which is why my mood had improved, and you get
on there. And the first thing I see this morning is Trump at a rally last night. We'll get
immediately off politics. But there's three gorgeous, like white teenage girls right behind
Trump at this rally going, build that wall, build that wall.
And Trump turns around and checks them out very clearly and then he turns around and does that little eyebrow raised thing
Like yeah, you like that. Yeah, to the audience and he's like, yeah, looks like these girls like clear plants
Because what three like beautiful young girls are at a Trump rally and then also in the corner because Trump always plants a minority
There's an an Asian guy
Screaming along with them build that wall build that wall and I shut Twitter
Again, like I always compare it to that book of the dead. Right. Just like I I shut it
Deleted from my phone and like threw my phone across the room. It's like holy cow
I don't know what's going on. You can't go in. You can't go in. I'm done. You can't go in. Yeah, Twitter to me is it's you know
It's it's it's
It's it's like looking into the eyes of the crystal skull like you're gonna go nuts
Yeah, you got out you got to walk away
You got to walk away which is a Indiana Jones in the kingdom of the crystal skull reference a film. I did watch
Yesterday immediately after I watched the last crusade again now. I have only seen it once in the theater. Should I revisit it?
If you revisit it you will be like this is fine. There's I'm not furious about it
There are a couple cringe -worthy things with shy LaBuff one of them is him swinging on vines with monkeys
Terrible. I remember that. I remember a lot of Prairie Dog reaction shots. Yeah, and those
aren't as bad as you remember. You know, for the most part, you're like, let's put it
this way. When they make the new one, and it's awesome, because they're clearly making
it to be like, we need to write some of the wrongs of the last one. And you look back on
this franchise in 10 or 15 or 20 years, whatever. Kingdom of the Christmas goal is just going
to be the kind of weird one that some people think is really fun.
It's not going to be a stain on the fucking franchise or anything like that, but I enjoyed
it.
I enjoyed a last crusade more obviously I feel like you're sort of forcing me into
Pat's movie corner so let's just open the door I'm not trying to I'm just I'm just kind
of thinking about Indiana Jones and my take on these films it was always my favorite I was
was always for best of worst. I was like, Raiders was the best skull was the worst. Now
I'm starting to think I'm going to put crusade over Temple of Doom maybe, but I don't
know about that. I mean, I go temple Raiders crusade skull. I love there was a time where
Doom was my favorite. I just I think it's just perfect. And knowing the backstory that Steven
Spielberg and George Lucas were both going through bitter divorces when they made it and
And they didn't realize till it came out how rough and terrifying it was, the one thing
that is questionable about it in this day and age is that probably also due to these
very wealthy guys going through the divorce, the love interest is a gold digging screaming
shrew.
But she's the good, she's good in the end, it's not she is, but she's a long way from Karen
Allen.
Well, but at least she's better than the Nazi in the third one, spoiler alert.
I was going to say like the the the one I would have pegged divorces on is the third one where the woman
Seduce is him and then turns into a nonsense
Yeah, and then dies at the end. It's the only one where the love interest dies at the end. Right. Yeah
Well, yeah, let's go to Pat's movie corner. I saw
game night and
I got to say it's a very funny movie
And I think it's a really shows you how bad things have gotten in terms of movie comedy
that A, this thing is being treated like it's an all -time comedy classic, it's not that.
But B, everyone's like, holy shit, there's a movie that's supposed to be funny, that was
funny.
That's usually the reaction I'm reading.
And I get that. It is a very funny movie. The cast is really great. It's all people. You'll either know or recognize
Macatams is funny in it. Bateman's funny in it. Jesse Plemman steals the show.
Well, all three of them. Creepy cop next door.
It's just very good. It's it's I would say a comedy remake of the game, which is clearly how it was pitched where you don't know what's real and what's not.
Okay, that's cool. David Fincher is the game, which is a fantastic movie. And it's very well shot
There's a tracking shot in it that I think can hold its own amongst the all -time greats
You're good fellow as your touch of evil. Jesus. And it's a fan like you never see a comedy with like that level of
filmmaking skill
It's the guys who wrote and directed vacation who are clearly like let's step our game up and try to get some directing work too
I like those guys
very funny movie with like a lot of your big traditional Hollywood laughs but
then a lot of like weirder shitting as well which I appreciate it all right good
movie I saw one you're never gonna believe go on never seen it flash dance okay
flash dance what a feeling for those of you unfamiliar flash dances the story of
a welder who does burlesque dancing at night because she has dreams of being a ballerina.
Also, she thinks ballerina dancing is just running really fast in one place.
So there's some complications.
There's some hurdles she's going to have to get over.
But I went into the movie ironically, I was staying with my dear friend, Big J. Oakerson in
New York.
he said you've never seen this you got to watch it because it just was on cable. And you know by
the end of it, I was I had chills. I was tearing up when she when she gives her big performance
in front of the board. And she does it her way. And the board includes Sam Kenneson. It is very
similar to the back to school. Yeah, we're talking about my mactic scene. All those movies in the 80s
It's ended with going in front of the board.
Yeah, and there's no board anywhere.
I've never come across a board.
No, old school brought that back.
They're in front of the fraternity board,
having to do a bunch of physical challenges.
It's amazing.
It is extremely funny.
I know a lot of people who are like,
it kind of falls apart at the end.
That's what it doesn't.
You idiot, it's a comedy.
And old school grabs the joke too
that now nobody can do ever again.
and it's a lazy way out, but it works so well.
They did it right.
But when they go, what's the funniest version
of the intellectual debate,
we got to put the Will Ferrell character up against
an actual smart guy, and they're like,
well, how do you get him out of this?
And it's like, he spews out this very insightful tirade
and then collapses off the ground.
Like what a lazy way to get out of a problem
but it works perfectly and everything about the climax of old school is lazy but to me that
adds to all the funniness of it because I think they they are winking to the 80s. I love it
and it's just great. And don't forget the the the best line of the movie. I see blue. He looks
glorious. I when I saw the movie I was I was excited but you know like I will see what this is
And in the opening scene, the cab driver, Luke Wilson's in the back and he's like, hey,
you know, there's no seat belt back here.
And the cab driver looks in the rear of your mirror and he goes, you're in the back seat
quit being such a F is like the first actual line of the movie.
And the theater was like what like, it's even that that word was well out.
but my lord, I love that movie.
But, I mean, you know, you're not laughing at gay people.
You're laughing at the man that's how he breaks down the world.
Yeah.
Like, this guy is ridiculous.
Dana Gold's got a really funny joke
where he's like, we talked about being at his dad's house
in like November and he's like,
see, dad, this is where I live in LA.
No, middle of November, it's 75 degrees out there.
And as that goes bunch of queers, all right, and his wife goes you can't and he goes so my wife then says me
You can't let him say that you have to and he goes what do you want me to say there is no argument to be
Yeah, the man thinks gay people a mint heat
Yeah, so my point is is the laugh is in the ignorance not in the that's true
But anyway
Wait, is it your turn? No, I had oh yes because you had flash dance
I saw what we could do that one on the show, so I'll leave it.
I watched Christine, not the horror movie, but the film with Rebecca Hall from last year.
It's streaming on Netflix.
I thought just a fantastic movie, particularly in terms of its acting, and it's about a woman
who is very depressed, played by Rebecca Hall, how she didn't get nominated for anything
is a travesty, but she's trying to stay positive as we all are in a horrible, horrible world
is in the 70s.
And she wants to do, she's a news reporter.
She wants to do human interest stories, right?
You know, like she sees a young couple in love and she's like, I want to do a story about
love, whatever.
And they keep telling her, no, if it bleeds, it leads.
The violent news stories are what we say on this podcast.
That's right.
Yeah.
The only one do violent news stories and they keep forcing her to do it to kind of keep her job
and eventually she goes further and further insane and deeper into depression and if you know the
true story it obviously has a horrific ending and they show you that ending but I I mean I'm hesitant
to call it a spoiler alert it's a very depressing true story but I highly recommend it and I thought
it was extremely timely in terms of the news now and how bad it has gotten the other one I watched
this week that was on the same theme. Was I went to a screening of broadcast news at
the writers guild followed by a discussion between James L. Brooks, the writer director
and Cameron Crowe, my old boss from Rodeys. Cameron Crowe was in the he easy. You'll remember
I portrayed Ben Frywater on Rodeys. Who could forget that? Just received a $3 .40 check
for it yesterday. Now you were nominated for that if I'm not mistaken. I remember the
campaign on Instagram. I was up for the three -liney award. So me and everybody else with
three lines or less didn't win but we'll get them next time. I didn't campaign hard enough
probably. Anywho broadcast news if you haven't seen it is it's a top 25 movie for me.
It is maybe the best romantic comedy ever made. It was one of the best written movies of all time break out performance by Joan Kusek
That's John Kusek when she runs into the water fountain is fucking some amazing physical comedy Albert Brooks destroys
It's a it's about a relates type of relationship you never see in these movies
It's all very like painful very real and that movie Holly Hunters line in the sand
with William Hurt
who's like the douchebag handsome reporter
that she's falling for is he inserts a shot of himself crying
into an interview with a rape victim.
He conjures up the tears for him when she learns
that he doctored his story this way, she's done with him.
He's getting ready to go to Hawaii with him
and start a life with him and she breaks it off because of this.
And to see somebody take that kind of a moral stand
And in a movie or in the world of news or anything else,
you know, it is 30 years old, but it felt like it was,
you were watching like a Catherine Hepburn movie or something.
Yeah, it is fascinating.
Powerful, beautiful movie in many ways.
It is fascinating.
You know, yeah, I agree.
I'm not, obviously not a Trump fan,
but I also don't think fake news is a falsity.
No, it's not.
I mean, it's a falsity when you're using it just to say,
Right. Hey, these four million things I did, I didn't do. It's almost like he's the,
it's almost like he's like Joe peshy and good fellows or something. You know, dude,
if you want me to like you, maybe don't kill spider. You know what I mean? Like, like,
clean it up a little bit. Right. And maybe I could meet you halfway on a pointer to hear it.
Sure. Sure. But you know, whatever. This ain't a political show, folks. We'll save the real
horror for the news anchors. Anyway, this is the last one I'll give you, Walsh. Dove
into Netflix's Riverdale. Oh, wow. I mean, so your week was Flashdance and Riverdale.
My week was a lot more than that. But we can't get into it on here. But yeah, no, yeah, Flashdance
I haven't seen Riverdale, maybe it's great.
This is the dark archie, right?
Yeah, the darchie, if you will.
I will, darchie -ling limited.
Yeah, it's based on the archie comics,
and it's a really dark take on it.
Now, I don't know if, I know that there were versions
of the archie comics that got, like,
they were for more, when kids got older,
they could read them, and it was a little more about
the trials and tribulations of a teenager or whatever.
Versus like jug head ate all the hamburgers again, right? So I know I've seen
porn videos where it's like Archie is
Taking Mr. Willoughby up the ass or you know stuff like you know they do family guy
Yes, I never wonder if you are jacking off to like stewie fucking lowest or whatever
Check yourself into a mental hospital. Who did I just see doing a bit about that talking about when the
Yeah, seeing the family guy, oh my friend Brendan Burns on the porn site, the side video
of, it's always available.
Stewie fucking the mom or whatever.
Homer and Marge.
Yeah, and his punchline is, what did I Google?
Yeah.
You have a funny punchline.
Anyway, so I have...
Speaking of what did I Google real quick, and I'm surprised you didn't notice, but I've
been working with a personal trainer to prepare for my wedding.
I did notice and I didn't, I thought weird saying to you,
you look good.
Please stop.
No, I'm serious.
I noticed in the garage coming in.
We'll think.
But, you know, it's, they drain every muscle to failure.
Like you, they're like, okay, now you're gonna do chest presses
but do it until you are like gonna start crying.
And then you switch immediately into working another muscle
until that one dies.
And then when you end, especially my first couple sessions,
I was like, I don't know if I can walk home.
Your legs are shaking, but it does work.
It's great.
But I went in the other day.
They told me I need to add some protein to my diet.
I had more protein since I'm lifting all the time.
I buy one of these RX bars and it's got like five ingredients.
It'll say three egg whites, two almonds, whatever.
And that's it.
So I buy them.
It's like a couple bucks at the grocery store.
I go home.
I hop on Instagram that night and I've got an ad for an Rx bar
That's disturbing. So what's going on?
Did they get that from my credit card? Did they get that from me eating it?
God only knows buddy. I'm getting real freaked out. God only knows. That's not a coincidence
You know these are these not like anyone even knows what these Rx bars are. You can't do shit anymore, man
No, fuck that's the other day
Yeah, I took a shit.
I get an Instagram picture of a shit.
Well, in any case, go on, sorry.
River down.
Speaking of which, this is now,
I understand there are some older versions
of the Archie Cows, but this thing is,
opens up with a brother and sister,
supposedly joint suicide thing,
that turns into clearly the sister has murdered the brother.
Okay.
And the brother and sister also are clearly fucking.
okay they don't come out and say it but they're clearly fucking you got Archie
bangin after his freshman year bangin a teacher or they're trying to you to
believe that they're they're fucking are you just kind of making that
insinuation they're holding hands and acting in a very odd way okay and given the
darkness and the heaviness of the rest of the show I'd be shocked if they weren't
trying to insinuate that okay it probably the original script probably had
them fucking and the network made them change? It's really, really dark stuff. You got Archie as I
said, fucking his teacher when he's like a freshman. Okay. And by the way, not in a, not in a,
you know, what to do, what to do kind of way in a, you know, Archie, I let my passions overcome me
and we can't do that again.
You know, they're not perpetuating
any or promoting a lesson of like,
you know, the Dolce and Fuck Kids.
It's more just like,
well, this kid's in a pickle of a situation.
And the only reason he's in a pickle of a situation
is because she's the music teacher
and he wants to learn music from her.
So he's going to her saying,
like, can you just teach me and she's like,
I can't, because she's clearly saying
she can't control herself.
Right.
Now here's what's crazy, Archie Comics. They're making adaptations of comic book movies
all the time. Why the fuck? Why the fuck are grown adults complaining that like new Batman
movies are too dark and why are, why is every comic book movie now a slapstick hair brain
comedy and then I'm watching the Archie adaptation and it's dealing with the
weighty issues. Why is that the world we're living in right now? Nothing makes
sense. Well, I don't understand. Hey, I thought Riverdale was a smash hit because
you can't pass a magazine stand without every cover. I believe it is. No, no, it's a
I just saw the ratings of it the other day. I mean, it's it's getting like a
point three or something. It's barely on the air. But it's on Netflix. What do you mean?
I guess Netflix maybe helps it or something, but no, I mean, it's only on Netflix, I believe.
No, no, no. It's a CW show.
It's a CW show. You're watching a CW show, yeah.
My wonder is no one, the show is like a Dawson's Creek, right? It's for your 18 and underset.
It's a Dawson's Creek, but like if Kubrick did it, you know, it's like, I
Why is wine shut in Dawson's Creek?
But I guarantee they paid a bunch of money
for the Archie brand.
What kid under 30 knows Archie?
I only know Archie because my uncle gave me a stack
of comics from when he was a kid.
That could have some pornography.
Well, now they're also doing like the dark rendition
of Sabrina the Teenage Witch,
which is a series of comics.
Is it dark?
Yes, okay.
There's a dark, you know who they just cast on it?
Who?
Brought some pincha. No, they didn't. They did. As who? I don't know. But it can't be that dark
if Balky's in the mix. Well, he does dark stuff. Sometimes he was in true romance. He was the
convict relief of true. No, it's. Look, I'm not saying Riverdale was without joy or humor,
but it's dark. But there's still wear in that crown. No, no, no, crap. There's a string of,
because that's from the same universe, Sabrina and all that shit, same whatever. But there's a line
of Sabrina comics that are very dark and serious, where she's like, it's way more like
Buffy the Vampire Slayer.
The craft.
Yeah.
And there's a line of archie comics that are about the zombie apocalypse.
Really?
Yes.
So.
Okay.
That's very weird.
It's weird, but again, it's just one line.
It's like there's, it's like how they'll be like a Superman storyline, where it's like, well
on this, this one he's on Earth, too.
And, you know, Superman is made out of ice
because of this thing.
You know, you're like, okay, well,
that's one of the storylines.
But the odd thing is, is let's focus on that storyline.
It's like when they made steel with Shaq, right?
And you're like, wait, what?
Yeah.
No, don't make that Superman movie number one.
Number two, don't make it with Shaq, please.
Yeah.
So Charles Barkley hosted SNL the other night.
That's where, that's where he did it
Back in the Nirvana days, which I understood, I remember seeing Charles Barkley and Nirvana in the same show
But what what were they doing? I mean what what's happening? I don't know Pat
Yes, me. It's a bunch of scary stuff out there
Wow, that was a desperate transition, but all right
Let's take it to Joe's scary stuff. I got I thought you would have appreciated this exact one
Sorry, I got a phenomenal book used yesterday. This book is out of print
If you can find a copy, I strongly suggest you buy it.
It's called Shock Horror, and the way that is stylized in the book is Shock,
exclamation point, horror, exclamation point, the astounding artwork from the
video nasty era. It is a really really great text. It's basically a reference book.
It's a hard -cover reference book that's beautifully done, and it is wall -to -wall
VHS cover art from what was called the video nasty era in England which was
early 80s VHS market which was quite saturated because there were very few
laws regulating any of it and because of the saturation the horror films in
particular would create outlandish covers to get your attention because they
they had to get your eye on the shelf.
I remember being traumatized every time I went
to my local schnux grocery store to rent movies
by the horror section.
It was rough.
And a lot of these were eventually banned and whatever,
but it's just a great book.
It's a really, really fun thing just to flip through.
And then also discover movies maybe you never heard of.
Now again, it's out of print.
I got it for luckily $35
dollars at the use book store in my neighborhood. I didn't even know it existed. I was walking by,
was in the window, and I went in like, what is that? I've been on that place. And then immediately
was like, I got to buy this. But I looked online to do some price comparisons to make sure I was
paying a fair price. And I didn't see it cheaper than 55 bucks online used. But if you've got the
cash, and this is your kind of thing, and you don't care about spending 55 bucks, I strongly suggest
you get it. I really, really like the book. It's very, very fun. And there's a great intro,
you know, a two -page introduction that tells you that basically what was going on in this quote,
video nasty era unquote. Forgot to meet the TV again. That is a head gum podcast. We like to remind
fine people because headgum has been so very supportive of us anyway that's Joe scary
stuff go get that book if you can or maybe your local library has it and you can just take
a copy out.
I think the reason it's so expensive and hard to find is because it was I think it was only
printed in England mainly and a couple copies made their way over here but it's copyright
right is 2005. So it's kind of old at this point, but not terribly.
And as usual, I don't have anything for this. Well, that's fine. I'm sorry.
That's fine. Let's get to the movie at Anjo, which we didn't even mention what we're
doing today, but die hard. No, I wish.
I heard with a vengeance. No, I wish.
That was when Bruce Willis remembered that he was in a movie when it went acting.
We're going to differ on this one but let's get into it. I don't know they're going to differ all that much but Joe and I last week
Together went to the theater. So a little picture called death wish
The remake. I'm always reminded of the Simpsons bit
Where they're watching death wish 12 and it's elderly Charles Bronson and he was I wish it was dead
Great joke
Death wish
was certainly the worst timing for a movie's release.
I've ever seen.
We are being rocked daily by school shootings.
Right.
And this movie, and I know Eli Roth is trying to get out there
and paint it like it's anti -gun.
Right.
This movie is heavily pro -gun, pro -defending yourself,
defending your family.
So now, just first of all, if you don't know what death was,
is. Yeah. You've seen the original job? Of course. Yeah. And apparently the original, nor this one,
capture the commentary of the book, which is, what is the true price to pay for vigilanteism?
Like, is this something that will make you feel better or is this truly even worse? Yeah. They kind
of brush over that in both versions of these of the book, but not particularly. But now you're
clearly supposed to be rooting for Bruce Willis. Yes, I agree. But so it's about a man who's
wife and daughter suffer a home invasion. His wife dies. His daughter is in a coma after a severe
attack. His wife played by Elizabeth Schoo who looks as she did in Adventures of Babysitting 30 years later.
Baby, I hate to see you leave this movie.
You still got it.
And then I'll just hesitantly say
I hope the daughter is 18 because Hachi Machi,
even in the coma, but what they didn't do
and what I appreciated because we saw
like a noon screening of this thing.
And I'm like, please don't tell me
I gotta watch this girl and Elizabeth Schoo get raped.
Because that's what happens in Death Wish,
the original movie.
I don't know about the book.
Yeah, well apparently they're apparently they are raped in the book, but apparently they don't depict the scene in the book
Okay, but in the movie in the original attempt they're getting there
It's very similar to Cape Fear where it's like is this gonna happen and they fight it's actually the exact same thing
I didn't even think about that. Yeah, in Cape Fear
He's about to fuck Julia Lewis the mom's like please take me instead in the winds of throwing
hot water in the, oh wow, the sailant's face, that's the exact same scene escape fear.
Yeah, so in the original Death Wish, none of that happens in the movie. I mean,
and they do show the rape scene and it is disturbing. Yeah, very.
And it's also led by a group of, this group of vigilantes or gang members led by Jeff Goldbloom.
Right, that's a whole other creepiness factor to it. I am going to
uh...
assault you
he's got a real creepy line where after they finish he goes uh...
he goes to his friend come on man got business
and uh... and then they leave but uh...
but you know look the first one plays much more like a taxi driver
like a very
sort of bleak
grimy gritty
hopeless seventies crime thriller kind of thing
you a fan of the rich
Yeah, I am as well. I think the I think the original is is is an impressive piece of cinema
I
Think it's a very interesting commentary of the of the times
Know it suffered a lot of the same backlash that this one's suffering from. Yeah
I
Thought this movie was I thought this was a much more balanced this remake with Bruce was much more balanced commentary than people are giving it credit for
I don't think it was saying,
yay guns, yay guns, yay guns.
I think it was saying we do live in a culture
where the wrong people can get guns very easily,
either legally or illegally.
Uh -huh.
Because that's always been my argument.
You know, look, I'm off for gun control.
I'm not for gun banning.
I mean, I want to keep some of these guns.
I'm for gun banning.
I want to keep some of them.
Because there are because people can get them any it doesn't matter. I don't own one
But I get it don't sell machine guns at the fucking Walmart. That's fine. There was a satirical element to that scene
Where he goes to the gun shop and the hot girls like well giving him a tour as if he's at the weed store or something
Well also, too the gun he gets illegally is a pistol right that's it
There's gonna be spoilers here guys. Sorry
it's death wish. You know what it is. But the gun he uses at the end to legally kill, the only legal
kill he does is in the end because the guy is in his house. All the other ones are on the street. So
all the, again, it's just an interesting commentary. When he kills illegally on the street, he's using
an illegal gun. When he kills legally in his house, he's using a legal semi -automatic rifle.
So I think they threw a lot of that into the story,
not saying, isn't it great that he's got a semi -automatic
rifle and he blew away the bad guy?
I think it was like, hey man, this is the reality.
This is the world we live in, how do you feel about it?
And I thought they did a good job throughout the movie,
having the dual commentary from the different radio shows.
One being Man Cow, who's a Chicago radio guy,
Who I'm not a fan of and who has gotten a lot of shit over the years for his
sexist and and but I would say
Seemingly racist big commentaries or whatever. I don't listen to the guy
So I don't know how spot on I am with that, but I know he's gotten a lot of feedback and that's or flack in that sense
And then and then putting him against sway from swaying the morning on shady shady 45 on serious and
is the other voice saying like, well, I don't know.
It's a white guy killing black people.
I don't know how I feel about this.
And like, and then that all the sway fan, I like sway.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know, man.
Coward all sway was always on MTV back in the day.
I mean, I don't, I don't get that guy as a, he's certainly not funny.
It's just a good radio guy.
I was stunned that he was still working in radio when I saw him in this movie.
Yeah, he's the morning guy in shape.
four. He's like a Charlie Rose type. Oh my God. He's very, I guess I'm used to a funny radio host.
No, he's very like learned it and it's very like he has rappers come in and he's like he talks
to them about like their significance and the history and what they did. One more power. So,
and I love Heather B too, who he was on the real world and used to be in boogie down productions.
And she's in there because she's co -hosts on Sway's show and she's throwing her two cents. I thought
they did a much if you read the average review of this movie it just says this is all dad hero bull
shit this is all you know gun gun violence is great and I just don't think that that's a very fair
assessment of it I think it's a very honest depiction of here's a thing that happens here's a
way conceivably you could react to it. And if you did react in this way, here's what
that would entail. And, you know, the last thing I've ever seen Eli Roth as, who directed
this, is some kind of fucking big wheeling, you know, right wing conservative with, you know,
I think that that's Eli Roth's MO. No, I don't know. So I, you know, I don't know. I'll
tell you this to everybody
you know we're having the diversity discussion in hollywood these days
almost every minute
one of the most diverse movies i've ever seen
and i don't mean because all bruce wills is going around killing guys that are
white now i mean like every
every area in this movie the doctors the cops
the the the the the the the lay people everybody
it was diverse it was it was white people and black people in a span of people
it was it was a very
every very diverse cast.
And I think that's an important thing to point out as Frances McDormand is scolding
everybody to use inclusion clauses or writers in their movie contracts when I've never
seen her act opposite a black person in my life.
That's true.
I watched Fargo last night, there was one black person in it and he gets thrown against the
wall by a Native American guy.
Yeah, and she's up there for three billboards.
I never see for three billboards.
I mean, it's widely called racist, which way you want it to come from.
Yeah, and I mean, it's just, you know, it's just like, give me a fucking break, man.
You know, if we're gonna, if we're gonna have honest criticisms of things, you have to
give credit where credit is due.
You have to.
You can't just say, this movie is trash because there's guns in it.
That's not fair.
Give it, give it, give it.
It's the credit it deserves.
Let's discuss now in reviews in terms of like, you know, representation is the first word
of the review. And people are like, I hated a wrinkle in time. I thought everything about
it was terrible. It's shot bad. The story's bad. The acting's bad. But it's diverse. So
I loved it at the end. And you're like, well, wait a minute. And it is a two way street.
They're not going to give that to a movie like Death Wish. It's very hypocritical and gross.
and I agree. It was a very diverse movie. My issues with the movie, I was entertained
throughout. I don't recall looking at my phone for the time or anything. My biggest issue
was with Bruce Willis, who has completely given up. The first time I noticed this kind of
performance from him was maybe cop out Kevin Smith's movie and Kevin Smith. Hope you're all
right sir? Oh yes Kevin Smith I've never met you but oh no I did meet him one time
and he was very nice. I mean you're a big tusk fan I'm sure he'd love you. Shouts
out to Kevin Smith I think he's recovering nicely from his heart. And you know maybe get
healthy you know you've been wearing giant jean shorts and hockey jersey for 40 years.
Well apparently I think he was like doing the right thing I think this was yeah if you're
After that and do a quick, huge, drastic weight loss, apparently that's the worst thing for
your heart.
But anyway, I remember after cop out came out, Kevin Smith being like, Bruce Willis is
a fucking asshole, like you can't even get him to try.
It's embarrassing.
saying, I'm sorry, not the cop I would have been good otherwise, but Willis at some point
was like, I got my money, but if you don't want to act any more retire in my opinion,
I don't, he is not trying.
And I know I think he's embarrassed by maybe doing all these directed DVDs, movies and stuff.
But man, I mean, he, he'll barely open his eyes to deliver a line in this thing.
I don't totally agree.
There were moments where I was like,
is he into this or not?
But then there were other moments
where he had tears streaming down it.
It was weird.
The heavy scenes, like where he had to sit by his daughter's bed
and deal with like the fact that his daughter might also die.
I thought he was bad in those two.
I thought he was good in those.
He was crying.
It's like, I gotta sit by it, look, my daughter.
Well, I'm like, come on.
Not those parts.
I just mean like the moments of like quiet rage.
Right.
So he had good moments in it and then other moments where I was like he does seem kind of like he doesn't care
But I also think he's a little out of touch at this point
Oh, well how long has he been playing that character? Yeah, that's true. You know, and it's like he was always the guy that was just like
Yeah, you know, like yeah, John McLean's always a drunk and like was like I can't be bothered with this and now I got to save the world
but yeah
I miss some of the old school charismatic Bruce Willis,
like with the, you know, it rarely happened,
well, I guess it did from time to time,
but like a death becomes her Bruce Willis.
Like he was a really good kind of character comedy actor
in a weird way and a few things.
But those are the only times I can ever remember him
really stretching out in any way.
The best, look, the best, in my opinion,
the best Bruce Willis role of all time is pulp fiction.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
It is everything you ever wanted Bruce Willis to be right, you know, and the and the and the I would put die hard is a very close second. Yeah, um
I, uh, oh, uh, another nod to Eli Roth. Um, I like that he added like hard his horror background came out in this. Yeah, couple real gross out types. Yeah, couple real gross out scenes. And then also too, he shot things suspensefully.
Like the scene where the home invasion happens,
he shoots it like the strangers or something like that.
So that added a whole new element to me,
which was a nice surprise.
I'll give you that.
The few gross out moments.
The one I kind of had to issue with
is when he's stapling his shoulder shut,
and I'm like, you're a surgeon.
He's putting super glue into an open wound to seal it.
I was like, that's how you do it on the street.
All right.
No, I learned that from Better Call Saul.
So, well, I guess he can't go into the office
and fix his shoulder because he'd get a lot of eyes.
Yeah, no, he can't,
but I learned that from Better Call Saul,
like on the show, whenever somebody gets shot
and then they're crooks or criminals,
so they can't go to the doctor,
they superglue the wound.
Okay.
That's like a real thing.
So I was actually excited when he did that.
Well, you learned it from a TV show though.
Not from a doctor.
Well, I think it's probably been researched a bit.
I don't think they're just...
Well, you can't make that assumption.
But I also thought the super glue thing was cool too because he when he put the brake fluid and the one guy's
Wooned that was real intense. Yeah, and he goes I'm putting a I'm putting a solve inner whatever in your slice is open is
What's the cyanic nerve? What is it? Yeah, something like that? What's what is it though? I can't remember the one at the back of your feet
Pouring a breath the Achilles heel. It's in the back of the thigh. So I was searching for I thought that wasn't the Achilles heel is the heel
Yeah, but he was in the thigh okay
Yeah, pouring Blake break fluid into a open nerve at one point.
I mean, there was some intense shit.
But he says the most painful thing in the world is pouring this type of thing into an open wound.
Right. And then two scenes later, he's got to put the super glue in his wound.
And I think that was kind of saying, like, oh, yeah, this is kind of like now he's got to do it to himself.
out. Right. Um, I love the bathroom sequence, which, uh, when he finally is going after
the head dude, oh yeah, that invaded his house. And when he just walks in the bathroom
and that guy's peed at the urinal and he just goes, get out. Yeah. You know, I just, I
got, I got excited. I got that was crazy. The opening fire and a, because he heard a phone
ring. He's opening fire into a closed stall. I was holy shit. It did feel like, especially,
I don't know if you heard this, but so we saw it at the Glendale Americana. Yeah. And directly
across the street is the Glendale Galleria. Yes. Two malls directly across from each other,
which makes no sense. Yes. Yes. Yesterday there was a shooter at the Glendale Galleria. You tried
to rob a jewelry store at noon on a Saturday in the mall and a security guard opened fire in the
Glendale Galleria yesterday at noon.
Did they get the guy?
We were across the street three days ago.
Morgan Murphy, our friend, was there
and had to go crouch in a back room and shit.
Very intense.
Was she in the jewelry store or in the...
She was in the mall and they kind of did a close down.
But I mean, to be watching this movie at this time
was a little nuts at times.
Listen, I have no argument against that.
It is a very sensitive film right now, right, the subject matter, but we're not that far apart from each other
I isn't that also
Here's the thing. Yeah, and this is why one of the things I do like about Riverdale
Isn't that the not the point?
But isn't that kind of what some art should do?
Shouldn't it play a great shouldn't it push some weird buttons and hit some wrong nerves?
Everything is so fucking safe and sanitized and yeah, it's like
I think, you know, it's like, when that guy did that movie,
the comedy with Tim Heidecker, which I hated.
I kind of liked it, but yeah.
Because every character was so despicably unlikable,
I just didn't like the movie.
But I didn't hate that he made it,
I just didn't enjoy watching it.
But when he got criticism,
somebody said like, you know, this is just,
the character learns nothing by the end of the film,
it's just disgusting, it's just an asshole.
You know, the guy was like, yeah, I'm sorry,
I didn't know as my responsibility to teach lessons to people you know like I was trying to tell a story about a certain type of person
That's what I set out to do. That's what I did right and it is what it is. Yeah, this is a person that exists
This is a type of person. So
Anyway, that's all yeah
I don't think we're that far apart on it. I think we both liked it to some extent you more than me
My issues were Willis and my other issue was just how they played him making that
flip from like boy the cops aren't doing anything about my daughter to like I'm going to start killing people
Maybe that was also a problem with Willis and him not showing that in his eyes, but
I didn't buy that transition at all. They could have put another scene in the original death wish
There's a sequence where Charles Bronson is vomiting. Yeah after he kills a guy because he's like I would have I done yeah
Willis it could have used one scene like that right
Willis is like, you know, eating pizza in his basement and angry that the cops are doing
anything, and then just turns to a vigilante, and it takes about five seconds.
Yeah, and then the first time he attacks anybody, they believe that the video immediately,
somebody gets it on their phone, they immediately goes online.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he's watching the video, and he's just like, I couldn't tell by his expression if the
character thinks this is funny, or if he's like, oh shit.
This this might be I might be in over my head here. It was kind of hard to tell yeah
I wonder if Willis had anything to do with one of the kids the police interview describing him as being in his thirties
I don't know if you caught that
I was like in his thirties
Well that that that in the other scene the other thing I love so Vincent Denofrio plays his brother always love events in Denofrio
And they think at one point the cops think Denofrio is the vigilante
Yes, and they go find an offrio to question him. Yeah, and they go we don't know, you know
We hear he's left -handed
No hair likes to wear a hoodie in good shape
Sounds a lot like you and I'm like Vincent to know for you. No number one is not in good shape
He is physically nowhere near the same size of Bruce Willis foot taller
And they have a video of Bruce Willis just from the back
I'm like look at the guy in the video. You think that's Vincent to know for you
The Nafrio was in better shape than he's been in a while, but yeah saying much no
Tenoffio is always a great character actor. He was the only good part to me about the Magnificent 7 remake and
Joe you were saying you actually thought that he was gonna be in on it
You thought he was gonna be the killer. Well, Tenoffrio at this point only ever plays a guy with shifty eyes, right so
there were many points
They play up and I'd really do to think it was just a red herring and it was very well done
and they play up the fact that Vincent de Nafrio has been convicted of some sort of crime
and is out of work.
They never explained it though.
They also talk about, they also show that he's recurrently needing to borrow money from
his brother.
Well, and you were saying you thought that might have been a red herring, and I thought that
might have been the original ending, and that people thought people liked Nafrio too much
to make that jump.
Yeah, because they do, I didn't think about it, but they were really setting him up to
be the kid.
they specifically say he takes,
he needs to borrow $2 ,000 from Bruce Willis.
Bruce Willis, when the house gets robbed and invaded,
he says he's got to tell the cops what they took
and he goes $2 ,000 in cash.
Vince and D 'Afril eventually pays the $2 ,000 back.
It's all very fishy.
Also, when the cops say that they're doing all they can
in the beginning, Bruce Willis' character initially
is like, okay, thank you.
And Dinofreo's character is like,
so you're just gonna see it screaming at the cut.
Like really playing it up.
So I just kept thinking like,
here's a guy that's broke,
it's gonna be a, before the devil knows your dead kind of thing.
He's gonna, he's sent these guys in,
rob them, just bring me the shit,
it'll be fine, and it all went wrong.
Yeah, but then that's not the case.
But it doesn't help that throughout the entire movie,
every time they cut to Dinoffrio, he's like looking down to the side, like it looks like he's like
just stolen something. Yeah, so maybe it was the original ending. I wouldn't be surprised. It felt
like a movie that had maybe had a reshoot or two or a restructure or two, but I'll tell you this,
if it had gone the path that a lot of Willis movies go these days direct to on demand or DVD, you'd be
like, this was really good, I think. The fact that it got the theatrical release, you
know, people were harsh on it. It didn't do great. It's an entertaining movie. It is what
it is. It's got a little bit on its mind. And I think we both recommend it. It's a flashier
brawl in cell block 99. Correct. And not as good. No, but yeah. Folks, we're happy to be
back. We are about to sit down and record next week's episode, which will be a commentary on
the long awaited. Wait, that might be the bonus episode. Oh, yeah. Well, just, just hold off.
All right. All right. I'll tell you on the website what the next one will be. Yeah. But folks,
thank you for your time. Thank you for your continued support. The numbers on the Facebook page are
going through the roof, which I love to see. The merch site is up at the Hoghouse on Etsy. The shirts
The shirts are available, Emily is doing a Beyond Fantastic job.
Get them all up.
Thank you, Emily.
And, you know, we'll see you next time and we'll see you.
And it plugs.
I don't want to show them that.
Yeah.
I mean, I want to plug my tour coming up.
All right, April of April.
Then after that, I'll finish my sentence with in hell
and we'll be done.
Well, then you can plug your show.
April.
I'm going on tour.
For all dates posted on Joderosa info or dot com or joderosa comity dot com go to it
check it out.
I'll see you in states like New Hampshire, New York, no, not New York, sorry, Pennsylvania
Michigan, you know, a bunch of different places.
So come on out and I hope to see.
I am on Twitter and Instagram at Patrick Walsh.
My show, Living Biblically, is airing Monday nights at 9 .30, 8 .30 Central on the CBS Network.
It is the absolute worst time slot we're up against all the bigger shows on television at once.
It's neither a smash nor a bomb at this point, but we need all the eyes we can get.
and seeing you guys talk about the show and about Joe's performance and you
know listing your favorite lines and all that on Facebook has made me feel
great and I really appreciate it. That's it and let me finish my sentence from
before with in hell.