I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, we'll see you in hell is back for the fourth installment of your August series
and we are here to talk about Alien...
Romulus, right?
Romulus
Another Alien movie with the title of a word I've never heard of
that means something about Greek mythology or something
Well, I guess it was the name of a ship in here, right?
Yeah, but I think the word Romulus is like the Greek god that planted
semen on Olympus or what, you know, it's always some connective thing like that
Sure, see, I'm actually going to be unprepared
Unfortunately, I saw Alien colon Rummy and Michelle's high school reunion
How was it?
Funny, but really funny, it just, you know, was not what I was expecting to say the least
Surprisingly funny
Can I tell you, like, with all the IP we're doing, we'll only make things that have existed before
I was weirdly excited about the Jonah Hill, I think he had written it too
It was going to be the Men in Black and the 21 Jump Street duo team up
because they're both Sony properties
Yes
And I was like, look, we're basically doing Abbott and Costello meet Frankenstein here
for Christ's sake, but if we have to live in this world, let's do it
Yeah
And it never came to be, maybe it was too expensive, but
I could be talking out of my ass, but I feel like there's that...
I feel like I just saw something that said that still has life in it
Oh, all right
I think
Well then, why not Rummy and Michelle go into deep space and confront the alien?
I mean, I'd watch that
Well, I'm glad you brought this up, because I have a news psycho that fits beautifully
right into this. Brian Cox, the most judgmental man in all of cinema, who's wonderful
Who does monthly McDonald's commercials while judging everyone
Yeah, I've literally seen interviews with him where he's like, Brad Pitt is an American actor,
he's quite good, and then the ghost commercial and you hear him go dot dot dot dot dot
All right, Brian, he just turns to the other microphone
He really had a lot to say about Joaquin Phoenix and Napoleon, not like that performance
I agree with him, quite frankly
This is what he said
Dot dot dot dot, I'm loving it
He said this recently in an interview
Yeah
What has... it's beginning, of cinema, it's beginning to implode, and the state of cinema
is in a very bad way. What's happened is that television is doing what cinema used to do
I think cinema is in a very bad...
Well, he's also saying that because he just was in succession
Sure, yeah, exactly
So anyway, he goes...
You know, if you're in the best show on TV, maybe
Yeah, he says, I think cinema is in a very bad way, I think it's lost its place because of
partly the grandiose element between Marvel and DC and all of that, I think it's beginning to implode
actually, you're kind of losing the plot. Now, I don't think it's an unfair opinion to have
The reason I found this noteworthy was, the Russo Brothers, the Marvel,
famed Marvel directors, the Russo Brothers, their new movie, which is going direct to Netflix,
has a budget of, brace yourself, 320 million dollars
Mamma mia
I'm like, what fucking bloated mess is this? I start reading, cast includes who?
Brian Cox
Oh, yeah, sure
I'll do it
The reason I went with this one is it actually has a very different feel
It was tackling much weightier themes than your average Marvel film
Shut up, Brian
This is what they'll always say
This is what they'll always say when they go do the thing they said they'd never do
They'll go, at its core, this is actually a very small film
It's about a fam, shut up, shut up
My agent said, I threw it across the room into the fireplace
My agent called and said, give it another read
Give it another read, not what I found was a searing take on capitalism in America
Yeah, this is right up there with Jamie Lee Curtis's Marvel criticism
followed by her Borderlands appearance, which is ranked to be, arguably, and by the numbers,
the biggest Hollywood bomb of all time
I'm seeing that, yeah
Borderlands, well, you know, they're claiming it costs 90 million
and it costs so much more than that because you get Kevin Hart makes 30 a picture
Jack Black 15 to 20
Blanchett and Curtis, both coming off Oscar wins
and they're not going to let them get anything less than Jack Black gets
So you're talking about 60 million in cast, Eli Roth directing
He turns in his cut, they go, what the fuck is this?
We have to reshoot this
This doesn't work at all
They bring in the Deadpool director, probably for more money than Eli Roth cost
He reshoots half the movie
And then at the end of the day, you've put in all this work
and all this money and something comes out that everyone hates and nobody watches
And what is the lesson learned?
Borderlands 2, let's do it
And in about three years, that's probably the lesson they've learned
The Acolyte on Star Wars, Disney plus Star Wars,
the controversial Acolyte series has been canceled
And that's wild for them
I don't think any of their Star Wars shows made it just one season
Obi -Wan?
Almost all of them except for the cartoons have been one season with a questionable second
This is the first where they said definitively it is not, I think, I might be wrong
But I think this is the first where they said definitively
Second season is not happening
And look, I'm not going to dance on the ashes like a lot of these macho YouTubers do
Like we won, they're listening to the fans
Because I think that that's very toxic in its own way
Just like we changed the design of Sonic the Hedgehog
We've risen again
I will say this, I do hope it's a moment where Disney is realizing it's not about
people not liking diversity or those things
It's about people wanting a good product and this was not a good product
They dropped the ball and hopefully this is a turning point
I don't know
More importantly, I got a lot of news psychos
This will be the last one I do, Pat
Did you see the Snow White trailer?
No, but I got a trailer to get to
I have not seen the Snow White trailer
Now let me guess, does it start with Hi -Ho?
Ig -Dak -A -Li
Yeah, a slow haunting version of Hi -Ho
Or Whistle While You Work, whatever it's called
Yeah
Visually it does look kind of neat
It looks sort of wondrous and fantastic and whatever
I was like, this looks visually kind of cool
And then it gets to Seven Dwarves
And there's been a lot of controversy around this
It started with old Dinklage
The Dink
You know what they've replaced the Seven Dwarves with, Pat?
Instead of seven little people actors?
CGI Dwarves
Oh my god
They still have dwarves
But now they're just fake
So they took jobs away from people
And then they just remade the people with a computer
It's insane
I mean, wasn't the whole point just that they were little people was the issue?
Yeah, which I still don't get
Because it doesn't
Yeah, now, so
I don't understand
One project where all these guys and gals could find work
They pulled the plug, that's crazy
And recreated them with a computer
Yeah
It's literally like saying
Not literally, but it's along the lines of like saying
You know, we're doing a new version of this old Three Stooges movie
But the portrayal of the black butler is racist
So we're not going to do it
So we're going to create a CGI black guy to play the waiter
Or butler
It's crazy
It's so insane
Yeah
See, we didn't put an actor through this unhumane experience
So it's better
It's like, yeah, but you still have him like having a bucket of milk splashed on his face
That's still really hard to watch
Now, the argument, of course, from the jump
Or the counterargument to Dinklage from the jump of this was
There wasn't anything inherently exploitative about the seven dwarves
They're wonderful characters and they're heroes in the movie
And it's a great chance for seven people to get work
But if you do think it is problematic
This is not the way you fix it
As you just pointed out
So he's probably mad he didn't get the call
He was probably like
They're making a seven dwarves movie and no one even asked
You must at least consult the Dink before making a decision like this
I went to Disney and I pitched the seven dwarves in Snow White
See, you flip it to empower
They said no and I said
I also requested that it be me, then the six dwarves
So I sort of have my own line of the poster and then Snow White
And then they really didn't like that
It was called Grumpy and the six dwarves plus Snow White
Whiny, he'd be whiny
I this morning, the second my eyes opened
First, as if some sort of prank by my cat who is never in my bed
She was sitting on my pillow with her asshole pressed to my nose
Just like you like it
Literally this cat has never crossed into my bed
I was just like the fuck
So after I pushed her away and thoroughly washed my nose
I watched the trailer for Megalopolis, the new one
Ooh, I didn't know the new trailer was out
Um, it's you're seeing a lot of footage but it's like quick quick flashing cuts
But here's how it starts, Joe
One of the most embarrassing movie going experiences of all time
Andrew Saris, 1972 original review of The Godfather
Oh no
Yeah, Joe
No
Then it's like a costly disaster
John Jankiewicz's 1979 review of Apocalypse Now
It does the whole thing through Dracula
A bloated mess
It goes through all of his movies
North?
It doesn't get to North, they leave that one alone
But um, wait, he didn't do North, Joe
Or Jack, I meant
That was Bobby Reiner
Yeah, Jack
He did Jack, yeah
Even worse than North
It's to me just the most embarrassing thing you could do to promote this movie
Is act like, hey, you didn't like this guy in the past
We know you're a legendary filmmaker
Quote your previous triumphs proudly
You don't have to do this thing where you're like making fun of critics
Or whatever it is
They used to do this, like David Lynch put up a ton of bad reviews
For Lost Highway on the poster
I thought that was funny
Well, it was what Jim Carrey did with Ace Ventura
When they got bad reviews
He was like, no, put all the bad reviews up
But that's great
Right
So I thought you were saying that's what he was doing of this
And I was like, that's kind of funny that he's doing it with a drama
And then it's like, no, no, no
It's not that
It's the worst version of that
Yeah, that's just my thing
This big multi, multi -million dollar movie
Don't come out and be like, hey, so we got to acknowledge the elephant in the room
That's not the move
You're already coming to us like hat in hand
And it's like, no, you've lost
Make us excited about it
From the visionary
Do the whole thing
Bang the drum
Give us the trailer where we see a quick clip of the Godfather
The biggest best scenes of each of his movies
Apocalypse Now
And then, and now, make us excited
That's crazy
That's fucking crazy, man
How does the movie look?
How's the trailer?
It looks bad, Joe
Looks real bad
Like, but why does it look bad?
Because I've only seen that one dumb thing where Adam Driver goes, stop
You know, I haven't seen anything else of the movie
It looks like one of those late Terry Gilliam pictures
Just too busy, too much going on
The cast, even though it seemed impressive
When you're really looking at it, you're like
John Voight, you know, wearing like a king's robe
Some people don't, should not do period pieces
It's like when Harvey Keitel was in The Last Temptation of Christ
It's like, you just don't have the vibe, man
That scene in Last Temptation
But we'll see, we'll see
I'll be there when it opens, guaranteed
That scene in Last Temptation
I'm excited to see Travis Kelce getting a lot of acting work
Who?
Travis Kelce, boyfriend to Taylor Swift
Oh God, is he in it?
And football player
Is he in it?
Is Travis Kelce in the movie?
Megalopolis?
No, he's in Happy Gilmore 2
He's also in some new Amazon action comedy
And it's just like, we're not even
I guess we did this with like O .J. Simpson back in the 70s
But have we not evolved past this?
Like he's a football player, nobody gives a shit about him
He becomes Taylor Swift's boyfriend
Everybody gives a shit about him
We're gonna make him the star of films?
At least with Happy Gilmore 2, I'm assuming it'll be like the Bob Barker thing or something
The action thing I can't speak to
But no, I was gonna say earlier when you mentioned Keitel
Yeah
I mean that scene in Last Temptation where he
It's the opening scene where he comes in and he's Judas
And he's going, you build the crosses, you're worse than that
Topped only by Irvin Kershner's appearance later in the film
With the full Brooklyn accent
Yeah
He's not the king of the Jews
And you're like, what the fuck is going on in this thing?
King of the Jews, my fat ass
Wait
Yeah
So
Pat is having
This is where Pat just took off his headphones
This is where his headphones have died
They haven't, I just suddenly couldn't hear you
I don't know what was going on
You can hear me now?
Yeah
We're here, we're here
Yeah, I'm here
We got you, we've got each other and we've got you
Do you have another new psycho or should we move to the corner?
I don't, but I did want to do one more Harvey Keitel in Last Temptation of Christ
Sure
Keep talking like this, it is gonna be your last supper
Right?
That's very good
Can't really do a Keitel, any Italian guy I do comes off like Gandolfini
Well I think Keitel's Jewish, but I think
There's some Italian in there
J. Moore does an impeccable Harvey Keitel
I've never heard a better impression in my life
There's a weirdly feminine quality about Keitel for being like the most masculine guy alive
Like his crying always comes across like a little girl sort of
Like in Reservoir Dogs and in a few of his movies
When he's like our bad lieutenant he does a lot of that like
It's interesting
I feel like Keitel too also has played a lot of characters where there's like a homoerotic
subtext going, Reservoir Dogs is a great example
There's this vibe that he's in love with, who's Curry?
Mr. Tim Roth
I know, but what's his?
Orange
Orange?
Yeah
I can't remember
You're not gonna die
You're not gonna die today
No I don't have any more movie corns
I did when I saw this movie and IMAX clocked
I don't even think it was a record but I clocked 38 minutes from trailer one through Nicole Kidman
It's just an arduous experience anymore
It is
You think, you would think we would have learned something from lockdown in redesigning this
experience and the only thing that has shifted is you can now walk into any major movie theater chain
carrying a Huxtable size hoagie and like a big gulp and they won't be like you can't bring that
in they're just like please anybody just please go into the theater please
Yeah
That's the only new thing that's that's that's all that's changed
Yeah I'm hearing a lot more just like straight up sodas being cracked open in the theater
You know I mean people have given up
I saw a guy at the gas station the other morning in a robe
Oh boy
That to me I was like look you're gonna all there's always the the 17 year old girl who's
out in pajamas and nobody gives a shit whatever a grown man in a robe is like that's end times
you know you can walk you can tony soprano style you can walk to the end of your driveway and get
the paper you cannot go past that curb barrier in a robe or you're just giving up
Yeah it's it's it's robe is the new sweatpants you know there was the Seinfeld you know what
I've given up
So you're you're equating the American dream with sitting in a pair of sweatpants eating
a giant block of cheese
Good show you should check that one out
That's the other funny clothing I don't care bit is I love when she's when Elaine's dating
Michael whatever his name is from all the Christopher Guest movies
and he tries to grow his hair out and he realizes that he's bald
Yeah because he's been shaving it for so long
She goes you got a stain on your shirt he goes yeah meatball fell out of my sandwich
and she's like you ate we're sitting down eating he goes it's from yesterday
Yeah yeah they should reboot that show
Yeah I'm sure it'd be just as good
Movie corner I got two that are on point with what we're reviewing today rewatches
I'll start with Prometheus I tried to rewatch Prometheus dear lord
I I don't know man I just the movie is just
Is that the first of the new ones?
It's the first yeah it was the first of the proposed Ridley Scott trilogy
Yeah
Where he was gonna
Which look I admire that Ridley Scott was gonna come back to this franchise that he launched
Many would argue that the franchise was cemented by Cameron's installment with Aliens the sequel
And I think a lot of people attribute the success of the franchise more to Cameron
necessarily because Cameron's design and approach was really what set the tone for the sequels that
followed but Ridley launched the whole thing in the massive success of the first movie it's a
classic obviously so I was excited that Ridley Scott was returning to the franchise and I
I'm not gonna deal with the planting of life and the origins of life and all that sort of stuff
which they do revisit a bit in Romulus but god damn the Prometheus man it's it's I remember
after we saw Phantom Menace in the theater excuse me we were all a little disappointed
and my friend Scott said it just felt like chapter one of a book it felt like it was kind of laying
the groundwork for what's to come and it wasn't that exciting to watch and I felt like that about
Romulus I mean I'm sorry Prometheus where it's like I mean yeah this origin thing is interesting
and whatever but it's just not enough I don't know man I just find the movie painfully boring
you're also immediately thrown off by Guy Pearce and the old man makeup
because I remember when I saw it I didn't excuse me I didn't know that it was Guy Pearce but as
soon as I saw him I was like that's a young guy and old man makeup why are they doing that
and then you realize oh it's so Guy Pearce can play the young version of the guy too
but I don't know there's just a lot with the movie where you're where you're just I don't know it's
just not interesting to me I don't find it interesting at all it's it was Prometheus
covenant and then we never got a third part we never got a third installment yeah which Romulus
sort of tries to address in its own way which we'll get to but I don't know I guess
I'm not a big sci -fi guy I find sci -fi nine times out of ten an interesting thought and
an interesting premise but a boring execution sure yeah you know I it's it's why I always say
sci -fi Star Wars is fantasy in space but you know Star Trek is about as deep as I can go
and even with that I'm very selective with sci -fi but you know I guess if I approached this without
knowing Alien at all and just kind of watched it as a sci -fi movie I might have a different
appreciation for it but I just find the movie very boring
despite its its intelligence you know I don't know when the last time you tried you watched
it or tried to watch it was but both were a one -and -done theatrical experience but I
do own both in 4k I have not opened them but I'm excited to watch I mean the
the franchise of Alien which of course we're getting to the latest one today you're talking
about in my opinion two classics one a suspense thriller all -time masterpiece in space two one of
the great action movies of all time Joe disagrees that's fine three sort of an interesting showcase
for an up -and -coming Dave Fincher but not really a great movie for a train wreck and then for me
the Alien versus Predators are a complete wash I liked the new ones when I saw them but don't
remember a thing about them I like them yeah sorry I know I was just gonna say I saw I hated Alien
Predator Requiem I think that's the second one yeah I thought it sucked I saw the first one I
saw both in the theater I liked the first one when I saw it upon rewatch no but when I saw it I liked
it because we were so starved at that point for a good Predator follow -up true I was like oh cool
it's Predator like like that was enough to carry me through it I kind of watched it more like a
Predator movie yeah but yeah I just I don't know man these are just it's a it's a it's a
it's a weird franchise man they've had way more misses in this franchise at this point than than
hits I'm shocked that it's still going there's there's a TV show coming out now about like the
TV show the the people that that make shows at FX have a monopoly they work on if you're a writer
under employee of any FX show you write for four or five of their fucking shows
so Noah Hawley has done for them Bargo which is on its sixth season he did that show
that I couldn't finish called Legion and then now he's doing Alien it's like guys like
I don't know that sort of thing really bothers me at a time when there are no jobs that one
man has that many jobs because the product will suffer yeah invariably you can't do that much
and have it be good no it's a very um it starts to become a very AI approach not meaning you're
using AI but meaning it's Amazon it's it's you know it's a it's a very just regimented approach
it's like you know this phase we will do these things and we will tick these boxes and then the
second phase we will do these things and tick these boxes and therefore we will meet the deadlines
and then the rail and it's like it doesn't really make for for artistic creation but I'll say this
I've been revisiting the Twilight Zone you know because it's my favorite show of all time
and uh I've been watching these Rod Serling interviews and dude I'm talking interviews
from like 1960 yeah and he's saying the exact same shit we're saying he's like it's a shame
this beautiful medium where we could explore so many magnificent stories and whatever and he goes
and it's just paid by numbers they're just doing the same thing over and over so I guess it just
never really changes but um it just it also I mean obviously it wasn't quite as bloated back
then but um right anyway Prometheus I don't know let us know your thoughts in the uh on um
on the Patreon comments I'm curious if there are big Prometheus fans out there
uh yeah I've been loving the Patreon comments there's been a lot more of them lately and it's
about in the last episode and it reminded me of Joaquin Phoenix talk about a new psycho
so like he do you hear about that story he left that movie or whatever well he went to Todd Haynes
and Christine Vachon Christine Vachon's worked with Todd Haynes since the 1990 basically like
I watched one of his earliest films in film school and legendary indie producer Christine Vachon you
like the classic indies the most like difficult to get made projects Joaquin Phoenix comes to her
and Todd Haynes and he's like I want to do a sexually explicit full frontally nude I'm
fucking gay love story here's the the idea for it they're like that could be really interesting
Haynes and someone else writes the screenplay that you know he just brought him in the story
they collaborate on this thing they're getting ready to roll Joaquin walks and they can't replace
him because the role requires a man to engage in full frontal sex and you know
intense like nude sex scenes on camera with I assume boners and everything else so they're
completely fucked they're just like losing this money he walked by the way he walked for those
unfamiliar to the story he walked like three days before production it wasn't like he walked
mid whatever like there's a they said they're gonna sue him like yeah I'm sure they will yeah
you got you have to you got to set a precedent here I'm gonna do three 90s comedies that I
revisited pull a page from Joe's playbook and do a little theme I rewatched multiplicity
newly available on blu -ray this is one where if it if it makes the pilgrimage to 4k I would say
please avoid this movie does not look good in the blu -ray format I kept being like why does this
movie shot exactly like a multi -cam sitcom and then I realized because they were trying to
introduce this technology of four Michael Keaton's and of course you don't need a busy like you're
you know you have all this stuff to do in the editing room you're just going to shoot a blank
stage so that you can move the Michael Keaton's around like paper dolls or something
but man the movie just fucking sits there like I know Harold Ramis was never you know he wasn't
quite the Kevin Smith of his day but like he really did not put much into the staging and the the
shooting of his films that really wasn't his specialty it's not a lot of comedy director
specialty nor does it have to be but multiplicity to me just looked like junk it looked like an
episode of uh what just the 10 of us or something like it had a tgif vibe it looks like it looks
almost like um seventh heaven in those shows yes for when that was happening yeah and it's too much
you know like I think on dvd you know we talk sometimes about it sometimes a movie is just
supposed to look like junk and this movie did not really benefit from the upgrade to me it just was
hard to look at um Michael Keaton is awesome in this movie it's sort of his take on the nutty
professor he's got he gets to do four different characters uh one sort of a fussy uptight gay
guy one a macho uh like beer drinking get in your face guy and then the fourth one the very funny
one that everyone remembers is essentially mentally handicapped yeah but um and then
Keaton himself who's great but it's Lowell Ganz and Babalu Mandel the greatest name for a comedy
writing team of all time Lowell Ganz and Babalu Mandel um and there's they're known for their
you know like they did all those Ron Howard movies and a lot of the ramis movies and
you just get a lot of really funny jokes in this movie Keaton's great Andy McDowell's charming
this was during that period where Eugene Levy was just lost he was kind of the Fred Armisen of his
day where if you had any foreign uh supporting character they just gave it to him and it didn't
matter if he was uh French or if he was like Armenian or Serbian he's just Eugene Levy and
um he's sort of funny he he there was a long time where Levy would always be just way broader than
the movie he was in like just like doing too much and this kind of falls into that camp I love I
love I do love Levy in this because it's my favorite version of Levy where he's playing
a guy that seemingly has a who's trying to make it look like he has his shit together but he's
a moron like I don't like when there's one of the reasons I wasn't a huge Schitt's Creek fan
is like I don't like when Levy is a little bit sinister or selfish or whatever I like when he's
playing a dummy that's trying to present it like he's got it together yeah the whole gag in this
with the watch he's always late you know yeah yeah no he's funny um yeah I love I love that
version of him in the first vacation of course yeah when he sees the car I guess you think you
hate it now wait till you drive it it's one of my favorite lines of all time but um and that's a
Harold Ramis as well R .I .P. I'd like to say something weird here and this just might be my
own observation my guess is that nobody had worse taste in music than Harold Ramis judging by
the soundtracks he was putting in these movies do you remember the song that kicks off Groundhog Day
baby things are warming up cause I'm your weatherman oh god air over the opening credits and he plays
these awful songs over the credits so you just have to sit and listen to them uh real generic
again bad sitcom shit I think he actually wrote a couple of them so it might have been a way to
make an extra buck but um multiplicity to me plays like a really funny episode of a sitcom
it's not a great movie I immediately put it back up on Amazon for sale um but there you go Joe
yeah it's got my the the two Keaton parts in it man uh that make me laugh so hard when he's
classic Keaton when when the doctor is like what do you do to relax he's like well let's see I
never yeah and uh when the asshole version of him is pitching like turning the thing into the
bachelor pad right he's like we'll put a bar over here whatever and Keaton just goes
yeah it's not gonna work yeah I you know he I love him in this era um he
wait what was I gonna say Mike Keaton oh I know what I was gonna say I remembered this movie as
being Eugene Levy as the scientist like I remembered it as he he worked with Keaton
and he's like hey buddy you're running a little uh low on the juice at home and come on in here
and then they go into some side room and he shows him this thing he's been working on it's not that
at all I was mixing it up with splash I believe another Lowe Ganz Babalu Mandel joint um where
Levy is the inventor who I think is trying to get his clutches on Daryl Hannah yeah he's he's
and he's a bad guy he's the bad guy yeah yeah um and then he turns I think he turns good at the
very end if I remember correctly but um yeah so the overpowering love of a mermaid he changes his
eyes splash is awesome what's wrong she's a fish yeah splash has so many laughs do you remember
the little boat I think which this when I was little me and my sister and then later on me and
my me and my buddies would rewind this scene 50 times the only thing that came close was the dad
so I married an axe murderer but in splash he's in a it's Tom Hanks at his most like exasperated
his funniest he's in a tiny boat with a big fat captain who's like paddling him out and when they
get to like the middle of the ocean the the propeller stops working and the guy's like oh
no and then he dives into the water he's like I gotta head back and get it so he hops into the
water he goes where are you going where are you going and he goes I gotta head back I'm
gonna get the little boat looks around and he goes boat oh man it's all delivery there's nothing
all that funny on the page maybe but Tom Hanks is hilarious in that movie that's a perfect joke
the part that killed me as a kid and still does is when she shows up naked at the Statue of Liberty
tour and the tour guy goes bunchy balls I mean yeah what a perfect thing to explain
and then of course the the John Candy but the the racquetball scene was another favorite of
racquetball candy dropping the change and looking up girls dresses oh I forgot that aspect yeah
Hanks going what are you doing man and he's like hey look if something works I stick with it
that's a very funny response yeah um all right I got one more it's Alien Covenant the follow
up to Prometheus yeah this is um this is where you realized Ridley's prequel trilogy was in
trouble because he was like we're doing Prometheus we're not even showing any xenomorphs in this
and it's just called Prometheus you figure it out and then the second one immediately they're like
why don't we put an alien colon in front of and bring in a few xenos yeah um but it continues the
story of the first one where David played by Michael Fassbender who's the android a sinister
android much like Ian Holman the first alien um he you now I did not like covenant when I
saw him in the theater we reviewed it on here and I thought it was very boring
after I saw Romulus I went back and watched it again and I gotta say I I it started slow
and I was kind of like oh god this movie is just lifeless and then once it got moving once they
land on that planet where David is I was like this is pretty cool like I'm into this now now I
get what Ridley was trying to do with Prometheus this is a more interesting version of it and I
just really enjoyed the entire concept that David this evil android was hell bent on being the
on earth the god figure I love the the the analogy of an android being like god because it can exist
forever yeah uh and it can be omnipotent in its own way and all that stuff I love the reveal that
he destroyed the race of aliens that created the humans so he is essentially now top of the food
I love the twist where he says when you first see the xenomorphs in this movie they're white
and they look different and then you and then he reveals he has had a missing element in creating
the perfect life form and you realize that missing element was a human to plant these
things in which is the whole thing with alien and he does it to Billy Crudup and the first
android and named and his grandmother which I found was a weird choice a grand mom android
uh and and and actually they called her grand droid if I remember correctly
in a full fat suit like big mama's house which was unnecessary um I I thought he was great in it I
thought the whole cast was great um even I not even I don't mean to say that like I'm taking
something away from him but it is cool seeing Danny McBride in a very serious role like he's
there's nothing funny about him and he's got dramatic moments there's a part where he realizes
his wife was killed everybody's very good in this um particularly Michael Fassbender um James Franco
is just in a weird cameo he plays the captain that dies when the pods open because his pod incinerates
and he's he's literally in it in a picture and then in a video clip that his wife watches
and that's it it's clearly like just he was a fan or something but it's a very strange cameo but
anyway um and then the alien showdown at the end takes place outside during a rainstorm on a ship
in daylight and it looks really cool and it's different and it's fun and you know I thought
they did and then there's a second showdown where the alien is there's a second alien and
it's on the ship and they didn't realize and they have to fight it that's kind of like par
for the course with these alien movies which we will also get to in Romulus um you know it's just
there's always the second ending in an alien movie where you thought it was done but it's not done
um but I really liked Covenant um there is a weird scene though when they realize there's
another alien on the ship at the end two of the survivors it's all married couples because they're
a colony crew they're going to colonize a new part of space um one of the couples is
fucking in the shower and there's they're listening to like sexy r &b which this always
bothers me in a movie like this because you're like it takes place in the year like 2200 and
they're still listening to music from the 90s or whatever it's kind of a weird choice but anyway
um still listen to oldies yeah yeah but we don't listen to music that's 240 years old or whatever
you know what I mean like or 20 years 10 years old so anyway but they're um they're in the shower
fucking and you realize the alien is in their block of the ship and McBride and and another
character are running to to save them and it cuts to them having sex in the shower and the alien
tail goes into the shower and they don't notice it but it's sleeks in like all sexy and you can
tell that you could tell that Ridley Scott thought that that was kind of funny like like let's have
the tail come in all sexy but like it's it's it's going to be creepy and it doesn't really work but
the sex alien tie -in that has pretty much woven through every one of these alien movies since three
I always find weird there there's a I mean for in four if I remember correctly she full -on fucks
the alien and there's like a scene there's some sort of weird yeah coupling it's shot like you
thriller it's her like getting felt up by the alien and in the first two I don't think there's
much of it in the second one there's some tensions in the first one if I remember correctly
it's interesting because it's kind of like now it's precursor to Carpenter's The Thing
but you know one of the great things about Carpenter's The Thing is is it's eight guys
up in this snow base tensions are high there's no women around so the second something's wrong
they're at each other's throats everybody's horny and isolated yeah you know and there's a little
of that in the first alien movie where she's the only woman and and all that stuff so there's
always and then also too the alien goes down your throat and comes out your stomach and impregnates
you and all that stuff there's always a bit of a sexual thing going on but and they always they
love to make these aliens look like vaginas and dicks oh yeah they love it that's Giger's
that's Giger's jaunt man he loves that shit you know the predator the mouth yeah you know it's
always very much yeah definitely not a a situation I would like to take some pants down and see the
predator but you can also make the connection of what they were going for there yes um but I
I did very much enjoy uh Covenant on on upon rewatch I would place it
and and without consideration of Romulus uh because I don't want to give away our take but um
uh I would place it uh I don't know third I would go alien aliens Covenant three four and Prometheus
to me I don't give a shit like yeah Prometheus just serves a setup for Covenant three is it's
just a like you said it's a it's a vision but it's a fucking snooze the the original version
of that script has been released as an audio drama which featured the characters from alien
and made a hundred percent more sense and of course they just didn't do it for whatever reason
and then four is just you know cash grab four is a goddamn mess um but that's where I'd rank them
okay you got um well another 90s movie that looks like a sitcom
that feels like a sitcom and that stars Andy McDowell and that movie is The Muse with Albert
Brooks um I will say there's plenty of solid chuckles in it Albert Brooks is rarely going
to give you a movie without some solid chuckles in it he's one of the great joke writers of all time
whenever I watch one of his movies I realize that comedically for me there may have been no
greater influence in terms of just like how I think about a joke um he's it's always an
unexpected you know punch to the stomach of a punch line I love the man um and he was one
of the first people where I kind of was along for the full career like well his early stuff
was in the 70s I missed that but I watched it on video growing up and then Defending Your Life
that was a big movie the parents and kids watched together I feel like a lot of families love that
um and it's just great you know it's almost like a deeper Woody Allen I loved when his comedy
started getting into bigger and bigger subject matter um until around this time The Muse looking
for comedy in the Muslim world in particular etc uh they just start feeling like his heart is not
in them as much and Albert Brooks is such a great chronicler of men and women
and their their issues with each other that sometimes when he goes off into other subjects
I find the stories lack enough of a backbone to keep going you know like he's not a plot guy
to a fault all his movies are 85 minutes which is great but like Lost in America to me is a movie
that doesn't end it just kind of like here come the credits um and he struggles with that a little
bit so The Muse when the subject matter is just you know a guy who now has writer's block hears
about a woman who inspires you to write better so he starts hanging out with her uh but she's kind
of a fraud I guess that's sort of an interesting premise it just it never kicks in you know you're
it never goes into that next gear um Sharon Stone is not funny so that's kind of a problem
I do love Albert Brooks I love him with Andy McDowell they have a great chemistry
Andy McDowell played off all of our great comedians in the 90s which is really weird
but she does bring out something great in Cranky Old Guys for sure I'm surprised if I could
interject I'm surprised at your Andy McDowell praise today in both movies you've mentioned her
I find her to be just a hole on the screen like I think she she's flat the entire time
she just doesn't do anything well she stands there and delivers lines and I'm just like she's so
boring and then I go I wish this was Mary Steenburgen I hear that she never got these parts
for whatever reason um but Andy McDowell who power walks through my neighborhood every day
so maybe I've I've warmed up to her a little bit because I see her at her most vulnerable
through my window like a creep but um Andy McDowell what I'm saying is she brings out
something great in Cranky Old Comedians Bill Murray and Groundhog Day Mike Keaton and Multiplicity
Albert Brooks there's just like they seem smitten with her and their performances become good I
feel like uh she's not an electric performer by any means but I don't know I like her more the
older I get my dad used to say he would leave my mom for Andy McDowell he would say that often
it's a nice thing we were we were all like you don't have to keep saying that dad um I used to
think she was awful my I had a joke that was um what do Andy McDowell and my uncle Gary have in
they both ruined four weddings and a funeral um I remember but I've I've changed I've changed my
take I find her sort of charming the movie the muse is just not quite sharp enough if you're
going to do another Hollywood satire and you're Albert Brooks you want it to crush and it just
never quite crushes despite having some great bits laughs moments but the muse to me was
the beginning of the decline mother is now getting a criterion release which is very exciting
um but mother too feels sort of like a sitcom you know I love mother I love mother because I
do too it was so accurate to my relationship with my mother that I was like this is what I love
when Albert Brooks is this insightful I also think uh actually let me look this up go ahead I'm sorry
I don't want to well yeah I mean that's just what I'm saying his when his target is too general like
the entertainment industry that's when I find he's at sea a little bit when his target is a
mother's love or jealousy or you know uh the need in lost in America to like drop out of society
then great I love them with kind of meteor subjects then again I sure didn't like comedy
in the Muslim world so um a legend I love the guy and then the other one the third one was Mrs.
Doubtfire uh as I texted Joe you know something like frankly this man had plenty of other options
to see these children when you watch it as an adult you realize he just didn't have to to do all
this um it's it's an insane movie it's weirdly it's so much crazier than Tootsie it's the same
thing but the reasoning is absolute madness the reasoning in Tootsie has only become more
progression and of the of its time you know that that somebody would do such a thing would dress
as a woman because he'd have a better chance getting a part that that's almost a movie that
would be made today to me um this is Doubtfire I hated it from day one I saw it in the theater
I can't stand the movie I feel like it's the problem with with with many Robin Williams movies
it's the version of the thing that has nothing to say Tootsie has a point there's a commentary
the character learns about right gender relations and and his own selfishness and and what women
go through and and it's it's got an edge a guy is going to dress up as a woman because a man
he as a man he can't get high there's a point Mrs Doubtfire is just watch this guy do a zany
thing to be with his kids it's like who gives a shit that's not enough like I don't care it's
not enough like you can you know and any dad would go well you don't have kids so you don't get it
it's like okay fine but it's it's it's like saying like I don't know if any dad many many dads would
you know but that to me is not enough for uh there's got to be more to it than that but yeah
one of your buddies is pulling on a pair of tights he's like listen bro until you've had kids
if you wouldn't get it um the movie look it's not without its charms I remember
I went to see Mrs Doubtfire on opening night it was sold out me and my buddy saw a perfect world
instead with Clint Eastwood and Kevin Costner probably the most underrated movie in in the
both men I fucking loved it but you could hear and feel the walls of our theater being rocked
by the waves of laughter coming from Mrs Doubtfire as we watched this very somber depressing movie
and I was so jealous and look I saw it two three times in the theater when I was a kid I was like
oh my god this is so funny it's great it's kind of not you know like at the end the big farce scene
you feel like any Frasier writer could have done a better job you know like he's running into the
bathroom to change in and out of a full old lady fat suit while having a business meeting with his
boss the drunk Robert Prosky and Prosky keeps making him drink which is kind of funny but like
clearly the I guarantee the studio was like if we're going to believe anybody's this stupid they
have to get real drunk because it it suspends your believability too much I love a far scene
I love a door slamming everybody running in and out kind of thing I really do but so much about it
in this movie doesn't make sense in a way that farce has to make sense or it falls apart
so like when he sits down across from Robert Prosky dressed as the old lady you get kind of
shock laugh when he realizes it's it's also the same exact scene as when Sidney Pollock is like
I begged you to get help you know it's the exact same scene but Robin Williams would never do this
he would say to his boss who's there drunk with other men having fun hey you know what a family
matter has come up I gotta go handle this and when it's that easy to get out of these situations
the comedy dies to me yeah yeah you have to work at it and that's what's so frustrating about
comedy executives is they don't get how hard that is how hard it is to to pull that high
wire act of making you care about a scene that that dumb and I don't think Miss Doubtfire does
it I think a lot of us were just laughing at Robin Williams in a dress back in the day doing the funny
voice but also by the way it's also by the way much more forgivable when you're in season nine
of Frazier yeah of the ninth 24 episode season and they're they're doing a dinner party farce
episode or something and you it's more forgivable to go why wouldn't Frazier just say I can't do
this to sure like they got to fill they're like they got to fill episodes here with a movie it
really is glaring I got I hated that fucking joke from the minute I saw it it was a run by
fruiting fruiting oh my god terrible probably improvised on set one of the most famous jokes
I won I won a nice bet off my buddy Dave King very funny comedy writer that it was a jog by
fruiting he insisted it was jog by and I would have gone 10 ,000 if he had if he had bet I would
have gone to the ends of time I was so convinced and I was right but Mrs. Doubtfire it's look it's
fun Robin Williams didn't have a lot of really great movies he's he's awesome in this in a lot
of ways yeah he's so committed he's so good Brosnan's a good foil Sally Field's a good wife
everything's kind of hitting I just wish it was a little bit tighter and that martin mull wasn't
in it he popped up and scared me like Jason and Friday the 13th forgot he was involved
um all right um shall we let's do it um yeah Joe you're gonna have to handle the the plot
because I was I was dimming like uh when you know when you're falling asleep on the drive home
I saw this at a 12 noon screening alert chock full of coffee excited to see it in IMAX and I
found the first hour of this movie so fucking dull that I couldn't really tell you what even
was going on Joe uh it takes place 10 years after the first alien movie pre aliens um it
is about a group of young people I guess 21 ish uh they all of them to all of them near children
none of them with a personality and what I was saying to my I'm sorry I'm immediately
interrupting you and then I'll stop but like they these kids like look at aliens James Cameron
James Cameron is not a master of um you know character and dialogue and those things he's
he's a he's too blunt like like Lucas or something but he's such a craftsman that you kind of look
the other way at times or I do anyway um but in that movie very casually in 1986 the crew is
completely diverse even though we pretend that diversity is a brand new thought the crew is not
only diverse but everyone has very specific personalities and traits that are apparent
the moment you lay eyes on them you got Bill Paxton is like the fourth lead in the thing
he's just some like hick in the movie everybody has their their role and the same goes for alien
one you spend a lot of time with these people you get to know them and love them this movie
just doesn't have the time it's some it's a two -hour movie that gives you zero character
development um I would disagree as far as the main character is concerned and her brother who is an
android but he that the kid I think his name is David Johnson yeah kid that plays the robot in
deserves a fucking Oscar he was amazing I was good this kid is so good so I watched the
red letter media review of this and Mike from red letter media said something that I 100 agreed with
he said I started watching this and I thought this movie is the greatest movie this is so awesome
and then there was a turn where I was like this is the worst movie I've ever seen something along
those lines and I really agreed with that take I did find the opening 40 minutes whatever it was
very interesting I liked seeing the mining planet I liked seeing you know the shit that humanity is
now living in uh -huh and why these space explorations and this corporation is trying to
expand outward into space I like seeing how awful people have it back on whatever planet they're on
uh I bought the stakes I was like okay these guys are desperate they're kids they're gonna do this
heist where they're gonna go up to this defunct space station they're gonna steal fuel so they can
finally escape this planet and travel whatever where this planet where they're essentially
enslaved I thought all that was really interesting and I gave a shit about this main character and
her brother um they get onto the space station and as you can imagine something will be afoot
on the space station and the aliens will appear which is what happens um you find out once they
get on there well you learn all that you learn what the the purpose of that space station was
because once they get on that station there is another android that they reboot that android
is ian home uh who played the android the first alien now ian home is dead so they do a deep fake
whatever this is where you start to realize we got problems they pull the android up they've
got him shadowed and you can kind of see that it's ian home and you're like okay this is cool
they're gonna keep him shadowed you're realizing oh my god that's the android from the first movie
all right cool then of course they light it up like an episode of the golden girls
full close -ups on ian home's deep faked folks it looks so bad yeah
when i am doing my nightly instagram reel scroll watching some tiktoks i have completely fallen
for such videos as like john goodman break dancing at his fattest and i've been like
holy shit and then just realized i've been totally fooled probably made by some guy literally on
microsoft paint on his family computer how in an otherwise beautiful looking movie beautiful and
imax i must say alien romulus how did this slide we spend 10 minutes tight on the face of some of
the worst special effects i've seen it's like as if the irishman instead of doing the the stomping
which did look bad from far away it's as if we're suddenly tight on deniro's fake face for like
minutes it's very odd it's odd very odd choice and up until that point you know there's a sequence
where they're approaching the space station it looked majestic and i was like and i thought to
in the theater i go finally finally a popcorn movie that looks like a popcorn movie again
in the theater like this looks like a big budget well -produced movie and then you get to this deep
fake and you're like oh my god so it is then you'd have to think maybe there would have been a
discussion like guys let's let's throw another million dollars at this another million dollars
and another three weeks of work i don't know i can tell you i can tell you exactly i i would
bet my bank account that this is what happened that alien was not ian home or i'm sorry that
android was not ian home probably and then in the 11th hour they're like let's make it ian home
yeah and then you got problems and here's why i think that he's not the same android
he's just an android he's the same model right so already now you're confused you're like wait he's
not the leftover android from the first one so wait then why the fuck is it ian home like why
yeah that wasn't some big established thing that all the androids look alike or whatever
like that i can remember um in in in the ridley scott prequels it made sense because
he david was the first so it would make sense that shortly thereafter another android would
look just like david right in in in alien it's years and years and years later it's like
i don't know so that was confusing the android then goes on to explain that there are you know
they were on a mission to save human life and that they were collecting these specimens from
the perfect organisms around the galaxy the perfect organism is the xenomorph that's where
they reintroduced the black goo from prometheus and the stuff that that david and covenant uses
to kill the uh planting race of of super beings so you know that the black if you've seen those
movies you know the black goo is bad um but in this the characters don't know it's bad and and
ian home is saying it's it's it's it's basically a cure -all it'll it'll make you a perfect person
and make you live a hundred years longer and all that crap and it's a lie uh where did they get
the black goo from well it was extracted from these xenomorphs so you know that they're on
some things on the ship there's no xenomorph from the ship there's just face huggers on the ship
which they reveal in a very long sequence that there's dozens of face huggers which all to me
looked like i mean god bless practical effects but these fucking things looked like they went
and bought them at halloween adventure and then like tied them to a stick yeah i read after the
fact that this used practical effects which i was like all right cool um the xenomorphs infect some
of the crew i'm sorry the face huggers infect some of the crew the xenomorphs break out and then we
gotta fight and that's basically your plot um the and then they also at the beginning of the movie
declare that this space station is going to crash into the planet it's hovering above in 36 hours
so it's pretty blatant foreshadowing so i thought well that's kind of cool
the final fight will be on a crashing space station that'll be exciting right that's not at
all what they do um the space station crashing serves zero purpose other than it will destroy
any evidence of this research they were doing i guess but if this research is so important
why the fuck does the corporation not care about this defunct space station where it's all sitting
and what so this is where all the plot holes start and it just starts to get dumb the first
act of this movie looks and plays a lot like the original alien the second act shifts into
an attempt to do james cameron's kind of style and then the third act they do their own thing
which to me the the most successful act was the third act it sounds like we disagree
i was bored at first then in act two i was like all right i guess we were doing a real slow burn
here but now we're kind of moving and then the third act even though i can't necessarily agree
with all the choices made i liked that i was seeing something crazy and fresh and new and
that also felt like fetty alvarez who while not one of my favorites i do like the energy and
insanity that he brings to his kill scenes and his you know like i'm talking evil dead i'm talking
don't breathe with the cum and the baster you know he has a way of creating like really memorable
crazy shit and i felt like he held that from us until the very end
i thought the third act so so listen we don't have to take you beat by beat of every encounter they
have with the aliens but but the short synopsis of it is or summation of it is
first of all they show you in the trailer almost everybody that dies so you there's really no
surprises there the kills from the alien are all boring because we've seen all of them before
there's nothing left to do with this we've seen it it's it it's over like really the second mouth
coming out was kind of like the big innovation that was the big alien 3 trailer and um yeah it's
lost its power to shock for sure none of it is shocking the chest bursts aren't shocking anymore
none of this is interesting uh and in the third act oh god leading into the third act mind you
they have this wonderful android character throughout the movie has been impeccable
when he kills the xenomorph and you're under the assumption it's the final kill he does it to save
his sister and says to the alien get away from her you bitch and it's a terrible clumsy callback
to laughs laughs and claps in the theater i i almost walked out and i usually don't let that
stuff get to me but i was like why are you giving this line to the android character if you're gonna
do it not the one character who wouldn't do this who wouldn't make some stupid quip referencing a
movie that he couldn't have seen it's just lazy it's it's what they did in the second expendables
when they started giving everybody their big lines and they just were there so they could say them
they didn't have any relevance to anything yeah um the third act then you think it's all over and
as i said earlier every alien movie now has to be we thought it was done but there's actually
something else on the ship sure the something else on the ship in this one is a pregnant crew
member injects herself with the black goo because she believes it is life -saving because she's dying
and of course it's not she's been tricked and you find out the purpose of the black goo is to not
save life it is to i don't even fucking know cause people to give birth to
it hybrid beings that are half xenomorph half human and she gives birth to this thing
that immediately grows into a seven foot tall one of the strangest character designs i have
ever seen in a film almost felt like they forgot to here's what it felt like they showed the
prototype of it to the director and he was like do no more this is so creepy i love it and they're
like no this is just the bare bones we need to still make it creepy and like flesh it out and
give it color and he's like no no no this is perfect because it feels undone it does feel
disturbing sort of um but yeah it was nuts it really was nuts well it looks exactly like
um if you saw the tim burton charlie and the chocolate factory i did there's that scene at
the end or towards the end when all the kids that got you know because god forbid the kids met their
doom they have to show that they all lived and the one kid that got like stretched out or whatever
the fuck happens he walks out at the end of the factory and he's all like tall and lanky and
it looked like that it looked like a weird version of gumby um it looked fucking stupid
the concept to me of the cat of the monster was fucking stupid yeah and then they fight that thing
with the series the giving birth to the alien is not stupid i like that idea
well that was kind of cool because i was like oh this is like a new version of the face hugger
then it turns into this stupid fucking thing you're like which i mean it's a new version
of the chest burst excuse me but then it turns into this dumb it's i don't know man
and then they kill it and then the space station crashes but they're off of it so it doesn't even
matter and by the way all of a sudden they go space station you know the the voice of the ship
comes on and it goes space station crashing in t minus 12 minutes you're like wait a minute it's
been 36 hours like they just got there like this i thought this was like three hours had passed
yeah like they do nothing to show time lapsing right they do nothing to show hey nobody's had
or drink in in in well over a full day yeah they find guns at one point and they're like i guess
they're the guns from aliens and they're gonna they're like great we can shoot the xenomorphs
then and then the android's like no you can't you'll the the acid for blood it'll burn through
the ship and open up the bottom of the ship into space and then they figure out a dumb anti -gravity
plot device so they can shoot the things but then the blood's floating but then you're like but yeah
but you already established that the gravity is going to shut off again and it's still going to
be the same problem the whole thing just was fucking dumb it was just callbacks the yeah the
they literally did a lot of the same exact scenes um you know like everybody caught in the walls was
right out of aliens when they stumble upon that like layer um there there was a lot of that a lot
callbacks a lot of nods which is fine i guess until until get away from her you bitch i was
kind of fine with everything but and and what i really liked was the turning off the gravity
bit i thought okay this is a nice set piece i have this feels fresh to me i haven't seen this before
but what you're saying there joe then when the acid is floating through the air again cool okay
we're building we got more obstacles but when they turn it back off and all the acid crashes into the
ship then why does it not destroy the ship like we were all warned it was going to do it it does
but it just does in a way where you don't give a shit and it looked to me like it just went through
a grate like down and i was like oh okay i guess that wasn't that big a deal it has it just has no
real purpose and then and then the way they kill this hybrid thing at the end if i remember
correctly it's not even related to maybe i might be misremembering forgive me if i am but if i
remember it's not even related to the whole being burned in the bottom it sort of is but then it's
like they set it on fire i don't fucking know it was just it was just this junk pile of callbacks
to the franchise of cheap nods to things and then new shit they tried to shove into it
that didn't work alongside everything else it reeked to me of studio notes it just reeked to
me of tons of studio notes and too many cooks look they've been trying to make this fucking
alien movie with with different people for 10 years yeah you know they were going to do it with
the guy that did district nine right right then ridley came back and he was going to do his three
and then fetty came in and i think noah holly was going to do an alien movie that became the show
but um yeah it doesn't quite work i don't know if it's been successful and i'm not sure if it's
been successful enough to start its own little franchise to me i would really hope they dump
cali splanny or whatever her name is i i just i got nothing from her character here i think
its weaknesses in its total lack of interest in its own characters to me i think especially if
you look at those first two it's its focus on character is what makes those movies pop
so it makes you care throughout the running time um these guys were all sort of the same age the
vibe it's like they don't even take the time anymore to go like here's the fat one here's
the butch one here's the the sensitive one you just get six people that seem to have no real
traits um that does help to make the ai character pop he is great that's a really great performance
he's the pop -out standout character but it's not enough for me i liked aspects of it it looked
cool and i max but not a great movie by any means no um i as of now the movie has grossed
113 million off an 80 million dollar budget it's sort of teetering right in that area of
there could be a sequel but these days that's probably not enough money no uh you know i'm
it reeked of you know first of all disney's got its fucking umbrella over this too so you know
this to me this felt like a hulu movie it felt exactly like prey which was the predator version
of this and it felt exactly like the hellraiser version of this which is to say you're kind of
getting the vibe right but it's also like why are we here why are we doing this um and they all
to me had that same sort of look that same sort of vibe that same kind of playing it too safe
feel um that has to be a disney influence because you can just smell it all the product starts to
look the same i thought fetty you know did a decent enough job with the evil dead remake i
really like that upon initial watch upon revisits i find it a little flat but it's it's decent uh
don't breathe i was not a big fan of pat was liked up girl in the spider's web was his third
movie uh it was essentially a bomb i have no idea if it's good um don't breathe too he didn't direct
but you know it was whatever uh it was fine texas chainsaw massacre terrible he did not write or
he wrote the story and now alien romulus i'm a little i'm a little on the fence about
fetty uh but we'll see um you know i think he's got promise but uh i don't think i don't know
i think this this felt a lot like what he did with evil dead because evil dead was was similar
it was it was the same plot it had callbacks to the originals
but it all kind of had its own place and made sense uh for better or for worse and and this just
didn't do any of that so my hog is blastedly down for alien romulus uh you know like so down it
into one of the eggs that the facehuggers are inside of i mean mine's i think maybe mine's a
little higher than yours but it is still down folks we'll be back in september probably with
maxine we're just waiting for the price the rental price on that to drop uh so everybody
can hopefully watch it affordably uh possibly the fall guy i know we keep teasing it but uh
but there's a lot of good stuff coming out immaculate on hulu has been discussed yeah
yeah so we'll be back with some good stuff uh in the meantime please come see me at steel city
for the warm -up shows for the special september 10th and 12th phoenixville pa uh and then
summerville massachusetts at the crystal ballroom in december go to joe de rosa dot com for tickets
also many tour dates for the joystick tour which launches in january of 2025 uh have been
announced please get your tickets please come on out to see me i will be i just want to plug the
cities if i may uh i will be coming to starting in january toronto fort worth texas san diego
tampa florida stamford connecticut and timonium uh maryland so uh come on out hope to see you
thank you all we are at see you in hell pot on instagram tell your friends about our patreon
we thank you for your support we will see you next time and we will see you in hell