Hello folks, welcome to another episode of We'll See You in Hell, the podcast brought
to you by the Fangoria Podcast Network for more info about the network, including this
program and other programs, how to follow our show and other shows and finding episodes
of every show, not every show in history, but the ones on this network, please visit
fangoria .com. And now here we are. We'll see you in hell. My cohost, Pat Walsh. Hello.
In full stereo new format. Yeah. For those of you that haven't heard, you want to explain
it to him? Absolutely. Each week we're not, we're no longer tied to a movie. We were
finding that listening to ourselves talk for, in the case of the shining, for example, two
and a half hours was pushing it. It was pushing even our interest in what we had to say. Um,
so we're switching it up. We're doing, uh, sins, which keeps, allows us to keep the title.
We'll see you in hell. And each week the loose headline of the podcast is a different sin.
We're going to do the seven deadlies up first, then get to your more minor sins. We've done,
uh, help me out, Joe. We did anger rage. We did. Wrath was the last episode and before
wrath was gluttony. And now this one today is lust. Today we're going to talk about lust.
Lust. When you, when you want to get your fuck going. The interesting thing about these
deadly sins is that they are all things everyone does pretty much every day. It is true. You
know, like how bad can they really be? Are we really putting murder up with fucking gluttony?
Well, that's not an every day. Yeah. Murder is also not one of the deadlies. Yeah. One
of the deadlies. I guess they're saying that these are the sins that lead you to, I will
say this. I'm not a religious man, but I will say the seven deadlies are a pretty good code
or idea of whether or not you're going to be leading a happy life. Exactly. I grapple with
these sins every day and I lead a pretty profoundly unhappy life. Yeah. But, uh, I also feel
generally okay. I'm not really depressed or miserable or anything else. I just always find myself,
you know, a little raw around the edges and I think it keeps me alive basically, you know?
I feel as if I'm drifting into some sort of Hunter S. Thompson cavern dungeon at this point. I
remember watching a documentary about him where they said he just kept doing more and more drugs
to try to get to this magical place of creativity and he never did. He was just so fucked up he
couldn't write properly. I feel like maybe that's sort of the road I'm headed on. Okay.
Where eventually they're going to go, did you go to that show the other night, man? What is he
doing, man? He's up there with a. Well, the hope is that people will tell you when you hit that
point and then you do 50 percent as much. And then you say, fuck you. I don't know. You're not my
fucking mother. That's more like what you would do. Yeah. And then you keep going. Yeah. Lust is
for me. I think one of the lately has been one of the more easily controllable
sins because Prozac Prozac evened out my libido a bit. OK, it kind of made me have just a normal
sex drive instead of like the sex drive of an addict where I'm jerking off twice a day and sure
thinking about sex constantly. I wouldn't make an addict. I guess. Hello, my name is Patrick Walsh.
But I'm now I'm now I masturbate a few times a week. That's it. Yeah. We're literally the
the cliche. Like what's the podcast? You talk about how many times you jerk off in a week. Yeah,
actually it is. I masturbate a few times a week. I'll tell you, I'm dating a girl. I can take it
or leave it. We have some sex. Fine. We don't. I don't. I don't care. Half the time I'm too
tired from that hoagie I just did. Well, that is it's a healthier place to be. I think what
they're saying with the deadly sins is you don't let it overtake your life. You don't let food
drug sex anger overtake your life. And these things are always in danger of overtaking my life.
And I would imagine yours as well. But I'm always like, whoa, whoa, whoa. And I'm glad that I was
raised with some sort of moral code to rein me in now sex. I'm in a relationship and, you know,
I'm not going to get too deep into my relationship, but I'm in the kind of relationship where I can
truly have sex whenever I want. I'm not in the everybody loves Raymond thing where, you know,
it's like, not tonight, honey, I can have sex whenever I want. Is there anything sadder than
on that show watching him like grovel for the sex? Well, it makes me really sad when you grow up
watching only those shows, married with children and on and on. You think that's what it is.
And maybe it is once you get married. I don't know. I guess in her case, she wanted to have sex and
he didn't, which was the flip and married with children. It is funny on married with children
how disgusted by the idea. And how hot she is. Yeah. How slubby he is. Yeah. She's 10 times more
attractive than he is. And maybe the worst example. Yeah. And he's just disgusted by it.
Yeah, that is it does make me laugh. But yeah. Well, where does lust fall? You said these sins
threaten potentially taking over your life. Where does lust fall in the in the ranking?
You got seven. Well, it's less on the list. It's a minor one for me, except, you know, like
where lust would threaten to overtake my life as if I was always out trying to cheat, which is not
something I am doing. Unless you're talking about your diet, am I right, Patty? Yeah, sure.
Folks. Folks. These are the jokes. But where it has in the past, like let's look at a time when
I'm single, because I feel like I have a extremely healthy, satisfying sex life with a person I love
who I've been with for a long time. All right. We get it. She might listen to this. She doesn't listen
to it. All right. But sure. Like now she's out of town for a week. Where lust comes into play for
me is I resort back to my single days where, Joe, I can lose an eight hour day with the jerking off.
Now, that's not something that flares up often, but I can get into this thing where it's like,
let's look at this porn site. Now I'm now I'm deep in this. Then you click on one and sometimes it
doesn't take you to the video. It opens up another point. So you're familiar with that. Of course.
Then you're like, oh, what? I've never seen these clips before. They call it rubber banding.
Yeah. Then you're down there. They don't call it that. It sounds like they should. Right.
Yeah. Rubber banding. I would buy that. All right. And I can lose a whole day. And, you know,
maybe you pop off eight times. Maybe you pop off once at the end of eight hours.
But at the end of the day, I look at myself like, holy Lord, what have I done? What have I become?
I try to avoid porn, you know, but once you start slippery slope.
Aaron Patrice O 'Neill used to have a joke about, like, like porn in cyberspace and saying, like,
he like sub clicks so many times that if he was an actual space, he wouldn't know how to get back to
his ship at that point. Like, yeah, exactly. He had gone so far into orbit. And it's like,
I've been there where you're just like, you're like, oh, God damn it. I want this to be a movie.
Why is it another Web site? Well, this is interesting. This site does offer some other
things. I've I've had a point of contention with something that took place in the show Love.
OK, I love love. I like it's kind of divisive show, but I really loved it. I like it quite a bit.
But there's that scene in the first episode where the two sisters try to have sex with him
and he's disgusted by it. Yeah. I was watching it with a friend of mine. I said,
the fuck's wrong with this kid? That's awesome. And she was like, you're disgusting. And I was
like, well, I don't know. Am I? Because this show is portraying it like it's a seemingly normal
thing. I talked to somebody whose issue with that scene was that he was look and God forbid,
he used to be my neighbor. I've met him. He's the nicest guy. Paul Ross seems like a nice kid,
but he is off the charts nice. But this person was like two attractive young girls in their
underwear are going to have sex with this guy. That's what I'm supposed to believe. That was
their issue. Well, I would say he falls in love with Jillian Jacobs, you know, like that is
something that that can be a difficult obstacle. I imagine for women, it's even harder to overcome
that obstacle on a show because you're always seeing hot girl average. I will. I will say this.
I have you never see it the other way. I have one or two friends that have lucked out into
threesomes here and there. And it's it's stories like that. They weren't sisters, but it's stories
like that where it's like, what is what is a porno movie? Yeah. And it's not it's not the good
looking chiseled guys. It's always like the nerdy whatever guys, because I think certain girls find
a real attraction and a safety in that we can feel comfortable with this guy. We know he's not a
freak. Yeah. He's probably not a womanizer. Sure. So that's what made me find that scene
believable. But it's also like, oh, this is your show. So you get to write yourself into this
scene. But but back to the lust aspect of it, I mean, I was like, that's
I mean, that's a that's a that's a grand slam. This guy just should have hit. And other people
were like, that's disgusting. Yeah. I'll comment more on that after the show in case my girlfriend
does decide to listen this week. Well, I said to my friend, I said, look, I don't have siblings.
So maybe I'm just unable to put it in any sort of real perspective. To me, it's just these two hot
girls want to have sex with him. Right. And it's really freaky. Yeah. No, I just meant the area
you were talking about. I have some knowledge and could could discuss. Well, clearly,
clearly, it's not good what you're going to say because you need to say it off the air.
Clearly, we're not going to stop recording and you go, Joe, that's disgusting. No, no, no, no.
I already feel like I've said too much. All right. Move past it.
Um, what are your big issues with lost on a day to day base? You know what? Let me let me quickly.
When I was driving over here, there was an American apparel ad. Usually those girls are too
strung out looking heroin looking. It's not for me. It's all part of the appeal. Yeah. They had kind
of a thicker girl sort of pulling on a pair of pants. She was in underwear and a bra or something.
And I almost wrecked my car. I came very, very close to wreck my car. I had to slam the brakes
on. I was staring at it. And, uh, that sort of thing, especially in LA, especially if you drive
down like sunset or, uh, you know, that toll area, sunset strip, you can see things where I'm like,
if I had kids, I wouldn't, I didn't see things like this. So I was 10 years old. I would be
terrified to drive my kids down this place where you're seeing basically people fucking on the
side of the road. And when that is around you at all times, I think that that fucks with guys in
particular, because you start looking, if you look at your whole life only at porn star bodies,
stripper bodies, uh, model bodies, uh, you know, you're looking at all these different sites,
you're looking at all these different billboards, all these different commercials. When you see an
female body in person, very rarely is it that, uh, and if you have never seen it, it might not be
cool to you because you've only seen these other things. I think that's what's ruining
people. And I think it's going to really funk up some minds that are coming up now.
Well, it is, it is a lot of access. Uh, you know, I hate that every episode I go,
talking about something similar in my act, but I am, but I have a thing in my act right now,
but the internet and I'm just like, I don't want to be able to jerk off to anything I think of
instantly. That's not like a healthy thing. Like porn, the whole premise of the bit is like porn
anal used to be this event and porn, like as it should be a woman shoving something up her
asshole for you on camera. And now it's just like run of the mill. You just take it for granted
because there's so much of it out there and it's so competitive because it's all free, illegally
free by the way. Right. And it's ruined it. It's like, there's no, like we have no appreciation
for the risk these women are taking. And for the position they're, I mean, it truly is a gigantic
sacrifice. And we're just like, yeah, of course. No, that's what you do. Yeah. It's like, no,
that's not what you do. These are like evil, can evil level, fucking stunt show people. And
they're getting zero credit for it. We don't even let them be in like real money for him.
Very little money. We don't let them be in like real TV shows and shit. Once in a while,
somebody creeps through like Sasha Grey or run Jeremy creeps right back out. Cause we never saw
her after that movie. Yeah. It's like that, you know, it's, it's kind of bullshit, man, but it is
bullshit. It's it's, we don't treat them very well, but I'll tell you my, my lust struggle,
if you will, uh, is that I'll see a woman, uh, that, you know, it could just be an average woman
that I wouldn't look twice at, not out of any disrespect, but just like,
she's a very, very regular person that you would see on a very regular basis anywhere in your life
or throughout your day. I'll see a woman like that. And the tiniest thing I beat a diner or
something, the tiniest thing will light the fuse for me. And, and I'm talking like her shoulder
muscle, just the tiniest fucking thing. And then I can't think about anything else for days.
Like I'll just for days be like, why anything but that particular girl or like I have to have
something. It'll go from here's a girl that I could take her leave to three days later.
Why didn't I get that girl's number? She's the hottest thing I ever saw. I'm a fucking idiot.
That was probably my wife. Like, I mean, I go, I get like nuts about it. But you do go up and talk
girls way more than most. Uh, I'm not shy in my old age. I will say that, which I like about myself.
Yeah. Uh, you know, I try not to be sleazy about it, but I do try to talk to girls that, uh,
that interests me, but you don't talk to all of them. Sometimes you just can't. I saw a girl
the other night, a good luck bar. I was dying to talk to her, but she was with four other girls.
And I'm like, I'm not going to be the guy that walks up to the table of girls. That's when you're
company. Yeah. I've never once done that. Yeah. I was like, there's no fucking way I'm doing that.
I've almost never walked up and cold talk to a girl. There's always been an intro or if the
girl stares at me for 10 minutes, maybe I'll go over and I can only assure you that doesn't happen
often. If you can get that smile and nod out of them. Yeah. If you make eye contact, then it's
a lot easier. Right. Sometimes I'll send a drink. I've done that many times. I'll send a drink on
over. Yeah. With an almost apologetic explanation from the bartender. Yeah. You know,
because I mean, I've often, I've often said, uh, I could have my hands on a girl's bare breasts
and still need a mutual friend to tell me that she likes me before proceeding with it,
which I regret looking back on my single days because I, I can't tell you what a coward I was
for really my entire life. You know, like my girlfriend now approached me, like that's kind
of what I needed because I don't know if it's self -esteem or what, but you just don't, uh,
I would never act on my lust, which I feel like might've been a mistake looking back.
I don't think it's a mistake. Why not? Especially in LA people, like you forget,
and honestly it might be growing up with everybody loves Raymond, which not even a show I watched.
Um, but like all these different shows about men want sex, women don't want it. And you forget that
women definitely want sex and they're looking for it. Um, and it's easy to assume that they don't
and that you're bothering them every time you go up to speak to them, which are in some cases you
are, but more often than not, they're like, Hey, cool. Hello. Maybe you're not going to have sex
with them, but people are always up to talk. Well, people want to be social. Girls get horny,
just like the boys do. Uh, the, uh, well I say, I don't think it's a mistake to act on or to not
act on your lust. I mean, they're definitely wrong. There are wrong ways to act on it,
obviously, but I'm saying like in a healthy mutual agreeable engagement, whatever, you know,
sometimes that can be really fun. Sometimes the other person just wants to have a quick
session with you too. And it's, it's, it's one and done and you're both happy. Sometimes it can back
fire where you think you, but the times it causes me problems is when I think I really like somebody
and then I find out after we have sex, it was just lust the whole time. That sucks because I,
I honestly have no way of knowing that in my brain. I just think like, no, of course I like this girl.
She's great. Yeah. And, uh, that's why I think it's really dangerous to not have sex till you get
married. Sure. Couples that do that. I'm like, my God, what if you, the second you bust the nut
on that honeymoon, you just realized you were in a three year lust binge. Yeah. And you're like,
I, I hate this person. I have always had sort of an issue having sex outside of a relationship
or at least dating because of the way I was raised, which was wait until you're married.
Right. So I'm opening the door. Oh, sorry. I'm just opening the front door. You know,
for the lust podcast, you're going to open the door so everyone can hear us. Well,
because here's why the first time we did this with the door open, we said we had to shut it
because we thought it was going to be too loud. Like you couldn't hear anything. That's true.
And, uh, secondly, I'm hot as balls and all this talk about lust isn't helping.
Uh, I'm sweating and I've also just had enough beer at this point that now I want to get drunk
again tonight. Sure. And I'm ashamed of myself and I don't understand why I feel this way.
Why do I feel this way? That's a different podcast, Joe. I don't think it is. I think
it ties into lust. Well, we talked about this with gluttony. You have a few and you want more.
We have holes in ourselves, Joe, emotional holes. They're not being filled emotionally
in your case and perhaps in my game, the way you want them to be. And you wind up
trying to fill it in other ways. Let's talk about how I want my holes to be filled.
Uh, no, but my dad told me and I bet he would regret this style of parenting now.
Uh, as I said on the drinking one, he said, if you ever have a drink, you'll be an alcoholic
with sex. He was like, a, he told me it is like the feeling when your arm falls asleep,
but you start to get the feeling back and it's that pins and needles feeling across your entire
body, which is the worst feeling in the world. Right. And it sounded like a living nightmare.
So that's an orgasm. He's like, sex is great. You never have sex before marriage. And he told
me about a friend of his who had gotten his girlfriend pregnant just by making out with her
naked and these crazy. And I bet if I asked him about it now, he'd be like, I never said that
when you're 10 years old and your dad's talking about sex, you remember every word verbatim.
That's exactly what he fucking said. And it terrified me from sex and made me think that
who would be willing to have sex prior to marriage has to be some sort of degenerate.
And I felt that way for a very long time. So even now, even when like, I think all that's all
stupid, I don't believe that I don't feel that way anymore. And I know in my heart, I don't.
If in my single days, I would be going to have sex with somebody who I had in my mind just met,
maybe it was date three, or maybe it was, you know, the night we met or something. I couldn't
come to terms with why is this girl willing to have sex on the first night? Right. Don't she do
this a lot? This is this must not be a moral person because of the way I was. Those things
are creeping in. It's not the way I feel in my heart, but they're in the back of my head like,
but Pat, if you're supposed to wait till you're married and this girl wants to have sex on the
first date, I was in that boat too. It really fucks with your mind and makes sex a bad thing.
And the times that I had a casual hookup sex, whatever, I wound up like clinging to that
person. Like, you know, like when they would leave the next day and it would be out, it's what it was
or whatever else. It would make me very sad. And I would often feel like, you know, it was just very
unfulfilling to me. I cannot be one of those guys as like, you know, Pete calls it a fuck guy,
who just like goes bang somebody like that's fun and that was fun and heads out the door.
Not saying I caught feelings either necessarily, but it really messes with your head when you're
raised that way. I was in that boat too. I was raised very Catholic. You know, I thought that
STDs were punishments. Sure. I thought that every action had a negative reaction. So I had a very
crazy. And every time I would have it, I would be wrecked with guilt and fear afterwards and
everything. It took me a long time to get over that. And I hated it because I knew deep down
somewhere it wasn't true. It wasn't real. I knew it was some kind of bullshit psychological baggage.
And I was happy when it finally did go away. But here I am now as a guy at 38, not prone to serious
relationships, not against them, but just haven't been in many. And it's the other end of it where
it's kind of like I made up for lost time and I dated, I date a lot and I have a lot of fun.
And it's always, you know, it's always very great and very respectful. But there is a part of me
now that's like, oh shit, that I did. I go the other way too hard. Am I not going to be able
to settle down? I don't know. But then I think maybe I don't want to settle down. Who the hell
knows? Well, you always can decide to settle down. Of course, they say you'll know when you know,
are you saying you have casual sex a lot and that you'll be always be chasing that?
I don't have casual sex a lot. I date now, but like not very seriously. Sure. I'll hang out
with the same girl for a little while. Right. And for whatever reasons, it doesn't get more serious
usually. I would find which sometimes a lot of times their decision to like, but it's just like,
my point is, is like to me, casual sex is like, oh, you're running with three different girls
every week or whatever. I try not to do that, but like, I don't know, man, my buddy's married.
I have many friends that are married. So this man will remain safely anonymous. But
he called me the other day and he was like, he's like, I've been where you're at,
where you're questioning things. And I've been on the other side of it now. He's like,
I'm telling you, it's better where you're at. Oh, he's like, I'm not saying marriage is
terrible. I'm just saying the wrong person. Well, he's just said this. He goes, he goes,
marriage has its ups and downs as does being single. Yeah. But the downs of marriage are a
lot harder. Sure. But aren't the highs much higher if you have kids and doesn't sound like it to me
for him? Doesn't I don't look. Well, he doesn't speak for everyone. There are people who are in
families who are over the moon, happy with having kids. I have a buddy who I never dreamed would
get married, let alone have a kid sick. And now he he's racing for the phone when we hang out to
call his daughter before bath time. You know, it's a sick thing. This kid's thing. It's sick.
That's you have no interest in it, but there are a lot of people it works for. They're sick in
their head. You exist because of someone. Are you in your second 24 ounce bud? Yeah. And
Yeah. It's impressive, man. Is it? It's it's two beers. It's two 24 ounce beers. So it's four
beers. Well, I'm not. I just opened them. I just I'm impressed. I'm not criticizing you. But you
are. I'm not. I'm saying done with you. We're in the exact same boat. I started about half mine.
All right. I'm not critics. I swear to you, I'm not. I like your style. It happens every week.
I like your style. You're drunk over there every week. I like all over your style. Relax. I like.
I don't want to have kids at all. Marriage seems nice. I do. By the way, I do this so that I can
speak freely and not overanalyze every word I say on the fucking podcast. You know, every every
if we do these on a Monday night, you know, Tuesday morning, I'm always like, hey, do you
think I shouldn't have said this and that and that? Yeah. Whereas I don't care, let alone a
fucking lost podcast. There are people lusting after this podcast. They want more. They just
want to use this for our talk. Danny, a couple of people that you mentioned, I can't do that either.
The amount of guilt that goes on. You know, I had a had a pretty long stretch of being single
prior to my relationship, and I would be dating two girls that I really liked and just feel like
I'm so terrible that I'm doing this and I couldn't commit to either. And I wasn't comfortable in
either. But that's what dating is, especially like in L .A. I was acting like Pat, you're this
cad when the truth is everyone is doing it. And, you know, at least one of the two girls
was definitely dating other people as well. Right. But I went through this whole thing of like,
I can tell she's starting to really like me and I shouldn't be dating this other.
And would be so noncommittal to all involved because of this guilt. Right. That that's how
you wind up pissing people off. Yeah. I've had a lot of the time when I overcompensate to explain
my situation and be protective of the other person's feelings or whatever. That's usually
when they get pissed. Yeah. That's usually like a fuck you. What am I a fucking child? Don't do
this. Right. Who are you to think I'm this concerned? Right. So I just try to run with
it. I try to be honest as I can be. And but don't you think transparent girls are completely rightly
sick of the fucking guy, especially like look at L .A., the comedy scene. How often do you think
these girls that go out with these guys here like, look, I'm not looking for anything serious.
You almost can't say that with a straight face anymore. It has to just seem over the top
cliche. I don't think you need to say that. I think it's a crazy thing to say. Is that what
we're talking about? I think being honest is saying I'm going to this is what I try to do.
I try to hang out with somebody I find interesting. Yeah. And I let it go where it goes.
Right. Nine times out of 10, if it's not going anywhere serious or whatever, it's a very mutual
thing. It's not me going, sorry, I'm not into this. And then the girl's like, what the hell?
Right. There's just a vibe about it. There's a vibe in the air. It's connecting with the right
person. But now I'm not with I'm not trying to be your therapist here. I've known you
two something years. Yeah. I've not known you to be in a serious relationship. I'm not.
I usually am not. That's not something that even interests you. No, it does. I just haven't
met the right person yet. I look at it as it's all I look at it like an alcoholic, you know,
one day at a time. Things happen as they happen. Sometimes you have slips, sometimes you don't.
But the point is, is when it's right, it'll be right. Sure. And and and it'll last. And even
when it does, when it is right, and it does last, there might even be some slips during that period
between the two of you on one side or the other. But when it's right, it'll be right. So I know
when it'll be right. I got good advice from my friend or another friend of mine who's very
happily married. Not the one that said the other thing. Not to say he's not happily married. But
my point is, is this guy sounds like it's not feels quite the opposite. But he said, you know,
the way you he goes, the way I ended up with my wife was I just dated and didn't have any expectations
and didn't limit myself in any way. And eventually there was one person that I wanted to spend more
time with. Right. And that led to me only seeing that one person. And she clearly felt the same way.
And then they got married and they're really happy. So I try to do it like that. I try to just let it
naturally, whatever. And I'm telling you, sometimes a lot of them 10 times out of 10, but nine times
out of 10, when it's going to end, it's a it's very mutual. The system works, at least for me.
You know, nobody's getting hurt or upset. It's just like, yeah, we tried and it didn't whatever.
Who cares? See, I got to say at the extreme risk of coming off. Arrogant, which I am definitely not.
Uh, I found myself when I was single having a lot of situations where
the girl was interested and I was interested and finding myself just kind of saying like
if something would fizzle out or whatever, hey, I'm sorry. You know, I don't think I'm
I'm into this. I don't think I want to continue with this or whatever. And always getting a very
hurt, confused reaction. And I think I would have to ask them, which I have in some cases,
it is because I am nice and I would we would hang out and have a lot like a really,
really good time and laugh a lot and talk a lot. But still I would be like,
no, but this isn't for me romantically. I'm not going to marry this person. And I would tell them
across the board, the reaction would be a pretty real hurt. And it made me feel
scared to even get into these things because I thought, well, maybe these guys who are assholes
are right because then when they go, you know what? I'm done with you. The girl's like, yeah,
that checks out. I would be really nice and fun and laughing and having a great time.
But then if I felt like I wanted to get out, I'd go, hey, I feel like I want to get out.
And the girls were always really hurt by it. I think there are a lot of
play into that. I think one thing is when you were last single, you were in your early thirties.
When I was in my early thirties, I found myself more in that situation, too. I think it's just
a result of a gravitating towards the wrong people. Sure. B, not being able to
express yourself in a healthy way and C, putting out wrong energies.
And I think that when you combine those three things, you successfully combine the three things,
you don't really end up in that position. And when you don't, it can be very complicated.
But when I was that age, I had the same problems. This was a very recent thing where I realized,
just put it out there who you are. Like in any other part of your life, for instance,
when you go to the bank, you don't go out of your way to say, I'm trustworthy
to the person giving you money or giving you a loan or whatever. Or when you see a cop,
you don't go, I swear to God, I don't commit crime. Like you let your energy speak for you.
Right. And it applies the same to dating. I think in terms of the wrong energy going out,
I would be like during this period of dating, at the end of the night, you know, like
be like hugging each other on a street corner and like making out, looking into each other's
eyes and talking and stuff. And then if the girl would stay over or whatever, you know, like
snuggling up to her and et cetera. And then, you know, doing that and then dropping on somebody
that you're not interested in continuing dating. I understand why that's confusing,
but my issue would always be like, well, then am I supposed to be a standoffish dick during the fun
dating part so that you're not surprised when I don't want to go out anymore? You're not supposed
to be anything. I would be loving and kind and funny and joking around and let me take you out
and let's do this. And unfortunately, that creates an environment of I'm safe in this relationship.
When you pull the rug out with certain people, exactly right. Well, I felt like I as an already
guilty person, I would be torn apart by hurting these girls' feelings. Not to me that they're
like, oh, my God, my life's ruined because Pat Walsh doesn't want to fucking date me. I'm not
that at all. I'm just saying that they were like, oh, I thought we were heading in a good
direction or whatever that would have more often than not. And I'm like, well, I don't know how to
avoid that unless it's just being a dick from day one. And I don't want to be that person.
But that's why I've always been better in a relationship because then you're
you don't have to be a dick. You don't have to be overly charming. You just have to be yourself.
And you also have to realize you're not responsible for somebody else's feelings.
You can be respectful of somebody else's feelings, but it's not your fault if they go,
well, I assumed it was this, this and this because you said these things. It's like,
that's not your fault. You're not going out of your way to be like, I love you. And then
crossing your fingers behind your back. You're being yourself with some distance. I was like,
yeah, you weren't saying I love you. I want to spend my life with you or whatever else.
I think just girls are used to assholes. And I think that just simply being nice and showing up
a can make people think like this is a more serious thing than it is. And I always had a
lot of conflict with that. And I know it goes the other way, too. I'm just talking from my
experience from a male perspective, from a male, which you said earlier, you believe is the right
perspective. No, I would never say that. I feel like the male perspective is very often the wrong
perspective. See, but in my opinion, you got to be care. That's that's very generous of you towards
the female side of things. We have to be careful with that because that starts to become sexist in
and of itself to start to go. Well, the men are usually wrong and the women need to be protected.
And that that's it's another slippery slope. I'm just already thinking ahead to any number of
people having a problem with anything being said. Just talk is what it is. And this is why. And this
is why you had a problem when you were dating, because you were thinking ahead too much. Yes,
that is very correct. You hang around with healthy people and none of us are healthy. Let's be honest.
We're all fucked. But you hang around with the healthier people you can find. And most of the
time, they're just regular people trying to figure it all out, too. Yeah. And they don't have
unrealistic expectations and things. You know, a psycho when you meet one. I'm not saying you know
it by the psychos at all. I'm saying no, no, no, I know. I'm saying but I'm saying all you got to do
is stay away from the psychos. Sure. Well, yeah, obviously. And you know, a psycho by the second
drink the first time you meet him. You're leaving out a lot of dates where it was like, holy shit,
I got to get out of this. This person is a nightmare. This person's blackout drunk. This
person just fell on the floor in a public bar, whatever it is. But I'm talking about what would
break my heart would be like a girl, you know, looking me in the eyes and smiling. And I could
tell. Well, unless I'm projecting that she's feeling safe and happy and I like what's going
on here and me thinking in the back of my mind, boy, I know I'm not going to marry this person.
Well, that's you think that on date three. And that's all overthinking. Sure. And I ruined what
could have been really fun, casual times. But I did not have fun, casual. Yeah, yeah. Because
you're in your head. You're in your head too much. Get out of your head. Well, I don't have to
anymore. I'm in a loving relationship. You are. But when you ruin that and that ends and you're
out there dating again. Sure. Sure. I want you to not be in your head. Right. When I'm divorced
and wearing pleated khakis out on the town at age 50. T -shirt tucked in. Oh, yeah. Beeper,
probably beeper. A beeper, a beeper on my belt, like a cell phone in my belt cell phone on the
holster, not a beeper. Yeah. Yeah. Cell phone in the holster. What would you what would you be
talking about at that point? The new Hyundai that you just bought? Sure. Sure. What else would
interest you at that point? Probably that James Spader show on NBC, whatever that is. Blacklist,
Blacklist. Yeah. Blacklist, you start referring to people you think are funny as a riot.
Yeah, he's a scream, man. Yeah. That's sad. That made me real depressed. Just that whole visual.
Sure. But do you find, which I think is if we're looking at the root of the sin itself,
do you find that lust ever takes you off your path of being a good person, your path of
uh following your career, any number of things is lust? Because there are people who they wake
up and it's like, how do I have sex? I have a couple of friends like this who are like,
I got to get fucked today. I got to get fucked today. And you're like, so you just never do
anything other than this? No, I don't. I'm not like that. Have you had pockets of them? Yeah,
I think there was probably a time where I would sort of feel like that. And that would lead to me
going out and having, I'll tell you what, that that led to me more frequently than not
drinking more than I needed to on a night because you're chasing the you're chasing the cat. And then
uh, see what I'm proud to say is I've never woken up in the morning and been like, look at this.
What did I do here? Never. I've always been like, I'm glad I had that sexual encounter,
which I have, I know almost no one can say. No, I've had many of those, but not at the girl.
I'm not going to lie and act like a saint and say, I've never woken up next to somebody. I'm gone
like, oof, right. You know, the goggles were on, but everybody, women and men have done that.
But I'd say more frequently, the bad feeling was not at that, not directed at the person was more
directed at me. Like, why did I do this? I mean, this was just, this was just an empty thing to do.
But again, then like a lot of the time the girl felt the same way as in it felt bad,
but felt like, Hey, it's all good. Like we just, we hung out and then I was like,
I'm being too hard on myself. Every time I've confessed that to a friend and said, you know,
I feel bad. And I tell the story every time the person on the other end has always said,
stop it. Just have fun. What do you just enjoy yourself? It doesn't matter. I truly do believe
that cliche of when you're an old man, like looking back and being like,
I could have had more sex, you know, cause it will get to the point where,
and hopefully we're all married and in love at this point. So it's irrelevant. But yeah,
I mean, the idea of you being alone at a certain age and completely unable to have sex in any way,
you know, that's, that's a, that's a, that's a likely reality.
Do it while you can.
You know, so there's, you know, I moved out here about 10 years ago. I went to a Halloween party.
I hooked up with this girl in a cat woman outfit, a very, very attractive, very attractive,
daddy likey. And I had actually driven all the way to my home and got the text. Why the hell
didn't you try anything with me? And then drove an hour back to, to meet up with her, but we hooked
up the next day. I wake up, I'm sitting in my car and I was like, I can't tell you how many times
throughout that week, I talked myself out of texting her because I felt like I've had sex.
This was early on. I've had sex with this person. I have to let her know I'm thinking about her,
let her know that I care about her because of the way I was raised. And I would have horrified her
had I done that. But there's some element of that stupid kid in me to this day where that's why a
casual sex thing doesn't work for me. I find myself being like, is she okay? Is she, you know,
as far as the actual act of sex, maybe that's good. As far as after it, especially in these
casual things that are happening all the time and were always happening around me,
uh, I was like, but doesn't her donor feelings get hurt? Isn't she upset? It's like, no,
that's, it's a foreign concept to me because I was raised Catholic, which sucks.
Now, the sooner you realize we're all a bunch of pig people, the better off you're going to be.
All sacks of beef. We're all pig shits. Yeah. Just disgusting swine pig shit. Sure. All right.
Absolutely. So don't worry about it. Yeah. All right. Enjoy yourself. I don't anymore. I'm
actually am tapping into what a nightmare it was for me, uh, being single. I did, I did not there.
Of course there's high points, but I never had the crazy great times because I was always wracked
with, Oh, I have to explain myself to this person who definitely doesn't need to hear my explanation.
Yeah. You've had, you've had any long -term relationships? How many was it? Three,
four at this point. I have had, I guess four, three yearish relationships for two to three
years, which takes you out of the game for a while, but I am more comfortable in that capacity.
I also can only really be comfortable sexually in a long -term relationship or in a relationship.
Sure. Uh, I can do it and get the job done, but as far as like,
okay, now I feel safe and secure, which I think everybody feels to some degree, but maybe not.
Uh, I, I, I've done all my best works actually in a, in a long -term relationship and by best work,
you mean what, you know, define it, break it down. I, I, I know what I'm doing more. I'm not, uh,
yeah, that's the other thing. You're not fumbling with the condom rack, rapid, the condom itself.
When I, when I pick up that condom, that to me, I'm seeing Jesus's face in that condom, like,
boy, if you were really following my teachings, you wouldn't need this. Would you like, like
literally as a 30 year old man, every time I got that condom out, I would hear Jesus being like,
this is unclean. If you need to cover up, obviously you don't feel safe in this. And I
would get tested for SEDs every three months. Many a doctor has told me, I'm not testing you
for that. You don't have symptoms. I will not test you for that. And me saying, please test me for
that because I need to hear no. I, if I didn't have sex in a three month period, I would still
get tested at the end of that three months. Cause I would say, well, you know, it could be lying
dormant in me. Cause you get on those little web MD sites and it's like herpes can lie dormant in
you for years. I would be so deep in those sites and so racked with fear, guilt, anxiety
with all these sexual encounters, drinking and help that to some degree. If I had smoked pot
at the time, I guarantee that would have helped a lot. But you know, for something that so many
people do constantly, it all, I always treated it like, Oh my God, it's this huge thing.
Which it wasn't. It's not, it's not, it's, it's pretty basic stuff.
Yeah. It's pretty basic stuff. We live in a really, well, nevermind kill me. I was just
going to say we live in a real contradictory society, but thank God it didn't go down that
road. That's fine. You can say that. I don't want to go down that road. Uh, I'm all lusted
up to be honest with you. I gotta, I think I gotta go out and bang something tonight.
Bang something. I'm kidding. It was a joke. It was a call back to your thing about,
uh, the guy waking up and saying, I gotta get laid today. Uh, and by something I don't mean
woman. I mean, possibly male or inanimate, possibly animal. Who the hell knows? Uh, what
are you going to do tonight? I'm going to a screening of the new Bob Odenkirk movie,
which my dear friend Brian is receiving his first producer credit on. And I'm very proud of him and
can't wait to see it. Fancy have fun. I will. I got a show. All right. I'm a little concerned
that we haven't talked long enough. What time is it? We're at about 45. All right.
What are you going to do? You know, I'm lusted out over here. You know, no, all right. We covered
the bases. I think, right. We talked about porn and we talked about random sex. We talked about
since people turn to us, uh, for movies and we didn't discuss movies at all this podcast,
should we? I saw Zoolander two. It was worse than you could ever imagine.
Porno movies. Yeah, that's true. Uh, and if we're going to talk about,
um, like a horror movie would be more appropriate than Zoolander two.
Well, we always talked about whatever movies we saw that week. Right. Um, come on, Joe,
don't throw me out of the fucking bus. So weren't we just talking about something that had some good
surprise nudity in it? Or was that on the last episode flight that was on the last episode?
Well, we can bring it up again in the lust podcast. There's some good,
unexpected. My name is Earl. She's righteous. Yeah, she's righteous. She dated a former agent
of mine. Really? Well, they were married. Yeah. There's a lot of hot women out here in this,
in this crazy town we live in. That's the thing. So you have this, I tend to kind of
keep it on lock, but I have this at times as well. Um, crazy per capita attractiveness here,
which you go, I go home to Missouri. I'm Tom Selleck in his prom, you know, here it's very
different. And I have had numerous friends like this where it kind of scares you. You've had
periods of this. I've had periods of this where you see a girl walk into the restaurant you're
eating and it's just like, God damn it. Yeah. God damn it. Like it's upsetting. And I don't
know what that is really, unless it's just an anger that you can't be with that person.
It's just, it throws your whole day sideways. Yeah. You don't need to see it, but it's like
seeing a violent death or something. It's like, I'm going to think about this all day now.
Now, do you ever approach those girls? No, no. I don't know. I sometimes I do.
Is that like, why would you talk to me or? For me, it's all about right place,
right time. I don't really approach girls in diners. I guess is where I'm getting it.
Well, you always hear like Megan Fox and people be like, well, no guys ever approach me. Do you
believe that? I do believe that. I think a girl like that looks so much off the page of Maxim.
Yeah. I feel how guys approach it is like, damn girl, you come sit on my dick, whatever,
like you're fucking incredible. And that's not going to bring them to you. But I feel like they
must get hit on aggressively like that a lot. Like the other night when my dog was lost,
my friend Michelle, who's quite an attractive woman, but devotedly married, was helping me
look for the dog. Yeah. And we were in a parking lot. And I said we pulled in the parking lot to
see if he was in there. And I said, can you ask this guy over here if he saw the dog? And she
rolled in and went out. She goes, excuse me, sir, have you seen a little white dog? And the guy goes,
I can't hear you. You got to come over here and talk to me. And I was like, OK, then glad to see
that even in a time of crisis, there's a man in the CVS parking lot trying to get laid. He was in
a CVS parking lot, standing outside of his car, music cranked. Yeah. This is where he posted up
for the night. I have truly never once in my life and I am sad about this as I say it, been like,
you are so beautiful or like come at a girl with some sort of sexual game or attitude. I can't
do it. The only time I've ever done it is my old go to line that worked a lot was I'd be talking
to a girl, a woman, a lady, and she would go blah, blah, blah, blah, back and forth, back and forth,
and shooting the shit. And then she would go, anyway, my boyfriend did it. The old movie. We've
all been on the receiving end of that. It's a tough one. My boyfriend and I would go, whoa, whoa, whoa,
boyfriend. What was all this? You would say that I've said it a bunch to girls and they always
like laugh really hard at it because it's you saying I'm fine with you having a boyfriend.
They're clearly dropping it in so you don't keep hitting on them. Sure. It's a nice way to
acknowledge that instead of just I've seen also seen in bars guys be like, you let me talk to you
for five fucking minutes when you got a boyfriend. I've seen that a couple of times. What are people
supposed to do? I did have a situation the other night that was kind of curious where I met a girl
and she knew my comp. She'd been to a show that I performed on and she knew me from that. And we
were talking for a while and it was very great conversation. And I said, Hey, do you want to go?
We were in a bar or whatever. I said, Hey, you want to go sit down? I'd like to sit.
She's like, I want to find a cigarette. I was like, me too. Actually, let's share one. So we
found a cigarette. We shared it. We're talking from this great talk. The whole meeting met. The whole
meeting started with her telling me she brought a woman to a show I performed on at as a date
sitting. We're talking. I'm gearing up to like, we should go out sometime. And I say, you know,
you're new in town. Where do you live? She goes, I live in Glendale. And I said, or at water,
I go out. It's great. You found a place already. She goes, well, I live with my boyfriend.
And I was kind of like, I played it cool. I was like, Oh, cool. That's great. Who's your
beard? And then she goes, he's on the walking dead. And I was like, this girl just, I mean,
she couldn't have swung from cool to uncool any harder than that whole exchange dropping his
credits. That's weird. Come on, man. No, I was telling you, I talked to a girl that I think is
fantastic at a wedding the other night for like 10 minutes. And we're talking and having a really
nice time. But like, in my mind, I'm not flirting. I'm just kind of being funny and nice and saying
funny things and trying to, you know, keep the conversation moving. And then it hit a point where
it was like, Hey, so you're staying here. Like what room are you in? Are you here alone? Whatever
else. And I was like, Oh, no, I'm, I'm staying in a room with my girlfriend. This girl walked off
a little angry or maybe mock angry, but it was pretty clear when she walked away that she had
thought it was going one way and it wasn't. And I was like, so what am I supposed to do? Can you not
talk to a woman or a man? If you're in a relationship, it gets a very dodgy. You don't
be like, Hi, nice to meet you. I have a girlfriend. That's crazy to say. Yeah. And it's also hard not
to seem like you're flirting or not for who the hell knows. I don't know. We'll figure it out
someday. Patty. All right. This has been you. We'll see you in hell presentation. The fangoria
podcast network produced by Thomas DeFeo executive produced by Ken Hanley of fangoria entertainment
for press opportunities, advertising inquiries and information about we'll see you in hell.
Contact Ken at fangoria .com. That's the email address. Follow me. Joe DeRosa comedy on Twitter.
Follow pat at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and I will be touring starting March 17th. This is
probably after that at this point, but North Carolina actually March 18th 19th North Carolina
Wilmington at the dead crow radio room in Greenville, South Carolina. I think it's the,
I think that one's like the 22nd Hattiesburg, Mississippi at the Thirsty Hippo
that Friday Lafayette that Saturday, New Orleans and then the following Tuesday through Saturday
at Acme Comedy Club Company in Minneapolis. Pat, do you have plugs or or what? No, this is all my
volcano off the coast of Waikiki on April 9th. And this is cause you're a virgin, right?
No, there may be virgins there jumping in as well. I'm just kind of doing it. It's a lifelong dream
of mine. It's Mount. Come on. I want to lay you. Oh God. Keep it on that last theme. I think it's
a way in the world joke. Actually folks, I'm not doing anything. But if you want to maybe say hello
and grab a burger, give me a call. I'd love to meet up.