Hey welcome to Will see you in hell it's the podcast about movies that you love and we love it I'm Joe
and over there across the country sitting from me on his computer is
folks is Patrick John Walsh in the he'sy
Joe is literally fanning himself as though he's a southern bell with the vapors
it's getting hot we were talking a little bit before we started recording about the the
climate report that came out this week it's not good if you're able to do anything to keep the world
from ending get out there and do it recycle at bare minimum no all the reports and recycling now are
that it did nothing and it was pointless that this is the problem yeah yeah all the reports yeah
like the news on recycling now is like it does nothing it like you know it's it's all miss it's
like kind of like nonprofits like where they're like you know all this money was just mismanaged right
you're like okay is this all the reports are something you saw on like Instagram news or something
here's the only reason I this these are my only two sources but this is why I believe it years
ago pen and teller did on one of their episodes of bullshit hold on this will come together now hang
on hold on one of the episodes of pen and teller bullshit was about how recycling was bullshit for all
these reasons like the plastic bottles are actually going here it's not doing anything blah blah blah blah
it was a pretty strong argument but I wouldn't use that as my source or my only source or whatever
what started to happen was I started to notice my more liberal friends recycling less and not giving
a shit and then finally I asked one of them like what do you do you care what we do with this plastic
bottle and they're like I guess put it in the recycling bin even though we know it does nothing now
and this is a well -read well -school liberal friend of mine who usually when he gives me information
like that is pretty on point and it's very unlike him to buy into any sort of conspiracy theories or
anything like that but I haven't seen that but I mean we got to do so well I mean why would you
see it where would you see it you know what I mean you think the Fox and CNN are going to report on
this it's not good news it's not salacious yeah yeah I mean Fox might Fox might go the left might want
you to put that plastic bottle in the trash are in the in the inside you know they might do some
expose but I haven't heard them so I mean look I realize the argument I'm posing right now sounds
flimsy at best but I mean when you when you started with pen and teller it's it's just never
Anna with a show called bullshit no less it's well it but how can you believe any of it anymore
they had New York Times ran a story the other day CDC is claiming Delta strain is as contagious
as chickenpox that is not true this is the New York Times now going against the CDC it's like
what the fuck is going on man well the report you said I mean it looked like it was still plenty
contagious but yeah I mean I saw today that the what I have which is Moderna is supposed to be
a lot better against the Delta variant than Pfizer so that gave me a little bit of relief yeah no
Pfizer saying the exact opposite yeah Pfizer saying if you get a third dose of their regular vaccine it will
protect you completely against Delta now okay the third dose of the regular vaccine that has nothing
to do with Delta this is insanity you know it is it really is it just it it seems like as I've
been saying from day one I just want somebody to hold my face and tell me what to do and no one will do
it and I'm sure that's what everybody in the world wants that's nobody knows and there's no one to trust
and it's horrifying but at this point I'd like one of those old school abusive husbands that won't
let me leave the house well let me have a job not just somebody that keeps me in and
through fear is protecting me from the horrors of the world yeah he looks into the bathroom and you're
putting on a little too much rouge and he slams the medicine cabinet door into your face that kind of
thing yeah I need a man in my life yeah because I'm sure I'll do it I'm certainly not one no I've
been out pitching a television program and that's what I was doing all day and it's you know it's
always good it's always good if people even bring you into here the pitch you know that's that's a
victory right there but it's like I am doing a 25 minute comedy pitch of just me speaking and
everyone listening to the pitch puts their microphone on mute so joke after joke is just met with
complete cavernous silence and I'm not going to be the guy who's like could you guys leave your
mics on so I know that it's working I just kind of minimize them and I coldly read for 25 minutes and
then at the end the feedback is great but it's like god it sucks to just sit there and get I mean imagine
doing Joe you wouldn't have to imagine I imagine doing a stand -up show where nobody laughs for 25 minutes oh
yeah I've been there yeah it's just like god it takes its toll you know it takes its toll it's like
all these suits and then people that the attitude on zoom you know somebody will bring their zoom up
and they're in complete darkness one of the executives your pitch and you're like it's turn a
light on your head of major network yeah you're dealing with a country of people who didn't do well
at their jobs to begin with regardless of the industry sure you know I mean just any
I would say I have worked to some extent to some extent meeting with with with some real time or
whatever I put time in I'm I'm entering now about the fifth industry I've been involved in in my life
okay with with with this sandwich shop in bar and everything yeah it's everywhere every job I've
ever had in any field I worked in politics for a while I worked in healthcare for a little while I
worked in entertainment forever I'm getting now into food services it's crazy it's like it's
absolutely insane people don't want to do their jobs and when you give them a beautiful excuse like
there's a slight chance if you step into this room you could get a variant of a thing even though
you're vaccinated that you won't probably go to the hospital for it would it it's just it's just this
is allowed everybody now I hate to say it because I was one that was like when Trump was saying like
people don't want to go back to work yeah but I was like oh fuck you dick and then I went
back to working I was like oh he was right yeah it's horrible
yeah myself included you know I've used it there's excuse to get out of a million things I didn't
want to do you know I'm not going to make it to that awful show I committed to I'm sorry that's a
variant I'll probably get there but as of right now I'm very excited to have anything in my life
that requires me to use my brain it's it's been too long and I'm starting to
fester uncle fester style too long too strong too down to get the friction on yeah speaking of
uncle fester style you know Tim Burton's doing this Adam's family show for Netflix and I got to say
it was one of the rare casting announcements where I went you know what guys you've done something
right they cast Louise Guzman as Gomez all right which I love that's very fun I love that he's
going to be like you know Mr Romeo and look like Louise Gomez that's funny to me and Catherine
Zita Jones that's his lovely wife Morticia and I was like you know what I can't argue with this
they've made good choices and burdens the guy to do it if he tries and by the way thank you Tim Burton
and the network behind this for calling it Morticia notice how there's nobody's angry about it
notice how when you just tell the truth to the fans and say this was going to be more
Morticia centered so it's called Morticia or it's called Wednesday yeah it's not called the
other Wednesday yeah yeah yeah but the point is is thank you you were honest cool it's a different
take Kevin Smith he's doing fun yeah what do you think that that I mean I'm going to be their
opening night like a fucking fool I can't give him opening night energy anymore after after Jay
and Silent Bob the new one I I will not give him full energy I'll wait till that stumbles into
who blew or something like that anyway if it if it plays in theaters even you know that's true I
mean it's Lionsgate there's a chance it could just go straight to streaming yeah no not Lionsgate
is it Lionsgate I think it's Lionsgate anyway it's still Weinstein he's he's financing it from his
prison cell I just true right or is it no no no no I just read before I got on here though that he
was it was like another victory for Harvey Weinstein and his LA I'm like okay hey that's a guy
where you know it's the same thing with Cosby it's like if they hit the streets what what are what are
people supposed to do you know well hopefully not take the law into their own hands yeah living some
sort of I get it they they did and then that's shitty and awful I'm not arguing that but we need
to be better this is the problem now is we're all like everybody's like well I'm not better why
should you you know you're a better why should I be you know that's exactly right yeah and it will kill
it will kill us all yeah we're at the end we're right in the end out here I'm pretty sure of it
and I know that it'll go on there'll be a new phase of people and it'll be a different place but I do
think we are at the teetering end of what we have known for the last 200 years as reality I agree
I agree at this point I welcome it uh I got to scary stuff I finally got my hands on a ps5
had to buy what's the deal well that came out a year ago and nobody can get them still I guess they
came out in November and they're still like impossible to get so I bought a year yeah yeah I bought
a slightly used from from one from a guy on eBay did they not make enough I mean what Pat you got
to wonder about reality when all of a sudden they're handing out a vaccine that was in terribly short
supply on every street corner yet you still can't get a ps5 it's outrageous
it's outrageous what did they make they make a limited edition 500 copies of the of the new
PlayStation they they release it like once every two weeks and bots buy it all up and that's it
and Sony is riding that that wave which is why I'm glad I didn't give Sony my money I gave my
money to a kid who gave his money to Sony and I got his like so it actually makes me feel good did
you have to overpay slightly he give a very fair deal I think I paid about a hundred bucks more
than I would have altogether but this thing is awesome it's super fun if you if you're lucky enough
to get your hands on one and if you can afford one I know they're not cheap you know so I'm not
certainly not throwing that around without without what's the word I'm looking for
Jesus Christ almighty I'm sorry without reason consideration for your financial you know
not I know this is this you know it was a big purchase for me it's a big purchase for almost everybody
right but anyway it's great everybody's got a lot of money coming in right now so yeah yeah I mean
you know they're probably not entering my zoom feed right now they're going to cut off my
S .B .A loan I got okay no look if we're getting locked down again I mean that I would consider that
an investment getting the fucking PlayStation 5 it's it's like you got to keep yourself entertained
and you got to keep them separated I got I now have the switch the Xbox Series X and the PlayStation 5
so I'm pretty well covered okay but anyway and and every other game system that's ever been made
many of them not everyone but many but I just got the game that the kid sent me with it who I
bought it from he sent me Spider -Man Miles Morales yeah and that's more of what I wanted to talk about
because I played the first Spider -Man game on PS4 and I was like yeah this is pretty cool man but like
I don't know it's a little repetitive and I'm getting kind of bored this Miles Morales game is so
fucking good it's so fun it's so awesome it's just a kick -ass superhero beat the shit out of a
million guys keep getting new powers awesome fun game and you know you're you're in a literal
uh rendition of the complete New York City like so when you have to go from Harlem to like
the tip of Manhattan you you like you have to do it and it's and you're swinging and shooting webs and
and it's just so fun man it's just so so fun it's a great video game for our scary stuff this week if
you haven't played it I would say it far exceeds the first Spider -Man it is not just a redo yeah that
that movie into the Spider -Verse I felt like it was a video game it the visuals really
lended itself to that so the same kid in this doing it yeah I recognize Miles from from
no no no I mean it's the same actor that did him in the movie oh I see my video games too yeah yeah
you know I well I got I got a scary stuff but I guess I'll parlay it into the movie corner it works
either way uh I watched all six episodes and there are sadly only six episodes because you're left
wanting more of Garth Marengi's dark place on Amazon Prime which someone I know has been telling me
through Instagram and Twitter and so forth that we got a watch at some point and I was like it's not
available um but now it's on Amazon Prime the the raves are right on it's Matt Berry it's uh who's
the guy from the IT crowd who's now a film Richard Ioday Iod yeah that can't be how you pronounce it but
that's how it looks um and a guy I'm unfamiliar with but uh good lord it's funny it's a show they're
basically showing you classic episodes of this like 70s British horror anthology written and
directed by this guy Garth Marengi who's supposed to be kind of a Stephen King blowhard type and inner
cut with scenes from the episodes are the cast and producers in the in the modern day uh discussing
what an amazing show it was and what an impact it has and that it's very funny very strange a lot of
great dry British comedy it's very young Matt Berry who I just think it's one of the funniest
people on earth I agree and the transitions it never gets old basically you are shown something I
sent you a clip that that illustrates the entire show it's Matt Berry the camera goes away for a
second when it comes back he's wearing like a child's werewolf mask that looks so bad like worse than
you could ever imagine and then it cuts to them in the present day and they're like we were doing
bowls to the wool horror make you couldn't make this show today and it's funny every time
there's they dub every line in it like a bad 70s show and that adds so much comedy every line is
said in the funniest most bizarre way possible um and it gets better as it goes you know it's like
immediately they realize what's funny about it and it just starts getting exponentially funnier
each week I loved it Garth Moranke's dark place whoever recommended it to me you were 100 % right
I watched rewatched Return of the Living Dead part two the last time I talked about this on the show I
think I said that I was disappointed in watching it and I I just felt that it was a pale comparison to
the original Return of the Living Dead um but I rewatched it one day just you know lazy afternoon kind of
thing and I got to say I was wrong I really loved it this was a movie I loved as a kid revisited
as an adult didn't like it now revisited again as an adult and I loved it um I think it's an
awesome awesome fun horror zombie flick um tremendous sequence when the when the government gas spills
the thing that's gonna bring them all back to from the dead of the zombies crawling through the earth
and you know like real Michael Jackson thriller style no running zombies in this one I don't believe
if I remember correctly they're all like the sort of staggering zombies it's got a similar sense of
humor to the first one um the two guys you know the two the two guys from the first one that get
infected um the the older guy from poltergeist and and the younger kid in the first movie they work
in that like facility or whatever near the graveyard in this one they're they're back but they're
playing different characters but they're still a team and they play grave robbers that get infected
and they're once again they're very very funny in it uh and I enjoyed it so much I'm thinking of
replacing my DVD with the special edition blue ray from shop factory I think or screen factory so
yeah I own it and I've never seen it so maybe I'll make a point of it the uh the return of the living
dead blue ray that they did is awesome it's got like a two -hour documentary almost too much
information on return to the living dead yeah any alternate cut of the film which was never released
which is really cool uh I watched Val which is new to Amazon Prime it is a documentary about Val
Kilmer uh I first realized something was very wrong with Val Kilmer when I saw the snowman where uh
if you've seen it Michael Fastbender portrays a man named detective Harry Hole and everyone involved
with the production didn't see a problem with that but um Val Kilmer was in it and they kept shooting
him from the back and I was like is he being dubbed and there was something weird and that's kind of when
I learned that he had really serious throat cancer and that's very sad I mean it seems to really only
be affecting him in that he can't talk and he has to push on a hole in his throat to speak it's not
the full um you know the thing they used to do is a joke and sitcoms where you have to hold the thing up
and it goes like a robot voice he just pushes on this plastic thing in his throat and that's how he's
able to talk um look cancer is very sad don't get me wrong it's a terrible thing Val Kilmer
making his own documentary about himself is a little weird especially for a guy who is a notorious
legendary asshole and impossible to work with so he is showing you he's basically one of these guys
who's been recording everything his whole life which sounds like the most annoying friend you could ever
have but um the so Lea Moon Fry the punky Brewster girl did a documentary about this that Hulu
released recently where it was all her old videotapes and if we're getting into this new thing where a
documentary is just any actor who's filmed their life can make a documentary I'm not going to keep
watching these things it's it's a little ridiculous he is able to pick and choose I mean he at one point
includes a clip of Robert Downey Jr. going is Val and asshole no absolutely not like from kiss kiss bang
it's like Val come on buddy there's a few moments on the island of dr morose set it is pretty much
chronological going through his movie career there's a few moments in there where he he'll include him
dusting up with a director a little bit the guy who did direct uh dr moro at one point is like turn
your camera off turn it off like you can I saw in his eyes the face of a man who was trying to do his
job and is being tormented by a monster I've been that man and the monster you've been
I've been bold I found it very very hard to sympathize with alcomer not due to cancer cancer is very sad
but when you're watching this I mean if you didn't know val directed it and you didn't question it
which I think is 99 % of people watching this you're going to be like what a sweet guy and what a great
career and I don't think that's particularly fair but isn't it sad the way we have to talk now
yeah it is it's so obvious that you're not knocking a guy with cancer you're saying and you still have
to be like I'm not it's not the cancer I feel very bad but is it to be honest Joe it's it's fucking
exhausting every minute is exhausting this is our second attempt recording this thing because of this
that's a joke then we're fucked you know blah blah blah damn it folks Val even though I've kind
of talking a little bit of shit about it I really enjoyed it I mean it's anytime you're going through
a guy's filmography and he's telling you some stories that's always fun for a film fan to watch
he kind of shits on top secret he talks about when he met his wife Joanne Waley Kilmer
he's like you know she was doing this masterpiece of the British stage and I was just doing this fluff
I'm like Val you've done way worse movies than top secret baby that movie is fucking hilarious
anyway he comes off as as difficult but a prickly genius kind of thing and I think in reality that's
not the case but the period of him being Jim Morrison where you see his wife at one point like
you can you can basically see her eyes flip into I'm divorcing this man when she goes to like yeah they're
divorced they get along but when she goes to talk to him about you know probably our child's in
danger or something like that and he's like show me the way to the next whiskey bug baby you know
he's fully in character and she turns sees that she's being filmed and it's like her face is just like
I want out of this marriage immediately anyway there's a lot of good stuff in it it's just like as
you watch it know that you're watching a movie anytime a man is editing his own life he's
gonna put in the best aspects and leave out the worst that's all I'm saying
um I brought this up I think last time but I didn't do it in the movie corner I watched the last
temptation of Christ dude that is so weird I put it in my blu -ray player last night and fell asleep I
didn't even start it I re -watched it only the second time I'd ever seen it it is a heavy flick yeah
you know it's Corsese it's it's a good movie Corsese doesn't really make a bad movie he just makes
movies you like less than others you know but uh but the Achilles heel in the film is the fact that he
for some reason didn't tell certain actors you sound like you're from Brooklyn
uh including Harvey Kaitel as Judas yeah second lead in the film yeah uh Jesus why did you betray us
why did you betray us Jesus yeah it's literally like there's uh yeah it's Kaitel it's it's it's
it's unhinged Kaitel like he's there's no the tea changes nothing he's like stomping around
short and angry and he's like you're worse than them you need to pray to your god it's it's crazy
it's so crazy yeah that said it's somehow still a riveting performance Wilm DeFoe was awesome in it
creepy fucking Wilm DeFoe as always like he really prays it's the only time I found Jesus creepy
in a movie you know you always find him is like he seems like a nice guy this Jesus is really
kind of stairs through you um Barbara Hershey's wonderful is Mary Magdalene uh it's a look whether
you're religious or not it's a challenging film I think everybody was sort of raised to look at
certain religions in a certain way because they're just sort of part of the public they're part of
the lexicon or whatever you know they're just part of the society so when you see those things
interpreted in a different way it can be a very challenging thing sometimes even if you don't
subscribe to it but uh it's it's an interesting movie and I think it's an incredible commentary on
the life of Christ and uh I don't know I just think it's I just think it's really a really cool
flick and worth watching so I would say check it out Peter Gabriel did the soundtrack and it's like
it's a very haunting soundtrack uh well there's that he goes in Jesus's eyes right yeah that's
a kickoff song yeah yeah I imagine if he shot him and that cuz yeah imagine the score says he
getting missed the score like Gabriel brings it over like back carrier or something and he puts it in
and it's in Jesus's eyes he just puts Jesus into all the songs now dude it's it's straight up like
it's like the passion of the Christ soundtrack where it's like it's like a lot of that
like it's really haunting and like echoey drum hits and stuff yeah uh I want to be gay
you're sweet Jesus uh the standout performances for me outside of the ones I've mentioned are
you've got David Bowie as Punches pilot he's great
uh I forgot he was in it he's only in it's like one scene but he's great in it
he was our Barb Hershey Mary Magdalene she was yeah I already mentioned her she's great and then you
have um what's his name who was the guy that lived to be like 98 there was in Twin Peaks with
smoke Harry Dean Stanton plays uh Saul and he's awesome in it which I thought initially was
miscast but then I was like he's so good in this but then you got like Irving Kershner is like a guy
leading the charge to Stone Mary Magdalene and he's literally like I have nothing to hide
not even exaggerate literally isn't an actor that's very strange so weird it's like it's some of
the choices in it are very very weird but uh but it's worth seeing I'll be checking it out that I
I forgot to mention the highlight of Val is him include he made very extensive audition tapes
for big directors and he didn't get these parts but he includes the tapes so there's a big video
for Kubrick where he's uh going out for the Matthew Modine role in Fullmetal Jacket and then he did
a video as Goodfellas where he he was pretty good he was Henry Hill and I guess he was in very close
contention with Leota but you get to watch these audition videos he made and honestly if I was an
actor I'd do it the same way I do some that really made me stand out um but I'm not so there you go
yeah I saw pray away on Netflix which is a new documentary uh short for pray away the gay um
I'm very interested in this stuff largely because a lot of my friends were Uber
super religious all throughout high school and that period where we were all sort of becoming adults
and I was like I don't really like this religion stuff anymore and like all those kind of weird
conversations but they went to these churches and I went on like a Florida trip with like a yeah I'll go
on your your fun church trip or whatever and they were doing this kind of stuff this praying the
gay away and um so the documentary should I think should be extremely interesting it's a fascinating
topic they destroy people's lives and you know you've seen it done comedically with Bruno and so forth
but those are real people like it's generally a guy who presents as gay you know not again we have
to explain ourselves they're you know yeah I know what you mean you would say this man is gay not
that there is a way we used to say we used to say openly gay that was that's how you would say it
like the 90s and 80s yeah right and you know in Bruno there and I think religious does something
like this with one of these guys too it's like look at this guy isn't this funny that this guy is
telling us homosexual these bad homosexuality is bad when he's clearly gay um this movie is much more
that's that would openly openly gay man he was out of the closet case sorry open day is out of the
closet my terms mixed up yeah so yeah openly wouldn't be right but but presenting gay is what I'm trying
to say I guess um so you're watching in this it's a mix of people with real haunted sad looks in
their eyes saying I love this straight life and I'm not gay and they're presenting gay certainly
and you know I'm not saying mocking these people is great but this like really somber sad presentation of
it is it sort of doesn't work either you know it's it's um it's a really dull documentary for as
salacious as the topic is and that's nobody's fault I'm not saying I want it to be one of those
documentaries where it's they got the little animations every five minutes to try to hold your interest
right I'm just saying like the people they chose and it's not that they don't have fascinating stories
but it's just they there's something not really compelling about it uh it's a lot of people
who are presenting gay but with with sadness saying I'm straight and then a lot of people who
used to be this way and now they're out and proud and happy but they have a great deal of shame
for the lives they ruined you know by by participating in these groups that really fought to
pray the gay away for people so I just I think there's a there's a a plus documentary to be made about this
I I almost feel like I've seen one I just don't remember the name of it it was years ago
but uh this isn't quite it there's a better movie to be made about this topic
last but not least for me I'm gonna do the best of enemies which is a title that's been used
for a jillion things at this point but this one is the movie starring I think her name is
tarage it's pronounced tarashi pihenson from empire tarashi pihenson yeah and uh sam rock well it's
based on a true story uh it's about a Ku Klux Klan member who becomes basically the leader almost
and a civil rights activist who uh is basically the leader of all the civil rights action that's
where they live I think it's Mississippi back in the 60s or whatever it is who are
brought together to work together to work out the school busing dispute uh that's happening in their
town uh and they bring together basically two side two panels in the town to sort out the issue and
try to make some sort of compromise and the two sides are uncompromising meaning like the white
side is very racist including clan members and the black side is mostly like civil rights activists instead
or people in the in the movement and stuff and she's chosen to lead this is all true with this
happened she's chosen to lead the uh the pro side and he's chosen to lead the against side and um
and they end up becoming friends and he denounces his life in the KKK and they end up working
together and our friends for the rest of their lives to find and you're what now the movie itself
the performances between the two of them are tremendous everybody's really good in the movie
it's a little cliche you know it's a little heartwarming where it needs to be and and confrontational
when it needs to be and convenient in places or whatever so you're not going to be blown away by the movie
but just watching this story and then over the closing credits when they're playing interviews with
the actual two people sitting with one another and talking about one another and all they did
together after this happened uh uh the you know the closing scene of the film is Sam Rockwell and
the gas station and when he denounces the KKK in front of the town all the whites that went to his
station boycott him yeah he's like i don't know i'm gonna have to close shop and then she brings a line
of cars and it's all the black citizens that he wouldn't service now saying like well we'll keep you
open now right and it's just watching this and knowing that this happened and everything
it's just it's so bittersweet because you're like what i'm a sucker for a movie where people come
together and heal you're just like you think about now and how it's everything is just like
fuck you no matter what you know what i mean i don't not saying you can't continue to have a life
if you better yourself or whatever that's not what i'm talking about i'm just talking about like
i was on the internet yesterday Chuck D from public enemy post did something about like
you you get the vaccine you're fine you don't get the vaccine you're fine you get the vaccine you're sick
you don't get the vaccine you're sick you get the vaccine you die you don't get the vaccine you die
he's like i don't know man it just seems like everybody it needs to just make their own choice and
let's stop dividing one another and hating each other it's creating too much separation and every
response to the post was like this is a shit take you're out of your mind there and i i wrote
under the thing i just wrote so you guys follow Chuck D and don't expect to be challenged like you
clearly haven't been a fan since 1987 like me this is what this guy does but it's just like it's so sad
to me like you'd never hear a story like this again where it's like these people were at polar
opposite ends of the spectrum one was clearly more correct or the correct one because one is
fighting for civil rights the other one is fighting for white supremacy there's obviously a bad guy
here there's a wrong guy but the fact that eventually when the bad guy said i'm sorry and i've seen
the light they come together and it's like okay now let's move forward like i always think of like
star wars and star track when like they'll be like they'll be like this man is a defector from
the empire he's got secret plans to show the rebellion right imagine if they acted like us they make
fuck you you fucking empire pizza shit i don't care what he has i don't forget yeah you're like
no it's a guy's trying to say he's seen the light he wants to know right now it it's something that you
it's like they say you don't know what you have till it's gone i mean like that is just something
you could always count on as being one of the building blocks of society and i really do think that
that not not is being lost has been lost and if we don't get it back we're we're destroyed i really
i do want to say though it's crazy this is crazy i got home last night from from a movie and i
was like i'm gonna watch something for a little bit i put in last temptation to christ as i said
it's about to start and i'm like pat you know you're not gonna watch this two and a half hour movie
right now i flipped over to i guess it was either amazon or hulu wherever you watched it and i saw this
movie the best of enemies i go what is this and i go sam rockwell and then i go 2019 how the fuck would
i not see a sam rockwell movie that came out two years ago what is this so did he even give it the
theatrical release it did it but it was very brief i mean look it came out like i think tail end of 2019
which now blurs right into beginning of 2020 because of code yeah that's true yeah it's probably
something that they were like we'll push this for Oscars and then i got no traction and they were like
then let's bury it in the ground and yeah and it's not like what they do it's not the best reviewed film
it's not pan but it's just kind of like you know it's a little cliche but there's enough here to satisfy
you and whatever and uh yeah i liked it i'm i'm a sucker though too for sam rockwell like the guy i'd
watch the guy you know eat eggs like i don't i don't care like i just i'm just maybe a huge fan cool
hand Luke reboot and you'll get to see him eat eggs i never saw who cool hand Luke and you believe
that it's i mean we were talking about the hustler last week cool hand loops probably better than that
it's amazing at those those three at least of in terms of that era for him hustler cool hand Luke
and HUD are three of the best movies ever met they're great the only part of cool hand Luke ever saw is
when he fights George Kennedy and he's going like stay down stay down and it upset me because i
only knew George Kennedy from breath mint commercials and naked gun naked gun so fucking weird they
would pick George Kennedy unless they were just like who looks like he has the worst breath in the world
because even once he sprays the thing i'm like now his breath still stinks you can tell you can just
tell all right he died right yeah yeah i love the man big fan i love them too i actually i never saw
his disaster pictures but anyway George RIP RIP Georgie key all right suicide these
suicide squad is the name of this one these suicide squads the original first movie in in ages
that i can recall walking out of i would later do it again with my wife halfway through oceans eight
because not not because it was unwatchable we were both just like i'm not doing this right now
um but yeah the original you'd agree Joe right horrible even with your DC love i liked it when i
first saw it and then the more i thought about it and tried to walk look they got me initially with the
Batman stuff in it with Affleck and the Joker stuff i liked initially and then the um the flash
cameo they they peppered it with things where i was like okay i like this even though my heart i knew
wasn't really a good movie i really liked will smith in that first one um margo robbie's great
as Harley Quinn she's get she gets better in that role every time she does it but uh she really is
great and birds of prey not a perfect film but i think i'd put it between the two you know it's
i so but yeah i'm not saying i'm joining you in DC love but i am saying that i i think that
i like their vibe better i think because it feels more adult like when i go see a marble movie
all rated are all that's rated all right you know like but i agree it is more adult and uh and my hats off
to james gun with this film because he made something that had some of the humor that guardians of the
galaxy had that didn't go completely off the rails like guardians of the galaxy two and every marvel
movie since then where they have become so comedic that there are no stakes for me anymore now i know
endgame avengers are supposed to be great and dark and whatever but you know my thoughts we don't
need to retread all that um but i thought he really walked a fine line in this i think he really
captured the spirit of the comic books um and i thought he made a really smart move by like i'm
gonna do these like kind of almost fringe suicide squad members yeah so we can just fucking kill
everybody and boil it down to like three or four of them that you actually really you know
care about and i'm not that you didn't care about the ones that die but you know it was it was a very
smart move whereas something like in the marvel universe every major character is front and center
and then it's like well now you can't kill anybody which is why Loki has been back 87 times from the dead
and right and you know and whatever all that so um yeah they kick this off almost like
scream style they kind of stole the bit from deadpool but it's like there's there's several actors
several characters many of them big stars peed devids and other people and they they're going on
this mission and they're dead in five minutes and it's you know it's uh it gives it a feeling of
craziness of anything can happen the deaths are super gory and violent really horror movie violent
slasher movie violent uh you know with blood and gore and everything and face it blown off that kind
of shit right that weasel character with like they they do a good here he does a great job of giving
he does a way better job than the star wars movies have done recently of putting these CGI characters
in a movie uh but but making you forget that instantly and just making them part of the gang like the
you know of course group and the and the raccoon and from the guardians movies but this has a weasel
that like with no dialogue it just it was funny to me every time I saw it king shark king shark
voice by so long who loved it I love the caring money sweet yeah what an endearing character wake
when rat catcher says do you have any who are your friends and he's like I don't have any friends but
you can tell he's so innocent he doesn't even understand why that's sad there are some really sweet
moments with king shark who is one of my favorite villains ever and I'm glad made it out alive in this
because I want to see king shark he's he's a flash villain usually I want to see him pop up in the
flash though I was very devastated that this is spoiler heavy I was devastated that captain boomerang
died immediately he was my favorite guy in the first suicide squad I think it's he's such an odd villain
and uh again he's a flash rogue so I um he was the one guy where I was like god damn it I didn't want
polka dot man died too polka dot man turned out to be a really fun character steals the fucking show
I mean the the performance was amazing and he was really funny but the the uh makeup job I just thought
was awesome and it was it was kind of subtle but like this stuff in his face the polka dots like
bursting out of his face were gross and cool um it's just a movie with 20 times the personality
that any of these Marvel movies have and to be honest for me most of these DC movies have had
I that is why I love James gun he's adding humor but it feels kind of like 80s humor to me where it's
in service of the action and the characters and it doesn't just detract in any way um it's just fun
good solid jokes well performed past is great I've known Steve aging many years it was so cool to see him
this and I've seen Steve head -to -head with viola davis you know yeah it was funny to me I loved it
love seeing Steve in this that was awesome love seeing Pete in it uh love seeing um oh
this is what I was going to say uh the we we I I have a retraction to make
John Cena was great we were shit two weeks ago he's hilarious his very first scene I was like I
need to remember and I didn't just say I'm sorry to John Cena because I also liked him in
blockers I was thinking of somebody else he's a funny actor he was good in uh streamers movie he was
very funny and he sinister when he has to be I mean his line the best line of movie was when he goes
when he goes I'm all for liberty and I'll kill every man woman and child I need to to get it or whatever
I was like this is that line and polka dot man going I turned into my mother in my head and
keep him murdered everybody like those two lines made me actually laugh out loud yeah um
but Cena was great and then of course leading the charge uh joe uh what's his name
kittering ken emin ken emin back and i just elba really becoming the new leader of the squad
and he's great in this elba was tremendous he was sure yeah you can tell it's funny
because you can tell that they want it smith because smith stole the show and the first one is
dead shot and you could tell they wanted smith back because it was smith was sort of the unsung leader
of the suicide squad in the first movie and then this one it's idris elba as blood sport right uh
and they're both being motivated by conflicts with their daughters and I'm like I feel like this was
probably written and then there were all those rumors that idris elba was just going to replace
will smith as the character and he said we didn't want to do that yeah so I think they just said
well let's make it blood sport instead but I think you can kind of see the the hints in the script of
like I think that was supposed to be dead shot but it doesn't matter it's blood sport was awesome
idris elba I don't think I've ever seen idris elba be funny yeah he's really funny he's funny like an
interview setting but he hasn't really gotten the change he was on the office too he stepped in
corral for a few weeks but yeah it's they had a real national chemistry I feel like James
gun is kind of beloved you know I remain I still think his best movie is his dawn of the dead which
he didn't direct he he wrote but his writing you know even slither and some of his better movies
always kind of leave me at a little bit of a distance I don't love him like I love Edgar Wright's
stuff even though they're kind of similar um in that they're all modding at different times so
forth but like this I think this is his strong suit it is bringing weirdness and personality and
excitement and actual laughs to this genre that in my eyes is dead I mean I was at a point where I
I couldn't watch any more of these and I thought this one was really good and I wouldn't say just
really good for a superhero movie though it is it's a really good movie it's a great action movie
it's well shot yeah and and moment to moment you know who's fighting each other and what they're
fighting about which I can't say for any of these Marvel movies and I never had to watch robots throw
each other around I was always watching people that I knew and understood even giving Idris Elba one
one minute scene with his daughter at the beginning you just immediately care about him and none of
these other movies take that time really talk about a good establishing scene because you're
you're immediately like oh Christ here comes the daughter and it's going to be like you see that
the criminals got the heart of gold and within 10 seconds he's screaming fuck you at his daughter
and they're like yeah I eat you I fucking eat you know you know right you're like I was like
there were some balls he moves in this where I was like man they really committed to that like they
committed to just making it what it is like I really liked how real I was bored in the beginning
because I was like I'm not just I'm just not going to care about this like what and then as
it went I just kept being like no this is good this is good and then it just kept getting better
and better and I was like you know what this is a really good flick man and I enjoyed I also enjoyed
there were some very cool like visual things he did that were neat like like I loved when he showed
what Harley Quinn like sort of saw and felt as she was killing everybody when it was all
rose petals and like whatever and it was this sort of metaphoric thing of like I'm a queen and
every man is always treating me like shit and I should be be showered with roses and I'm
instead I'm being forced to murder all of you I love that I love when they tell polka dot man like
pretend the starfishes your mom and you see that the giant version of a mom and it's just it's just
a mom it's like the most midwestern regular plane housewife mom it was so perfectly cast it was really
funny man yeah I thought that was awesome and then also when he's in the club that whole club sequence
was great but when he's like grinding on all those women and they all turn into his mom you know
really great memorable quick visual gags like that you just don't see the real tragedy is unfortunately
it bombed and a big part of that is of course coronavirus and it bombed financially it's so well
reviewed it did yeah well reviewed but it bombed financially and everybody's like but they put it
on HBO Max at the same time and we don't really know yet how much of a bite that takes out of the box
off as blah blah blah but we need movies like this to succeed so that our big budget popular
entertainment gets good and exciting and weird again and different again and it's I think that's a real
unfortunately I know this has been a very depressing podcast in spots but like that might be the
final nail in like weird personal filmmaking getting into these big franchises anymore and that sucks
uh it it could be who knows you know I mean especially if dune bombs you know because then it'll be
like okay so the artists are done we're gonna go back shit look I mean it's also it's got its own
thing it's got its own personality you know I'll give it that and here's the part of this movie that
nobody I don't hear at least anybody praising maybe they are maybe they're not here's a movie that
didn't shoehorn in any message didn't hit you over the head with the diversity thing or anything
like that uh those things are good in movies I'm not saying they're not but when they're obvious it
hurts the quality of your film when it sounds like the writer is telling you something that you need
to know or preaching to you it hurts everybody knows that this is an incredibly diverse film
and an incredibly empowering example yeah to women film and and it's never called out
it's never called out there's never like some needless black joke about Idris Elba there's never
some uh pandering female thing towards rat catcher or towards Harley Quinn or there's none of that
it's just a big diverse cast of people yeah and it works and it's awesome I love how fucking
sinister Amanda Waller is in this I love seeing viola Davis as a play I'm like I just a piece of
shit she's great they let her go unhinged in this like they really let her go nuts and scream and
everything and that was that was all funny I actually thought the rat catcher subplot was kind of
beautiful I thought it was great and when all the rats came it see that's that's another thing
and that's really all screenwriting is people like at the end of the day to make subcell is set up
and payoffs and this movie had a million little setups and payoffs and so when you go to the movies
next you'll realize how few movies have this but where you just set up a bunch of shit at the beginning
and you pay it off at the end John Sain is first line about how his bullets are so small they go into
other bullets and they're more deadly or whatever was super funny but you think of it as a throw -off
joke then at the end they actually show you the smaller bullet going into the bigger bullet and
that's a great payoff you know like and and gun is so smart about just lining them up
and knocking them down I'm also the guys on top of the world right now I'm glad I didn't cancel
him by the way yeah yeah and the out of sequence stuff was really well done how like
you'd get invested in something and then I would say eight minutes earlier and then it would show
you what was happening and then it would rat that would connect back to the thing you were
already watched yeah and you know it was it was it was just a fun a very very fun super hero movie
which in this in this in this economy and climate it's that's a hard thing to pull off I mean it is
so oversaturated I even loved a little meanwhile you know and stuff like that in the in the roots and
all that I just it's a movie that felt like a comic book felt like comic book and it felt like the
director cared about every minute of it and cared about just ringing out Max entertainment and he
did and I hope that David air gets to release his cut of the first one because that this is not a
reboot they keep going this a reboot it's not a reboot it's a sequel like their characters from the
first one Rick flag is back same actor Harley Quinn's back same actor Amanda wall was back same actor
captain boomerangs back same actor it's the same universe it's a secret who is Amanda Waller why is
that not not biola Davis is a man to waller oh okay that character I even infants as I was like
oh biola Davis I suppose I never hear characters names it's a big regret of mine I don't hear them
I only know it because I only know that because she's like in the comic book she's a pretty prominent
character so yeah um anyway but she uh but this is a sequel to that movie I hope David air gets to
release his cut because he keeps saying what you saw was not my movie what you saw sucked
and Zack Snyder proved that to be true with the with the Snyder cut of Justice League and uh that was
back to back with that suicide squad movie and I think it's the same fucking thing um you know I ran
online somebody said like help hissed off his David air because he must watch this and be like oh cool
you just let James gun make a James gun movie but yeah you chopped a shit and ruined it and honestly
I I want to see Quinn and Lido back together as Joker and I want to see it you know I think there's
there's stuff there to be mined and and uh hopefully that happens but in the meantime it's too big
super hogs up for the suicide squad indeed uh yes that is it for us we're going to be back next week
with or not next week you know how this works we drop them at the same damn time uh we'll be doing
the Green Knight the new Sword and Swarsory film oh yeah uh so I don't have what you know as always
Twitter Instagram Texas Forever podcast discussing Friday night lights a buddy Scott Weinberg's over
hated podcast discussing Freddie got fingered you know there was a comedy on Instagram and Twitter
and uh if you want more of me you can check me out on taste buds no press network channel on YouTube
and that's it folks we'll talk to you soon and we'll talk to you in hell