Welcome to We'll see you in hell it's the podcast you turn to when you want
to hear the talk about your favorite movies or maybe even a few movies you didn't like so much,
which may or may not be the case today, spoiler alert. I'm Joe DeRosa. Hey Joe, thank you for
keeping spoiler alert alive. You know, I thought it was what they call and comedy a clam, you know,
something that's just been used too much and it's not funny anymore, but you're out there keeping
it alive. I'll do it. I say it in conversation still. It's one of those things that's always funny
and yet people, people judge you now for using it. It's too old. It's, it's past its sell by date.
Right. I'll do a dead a dinner thing in a restaurant. I go spoiler alert. Yeah. The fondue is amazing.
Okay. Do stuff like that with it. I have fun with it. You know, I do it when somebody's like so I'm
watching Casablanca the other night and Ingrid Bergman said, whoa, whoa, whoa, spoiler alert. I like it
when it's an old film. Right. You know, yeah, yeah, where I've had time, you know, to watch it, but
do you think guys in the food market use it a lot about the food going bad?
You're in the food game. You tell me not around my place. We don't do it.
But I wonder maybe more of a supermarket fish counter scenario. Probably they're using that
spoiler alert term a lot when they got to get rid of the shrimp or whatever, you know, I bet somebody's
done it. I bet somebody's done it. Somebody must have. Do you think that we are being served food
that went bad during the pandemic? That people are just kind of trying to pull it off at this point
when we go to restaurant. I think there certainly is some leeway being taken with foods. Look,
I just actually had to take a food exam to get a certification and I learned a lot.
But one thing I know is like the shelf life time limits of food like according to like FDA standards
are extremely small. I'm not saying so don't follow them. You got to follow them. But yeah, I wouldn't
be surprised if some people are pushing the envelope a little bit now like, you know, we're two days
past what you're supposed to be, but it's it looks fine and smells fine. We could still serve it or
I also would I have definitely encountered is going to places that like on the menu, it'll say like
bison burger or something that they clearly can't get anymore and they just won't say anything
and just give you a regular burger and you're like this, you know, that I've noticed a lot of
and you don't really complain because you feel bad because everybody's trying to do their best.
But that's fucked up. You have to tell people they're changed their menu. I'm getting a lot of
work out of that. Yeah, I'm getting a lot of like I only go to a few places in my neighborhood.
So like when the food comes, I know what it's supposed to look like and what it's supposed to be.
I've ordered it 50 times since I've lived here and it'll come much smaller or with shittier
ingredients or and again, you're not going to grab anybody by the lapels and throw them against the
the soup pot, you know. You know, restaurants that have a soup pot just out in the dining room.
I'm picturing in like a mob movie what you'd mash somebody's face against in the kitchen and I
oh, I was for some reason picturing a big bubbling pot of clam chowder. I always think the flat top
grill is the sure that's the scariest one. Right. I wanted to say something while I got you folks,
I for whatever reason, oh, I know what the reason was, I played one of my own Joe's old podcast
because somebody told me, hey, the one where you guys talk about Pizza Hut Dracula. I believe was the
blade episode and Emily was like Joe was talking about how vampires and movies don't have to always
be eating blood. You don't have to go to a restaurant and order a glass of blood like they can
they can have pizza or something. Right. Right. Right. And it led to this big discussion of Pizza Hut
Dracula, but in the middle of the damn thing, just as I noticed in the middle of the classic
Bert Young story, it was interrupted with ads. And I'm like, look, these get a lot of listens,
people still talk about them and listen to them and they're chock full of ads. Everyone you hit
play and it starts with an ad. Joe and I have been on so many networks. I don't even know who's
getting money off this, but I know it ain't me and Joe. Yeah. We ain't getting time one. So that
was kind of annoying. And I was like, we should try to figure this out. But for the first time in
probably two years, I looked at our reviews and our reviews were always at a solid five stars.
I never saw it anything less. The issue is Joe has haters out there at the game from his days,
you know, to being on the shock, jock radio circuit pissed off some of the wrong people.
And he gets people who were like, this would be podcast would be great if Joe was dead, you know,
stuff like that, where you're like, okay, this isn't necessarily, but if it fucks with our overall
reviews. So if you've never thrown us a review, even if you just click the star rating, go do it.
I hear podcasts ask for this all the time and it seems desperate. But when I saw we were at a four
or five, I'm like, Hey guys, you know, help us out. Get us up four or five is nothing to shake a
stick. Okay. Nothing to shake a stick. And, you know, a lot of it was Joe stuff. And then I'll,
you know, we've always had this where it's people who stumble and go, they barely talk about the movie.
So that's somebody who just is not going to like what we do. Although I think in recent years,
we talked more about the move. Could you imagine caring enough to leave a review for a thing you
heard one time now? I mean, my God almighty. The one I saw was like, you know, we're 15 minutes
into this thing and they haven't even mentioned, you know, Nightmare on Elm Street six yet. It's like,
all right, guys. Yeah. But when I saw that stuck with me, though, Joe, and I really didn't know how to
react. I mean, it's with a lot of things you get presented with these days where you're like, all right,
I have to really think about this. And maybe I'm wrong because a lot of stuff's changing rapidly.
But it was a young lady who said she loved the show, but wished that you and I didn't talk so much
about women's appearances. And do we? You know, surely if we're talking about a pretty lady,
we remark that she's pretty. But I feel like we also do that with fellas. We talk about, you know,
Gosling and, you know, we always give people shout outs. So I was, I was like, okay, maybe that's
fucked up that we do do that. But then I also kind of think these people are movie stars,
like a big part of a movie star is that people are going to talk about the way you look, you know,
so I don't know. I apologize. If we do, I'm not saying we'll never talk about a woman being
attractive again, or a dude. But I mean, I do get when you're feeling like shit and you hear someone
talk about how hot somebody is. It makes him mad and everybody's feeling like shit at this moment
in time. We're not the kinds of guys who were like, I mean, the jugs on this one, man, you know,
like I don't think I can recall or a couple of times recently you had said, I saw a movie with
so and so she's in a great actor. She looks amazing. Yeah, that kind of thing. And then I know I've
gone in on Elizabeth Moss pretty hard as being gross looking because she is and she's an asshole
of a human. No, she sucks. Fuck her. I think they're saying is keep it on their actions. I saw
this a lot with Trump to keep it on his actions. And it's like, okay, but it only applies when it's,
when it's on the liberal side of the thing. You know, everybody called Trump fat in disgusting
and a pig and all these things. And nobody nobody once said that's fucked up. Yeah. No, that's true.
That's true. I if you're my take on it is this. If you if I think you're an asshole, all bets are
off. I'm attacking every part of you. I don't give a shit. That's my thing. That's that's how I,
but you we don't share that. You you you have a very different opinion. But at the same time,
I don't think we do that a lot either. I think I've only really done that with
one Elizabeth Moss, who I really have a disdain for. But only because she's part of an organization
that tortures children. I mean, call me crazy. Sure. But you don't go after after T Cruz because he
doesn't he doesn't brag. I think she's I don't think she's an asshole because she's a Scientologist.
I think she's an asshole because every time she wins an award, she preaches about how we need to be
better people. Right. If Tom Cruz did that, then I'd be like, fuck you, Tom Cruz. Yeah. You know,
and maybe I'd make fun of I mean, it's tough to find something on Tommy to make fun of in the physical
department. I mean, it is going strong. He's a he's a Picasso baby. He's a masterpiece. A masterpiece.
A make them say that said in respect to this woman's criticism. You know, yeah,
it's never our goal to sit here. You know, I would never be like Paul Blart too sucked because Kevin
James is fat. Yeah. You know, I wouldn't do that. You know what I mean? Like, I don't think
I mean, that sucked up. Her issue was was with women and stuff. And I think, you know, it's weird.
I'm doing a pitch with an with an actor and I had a joke in it about him being a hottie. You
know, right. And he was like, you know, I don't think we should do this joke. He said, because I think
now it's okay to talk about men as objects and and and their bodies and their faces. But it's on
the line. Women, it's not okay anymore. But men, I think it's it's okay. But I don't want to be the
last one to sneak in before they change it. And I'm like, I don't think it has to be that strict.
If you go into any city in America, people are talking about how hot an actress is or you know,
did you know, and women are just as bad. I mean, I'm listening to my wife talk about the sex
of the city ladies. They released the picture of the new cast. You know, they did. Who's the new cast?
Those news, quick news psycho. Who's the new cast? It's the it's the three ladies. It's just it's
not a new cast. They just don't have Kim control. It was it was the it was a picture of them like reunited.
And they didn't replace control with anybody like with a like with a West Indian transsexual
not a legit woman. They did. It's not an official replay. There's no one's going to be in the group
anymore. But they have added three new diverse women that I'm sure will be very much a part of the
circle. And is it and is it a passing of the torch? I don't think so because they weren't like
20. They already tried to do the young sex in the city and it was canceled immediately.
That's I'm such a fan of the show. These movies just keep getting worse though, man. This
got almighty. I don't know what we're walking into. And they picked it up for six, which is very odd.
You know, like you think could be a big event. Oh, it's a TV show. I thought it was just a third
movie. You know, Jesus. I mean, people hammer George Lucas for like crystal skull in the
Star Wars prequels. It's like, that shit doesn't hold a candle to what they did in those sex
of the city movies, man. That second one, especially was outrageous. I saw two in that theater all
two hours and 40 minutes of it. And it was it was jaws on the floor throughout. I saw that on a date.
Yeah, with a woman that was I wanted to have sex with so badly that I agreed to go see that movie.
And I snuck out. Unfortunately, it was Cynthia Nixon. It was your day to the premiere. You didn't know.
History. I snuck out. I said, I had to go to the bathroom. Or I said, I had to take a phone call
because I knew I could it could I could take longer. If you say yeah, after me, you're gone for 40 minutes,
you know, yeah, some quite, you know, looks kind of like you're taking a dump. But I said I had to
take a business call. And I went out and I snuck into you don't mess with the zoe hand. And I just sat
in there and watch that for a while. Wow. And then went back to sex in the city. I was like, I can't
do this, man. It was so bad. That opening lies a Monella performing single ladies at age 80. I mean,
that's something that'll stick with me until the day I die. Yeah, yeah. And clearly it was such,
such a good scene. Eddie Murphy said, we have to do a version of this in coming to America. Yeah,
they did. We're salt and pepper come out and sing what a king. Well, we we really weren't even
hard enough on that movie. I mean, what a nothing. I thought about it since I get angry every time I
think about it. Yeah. A man. Well, my friend, your main that he didn't get a better God damn it.
The whole thing just pisses me off. And I was talking this week about comedy sequels a little bit
with Joe because, you know, here's some big news for you all. It's not really screaming. And but it's
it's, you know, this movie is a big part of this podcast. They have announced in development.
King pin two. Uh -huh. The fairly brothers don't know if they're going to direct.
There's no announcement on cast. There's no announcement on time period. So maybe they're keeping
things under wraps. But I told Joe it can't be Randy Quaid. He's lost his mind. He lives in a cave
with his wife. I also said, go ahead, a good idea. The best idea. They'll never do it, obviously. But
now the character has become Randy Quaid, like where he's this political wild man. He's always
drunk. And they have to re -amish him. They have to save the homage community by bringing him back.
It's the opposite of the first movie. It'll be fucking hilarious. He's got to break big urn in
immediately because he's like, nobody knows a scumbag like Big Urn. Like, well, you know, maybe he's
being mentored by Big Urn at this point. Right. Whatever. I mean, you know, uh, God damn it. That would
be such a good idea. But I feel like it's going to end up being like, Randy Quaid has this, I
wouldn't be surprised if they brought Randy in for a small quick, like, you know, like an Eddie furlong
and terminator. It's, it's conceivable that they might do something with him. Yes.
My thinking, unfortunately, and this is probably how they had to pitch it to get it made,
is that they'll be a new young recruit. And we're going to be looking at Zac Efron and Amish Garb,
or we're going to be looking at Zac Efron just as a kid off the street or something.
But that's my worries. It's a new hot young recruit. Uh, Woody was somehow 35 when
Kingpin was made the original. Now this, this made me sit myself down and take a long look at my life.
He was 35. I mean, they made him look terrible and gave him the coma or everything. But now Woody is
60. He looks better than he did in Kingpin for sure. Um, so my thinking is maybe he's got the
million dollars still from the, uh, the condom rubber hand bowling tournament that he wins at the end
of the original. He's married to Vanessa Angel who they're also not going to give a leading role to
in 2021. So maybe, maybe Big Earn is fucking Angel or maybe she leaves Woody for Big Earn.
My take on it is this. They're going to hit a reset button. Angel won't be in it.
It's going to be Woody Harrelson is down in the dumps again because she left him and his life
is a mess again. Yeah. He finds a new kid, new opportunity and he needs to enlist the help of Big Earn.
And it's going to be Woody Big Earn and the new kid on the road trip or whatever it is for the
entire movie. And I think I like that. And the rivalry between Big Earn and Woody and all that
shit. Sure. I think that's what it'll be. We shall see. I mean, you would think if they don't have
Murray and Harrelson, we wouldn't be hearing about this. I mean, that I would hope. But then again,
no dumb and dumb or two had had Carrie and Daniels. It just had nothing else. I'll tell you this,
go get Keaton and Carrie. And I know we don't have Farley now, but do the version with those two
and whoever a newer funny fat dude is. Look, I'll take Kevin James is the,
as a promise kid, I would enjoy that thoroughly. Look, if we got to put Gatt in this picture,
I'll take it. If it brings it to the silver screen, you know, I was excited, but you got to be
cautiously optimistic. I mean, you could talk, you could do six episodes about bad comedy sequels.
There's, there's a long rich history. What do you think the worst comedy sequel of all time is?
I mean, I think the obvious answer is Caddy Shack too. But Shack too is horrible. I mean, for me,
it's got to be something I saw theatrically where I was excited because then it like analyze,
analyze that is horrible. But I didn't love the first one so much that it destroyed me.
I kind of like analyze that. I don't hate it.
I analyze that. There's, I mean, Dumber Dumber 2 sucked for sure compared to the original.
Never saw it. There's, I mean, there's some of the masks.
Those ones I kind of don't count because I'm like, it's so far removed from the original at that
point. It's like Ace Ventura, the young boy detective or like dumb and dumber or I'm like,
all right, these aren't really, these aren't really like, there's got to be a little more coherence,
you know, and consistency with the original. Like coming to America is one of the worst I've ever seen.
For sure. Yeah. Bill and Ted faced the music, honestly. And you know what, the guy in front of me on
the plane last night was laughing so hard at Bill and Ted faced the music. And I can't, I just
don't get it. I don't understand. What bullshit. I remember seeing Men in Black 2 in the theater and
being appalled, you know, and that franchise got even worse. With the third one. Yeah, hang over two
and three are awful films, you know, I mean, I watched a thing. This is the, this is why Hollywood sucks.
Or just one of the many reasons. I watched a video the other day. It was called the 23 Unmade
Films of Tim Burton. It was like all the things Tim Burton almost did. Yeah. One of them was quasi -modo,
starring Josh Brolin. God's sake. So I was like, well, that could be interesting. I don't know.
And they cut to the video in the YouTube cuts to a clip of Josh Brolin talking about the film.
And he's like, oh, it's happening. It's happening next year. And then I realized the interview is
from Men in Black 3. He's talking about this thing like they've got the sets built already.
And I was like, this, what the fuck with this business, man? Like I just don't understand why everything
goes through development, how, why it's definitely going to happen, then it never happens.
It's absurd. It's absurd. It happens all the time. And if Brolin is saying it's definitely happening,
they, they had already put several million into it, script drafts, etc. We're never going to
see that movie. I gotta tell you, I mean, even with Burton and Brolin, I have, I don't need to see
the fucking quasi -modo story with Josh Brolin. You kidding me? I mean, I wasn't excited to see it.
I just thought it was interesting. But I mean, you watched this, this video, I can't
remember the channel I saw it on. But if you watched this video, you realized Tim Burton is,
I always thought Tim Burton used to be good. Now he sucks. I don't think that's the case.
I think Tim Burton is a guy that just got tired of fighting. I mean, they talk about the shit
they put him through in this thing and like, and he's just like, but oh, this is another cool
news cycle. It's official. Keaton and Burton are signed on for Beetlejuice too. So I'm excited
about that. They announced it officially. Joe, I saw that news story five years ago. But they,
those Hawaiian. But it went, no, it went away and all this stuff. And then like two weeks ago,
they said it's a film. Keaton is officially signed on. This is happening. And I also thought
this was cool. Keaton, because he's coming back in the Flash movie as Batman, or as one of the
Batman's. And then his spin off apparently is going to be Batman Beyond, which is the rumor
where it's old Bruce Wayne training the new Batman or whoever, right? And Keaton apparently is
heavily pushing for Burton to direct that so they can finally complete a full trilogy arc of
their Batman story, which I think would be really cool. I would, I'd be excited about that.
It would. I mean, it's the only Burton thing I'm getting excited about these days is
now he does 10 for them, one for me. And I'm always hanging out for that one for him. The big
guys sucked. But I at least was like excited that he was doing something that didn't cause 500
million dollars. I don't know. He's a great, a great letdown to me. But I think you're right about
him. He probably fought for every little detail of those first masterpieces to get him on his
own terms, how he wanted everything to look and feel. And now he just rolls over because he's making
too much money and he's tired of fighting. You get sick of it. You watch this thing. It's 90 minutes
dude. Yeah. And it starts with like a 20 minute thing about his Pinocchio thing that he was going to
do and how cool the vision was. And he was going to do this dark true to the book version of it. And
Disney was like, we don't want to do that. We don't want to, you know, a lot, it's funny. The
recurring theme in a lot of the segments is Tim Burton said, we already have the Disney version.
Now I want to do the real version. And then look at Tim Burton now. His last movie was Dumbo
produced by Disney. Right. And it was not good at all. So it's a bummer, man. It's a real bummer.
But what can you do? Nothing. Nothing. Did you take us down to that movie corner,
Walsh? Unless you were going to see something else. No, I was going to talk about in the heights.
The big thing, I didn't watch in the heights, but the big thing this weekend, they were like
it was a bomb. It was supposed to make 20 million and it only made 13. It's like, well, hang on.
It was supposed to make 20. Who's deciding? It's available on HBO Max. So a lot of people probably
said, I'll watch it here for free. It's just the guy. The whole thing is dog shit. I don't
even know. I don't care enough to stand up for fucking in the heights. It's Lin -Man well. He'll be fine.
But it's like, now we're in this place where oh, quiet place, kick the shit out of in the
heights this weekend. And I'm like, well, yeah, quiet place is only available in the theaters.
How do you not factor that in? We're going to have a whole new world unless you want to pay $30
to stream it. I got to get my ass over there to see Cruella. I want to do it for the show.
I'm hearing good things. I would like to do it on the show.
You know, I've heard it described as the best of the best DC movies like what they're trying to do
with DC, but Cruella did it better. I have no knowledge of that, but I liked the film fine.
It was pretty entertaining. Way too long. Do an episode. All right, I saw, well, let me start with
kind of the most discussed film of our time these days. I know Joe Washington, well, as well,
certainly the Twitter discourse is getting into it almost as much as they did with
what's your face? Mandy. What was the lady's name? Mumford.
The lady who yelled at us for an hour and scolded us and called it a comedy special.
Who? Nanette. Oh, Nanette. Nanagats, but yeah. Oh, God.
No, look, that was kind of the one that really kicked things off with a, is this comedy? Why is comedy
so sad now, whatever? And look, that wasn't for me. I felt it, you know, we already discussed that on
this show. Bo Burnham's inside. I liked significantly more. The odds are that's because I am an
extremely depressed white guy who was stuck inside all year like Bo Burnham. I understand that,
but I think the kid is a genius. As with a lot of young geniuses, there's a little bit of an
annoyance factor that a lot of people, you know, people just start throwing shit at it. Like,
I didn't like this. I didn't like this and it's self -indulgent. And I saw somebody today being like,
how did he look at all this footage of his face close up? What to edit it? What a narcissist?
It's like, guys, he was alone inside. Jesus. Yeah. As they put up their eighth selfie of the day.
Yeah. Exactly. Best hashtag, best life. Oh, God. There's an annoyance so strong that when I turned it on,
I watched one minute of it, shut it off and said, I'm never watching this fucking thing.
However, when I returned to it, it completely worked on me. I watched all 90 minutes in one sitting.
I feel like that's too long for a comedy special, but it didn't feel long. I felt my jealousy
melting away. A lot of people's reaction is jealousy. And it's also knowing that they could have
done something like this over the last year, but instead they sat inside, fearing death,
watching movies, overeating, drinking. I did the exact same thing. There's a lot of complicated
feelings around it when someone's like, look what I did. And you didn't do shit. It hurts.
It hurts a creative person. That's what I think a lot of the backlash is because there's not much to
take issue with. I'm not a comedy song guy, but the comedy songs are really funny. He's got kind of
that weird owl nasal thing that's that can grate a little bit. Songs are very well written and funny.
He hits you with a acoustic song near the end that had me openly crying. I thought it had some
amazing lines in it. And there was a lot of good comedy, a lot of a fresh feeling comedy. A 90 minute
special should not feel this consistent and fresh throughout, especially one that he's been working on
for so long. It's really the only piece of entertainment about the pandemic that I felt
worked or affected me or moved me in any way. I think it's something very special. And I'll
probably never watch it again. It was very depressing too. I will also do this as my first selection
for today. I loved it. I think Bose is a genius. I've always thought he was a genius. I've been
impressed with him thoroughly from the beginning, from all of his early stuff up through now.
I thought this was arguably the best thing he's ever done. I was thoroughly impressed at his ability
to shoot record every aspect of this thing that he did himself. All of it looked beautiful. All of
it sounded brilliant. All of it was so incredibly written and so funny and so scathing. And that I
don't need to go out of my way to pick on Hannah Gatsby. But the argument I've always had with somebody
when I say I don't like it is, it's not funny to just preach at me and then get a clause breaks.
Right. There's got to be some kind of wit there, like there has to be, which is why the older you get
not that Bill Hicks was not a witty man, but the later Bill Hicks stuff, the older you get,
the more annoying it gets. Because you're like, dude, I'm not 32 anymore. And like I'm not
this angsty. And like, yeah, I don't, I'm not that mad at Rush Limbaugh, you know, that I'm just
going to clap at the, you know, the crafter thing or whatever. So hard does this now. If you watch
one minute of his monologue, you'll see him stare at the audience till they applaud like twice in a
minute period. It's embarrassing. So opinions are great. And opinions are valid. I think Bill Mar has
good opinions. I think Hannah Gatsby has some good opinions. I don't think they're good at comedy,
though. Right. So that's the difference. Bo Burnham, on the other hand, I think weaves a social
commentary into a shiny bubblegum sounding electropop vehicle. And without hitting you over the head,
it's it's biting and it's irreverent and it's sharp. And the disdain this man has for
celebrity and Hollywood. And and then also calls himself out on it for being a hypocrite and all
that stuff. Like, yeah, it's amazing. Getting ahead of, you know, the problematic stuff he did when
he was 19, you know, it's like, that's a pretty good way to get around this. Just make a song about
it and say like, yeah, I said some fucked up shit. And here we are. And it's it's all stuff that
like done slightly left or right. And I don't mean politically. I just mean slightly different
would have annoyed the fuck out of me. And it's also it's a special where I think your mood is pretty
crucial to it. You know, like, I don't know. I as I said, when I started at the first time, I said
I'll never watch this again. And I wound up completely loving it. But it's an experience. You know,
it's it's it really is the only thing I've seen that tries to kind of make sense of the past year.
He released it at the perfect time because we're not quite still in it.
It made it super personal that he was like finally ready to face the world again. And then this
happened. And he scared again and back inside it ends almost just sparing, you know, he's sobbing
at the end of this thing. It really is miserable. But it's kind of cathartic at the same time.
Generally, a young man sobbing in his own comedy special that he is filming himself
would piss me off. It would make me start going, was he really crying? He's a great. He's a good actor.
Was he acting? And this I just didn't care. I saw it as this big performance art piece that he killed.
He nailed it. It's it's really, really good. What's your second one? My second one is
Well, are we going to do the dentist on here? Probably at some point. I'll leave it. Yeah. I think we'll do it at some point.
I watched Shiva Baby starring a very funny follow on Twitter named Rachel Senate. I don't know her personally,
but she's funny directed it by Emma Siliconman who I think will probably be seeing a lot of. It's a very
short movie, which I love. 78 minutes. It is a college student who attends a Shiva. It's a very,
it feels almost like a lighter uncut gems because it's it's very a serious man. You know, it's very rooted
in Judaism. There's a lot of like, you know, Jewish comedy in this. That's really, really funny.
She attends a Shiva where she is accosted by her relatives, outshined by her ex -girlfriend.
And face to face with her sugar daddy. This guy that she's fucking for money is randomly at the
Shiva as well. I feel like uncut gems is probably an inspiration. And it's like, let's just look at
like a personal a small smaller stakes version of it. So it's just one of those movies where around
every corner is a problem. It's a very anxiety inducing movie, but it's also really, really funny.
It feels like in a world where we still have to pretend these Woody Allen movies are worth
watching. Like this is somebody who should just take the crown because it's it's got a sort of a
similar feel. Sci -able men is in it. Always hilarious. Supporting cast is great. I really liked it.
It's what it's three bucks to rent, but I'm sure it'll be on Hulu in a week. I really liked
throwing it back to Tim Burton. You know what, I'll close with the Tim Burton one. I watched a
little picture called What Happened Was on Criterion. No, it was gifted to me by the very kind Michelle
over at oscilloscope labs. It was one of the movies I got. It was it was written and directed
and based on a play by Tom. This is named Tom Noonan from from Noonan from everything. Yeah.
What a great little haunting hilarious dark picture. It's brilliant. I'm actually bummed that Tom
didn't do more as a writer director and play writer. It's on Criterion channel now. They're giving
them a little shout. Yeah, they just re -released this thing, I guess, or officially released it
properly or something like a year ago or this year. And I'm a big Tom Noonan fan, even though I
couldn't remember his name. The other actor in it, I had never heard of, but she's fantastic. What's
her name? It's a son of a bitch. Yeah, I was unfamiliar with her. Her name is Karen Silas.
She's really amazing. And when I watched the bonus features, seeing the interview with her
from now and seeing that she is, she sounds nothing like the character she's playing in the movie.
I was like, even like, you know, doubly impressed or whatever. Yeah.
Really cool interview watching Tom Noonan talk about the film too. I've never seen an interview
with Tom Noonan. The only thing I've ever seen him do is act and whenever he acts, he's
always a super weird or eccentric character. So it's fun just getting to see him talk and
kind of laugh in whatever and be just be a guy. But you know, it's about a 70 minute movie,
about an extremely awkward date. And at one point, it turns into almost a horror thing and then
it swings back. It's a dark, dark, disturbing and very funny film. I highly recommend it. And I'd
say especially if you're thirsting for something in that 90s indie film, you know, you mentioned
Woody Allen and and and Shiva Baby being the modern version of that. This is from the early 90s. But
if that's your thing, you'll like this quite a bit. All right. I watched it in college probably.
I barely remember it, but I do need to watch it on criteria again. I watched finally finished
Mare of East town starring Miss Kate Winslet. I think it's an easy recommend. I mean, it's a really
good little mystery with a lot of great character detail. Kate Winslet is really good. Gene Smart is
really good. And it's just well done. It's it's it being an HBO thing. I was like, is this
going to be one of those deals we're at the end? We don't know who did it because people that's
almost 50 % now of documentaries and these mystery shows. They just don't tell you things, which can
feel extremely unsatisfying. Even if in a documentary, they just don't know. It's just like, well,
then why did I watch this for 10 hours? Mare of East town is, I want to say seven or eight
episodes. It's really solid. Kate Winslet's accent was, I think, justifiably mocked. She basically,
she talks in an American accent and then she'll throw in one Philly word. So it should be like, yeah,
you know, I went over there and I was going to have a higgy like the Philly accent or like,
well, I went over to the water and then those right. It's like, no, you don't get to just pick
the occasional word to do the accent on. But outrageous casting. It's not outrageous casting.
And she's talking at one point, it's her and Guy Pierce. And I'm like, him too. It's like,
there's three people in this thing playing Philadelphia nights who are from, you know, all the way across
like Yorkshire. Yeah. It's, it's so strange. Are we shooting in South Philly today?
No, like doing like an Eric Idol character. Right. No, it's, it's weird to me. And HBO's the
biggest offender of it. I haven't heard anyone, I guess because it's why people play on why people
nobody cares. But it's like, I know you're not going to find actress from Philly every time. But
man, why is every actor on an HBO show not from America playing Americans? It makes no sense to me.
And they'll say things like, well, you know, that that outsider perspective really helps them understand
Americans better than we understand ourselves. No, it doesn't. Shut up.
Shut the hell up. He also just heard that she sold us like a $6 million apartment in New York.
And I was like, Kate Winslet has side apartment in New York that costs $6 million money. Yeah.
She was in Titanic. Yeah. But like, you don't keep getting money from Titanic. You get what you made.
Of course you do. You get residuals. She absolutely. Yeah. That's how the actors get residuals
for being in Titanic. Yeah. Yeah. I guess they do. Okay. Yeah. She's, she's been in a few
huge ones. And then she works in everything all the time. So it's like, you know, she's great. But
but yeah, so I don't think she should play a Philly. No. She's very good in it. I mean, like, it's just
you have to pretty much, especially, you know, people who've been to Philly or lived in Philly. I'm
sure like, what are we doing here guys? But it's a stacked cast. There's a lot of great people in it.
The mysteries really work. There is, they have some of these like red herring threads where you're like,
you know, there's one episode where you're basically following the ins and outs of a college radio
station and this young lesbian couple who are having trouble and it's like, what's going on guys?
Like, let's get back to it. But by and large, it all works. It builds to a very clearly speaking
silence of the lambs, a silence of the lambs inspired scene where mayor goes to kind of rescue the
people who are missing. That comes not it's not even in the final episode. So it's not a spoiler. But
that's really an exciting, suspenseful episode, some are better than others. But when I look back
at the whole experience, it's a solid B plus. I recommend the show. All right. My final is Tim Burton
film. I watched dark shadows. Which is really dark shadows on here, Joe. I did it already. Yeah.
Shit. All right. I watched goose bumps. You did goose bumps, Joe. I did? Yeah. Wait a minute.
I did these. You did them. Oh boy. Shit. Your glasses are on your face, Alice.
All right. You know what? I don't have another one. I'm going to save these other ones for the next
episode. All right. Aren't you watching a show? You going through Frazier again?
You watching just the 10 of us sell again. Sure. Sure. Good stuff. Anyway,
let's move on to our movie. Now we were we haven't announced what today's movie is. Now Pat,
we've been going at it a little while here. I don't almost say we pivot and just do Quiet Place 2
and save AOD for the next episode. So we can really dig into that thing. I'm all right with that. Yeah,
what? Yeah. Quiet Place 2 is, you know, Joe walk us through the plot. But if this one,
these two writers, the guys who did Haunt, these two young guys, wrote the original Quiet Place.
Krasinski comes on board as director and he shoe horns his name into the writing credits.
Now for part 2, the guys are gone. It's just Krasinski. He's just excited now. I'm enough of a writer
that I should I should be in charge of this huge franchise. And look, I think Krasinski is a solid
director, a surprisingly good director. It remains to be seen. That could be that could be 100 %
the crew in the DP. It's very well good. But I think he's he's, you know, does a solid job or a solid
job is most other up and coming horror directors of doing this type of material. But as a writer,
boy, this one, I mean, as Joe pointed out, we discussed this last time. I loved it drunk on
opening night. When I watched it again, there were plot holes I could not ignore. Joe did a great
job of pointing them out. But like there, I was also kind of like, how did I miss this shit?
This movie plays is a whole new ballgame. This part 2, it plays basically as a love letter
from John Krasinski to John Krasinski. His character died in the last one. Pointlessly, stupidly,
unnecessarily. Now in this one, he not only wrote it, as you pointed out, not only directed it as you
pointed out, figured out a way to get his character back in through a flashback sequence in the opening.
That really has nothing to do with the rest of the movie. It's not like it's a prequel. It's not
like this flashback really sets anything up. It's just a flashback so he can be in the movie.
And quickly, that flashback you've seen in its entirety, it was the trailer of the movie.
And it's where Blount is kind of driving backwards, trying to get away from the giant bugs.
It's a great set. It's a great action sequence. But that's not a good representation of the film.
Yeah. So then he's also got himself in the trailer.
Yeah. And then after this flashback, they jump back to the timeline of the original,
the ending of the original film. And every character in the family for the rest of the movie
chastises other people about how their dad was a better man than that person will ever be.
Talks about we wish dad was here because he took such good care of us. Not one mention of mom,
this lady trudging through the through the sticks with these kids or feet or bleeding.
Not one nod to like the strength of this woman, nothing. It's all about dad, dad, dad.
Even got Emily Blount who they've now, and I don't understand, they set her up at the end of
the last film as like she's going to be the ass kicker now. And I thought she was going to be the
swinging hero in this thing. She's barely in the goddamn movie. They shuffle her off to the side.
Like she's she's a secondary thought in this thing. Silly and Murphy pretty much takes the helm.
And the reason Silly and Murphy takes the helm is because he's a distant neighbor that they
eventually get to his farm. And he's the guy with the fires in the first movie you find out.
And Emily Blount shows up there with her kids. He's like, you can't stay here. I can accommodate
all three of you, plus a baby, plus me. They say, fuck you, we're staying. And then they give him
shit. Why didn't you ever come for us? It's like you didn't go for him either. Yeah.
And then Emily Blount gives some soliloquy about what a great man her husband was. And then their daughter
who is deaf, whose deaf decides I'm going to go out on my own because if I can get to the radio station,
I can project this signal from my earpiece that will we can weaponize against the alien invaders.
So she runs off without anybody's permission, even though her brother begs her not to.
And now Emily Blount chastises Silly and Murphy, again, you need to go get my daughter.
It's so at this point in the movie, I'm like, hey lady, fuck you. Don't get your own daughter.
It makes no sense. It makes no sense whatsoever. So that's basically what the catapult of the plot.
You're following a true A and B story, almost like it's a sitcom. You know, like it's blunt in her
crew and it's Murphy and the deaf girl kind of parallel stories. They are so devoid of suspense.
Like it's just, it's not written properly. It's not, it's not a movie that advances the plot of
the original in any way. It's almost, a lot of the rings have 100 years worth of fandoms,
so you get it. But that kind of story of like in part one, we go from A to B. And then part two,
we go from B to C like it's just boring. The quest they go on in this is not interesting in any way.
You don't even really get it. And when they get there, it's a record that's been playing on its own.
Oh, well, well, they're, they're meaning so they're going on a quest to get to this radio station.
They find and they find out that the radio station is on an island and they need to get on a boat
and get to this island. They get to the island and realize, oh my god, this island hasn't been
it's a safe haven because the things can't swim. The aliens can't swim.
And they're actually people, they're living a relatively normal life, all things consider.
And they go to the radio, and they find out that the radio station has been playing beyond the
sea on report or on repeat as a signal. So anybody that hears it goes, oh,
which is so fucking convoluted, have a recording of the man saying what to do. Yes.
The aliens can't understand English. They don't understand. So anyway,
they finally get to the radio station where this song Bobby Darren song has been playing over
and over. And then they show it's playing on vinyl, which is literally impossible. It couldn't,
you could, it's impossible. You can't repeat a song endlessly on vinyl. You just can't do it.
And it's little dumb details like that were Krasinski, because visually he thought a record player looked
cooler than a wave form on a computer. It's like, this is bad, you know, and then the,
the daughter goes in to the room and I get that she's supposed to understand radio equipment
because she's sort of studied it with her dad and whatever. But I mean, for Christ's sakes, John,
show her for a second trying to figure out where the buttons and switches are. I studied
radio communications in college for four years. If you threw me into a radio booth,
it would take me a second to go, okay, we got here here here. She immediately knows where every
switch is hidden, every fucking thing. She's taking a long dramatic pause to hold the earpiece to
the microphone for some reason. As Silly and Murphy is getting just mutilated outside the room.
Meanwhile, the dipshit son, who is instructed by his mother to stay down in this like little
like basement area so he can't be heard because there's three feet of concrete above them and the aliens
can't hear them unless they're directly standing above them, decides for no reason whatsoever
to put his baby sister in a box with a lid on it that has oxygen. So he can just go upstairs and
just wander around, which leads to him getting the alien destroying Silly and Murphy's entire
thing that he built. It's so stupid. It's just so stupid. The whole thing. It's like a 90 minute
movie as well. I saw some interview with Presensky where he was like, they asked me over and over
to write this. I was like, no, I'm just not going to do it. I don't think there's more story to tell.
Then we stumbled upon this and it's like maybe you did turn him down once, but this thing feels like
it's also quite a place came out two years ago maybe three years. He's foolish. This sequel was on
the docket like three months after that fucking movie came out. But it does feel like an
incredible rush job. It is it's short. The story doesn't it's not there's nothing interesting
or exciting about it. It's a retread of the original. These plot holes he leads, he might be one of
these directors who's like, I just care about moments and how the audience feels. I don't care
about the little details or he might be stupid and not understand that like you can't be playing the
same song over and over on a record. And even if you did over time, it would fall off the groove or
something would go wrong with it. It's not a it wouldn't work. So there's all these moments that
take you out of it. If I'm Emily Blunt, hey, I'd be a much happier person. But B, John Krasinski, my
husband hands me this script. And I'm like, my husband is writing this action movie for me basically
like part two where I really come into my own. It's aliens. It's Sigourney Weaver. She's taking care of
her newborn baby and her two children, one of them deaf. You really want the kick ass mom defending
her babies. You know, that's the plot of the movie. It's a no -brainer. She, as Joe said, is just
relegated to nothing. Immediately, that means that John Krasinski sat down and he was like, well nobody's
going to buy that this woman has to defend her kids on her own. We need her with a man, which is
fucked especially in this day and age. Emily built in feminist story at a time where everyone's saying
we need more projects like this. And you immediately say we better get a big strong man in here to
help this lady out or nobody's going to buy it. Emily Blunt is reduced to going back to
alone, back to the drugstore. Like we need to go to this fucking drugstore again. It's where
Krasinski goes at the beginning of the movie and you're kind of like, well, that's kind of cool
because like you're seeing what it was before the first film. Then she goes back to it.
And it's like, guys, how many trips you're going to make to this place? She's like at one point,
she goes, I have to go back because her son is hurt and she's like, I have to go get you medicine
or you'll be in a lot of pain. It's like, you've been to the store. You didn't think to take some
of this shit the first time. So there's that. And then there's just all the little brainless,
complete absence of logic throughout the entire film. Like we don't wear shoes, we wear bandages
on our feet and our feet are literally bleeding all the time because we walk everywhere without shoes
on, which also by this point your feet would be healed and scarred and whatever. But let's, you know,
whatever. And then Silly and Murphy's walking around and boots with them as they're doing that.
And it's like your first question wouldn't be, oh, dude, we can wear boots.
Yeah, you wouldn't say that. You wouldn't you wouldn't think so that's not a dress. The alien can hear
everything. You know, if you if you silently fart in the wind, it can hear it. Yet they've got
the daughter two feet away from it, cocking a shotgun. And it doesn't know where the kid is.
There was so many just lapses and logic like that that just made no sense. Like the whole thing where
they there's a sequence where they have Silly and Murphy on a dock where this little girl puts a new
surround his neck to trap him and then walks away. And then these like sort of scavenger sort of,
it's kind of like the road like these scavenger what you assume are kind of cannibal types
sort of descend on him. And they're going to do God knows what to him and the little girl.
And he just sits there. Yeah. It's like, dude, you know, you can take a new soft your neck if you want to.
Right. Like there's a reason they tie your hands behind your back if they're going to hang you.
Like, so you can't take the new soft of your neck. It's also like here, here's how bad a storyteller
John Krasinski is in terms of what's on the page. As I said, I think he's a fine visual direct. But
you introduce this like island of cannibalistic humanoids. And you really don't use them in any sort
of way. You know, they're there. They're a threat. But if you're going to do that, then part two
needs to be about meeting the other survivors and uh oh, they're cannibals and they're fucked up.
That's a good premise for a movie. The aliens thing of I'm going to protect my young is a good
premise for a movie. And and he just kind of kind of raises those plots. But really the plot is just
a general retread of we got to get from here to there. And it's not interesting. It felt to me like
a tremors two or something that would have been a direct to DVD. The production value is there. The
special effects are good. But the story is on a direct to DVD level. It's not good. And
you don't care about these people, really. Because as you said, when we first meet them,
you would root for them if they weren't telling this poor man, like, where the fuck were you? You coward.
And they bring in, they did this like it's fucking Friday the 13th part four. They introduce a black
character for one second. It's Jim and Hansu, multiple Academy Award nominee, Jim and Hansu,
who still looks incredible. By the way, he's got to be 55. And he says three lines and is killed.
It's like guys. Yeah, you can't do that now. Instead of setting up, instead of setting up a cool
character that we could have followed into the next movie. Yeah, maybe somebody that brings some
dynamic into the mix, add some tension, sets it up. And instead, they kill it. Yeah, they like
Star Trek fourth crew member this guy, you know. And it's just, the movie just sucks. It just sucks.
I disagree with Pat. I don't, I am yet, I shouldn't say disagree. I am yet to be convinced that John
Krasinski is a good director. Yeah, you can't tell when it's this budget level and this level of
production. I mean, for Christ's, a guy makes like a fucking music video, you know, for like the new
ZZ top record, something that never even sees a lot of day. And they're like, you're hired. You're
directing the incredible Hulk for right. You know, so like who knows anymore? Who knows if what he's
actually doing versus what he's not doing? You know, look, if he really is hands on with all this,
then it looks promising. I think really what happened here was a studio is putting a very high dollar
amount on John Krasinski. And they said, this sequel has to wreak of you. Yeah, it has to be written
and directed by you. We need to see your face in it so we can throw that into the trailer. And I
caused him to write a movie that centered on and focused on all the wrong things. Yeah, it makes
it makes him out to be like a Christ figure almost. And really I'm sitting there like I saw
quiet place twice. I don't even know if I remember the details of this family or or or anything,
you know, yeah, he actually seen everything he's directed. He did brief interviews with hideous men
which was a very boring indie. I didn't even I don't know he did any boring indie and three episodes
of the office. So he's not a newbie, but yeah, I don't know if we're going to see a long rich
directing career from him or not. But this movie sucked. It it felt like a rush job. They've had it in
the can now for a year, you know, it's like it feels empty. It feels like not a full movie. I know we
complain about movies being too long on here all the time, but this just felt like you guys didn't even do
the basic work of writing a story with three acts in it. Real snooze, snooze crews. This one
two hogs way down two hogs down. I've yet to see that back at the theater movie that had me pump
in my fist. You know, I like nobody a lot, but I'm really waiting for that big theatrical experience
that I just have not had yet. I got it with Ratham and I got it by the end of that thing. I was
I was hopping up and you know, figuratively hopping up and down. We were we were very excited
watching it, but anyway, folks, that's our show. Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter. You
can also check me out on the Taste Buds pod over at youtube .com slash no press network or wherever you
get your podcasts. Thanks for being here. If you're in the New York area, I'm doing sets around town
these days. So keep an eye out at the seller or the stand or New York comedy club. You'll catch me at one
of them. I am the Patrick Walsh. I am on Twitter and Instagram at those places. I don't have much
else to report. We're coming to you next with Army of the Dead. And we'll have a lot to say about
that. I guarantee it. We will see you next time folks. Thank you very much for all your support. As
always on Patreon and elsewhere, give us those five star reviews if you can. We'll see you next
time and we'll see you in hell.