music
how do you like those apples I'm done oh that's it I was just that you're
going to jump in I was just reading these comments and realizing that several
people thought that I was asking for strictly questions about ready player one
I will say you guys are terrible some of you at reading pretty simple instructions
well we'll answer the questions hellians were about to record ready player one
it will take an hour when that is done I will check the comments in this post
every single question that asked in that hour will be answered in this month's
patreon questions can be about anything so everybody wrote ready player one
correct questions the first two well answer them a deals a deal they could be
about anything including ready player one luckily most people did not
okay so we're good anyway yeah I thought you know Joe and I were going to do
an old classic today stir of echoes or I think it's a classic I don't know what
Joe thinks of it and you know I didn't think just doing a normal thing is good
enough for these bonus ones you guys are paying we want to try to give you a
little flare a little special a dish my pants are off for this recording right
and really Ernest scared stupid was a perfect candidate for it but we just
toss it out for free and it was nice to hear how many of you love that episode it
was very fun one to do it was fun and we stuck to the movie more than I believe we
usually do in a commentary episode yes although someone did point out that it was
like the 18 -minute mark where I'm like we should talk about Ernest I think you know
some of them we have gone longer than that now do any of the other Ernest films
tread into fantasy territory like Ernest saves Christmas I feel like we could do
it Christmas time I feel like it's you could call it a fantasy film right I'd
loved well and as you know and Ernest goes to jail he controls the power of electricity
and that's the one I would like to see because I remember that one being genuinely
funny wow that's got a snort out of me just because I don't know if there are
a thousand of these or what we're gonna get going yeah let's go
DD lashley asks what or who was your favorite cameo and since I believe
ready player what I believe she's referring to ready player one so I'm gonna I'm
gonna take that to mean who's your favorite cameo in movie history where you're
watching it and you're like oh that's awesome this guy's in or this girl's in
it and because I have mine right off hand right off hand where did that voice come
from I don't know I'm going to answer for me and I saw it very very early because
we're doing a project with one of the producers at the time that fell apart
zombie land that amazing Bill Murray extended cameo that's also mine was just
really yeah yeah I really want to see zombie land again so let's do that soon okay
show because what a thrill that was Bill Murray being in it and it was one of those
rare celebrity Bill Murray did a celebrity cameo and get smart and it was he was
like in a tree he was like a man dressed as a tree it was terrible like a lot of
times these cameos you're excited that somebody's in it and they don't they don't
have anything funny to do zombie land gave him like extended funny shit to do
it was an awesome cameo it really was somehow made it to home video viewing
without having that cameo ruin for me oh I just I thought just because I saw it
early I got it protected well pinkstone was very adamantly like do not let
anybody ruin the cameo yeah you know so I was very careful about it just such
just such a treat crazy that we both have that loved it were you thinking that
before I said it yeah in movie history that's mine and I'll add on in TV history
because I think I've mentioned it before Bert Reynolds on the Golden Girls him
showing up at the end of the episode where the premise is basically that Sophia is
clearly lying about partying all night with Bert Reynolds right and that's the
joke and then he actually walks into the fucking house at the end it's pretty
nuts can you imagine the overage pussy thrown at Bert Reynolds on the set of
Golden Girls his line is they're these new roommates you told me about
yeah Sophia says yeah and he goes which ones the slut that's that's his watch that
with you I remember yeah yeah it's a great cameo it's very funny all right Greg
Sorenson asks long time listener first time caller did either of you read the
book this is there's only two ready player ones very good if so please talk about
how dumb it is if not just hypothesize how dumb it is I'll take my answer off the
air I have not read the book I have not read the book either but I will say this
we're not for two of my dear friends swearing to me that it's brilliant I was
watching that movie going how could this book be good yeah I mean like if I
had seen it without reading the book I would have been like yeah it was a pretty
scary movie I mean it's all right I imagine the book probably goes deeper that
with this I was like I don't want to read this book ever I could not have less of
a desire to read the book so none ready no I'm not player one yeah no I was
yeah that's the stupidest thing I've ever said in this podcast I was trying to
say something I lost track of it I also maybe I'm slowly having some sort of
stroke when I started talking in that weird accent for a minute it alarmed me I'm
sober as a judge I am too my friend believes he might have had a mini stroke really
yeah he said he was watching TV nobody in comedy just a regular friend he said
he was watching TV and he had like he like got all like weird and he he was like
when he was watching the news he was like they've been talking about this for a while
wait what's going on and he like didn't have his equilibrium and like interesting it
was yeah he was like he said he thinks he might have a mini stroke he's got to
see all these doctors now Matt Moy the gentleman who played the Asian short
diner owner on two broke girls yeah had a stroke at age 30 while he was on the show
yes and it can happen just yet another thing to worry about is he okay did he bounce back
totally okay he said one day he could not tie his shoes he didn't know what was
happening and he's totally fine he wanted to do an interview with a magazine about like
how this can happen and what to watch out for and so forth and our boss goes what do
you want to be known as stroke boy you're on a hit show that's nice and that my friends
is the television business you're supposed to talk about living biblically on this
because you said on the other thing you would I will if we have time all right Aaron Griffith
asks was wondering if Joe got any deeper into trailer park boys I have how many hours of
it are there like it's it's ten seasons right it's an ungodly amount of content it's
like getting into you know it's like saying yeah I think I'm going to get into Sinatra right
when I'm walking into the section at ami but just being like Jesus Christ right it's a lot
but yeah I did and I've enjoyed everything I I circle back to it every few months and watch
a few and then I and then I put it down again and then I circle back and watch a few but people
are telling me that I'm I mean I know he said you're wrong for this but the things I've enjoyed
most and it's probably because it's where I started were the abroad stuff where they went to America
and when they went to Europe and I like the actual show a lot too but those were my favorite things
I also really like the live specials quite a bit okay um but I I love the show I love the
troop I'm glad they're doing it again because apparently they stopped for a while they wanted to do
something else and then they went back to it if I'm going in I should just start with season one
I wouldn't man because I when I started watching the show I went back and tried to start with season
one and it's a very different dynamic okay that the poster boy bubbles they got with the glasses
he's not a main character yet right I think like I would start with the travel things
if I were you start with the one where the I think the first one is the one where they go to a
Europe and there's are there's no continuity or running jokes or anything to care about it's just
literally they go to Europe and they're all excited because they're supposed to be going on this trip
and then they get there and they find out it's like a road rules kind of thing where they have to do
tasks to get money okay and they're furious and and they then they suck at all the tasks and it's
sort of a little it's a little jackassie in the sense like some of it seems real okay whatever
it's very pretty for the new Johnny Knoxville I'm very excited I am too just a comedy with those stunts
peppered in I'm very excited I'm glad that he's normal Knoxville agent this one yeah I'm excited
that Pontius is in it I got thrilled I mean thrilled it's a funny trailer yeah and it made you
realize how few laughs are in trailers these days trailers funny and like in the same way I
lit up when I saw Han Solo and the Force Awakens trailer I lit up the same way when I saw Pontius
with like a squirrel biting his dick yeah which was always this thing on jackass and I it just made
me laugh so hard yeah I mean there's nothing there in terms of pure theater laughs those three jackasses
cannot be beat I agree well and what it's a shame because we need one now more than ever and
hopefully this will be it who knows yeah this one's for me Kristen Lawford and asks how and why
did you start with Vine Pat as with everything else with these apps I mocked it and thought it was
stupid until one day I was like well all right Twitter I remember thinking why would I give away
my jokes for free I wish I had listened to that I'm not started right sure the time I've wasted on
Twitter Jesus Christ but Vine always seemed very stupid and I thought most of the content on it was
at best unfunny at worst horrifically racist and then one day I was like you know I miss acting
take six seconds out of my day I don't think I ever made a Vine when I wasn't high because that was
when I would get the confidence to do one and weirdly I'm probably more proud of those that little
collection of videos than a lot of stuff I've done I thought they were weird and funny and I enjoyed
doing them and and the fact that I I connected and hit with people gravy spawned our friendship that's
true that's true that's true and and man I used to get a lot of six sexual
DMs from people the problem with Vine is that I was starting it at the top of the age spectrum for
Vine and I never know if the DMs coming to me were from 14 year old girls or people of age and
it's a little nerve wrecking I never partook but I loved doing it thank for asking heightened
Davidson asks how do you guys keep your heads with all the ups and downs of your careers
I mean the short answer is we don't we right honestly a big help a big help is Mr. Joe
Derosa we vent at each other we text each other all day look at this fucking son of a bitch
look at what this asshole posted yeah I sent Pat a post today from somebody and I just wrote Jesus
fuck yeah I mean yeah the all show business is is ups and downs it's best to remember that it's best to
remember that most things don't work most things don't connect nobody sets out to make something
that that doesn't connect but the the the reason you get your heart broken is because you forget that
and you think this is going to be the thing this is going to be huge this is going to be you know
you can't think that way you got to assume everything's going to suck everything's going to be a
miserable experience and then you can make some some money at it I agree Walsh is a is a pillar for me
you know you're good friends which you'll have few of in this business you will keep you sane
um and you know doing the podcast sort of you know us having a standing date every we
not that we don't hang out outside of it but you know this standing date to hang out every week at least
once and do this it is very helpful gives us a chance to bitch gives us a chance to just talk about
stuff for fun and not as an opportunity but it is tough man it's tough it's a lot of ups and downs
woo and I got to tell you it's easy to forget this but most people have only downs
and I don't mean the syndrome I'm talking about folks uh folks you know like some people only have
ups that's right who don't generally those people who don't deserve yep um but I would say you
know it was only 10 years ago where I was like well it didn't take me long either I was like I'm
never gonna make it never gonna connect nothing's ever gonna hit never gonna get a job
and that is so much the norm out here that it's easy to forget when you have a setback that
numerous people are 50 out here and they're like you know maybe tomorrow's the day I get that
writing gig 50 there's tons of people like that out here it's uh and by the way you could right
you know you never know when fate will deal you hand but uh boy it is not a as David Cromwell said
this shit ain't a meritocracy and he was absolutely right um no it sucks uh Sarah Catherine
she of two first names asks us would you ever consider doing a video recording of the podcast
absolutely in fact Pat and I have talked about you know possibly trying to turn this into some sort
of video component you know like like a TV formatted kind of thing uh I don't know if we will
but we certainly have discussed it uh and we're certainly discussing now more than ever with uh
Ken Hamley and Emily Florence uh doing live shows and stuff so the ball is finally rolling in that
direction so I think all of that will will lend itself to it but I you know I was thinking the other day
we could do a video thing for the patreon and add another tier and say well if you pay this you
you get a video of us doing something but you know then you're getting into editing and shooting yeah
I mean we could do maybe a bonus one week I mean it's amusing to me looking at me and Joe right now
to assume that anybody would want a visual component we're both lying down essentially
in exactly the same position you'd get to meet con Joe's dog who's looking itself
yeah um it's not that visually exciting we did and I never understand why anybody would watch
a video podcast unless you got little sketches like the normal download one or something but
we would absolutely do it and we will do it I would say uh thank you for asking
okay Tucker Rouch asks which critically acclaimed film do each of you hate the most good question
um well I mean look I'm gonna double down on what I always say the god damn terminator movies aren't
any good oh for god's sake and I fought with since I fought with Pat on the podcast about this we
recently fought in a bar about it and my uh Pinkstone was with us he was jumping in on me everybody
was pilot on me nobody wondering I don't think that they're good movies I keep going back every time
they release one uh I think the the first two are absolutely fantastic I think the first one's better
than the second one you've heard my spiel on the set I don't need to do it again but yeah but Cameron
I think almost everything Cameron has made I'd say could almost do a first place tie for me okay as
acclaimed that I think is not good which he he can't stop opening his fucking yeah these days man yeah
well him saying he's getting superhero fatigue I agree with you James but then of course I saw
80 people tweet you're the guy making five avatars right yeah yeah yeah so that's my answer um yeah
I mean uh of all his movies I would say the least successful from a storytelling standpoint is
avatar and to think that we want five is just and it's such a risk like on two I have a feeling the
box office is gonna dip quite a bit from one and then by the time you get to five what's what's gonna
happen uh I couldn't give a rat fucking ass I don't think I'd even see it it would have to be under
two hours if I'm gonna if I'm gonna see another avatar it won't be I mean it was the 3d was novel
I know that of course that's not the first use of 3d but now if I'm not mistaken wasn't that the first
like it's back in theaters and this is always my argument about James Cameron with almost everyone
of his movies and it was what I said about avatar I go okay it was the first like real D movie take
that element out of it it's not a good fucking movie you know Titanic it's like 10 things not
bad but it's like everybody's like and the boat looks like it's actually sick and I'm like yeah okay
but at the end of the day do you give a fuck about any of the people in this thing I absolutely did
and I really loved Titanic and watching it recently on 3d maybe love it even more it was all right
I'm gonna get a lot of bounds on Titanic I'll admit that no I that's when I get people's hey it's
a little small sea but I mean it's a romance and not only that but a historical romance which are
notoriously small sea and you got the caprio running around in the galley right being a fun kid
which is Titanic is great is your answer avatar no not at all okay my I mean shit it's always
you know the four -year consideration movies for the Oscars that everybody starts talking about
and gets me all wound up every year there's like 10 to think about what is the ultimate one it's
hard to say like what you know I'd have to look at like the the most critically acclaimed film list
or something I'll play it safe here and go with like a shape of water as a recent example all right
I mean just there's always several movies a year where I'm like what are you thinking what are you
talking about with like a hundred percent it happens all the time and how the fuck did that
story just go away shape of water that did you watch the short film that he was accused of copying I
didn't was it close it was ridiculous it was you were like there's no way this wasn't copied really
yeah and it just went away funny how the really things just go away okay I'm fucking believable man
I did not know that I mean especially because that was kind of him collaborating for the first down
to the way it looked yeah like the like the art design of it all right I mean look I another one
that pops to mind is English patient never saw maybe that would would be better now that I'm an adult
but I remember really loving when Seinfeld went after the English patient because that was a time
where you never went after those big Oscar pictures where Elaine is screaming just die at the screen
but really were they did some ballsy movie jobs absolutely they did the JFK thing right right
they did the shinlers list make out right those were a pretty edgy first sitcoms back then
yeah I mean for me it's always going to be one of those big sprawling uh epics sure that just
bore the shit out of me out of Africa and all those kind of movies oh I hate all those kinds of
flicks eyes yeah oh Christ yeah wait Oz that Australia movie no it was Australia it's called Australia
sorry I thought you meant Oz the great and powerful which was absolutely terrible as well
all right next cue uh the flip side from Mike Hasler St. Louis's own an old an old commenter on my
blog that I had 15 years ago how are you Mike uh which notoriously disliked film will each of you
defend to the death Joe is yours Norbert it's you you people know my answer Batman versus Superman
till the day I die oh I'm going down with the ship on that one wow you'll all realize one day and by
the way I'd like to pat myself on the back as a prequel defender and someone who saw the Star Wars
prequel several times in the theaters and argued at length for years at parties and in bars about how
they weren't bad movies I'd like to pat myself on the back that people now are so mad at Ryan Johnson's
the last Jedi that they are now saying including Simon Pegg who was a prequel hater now saying you
know maybe the prequel is weren't so bad maybe we had it a little better than we thought we were being
kind of bratty what what made Simon Pegg say this because he hated last Jedi he was apparently not
happy with the last he was part apparently part of the fringe of people that were not happy with last
Jedi I wasn't thrilled with last Jedi but I kind of go back and forth I mean I certainly liked it
um yeah for me I mean I have I have tons I mean uh I guess it's gotten a little respect over time
but a review that I can almost cite verbatim was the F given to Kingpin by Alicia Schwartzbaum
and Entertainment Weekly in 1996 uh the un F idiotic and I was pacing stripped of her job I I agree
I tweeted at her once and she came back real hard I was like oh I was just kidding you cannot like
the movie that's fine but um I mean yeah Kingpin is not a kingpin is a panned film for sure
but notoriously disliked that I enjoyed um well I wish I was the kind of guy that could think of
these immediately um I'd have to look at like a list of hated movies but I feel like there's always
a couple of years where I'm like that was that was pretty good what are you talking about well I
remember you were the one that told me vacation was funny and had like a 23 percent or so
reboot sure you know yeah yeah generally it's comedy you certainly can't trust rotten tomatoes
on comedies that's it's just you know because most critics are older I guess now in the internet
age that's not the case but comedy's a young man's game uh okay yeah I wish I wish I had a better
example I'll say I'll say Kingpin but you know that there's a bunch um and a lot of the fairly
brothers output I thought whole here we go I'll go further with you because Kingpin has a lot of
respect I thought hall pass was a funny move I like tall pass I didn't I didn't hate it and there was
a great joke good cock joke in it oh yeah yeah we're oh and Wilson had that the giant dick next to
his next to space yeah I like top it today this was really funny and Simon merchant was very funny
in it Steven merchant sorry it was really funny in it um and I like you know I like
well I guess I will I will say all the fairly brothers restue just yeah that's where I was
gonna go with this all that fairly brothers output that is just shat upon three studios has funny parts in
it um shallow how has funny shit in it stuck on you is a pretty good Hollywood satire it's got some
funny shit I believe stuck on you was their last decent film okay fair enough uh now you're
also gonna say the heart fairly enough I can't go that far but there are lots of those kind of like
comedies that you'll find for a dollar at the grocery store that I thought were better than most
because I'm happy to just see people trying to make me laugh all right and I have low standards for
comedies because they're so rarely good okay a couple you know a few laughs I'm on board Emily okay
Emily is reminding me I can turn comments off thank you Emily Josh Browne what what are your
favorite horror comedies I think we've probably discussed that on the show before mine is unquestionably
tremors okay but if we're going for a true horror slash comedy I think that's got to be it I just
thought it was really a perfect blend of action horror comedy and scintillating banter between bacon
and more you yeah you once called it electric off the charts I believe the charts yeah mine
stands down the burbs 110 % sure it has been forever yeah we'll always be uh yeah burbs is fantastic
I can't say enough good stuff about the bar I actually think the burbs is one of Tom Hanks's
best films but it's but it get it just got kind of shuffled away in like 80s movie right in the 80s
movie garbage toss out or whatever it's it's so much better than it gets credit for the humor is so
dry yeah uh it's very smart it actually does have creepy parts in it like it's it's really good all right
yeah I mean as far as critically pan stuff go I mean Turner and Hooch money pit Turner Hooch was
no Turner Hooch was a huge hit huge hit yeah I can still be a critically pan move critics pan
Turner and Hooch they as far as I can recall uh who's Harry Crumb I probably has a nine percent
hilarious movie the lot on Karen Kilgareff once again was honestly legitimately mad at us that
was we told a lot of 80s comedies are like that where they were just completely lambasted I was listening
I'm listening to an audio book about the making of caddy shack and they talked about how everyone went
to this press conference the day after it opened with like coke eyes hung over it was at danger fields
comedy club the only person who dressed up was Ted night and he shows up in a blazer with his
hair slick like oh well thought we were doing a press conference why do you guys all look like shit
Bill Murray comes in and Jim shorts with a pizza and he's like sorry I'm real hung over with giant
glasses on because everyone had heard how shitty caddy shack was it was shat on by the press and they
were like let's go in here and do this fucking shit now they all went out and got tanked the night
and now it's a legendary picture by the way speaking of Turner and Hooch yeah remember how you
were looking at my HBO history on Hulu and you said why did you watch Richie Rich yeah and I said I
didn't it just put it on there for some reason that was the truth it keeps adding shit it's got the
sequel to canine on there now canine 11 yeah yeah I didn't fucking watch that it's in my fucking
recently watched just just somebody with terrible taste to have your password
yes really yes they do well I need do I know this person because this is really bad taste canine 11
and Richie Rich you don't know this person Jesus I realized on my HBO I had all sorts of weird
shit and I realized Pete's been using it for years Pete who's going into season three of an HBO show
will not spring for HBO he uses my password this is a man that once said to me I've bought the
movie on iTunes because I was too lazy to get up and get the DVD out of the other room right won't
spring for the HBO go well he call he texted me was like can I use your password you want to watch
the Spielberg documentary and I was like Pete you can have it but shouldn't what I don't understand
like right not forget the money but you work for HBO like what are you talking about and he admitted
that he'd been using it for years he had borrowed it once before and that explains all this weird shit
you know I'm glad it wasn't like some soft -core erotic or something popping up
he'll he'll lean lean yeah he left a Christmas gift here for his brother yeah he dropped it and
said I'll be back I'll be back to get it tomorrow I said no problem it was here for three months
to the point where I texted him hey Pete I have an idea for a fun hang it's called get this
fucking shit out of my apartment so you know the I'm not this HBO thing makes sense all right fair enough
all right Amanda El Zamora asks what has been your worst celebrity interaction oh all right I got
one okay you can go first if you weren't oh boy well I mean unquestionably Max Weinberg drummer for
Conan the Max Weinberg 7 biggest asshole I've ever seen and I think I talked about him on the show
but he used to he about gave me an ulcer because it was kind of my first I loved and idolized Conan so
much I was a 22 -year -old kid working on my favorite show and everybody couldn't have been nicer including
Conan Conan's got a bit of a dick vibe but you know he says it with love Weinberg man
he had to have a bucket of ice to ice down his knuckles after doing the literally the easiest
drumming and if you forgot that bucket of ice in his dressing room he would come out shirtless
and just scream in your face he made these interns cry like you know 18 -year -old girl sobbing
every day he brought interns out to his house to do yard work one weekend for the entire weekend didn't
pay them and said this is this guy's been drumming for Bruce Springsteen for 40 years the man has a
billion dollars ridiculous uh just a complete asshole and the other would be when parasilton came
to SNL you know just a nightmare trashed her dressing room dog shit everywhere but that wasn't
necessarily a mean to me generally celebrities are nice uh and they have publicists who are mean
on their behalf uh mine is uh we'll always be uh it's not Dave Chappelle I was on I'm saying that
because I was on tour with Dave Chappelle in the story and I don't want you to think I'm going to say
he was mean to me he was Dave was Chris Isaac yes I think we may have told both of our stories all right
well the Chris Isaac story I'm going to tour with Dave Dave's treat me like a god damn
prince amongst thieves making me feel like I'm really part of this business just being the best dude
interest me introduces me to Chris Isaac because he knows that I love the album forever blue so much
yeah Chris Isaac uh says he turns to me I tell him how much it meant to me to find my life and he
said yeah thanks and just turn and kept talking to Dave didn't just couldn't have given rest of a
shit so anyway I hate to hear it I just watched uh Chris Isaac perform uh two hearts on MTV Unplugged
that was the YouTube poll I was on the other night man what voice sounded as good as it did on record
I just kind of wanted to know like does does he effortlessly hit those notes that I do I hit in my
car no problem but sure enough he did he sounded great and forgot to write those songs and sing that
well and be that handsome I feel like Chris Isaac should have been an even bigger star well I'm going
to say this a lot of his album suck that's true you get that forever blue record and you're like and
that's the big one and you go oh my god I got to get more you start get branching out you're like
what is this they're well they're inconsistent the singles are usually good and yeah I'll go
grant you all right fair enough uh misty Zavar asks if you were on a deserted island with only a screen
electricity a blue ray player and your three all -time favorite movies what would those movies be
well just for an occasion like this I keep my favorite films written down in my phone in my phone
my top 10 and I actually want to see my top three in my top 10 I'd have to switch this
but hand in her sisters is my number one Glangarry Glen Ross is my number two goodfills is my number three
if I was put in on an island though I'd have to move that around exorcist would get moved up
into the top three because I'd won a little hard now and again and that third I don't even think
I think kingpin would have to go in there because I'd won a comedy and then I got to be honest guys I
think empire strikes back would get put in there were raiders because I need you know you need to
escape a little once in a while so my top three would be different if I run an island yeah I mean
island does kind of switch it up if you would ask me my because you're also asking my three all -time
favorite movies island might switch it I guess it shouldn't my number one is going to be goodfellas
my number two is probably going to be playing strings automobiles number three maybe sling blade
and then my other favorites are it's a wonderful life do the right thing Jackie Brown you know
raising Arizona I'd want raising Arizona there I think that's an endlessly re -watchable picture
um there you go there's a bunch uh just saw this on Instagram fantastic onion headline I'm glad
you're on Instagram well I just I was looking to see if there was you know stuffed with no I wasn't I
just we were talking I looked at it I'm sorry it was weak of me that doesn't make it better I apologize
you give your answer and then hop on Instagram for mine I just got I just I I'm sorry I'm apologizing but
this is people are paying for this this is very funny go on onion headline new California law
invalidates thousands of marriages between ship captains and the sea
is that a brandy reference or just enjoy oh it's like our captains are always like I'm married to
the sea right well you know the song brandy no say I said brandy I think you're a fine girl what a good
wife you would be but my life my lover my lady is the sea I think that comes from this from the
ship captain saying it yeah I don't think the song is from the point of view of the other ship captain
yeah I don't think the guy that wrote brandy came up with that all right fair enough
Chris Marsh asks either of you have a good loss of virginity story
oh yeah all right I was in a bar I didn't lose my virginity at all it's 21 years old I was very old
and I was in a bar and I've always had a bit of a flare for an older woman you know I always find
that very sexy uh 70 75 oh that's that's a spring chicken in my book uh and I was 21
I was sitting next to a very attractive woman who was like in her mid or late 30s so at the time
that was quite an older woman to me yeah and I started talking to her we started hitting it off
and she was a professor at a college that I had attended and transferred out of okay and I started
dating her and she told me look we were mess we were fooling around one night and she said I want to
stop this before it goes too far she goes I didn't tell you this but I'm moving away at the end of the
month to Atlanta Georgia okay and I said okay and she goes so I I can't sleep with you because it's
just not gonna mean anything and I don't want to do that and I said look uh I got news for you I'm
a virgin and man did she love the idea of being number one okay on her last night in town she
she I would gifted my virginity to her uh made love to an older woman who showed me the ropes how old was
she she was 37 36 somewhere in there you know went well went great okay went great you wrap it up
yes I wrapped it up okay yeah could you wrap this up and I also remember not understanding how
condoms worked at the time I still don't thank God I don't have to use them and I remember asking my
friend Dan like you know I used a condom uh but but my penis still felt wet when I took the condom off
does that mean her vaginal juices got inside the condom and he goes no you fucking idiot that's just
what your dick is like from the lubricant on the condom right and he did a he he mimed for me
what a what a germ would have to do to get inside the condom sure and he and I remember the whole time
that he was finger using his fingers to show the germ walking up the condom to the rim he was going
well it's not entirely true though I mean if you're in balls deep uh you're getting juices around the
rim on your balls yeah but they're not getting in the rim if you didn't pull the condom all the way
to the balls you're not getting full coverage juice isn't getting in the rim though juice isn't
getting in the tip juice isn't going from the rim up to the heel I did that was more for the funny
visual of a bug rolling to the circus music I don't think uh they like the term juice either but
um sorry I'm sorry her squirt I meant to say I lost my virginity a year later than you Joe uh
which was already shockingly late 21 I was 22 wow uh I never understood how anyone had sex
I have been notoriously bad at like talking to girls and then I had my first drink and I was like
got it now I understand how people have sex it was just that easy you know because like the
thing keeping me from going like hey what about the two of us have sex was alcohol and by the way
that that's always been my line hey and I put my hand on the wall behind them right kind of lean at
you'll only do this to women that work for you correct yeah well I like it when they work
directly beneath me folks and above me uh no I yeah I guess it's a decent story I
I'm have my first drink I was like okay I understand um because I had a long time girlfriend as well
who basically would have been fine with other means of sexuality but not in the front
um and I did not want to lose my virginity in that manner um we went
when I went to New York basically I had been in New York a week I lived with this kind of nutty
woman who would drink a bottle of red wine every night uh and get kind of weird and flirty but I was
not interested right at all right and uh finally she said hey I'm gonna be interviewing some new roommates
for this other room I had this couple that lived there who I'm still friendly with that I loved
she was like they're leaving you want to help me meet some people I met these applicants and there
was one really really attractive young lady I was like I'd go with that one I did she didn't know
anyone in the city I didn't know anyone in the city my friends came to visit we all got really drunk
we got back to the apartment I started to walk down the hall to my room she grabbed my hand walk
me down the hall to her room we did it part of it was the drunkenness part of it was that I had been
masturbating for years and years three four times a day right uh but it took me I have the exact
opposite of everyone else's virginity story it took me forever forever to come right where I sort of
apology I was like I don't know what's have I'm sorry it usually doesn't take this long right and
then I had to say to her which I never would say now afterwards I was like sorry you know that
that was my first time I don't know why that took so long and she was like sad up and bad it was like
your first time I mean it was a man it's a grown man right um and I wished I had not said it but it
it certainly wasn't magical but it led to many uh superior times after that did you have sex
were there ever again meant I'm saying I just uh I thought you meant superior with other people
no well of course that but we we had tons of sex and then um I didn't realize I didn't want to be
living with somebody I was having sex with tried to break it off and thought we could just go on being
uh room we moved out and got a place together and those wheels were in motion with once we thought
so after we thought I set up a bed it was kind of like now I'm having sex with somebody I'm going to be
living one on one with yeah that didn't feel good and believe it or not that stuff went south
a real fancy yeah all right uh Joshua Taj Bozeman asks how on earth does a grown adult make the sort
of bromantic friendships like the one you and Joe seem to have not seem to not to mention the seemingly
endless number of friends you guys mentioned from time to time it's not endless believe me especially
an adult who dislikes bars and insanely crowded places are you guys just very lucky or am I
missing the special sauce it's a touching question it's a great question it is much easier to make
friends when you're say in high school or college because you're surrounded by a lot of people with
the same same age same general interest but um I would say it was quite a fluke I met Joe through
Pete we went to dinner together I when I saw Joe I was like fuck I hate when people bring
guests it makes me uncomfortable I just wanted to see my friend uh Pete's big on that we're just
shitting all over Pete this week you don't need to add him and tell him this folks it's all lighthearted
but Pete's always like hey here's this guy and I was like oh and uh the Joe and I connection was
immediate and very rare I'm not I'm not normally that person at all in fact I normally hate most
people I meet uh so I think it's rare and it you just gotta you can't put yourself in a position
where you're never gonna meet me one it's the same as dating you have to meet someone you don't
have to go to an insanely crowded place uh or a bar but it's hard it is hard we're what we are
insanely lucky to answer your question I continually not saying as close as I got with Pat here but
I I'm continually seemingly making uh friends in adulthood but because I am quite open to it
I also don't like people but that that that that makes me open to it because when I connect with
somebody uniquely I want to be their friend so I've connected with Pat that night uniquely to get
another Pete dig in because we all watched Ace Venture when Nature calls and Pete mocked it as being
a bad movie right and Pat and I were like what the fuck are you talking about yeah so when
when something like that happens with me where I really bond with somebody on so I'm like
I think any friends with this guy right I didn't realize that that was the first time we hung out was
that Ace Venture tonight is that same night about that that was that Pete went to Mass Hall or
a little doms yeah yeah yeah I remember little doms not the rest uh so that's I think if you're open
to it and you recognize a specific unique connection you have with somebody it's anything's possible
yes um find out of one of these Helians lives in your hometown or so I always see these Helians talking
I'm like I hope at least two Helians of fucked I'll say that and I hope at least 50 Helians have
become friends I see you guys all interacting you must be friends that's nice it is nice uh but online
you know especially in dating I missed that whole world I mean get get online if that's your thing
but you do have to leave the house to make friends generally um try activities I wish you luck
yeah you know you know I hate to say it but join a team or a league or something uh and
that'll be a night of awkwardness but usually you'll find somebody you vibe with
Paul Merchie asks asks what's the movie you love the most that most people hate man we've answered that
Greg says well for Joe it's obviously Batman versus Superman see they know me
I hope they find about how shitty that movie is we've done it we've go back through the archives
Danielle Duer asks Pat how did you and Heather meet and for Joe how did you and con meet
Erica Branding says my friend Katie helped Joe get his dog who is a rescue is that your story
oh yeah that is that well that is well Katie yeah Katie told me
all right so Katie had gotten a dog
and I said well it's a great dog and everything and where'd you get him or her I think it's her
and she said there's this place called no kill LA and KLA to no kill shelter and
you know the good thing about them is as you can you can kind of look up the dogs on their website and
stuff right so I went home that night I looked up the website I looked at dog profiles they had like
just like on a dating site they had like parameters you could put in so I was like okay I don't
want a dog that weighs more than this and you know should be this a around this age or whatever put
all that shit in and they had a profile for old con here at the time his name was Chance
which I changed obviously but they had a video of him and I was like that is literally the exact
dog I want that's a perfect dog and I went down to get him and when I met him he was kind
of a douche like he didn't really talk to me not talk you know what I mean he didn't he seemed to
he seemed to give a shit like take it or leave it buddy I'll stay in this fucking pound I don't care
right and then I met a chihuahua who was very friendly and lovable and I almost took the chihuahua
and I was like I got a dice rolled on that that terrier man something about him I just like it
yeah so I brought him home and the rest is history and then I found out actually him not being all
over me was a was a good thing because it showed that he's a trained dog that isn't going to jump all
over you he was respecting boundaries and stuff which I didn't know that at the time I just thought
he meant he wasn't friendly did he have the bark that bark came later he only barks when when
we come in the door I guess unless he does it at home throughout the day no he barks when somebody
comes to the door he barks at people but I think he just is saying hello his tail is always wagging
okay and he's never mean about it he's never growling it's just feels angry and hostile to me because
the bark is horrible yeah it's a horrible bark it's a harsh bark and my cat has developed a harsh
meow as well and it's getting annoying what's a harsh meow that's so weird my cat noise
caused Tom to make the first move and I've seen he jolted up like in a horror movie he didn't care
for that but we are so adorable and it's just a funny cat like we laugh all the time at this cat
but this meowing is not helping it's cuteness at all listen to this bark
don't force him to bark I just want to get right here that that was the good bark there's a bad
one too anyway Heather and I met basically through a friend whose girlfriend was best friends with
Heather it's kind of the standard way um but we met at a music festival for the first time
going as a group and it was one of these EDM type deals and I was not kind of not into it but I really
wanted to see James Murphy of LCD sound system who was DJing so I was like I'm gonna go watch
James Murphy and everybody else wanted to go see something else and I was like that's fine I'll go
that I'm the other one wants to see this and she was like I'll go with you I want to go with you
and I was like no because I knew she wanted to see what everybody else was seeing I was like don't worry
about this is how I didn't get laid for so long I was talking myself out of it and so finally I
probably heard her fucking feelings I thought I was sparing her feelings and being like you don't
have to come with me she was trying to hang out with me so she thought I wasn't interested she came
to a taping of a show I was writing for I met her briefly and then she came to a party which I found
out later looking to get with the wall she had been into me from afar and there was a time when
that kind of had to be how you approached me because I was bad at the approach right she was dressed
very provocatively she walked past me and slapped me on the ass and I was talking to our dear friend
comedian Laura Keitlinger she goes why the fuck are you talking to me and not that dish over there
and I was like you're right strike up a conversation here we are five years later wow I remember
being very angry because I did not want to be in a relationship and I talked her for like an hour
and I was like fuck I like it I like this story uh it's a cute little story you might hear it at the
wedding who knows oh I plan on telling it at the wedding this is beach I got a speech I love the idea
that Joe will be having his first drink in two months at my wedding I might not though
I might just not drink all right well then don't do the addibles I don't need I don't need you
weird at the way I'm not gonna get weird relax but I might not drink but I feel that you'd be so
disappointed if I didn't drink it you're wedding I would a little bit but I don't care but I don't
I just might not drink but yeah that would be fun to get real shit faced yeah and get up I she
comes anyway she comes to the bar to get with Pat she's got she's showing it off
there's a smoking patio also at that my wedding by the way for reefer for whatever you want
well I'll be smoking a few stooges as I like to call the sigs we're gonna have some guards as well
Joseph Ray Goza asks Pat do you think you will ever run out of ideas for on with the Joe's I
already have frankly I I turned to the Facebook page because I mean the real issue is if I thought of
one on the way over here I'd be good to go but the fact every week Joe I'm like oh shit I need to
think of one now while I'm on the air it's too much pressure it's like trying to piss while somebody's
staring at your dick and look we've all been there and I am staring at his dick while he is doing that
part right so Taylor Parrot asks and then I assume I'll ask again because his last name's Parrot will
you ever do a live show big question maybe have us hellians in a theater play an awesome horror movie
you two have mics do commentary throughout the showing the wheels are very much in motion
what we already talked about it we did looks like we're gonna do one in October hopefully I think we're
gonna do smaller dates prior hopefully we'll let you know you'll be the first to know rich McBeath
hopefully a real name for Joe top five rap producers five sorry it's a good question just curious
no that's a great question DJ premier is my number one uh Dr. Dre is my number two
um the bomb squad who don't really do much together anymore I don't think my number three my
number four is Sir jinx who produced a lot of the earlier ice cube stuff and my five is DJ mugs
from Cypress Hill I like the producers who yell their name at the beginning of a track
well that's DJ Khaled that's the DJs that do that they make like mixed tapes and then because
they're just playing you other people songs they have to yell their own name right over the entire
mic will made it and I guess that's in their contract you want to have a hit you gotta let me put this
on the DJ mustard I don't I mean there's some great DJs out there funk master flexes great you know but like
you know but uh some of those mixed tapes I've never heard of DJ Khaled when some of them I'm
literate like the Wendy Williams would put them out and it's like this is literally just a compilation
of other people's songs and you just put your name on it yeah yeah yeah um all right I think
that these DJs were talking about now are producers they have the beats and they just go they go by DJ
but I don't I don't think they're like DJ DJ who DJ Khaled you know he's a
yeah I think he actually makes me yeah he does he does as does you know Mike will and etc he's a
producer um pat whatever happened Emily Griffith asks pat whatever happened to your neighborhood
stalker that hey boss story of yours still gives me the creeps told this on the you made it weird
with Pete Holmes podcast as I believe I did the virginity story sorry but uh he still lives in the
neighborhood I haven't seen him in months I think they I know they don't give lobotomies but it
seems like they gave him a lobotomy he looks comatose when I see him he's never outside anymore
and he was a real problem for the first year I live there now have you said to him hey buddy you
don't lobotomy I don't lobot a you have you said that to him yet I will the next time I see he won't
get very good because it's a lobotomy but yeah I mean he's still around until he goes off his meds
again and and kills us both as we sleep and hopefully that doesn't happen all right test and that
asks what is both your next big project coming up TV gigs writing all right test uh I
have a project I have a pilot that will hopefully be happening soon I've postponed a lot of other stuff
because it was supposed to have happened a couple times already but we're we're having a little
little red tape issue so hopefully that'll be out soon and and and I'm trying to sell a book
in a film so we'll see yes and I will my show hasn't been cancelled but it has it also basically has
it's like a 99 .9 percent and they do this because they're miserable fox who I mean specifically
CBS here it is and they will try to keep you from taking other work and they do this to actors and they
do as to writers as well but they won't officially cancel it they'll leave you hanging on now is staffing
season the time when I should be going on meetings to find out what my next project is and I am doing that
folks but I'm doing it like illegally because I'm under contract they'll let me know the shows cancelled
after that period has ended so that I can't take work um these people are soulless and awful I do it to
the actors you know the entire cast currently can't go do other projects because they're hanging on
for the show that they just pulled off the fucking air um so I I'll wind up somewhere I have a lot of
things in the hopper I've got shows I've got movie things I've got things happening I don't I don't
have anything to announce just yet but you know I need to have this stuff officially done before I can
move on and make announcements uh we have about time for one more we're at about 59 minutes here
I promise these people I was reading them till I said stop so we got more to go
all right we got more to go how many more and we don't always have to be an hour we can go over on
this well how many more just so I have an idea any you know the the ends inside but you know here we
go all right we'll pick it up a little bit and maybe there'll be some doubles I'm enjoying myself
I'm not having a bad time I just you know got a dog and everything describe your dream woman ask
the man to leave some uh it's and I I can tell from her question she's hoping you describe her
I'm gonna go with the old Kastanza Marisa Tome probably okay it has always been the uh she's
saying describe not just like pick a celebrity that you want to say just what Marisa Tome looks like
and then I don't have to go through all the damn D I'm not getting into like there's no personal
personality why that stuff no no everything about everything about Marisa Tome hits what I would love
and a lady okay like the figure the face the spunk the attitude the talent the sense of humor
everything about her is spot on do you think that holding this ideal of of one of the most perfect
women in the world might have kept you single low these past 40 years no I've never held her as my
ideal in real life I'll go out with anybody but yeah no I'm kidding I know I've never held anybody
the ideal I'm just saying you're talking like dream woman and I did if I had to make a woman like
weird science I'd make Marisa Tome I really can't disagree with that I mean she's she's
more attractive and appealing 30 years later than she was like in my cousin Benny it's incredible
uh question for both what is your most prized possession I think we am I sitting next to yours Joe
yes mine is my 1983 mint condition star wars arcade cabinet that is also rigged to play the empire strikes
back game as well and con and I gotta say I feel like if Marisa Tome was in the department
that would seal the deal for her the star wars machine I think she would think it was cool I think she
wanted she'd say yeah let's play this fucking thing why I'll see you have it she might
my most prized possession I will say is my and I own the entire criteria on collection
you've you've gotten there you finally own on blue ray I own the entire criteria that's great
every every criteria on blue ray on the DVD no but blue ray I'd do and really all that is is when
I was a kid I would be like wow what if one day I could do that it's actually not hard to do they come
out with three a month 60 bucks no it is not 60 bucks do those fucking things start at like 30 40
bucks man I only buy them at the Barnes and Noble 50 % off sale okay or through the criteria on website
which is they're always 20 bucks you can get them for 20 on the website when they have a sale
when they have a sale and when you spend a certain amount they give you a nice $50 gift card and
ain't that much that you gotta spend they're a great company all right that's probably mine you know
I have a simple man I don't I don't have a lot of possessions okay or my record collection which
brings us to my next question Kevin Marcinic what are some records both of you have been into lately
doesn't have to be from this year lately well I've been listening to oh god
I've been listening to this Elvis comp that I've been enjoying Presley or Castella
Presley on vinyl I've been listening to Sinatra the reprise years which is a nice vinyl set
so when he said doesn't have to be from this year he did mean it does have to be from the
century oh boy oh bad religion the gray race just came out on vinyl colored vinyl remastered
I just picked that up I'm enjoying that revisiting that record and
man I'm blanking I know I have something else that I've been kind of spinning a lot but I can't
remember but that's enough it's a great answer I finally I because I get obsessed with shit
listen to them exclusively for a long period of time just now after like a year plus I have broken
my tusk Fleetwood Mac addiction I was always listening to tusk by Fleetwood Mac particularly the
Lindsey Buckingham songs which they now have thrown him out of the band again he's out of the band
they what do you do just like the last time they had to replace him with two people
why is he thrown out I'm sure he was being a dick he's a notorious like prickly kind of perfectionist
type guy they threw him out there placed him with the guy from the heartbreakers Mike Campbell
and also with Neil Finn from Crowded House and is the is the witch lady still in there what's
your face Stephen X yeah oh yeah I mean without those two there wouldn't be a band she's in there
because she was gone for a long time right they've always had one of the other but I think next yeah
next was out they've had the the keyboardist Christine McVee was out for a while you know it's a it's a
it's a band where they've all fucked they all like cheated on their spouses with each other there's
a lot of bad blood and probably things that didn't get resolved they need to do that metallic
a therapy shit they probably won't do it um I listen lately I listen to a lot of roxy music
which is a band from 70s I love them the song both ends burning I listen to every day to get ready
I listen to
well I don't know I tend to be a song guy I make big playlists listen to a bunch of songs I like
the new LCD sound system I uh I don't know what to tell you I again these are hard to think of
on the spot all right the new queens is pretty good but not great new queens is tonic I came and
went with that one I loved it and then I it doesn't kind of stick around but their cover of good
by yellow brick road is phenomenal they did it live when I saw them it was it was great um yeah
I think that's probably enough I I could go on and on but you know whatever um next cue
if you could switch two movie characters what switch would lead to the most inappropriate movies
asks Brooke Adams I don't understand that question if you could switch to movie like put somebody
in the in another movie let's say I okay the nutty professor the Jerry Lewis nutty professor
in uh shinler's list I guess well that's the day of the clown crime I believe well yeah it's what
maybe think of it but that might get released this year by the way on DVD we might finally see that
movie oh really that's a notorious uh Jerry Lewis bomb that got immediately like put into
a vault because they were so embarrassed by it but it sounded like life is beautiful it's a guy
trying to make comedy in the Holocaust you people have seen it Harry Sheerer is one of them yeah
all right um I'll I'll say uh that is a hard question I'll say Mary Poppins in the wrestler
with Mickey Rourke and then so he's the re he becomes Mary Poppins and uh she becomes the wrestler
I think that's a good answer okay holy shit the next question is who's your favorite wrestler
that's weird synchronicity the police the roger rich asked who's your favorite wrestler the rock
hands down of all time I never I love the rock and uh I've just never been into wrestling my
my favorite I know the ultimate warrior used to scare me a lot as a kid but you know I'd go
with somebody big that everyone likes you know like either Hulk Hogan or uh I don't know the giant
I guess I always like tugboat the big fat guy hmm earthquake I mean the rock just a few people have
had that kind of charisma yeah I have his DVDs in with my comedy DVDs because I literally just
watched him laugh hysterically okay it's just an amazing fucking character I love it all right
I like that new breeders album quite a bit I saw them the other night front row
absolutely killer if they if they come to your city go see them are both deals in the band right now
both deals the uh Kelly deal looks like Michael Jackson she these are two of the least glamorous
rock stars of all time I mean she looks like Michael Jack her face is entirely new
and it looks a little unsettling really you hate to talk about it but um it was jarring to me
then I looked them up and they're like 57 the breeders yeah uh and Kim comes out you know I hadn't
even brushed her hair you know like it was weird to see and especially because their twins like to see
them look that different is a little weird but uh Kim deals voice is still just absolutely incredible and
their new album is pretty good um I liked I liked half of it I thought it was I had too many
slow numbers on it but I'll go back they tend to go more that way and they sound a better
live the new songs sometimes that's the case uh favorite ballad asks Patrick Baxter so favorite
Patrick Baxter asks what is your favorite ballad I guess they mean what you know favorite slow song or
favorite sad song my favorite ballad and it's a contender for my favorite song of all time is it
was a very good year by Frank Sinatra I love the song used to genius effect and the sopranos
the show you refused to watch it was a season premiere they used the song to update you on everybody
in the show it was incredible uh it's a brilliant song it's beautifully written it's beautifully
orchestrated his version of it is you know the one for me oh boy haunting I'd use the word haunting
my favorite ballad I mean that that's impossible there's too many to choose but a few that spring to mind
are uh Elliott Smith ballad of big nothing I find that a beautiful and insanely depressing song
I would say I love stolen car by Bruce Springsteen very sad song
um and I you know there's too many to choose I I need time to think I would say there's a bunch
that's all that that's all I can say wicked game by Chris Isaac is a great one go yeah um
I'll get back to you I'll get back to you all right um
boom boom boom boom boom boom which VHS cover art scared you the most or left a long lasting
impression from the days of browsing the rental store before you were old enough to rent scary movies
as Derek Clark I had I would say all of them because all horror boxes scared the shit out of me
because I was a coward as a kid Joe yeah want to particularly stand there yeah and it's my favorite
horror movie the exorcist cover to this day gives me the creeps uh which is funny because the cover
is of the priest he's the good guy in the movie right but it's just real fucking creepy so I that's
always been the one that resonated most with me okay um and yeah I really couldn't even even name
just one but I mean uh that you know we talked about uh doctor giggles you know for some reason
then you flip it to the back and there'd be a thousand things back there that would scare me they
all scared and then you see them when you're an adult and you're like I was scared of this like what
what the fuck um all right there are a lot of these I can't deny it we're getting close
Allison Lee asks what was your favorite childhood novel and please read Harris and me if you
haven't it's hilarious is that the Harris Whittles book I don't know all right I would think so but
my favorite childhood novel without question was Maniac McGee I absolutely loved it it's it's for
you know a 12 13 year old kid probably I recommended it to a woman I worked with
and uh she read it to her son and it like traumatized and she was like how depressed for you
as a kid that you liked that book I was like very depressed uh and but and earlier than that I loved
a book called Rent a Third Grader but Maniac McGee I imagine would still hold up it was great and I
loved all those Beverly Cleary books Ralph Alice Mouse Ramona Ramona the past all that I loved
that I loved the something queer series like something queer at the library something queer at the
museum there's a title you couldn't have anymore it it meant it in its traditional sense like uh you
know it was these kid detectives something strange as a foot here right uh but I also really loved
and these aren't novels but they were books I adored as a kid scary stories to tell in the dark which
a lot of modern horror fans loved as kids they're making them into film apparently but we just talk
about horrifically graphic etchings to go with these stories uh and they were great stories I
still will listen to the audiobooks uh they're just a lot of fun did you do goose bumps I was too
late I was too late and did you do the Christopher Pike you familiar with him no you had a book called
Monster that had like a one paragraph hot tub jack -off sex scene that I jacked off to 80 million times
for kids it that was when you're heading to the teen years Christopher Pike was sort of the older
goose bumps by like three four years I didn't know Christopher when goose bumps popped I was already like
doing uh tells him the crypt and rewatching tells him the dark side that sort of thing okay fair enough
uh if you could replace the lead and act and lead and act oh and uh if you personally could
replace the lead and act in any movie which would it be ask Elizabeth Myers uh Indiana Jones
be a very different picture well I'm saying it's a fantasy right I mean right but I don't think I
could do it I'm just saying if I could be have a wish granted or Han Solo one of those two right I
would say I wish we could have prepared answers I if I could replace lead in any movie
maybe somewhere I could be like a rock star no you know what I'd want to be Rick Rannis's part in
little shop of horse I can sing those songs well uh really yeah that'd be fun he's a weasel of a
fucking that movie he's a nerd hills people he's feeding them to the plant I mean I don't know
I think that'd be a good one that's the one that popped into my head all right I'm sticking with it
that's fine well we have 48 more questions to get to so now we're getting close Chris Goodnight
asked what was the first game Joe remembers beating oh video game um
christ it's got to be super mario brothers that's got to be because that was one of the first
if I can if I remember correct well in my home that was one of the first beatable games you know
games up until that point for the most part not everything but you know there were there were
exceptions like adventure or or venture and stuff like that but you know for the most part games were
ports of arcade games and and they were just play for points and eventually maybe you can hit a kill
screen if you're a fucking psycho right but mario brothers was the first game where it was like I
remember they're being a goal of saving the princess and being obsessed enough with the game to do it
so that is my answer yeah I think the first and only game I ever beat was we mario which me and my
old roommate Jared had just the best time playing and when we beat it about a week in of basically
playing 24 hours a day we stood up hugged each other walked down the hall and each went to our
separate beds to sleep there's a magical moment beautiful uh that wasn't that long ago I'd
probably ten years ago no well my story's from last week oh uh luke physiock asks what is the most
awkward exchange both of you have had with a celebrity in the business pat you can't pick acroid
after Conan or Juliet Lewis at your housewarming party well Juliet Lewis is the best possible one I'm
sorry and mine's still Chris Isaac yeah I mean this is similar to an earlier question um
well or uh Christopher walkin talking to us for an hour about how drummers get all the girls which
I've also told the spot here it's the drummer gets the girls Erica branding asked what was your
favorite stuffed animal growing up that you were inseparable from mine was my elf whose mouth I
thought an eventually caught fire on my heated reading lamp that doesn't get less disturbing that
story mine was my chubaka which my mom still has an a box in the attic ever home and I by the way
I didn't fuck my chubaka I respected him but it's respected out you can respect someone and
fuck that's your problem now now fucking the doll and then letting it burn to death is you know never
came and then else mouth uh but the uh what's it called yeah my chubaka which my mom still has
it a box in her attic in in my parents house and I go you got to throw this thing away even as a
collector of shit like this like Star Wars shit and toy throw this thing is disgusting it looks just
like a matted hair ball and she's always like but you could give it to your son one day I'm like
who what child would want to touch this thing uh it looks disgusting yeah but as a kid I loved it
moms cannot give shit away yeah can't give shit away I don't think there's anything for my childhood
that that still exists but maybe that's fine I don't need it well what are you gonna do with it you know
I'm not uh whatever you call it not a sentimental man I want everything thrown away too
Anthony Manito asks for a man without shoulders how does Joe sound like he's constantly shrugging
uh the old shoulders bit this is back from the ON 8 days it seems mean to me it's like like it was
it was a it was a trademark on my ON 8 days uh he's just that's just he's just being funny all right
I mean it's just tough to to get it nothing I'm not not laughing at the joke because I'm like
because I don't like it I'm just stop to get a good no shoulders crack in these days I've kind of
heard them all but fair enough yeah Shane Nazarian asks I know you guys are into Fuman too very much so
are you into any other stoner rock bands or sludge slash doom bands absolutely I mean I've been
waiting till this weekend because I plan to get baked and listen to the new sleep album I cannot wait
to hear the new sleep album I love sleep uh both the thing and the band man I I'd like to check
that I don't know they had a new album out yeah fool is fool is is slowly becoming my favorite bad
of all excuse me of all time but uh I like the shrine quite a bit um they're good they're really good
Sabbath of course there's some choice deep purple records mainly machine head and in rock
from the 70s that are really fantastic stoner rock records you haven't had a trouble
trouble troubles a great band I happen to hear it amoeba the other day and shazamdom they sounded like
exactly like Sabbath and they were terrific oh uncle acid I like quite a bit it's very stoner rocky um
smile who became a pop band but their first record McKee is a super great so stoner rock album if you
can find a copy of it I suggest listening to it it's very good how's the pop stuff great great I've
never heard of um and my you know mine of course is those first queens of stoner albums oh yeah those two
yeah I like I like a great deal of stoner rock especially when I'm stoned in terms of doom band I
never like the cookie monster voice and that kind of shit now and you know yeah I agree uh can't
lay love you can ask fuck Mary kill Frazier bulky earnest I'm marrying Frazier all day long baby
I mean they'll keep the conversation flowing uh you fuck bulky it's an exotic night yeah you kill
earnest I mean the other guy's gonna drive you up a fucking wall after two hours weirdly I think
that Frazier would be the man to fuck Ann Mary I mean I Frazier's gonna be the best lay and the best
conversationalist keep it going but if I have to choose you do it you do need to kill earnest I mean
earnest is many things a sexual being is not one of them bulky yeah you're absolutely right
bulky fucking Frazier Mary uh Tim oh my god Tim this last name Calc flash sorry I'm sorry Tim
but that's a crazy last name where is the best place you have traveled uh I've only been to London
Paris and Amsterdam if you're talking outside of the country and it was a dream trip and I think
Amsterdam was my favorite part of it it was just fantastic yeah I'd probably agree I've been I've
been to a number of places at this point um all of them were great you know but uh I think uh Amsterdam
is still probably my fave which you know who knows if I went back now and I wasn't like boozing it
up and everything I don't know maybe but I just had a partying hell of a time in Amsterdam I really
do a two and a half week honeymoon degrees I certainly hope that that is my new answer when I am done
uh Matt little asks if you've seen I'm dying up here on showtime what are your thoughts opinions about
it I only saw the pilot which I guess is is the answer to your question and of course it's unfair to
judge a show on its pilot but I didn't feel like it was for me um we we've hit a we've hit a
capacity on shows about stand -up comedy uh I agree I have a lot of friends on the show so I hope it
continues to do well for them and I hope that uh you know I hope that they're enjoying the experience
but but I would agree it's not really for me I think it gives it gives a little too much service
to the comedy store I like the comedy store I do shows there that is not a shot at the comedy store but
I agree with Pat in the sense that we've we've hit capacity and I'm kind of
whether it's a documentary or a TV show or movie at this point I'm kind of tired of this premise of
the the struggle of the comedian and and how we just marched to the beat of a different drummer and all this
I mean Jesus Christ man there are people starving to death around the world every day we're sitting here
praising somebody's uh bravery to to go on stage and talk about their mother I completely agree
say come on and at the end of that pile when it was like you got to talk about yourself don't talk about
and then get up there and then she's like I'll do some personal material and it connects with the
audience that's I've seen that 50 times now in a variety of these shows so uh the line of the I mean
the line in the first episode of the kid dies and they go we need to get it we we should book a church
and then the lady goes where in a church oh yeah I mean it's like come on man this is like for me it was
anybody in any walk of life taking themselves that seriously you make that's what comedians especially
make fun of yeah so anyway for me it was having that that the only black kid in the show uh jerk
off for a priest for money I was like this doesn't seem to fit into the show that actually happens in
the bottom I thought that was a bit much yeah I thought it was a little too much strange Ben Lee
asks Pat you have talked about enjoying a visual experience for its own sake and can let the story
fall away if the visuals are interesting enough examples neon demon jeepers creepers doc strange
three movies Joe despise so then what explains your distaste for blade runner and the sequel which
when you admit that it's visually interesting um I don't know what to tell you I I do think blade
runner is visually fantastic um but for me it is so boring that I'm not able to find any interest in
it whereas neon demon jeepers creepers doctor strange all three of them uh at least what was happening
in them kept me interested enough not to say I didn't have story problems but um you know neon demon
whatever is a is a experience as opposed to a movie and blade runner was trying to be a film
noir like a plot heavy kind of thing and the plot didn't work for me I don't know what to tell you
I think our most controversial opinion by far is blade runner people don't understand
I don't understand if you if you wrote it down on paper these are the ingredients for the movie
I'd say this is a delicious recipe I can't stand the fucking movie yeah uh Joe any thoughts on Jeff
and some aliens being yanked after an initial renewal your written episode was easily the best of the
bunch thank you for that compliment uh no no opinions I don't even know what got yanked to be honest so
you know you're part of so many uh things in your career that some of them are
are going to be constants and others are jobs that you have that you know you have them and then
it's over and that was sort of one of those jobs for me so I don't really have any thoughts I wish
those guys well though and I hope they uh land on their feet yes Dan Clark asks what should my wife
name are upcoming child con I agree con Joe you shouldn't be asking us Dan you need to talk to
your wife uh and congratulations and good luck I hope it's a little hellian Joe price asks ready
player one best movie of the year or best movie ever I haven't seen it yet but I want to know how
loud I'll squeal when I do well Joe just listen to Monday's episode because uh we did not love it
woo you are going to be disappointed my friend and that is when I cut them off but since there are
only a couple more that went past the thing let's just do them and be done with it what is it
a couple more literally two okay uh a sort of longest episode ever with 90 minutes that's fun no no
I'm saying I'm patting us on the back we're at 90 minutes no commentary that's right by the way
I don't feel the tired that I felt during the commentary it's because it's something about I don't want
to talk to me a lot coming at us yeah anyway we're getting you know specific questions as opposed to
just talk for 90 minutes uh why did Joe tell Connie to do what he did had tangus as an ass if you be
a fly on the wall if you could be a fly on the wall in any movie set what movie would it be mine would
be the twilight zone 80s movie you're gonna see some sites there I would be curious on how they
could let a death lead actor happen how could be so careless well I ask you to read that uh twilight
zone book that I read which was fantastic um that tells you exactly how it happened but Joe what would it
be I would be a fly on the wall of the fly and I'd give extensive notes on the inaccuracies of how
they were portraying a fly's lifestyle okay you like the fly though right I love it uh
and for me I mean what could be cooler well no I almost of course I'm gonna pick my two favorites I
mean good fellows to see that movie come together can you even imagine how amazing yeah that'd be
pretty incredible and then my other I gotta say plans trains I mean Steve Martin and John candy hanging
out I would honestly say in all seriousness uh I would probably pick the dark crystal that is such
in a Marvel film like the spectacle goes beyond anything I can even comprehend how they did all
that with puppets is I don't even understand yeah and I would that's and the fact that they built
those sets too like I mean I feel like if you were on that set you'd literally be stepping into that
world that'd be pretty fucking cool right uh yeah I'd also say blues brothers because so many drugs and
also you get to see James Brown, Ruth Franklin, Ray Charles you still get to meet John candy I
mean it's a dream yeah it's a good one and then well last question we already answered Caitlin
McGinley asked how did you and Joe meet we were set up by Pete basically sort of a double date situation
situation um guys this was very fun thank you for these excellent questions I think it is likely we
will do this again down the line it was a success um we don't do plugs or anything on these so we
will just say thank you very much for being loyal patreon supporters we can't tell you enough I'm
much we appreciate it and we are in the work stage of putting together a live show so we will see you
next time folks we love you and we will see you in hell