Get downtown the easy way aboard Amtrak with all the legroom and then of that middle seat stuff.
Driving just doesn't track. Learn more at Amtrak .com.
Amtrak, retrain travel.
Say hello to the next generation of Zendesk AI agents built to deliver resolutions for everyone.
Load by over 10 ,000 companies, Zendesk AI agents easily deploy in minutes to resolve 30 % of interactions instantly.
That's the Zendesk AI effect. Find out more at Zendesk .com
Start beans on your own.
A podcast network.
Welcome to Will See You In Hell, your favorite podcast to get information about horror sci -fi and fan.
The fantasy films and once in a while an action flick a comedy thing or a dramatic farce.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
A dramatic farce.
I'd be interested in what that is.
I would do it.
I think it's invented a genre.
As it was coming out of my mouth, I really liked it.
People coming in and out of doors crying for different reasons.
Yeah, farce by nature is a comedy, but that's fine.
I'd like to thank right off the bat our new sponsor Audible.
Thanks for coming on board and helping us out and being part of the family.
Absolutely.
Folks, today we're going to be talking about a documentary called Horror Noir.
Noir.
Horror Noir.
That's my Missouri coming out.
And it's available on the Shutter app, which is another sponsor and it just winds up being a coincidence
because we picked this title before they became a sponsor, but we love Shutter.
And this is a great time to check them out.
If you haven't seen this documentary or the other great contents that they have.
No, we're not obviously going to get right into the movie.
We'll come back to it.
But before I forget to mention this, I wanted to ask you, the title confuses of this film, Horror Noir.
I thought New War meant like detective movies.
Noir does.
In this case, I believe they mean noir as in black because it's about black horror films.
Is the word Noir means black?
It does.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Okay.
It can also mean like it means like a dark wine as well, you know, like Pinot Noir.
Oh, I didn't.
Oh, oh, duh, duh.
I love it.
And noir as a film genre means like a dark film, dark themes.
That's what that means.
Yes.
I thought it literally meant detective.
No.
Well, you're not taking a sharpest tool in the shed as smash mouth.
What's that?
Says the man wearing a sweater and a collard shirt in 80 degree weather today.
I just drove in from Lake Arrowhead where it was 25 degrees last night.
I went to get a newspaper to start a fire with it because that's how edgy I am.
I don't even read the news.
I burn it.
But I got out of my car.
My door flipped open.
Like I thought it was going to come off its hinges.
Like I was in the Wizard of Oz and I was my blood is not the same as it was when I lived in Missouri where we actually had winters.
I can't tolerate it anymore.
So I was wearing several layers the whole weekend and here I am.
Now at any point.
I feel quite comfortable if I may say so.
At any point during this stay alone in the cabin.
Did you begin solving a murder where you found out you were actually the murderer.
But you didn't know it at the beginning of it.
Anything like that happened up in the cabin.
No, because it was just me in the cabin.
So that would have been a really weird.
It's just Johnny Depp in secret window.
Oh, that was a secret window reference.
Exactly what it was.
I don't remember that movie at all.
I saw it at the theater.
I remember it being terrible.
Yeah, it sucks.
He's in a cabin and he.
He's in a cabin alone, but he kills somebody somebody.
It's I gotta remember.
It's got something to do with like he there's a murderer on the loose and he's the murderer, but he's hunting himself.
You know, it's one of those 1408 kind of.
I bet that they came in through that secret window.
Folks, let's get on.
If I may with the show and at the same time on with the Joe.
I don't know what I was doing either.
I didn't like that.
I'd freak me out.
Major dog panic and then sneeze on me.
I'm in a terrible seat in my apartment.
I'm on the side of the couch.
Sun just beating on my neck.
It's just brutal.
I have been angry and uncomfortable for weeks and I can't seem to shake it.
And knocking off the drink and didn't help.
I'll tell you that much.
Pat is on a drinking break.
God knows why.
I'm on a everything break.
I'm doing a cleanse.
Five day cleanse.
I had just, you know, fallen to shit.
I was unable to exercise or do anything I normally do.
And I do like to do this once a year.
Kind of reset the old system.
Drinking just a disgusting juice to stay alive.
Now, I've been doing juice is a very generous word here.
It's ginger, lemon and cayenne pepper.
I've been doing it in the morning every morning.
A smoothie.
Yeah.
But I just make it with water so it's not really that smooth.
It's more like a thick juice.
But I've been doing every morning.
One green apple, a bunch of spinach and kale and water with electrolytes in it.
And it gives me quite a charge every morning.
Oh.
And I feel that, you know, I ate two doughnuts after that today.
And I felt like it was kind of okay to eat the doughnuts because I had a 64 ounce fucking thing of spinach.
You're drinking every morning, 64 ounces?
My blender is 72 ounces and this thing fills up far more than half of it.
Okay.
But it's probably 32 ounces in all honesty.
But I think from what I've heard, if you eat a bunch of shit, it can help a little bit to eat something healthy after.
So you may want to go doughnuts than juice.
Well, sure.
I mean, I don't do doughnuts every day.
I'm just saying it was Saturday.
There's a wonderful little Italian shop up the road.
I stopped in.
The guy had doughnuts filled with Italian custard.
I said, well, I got to try these things.
They were magnificent life -changing doughnuts, these things.
Joe, might I ask you not to tell me where that place is?
They were filled with a paprika lemon ginger custard.
Right up your alley.
Paprika.
Didn't you say that drink was paprika, ginger, and lemon?
Oh, I did.
I thought you were saying that they had...
I don't know what these italians put in their doughnuts.
I've never had one.
These waps.
What do they do over there in Italy?
I'm waiting to hear from Heather, my wife.
I came home to find my bathtub.
Not full, but certainly packed with quite a lot of cat turds.
And we have a litter box that the cat has never ventured outside of.
And I need answers, frankly.
It was disgusting and wild, and I need answers.
But she's working, and I'm waiting to hear.
That's gross.
Let me tell our listening audience, our sweet helians if you will,
why it's such a tragedy you're not drinking today.
Yeah.
I was invited, folks, to attend a show at the Legion Hall here in Hollywood,
where I am an honorary colonel.
I'd like to add.
Sure.
And a member of the hall, it's a veteran's hall.
I've performed there as a comic.
And tonight, they're doing a big benefit fundraiser thing.
And the great Ron White is headlining.
I was invited just to attend the show.
I happened to bump into Ron White the other night.
I don't really know the guy.
We start talking at the comedy store bar.
We're having a few drinks.
He says, you're coming to the show.
Do the goddamn thing.
You're going to be there.
I'm going to put you to work.
It puts me on the show.
It's going to be a night I'd imagine of flowing drinks and comedy.
And one of Pat's favorites, Ron White on stage.
And not only can he not go to this thing, he can't drink.
I mean, this would have been like one of the best nights we've ever had together.
It really sucks.
And I have met Ron White.
I doubt you would remember me especially with the amount of tequila that we drank the night that we hung out.
But yeah, that really sucks.
And I'm going to an engagement party.
I was just telling Joe beforehand.
I'm like, you know, Heather text me.
She's like, hey, you know, we got to get something.
I looked it up.
We got to get like a bottle of Dom Perignon.
Or we got to get like a super nice gift or something.
And I'm like, in addition to the wedding gift.
And yes, of course, you have to get a wedding gift.
When does it end?
It doesn't.
I used to have a bit about this in my act that I don't remember how the bit went.
But I just remember talking about, it's like engagement party, christening.
Sorry, wait, engagement party, wedding, christening, baby shower.
It's fucking ridiculous.
You started the family.
Go have the goddamn family.
It's not on us to fucking nurse you through this shit.
You know what I do when I can't afford a car?
I don't buy a car.
That's how that works.
Now, Joe says this, but I just pulled up behind a Jaguar that says proud parent of a.
Folks, it's the first ever doorbell on the podcast.
Why don't you take the, why don't you take the wheel and I'll see who's at the door?
I will.
Yeah, so it's probably my car.
That's what it must be.
I got to move my car.
Do you think that's what it is?
Anyway, folks, I pulled up behind Joe's Jaguar that he bought, like an old used car.
And it says proud parent of a USC Trojan, which I found pretty hilarious because Joe is not.
There's a lot going on at this door, folks.
If I'm being honest, I'm worried that Joe's going to get shot.
He's fine.
I wanted to add a little horror style suspense to the podcast.
Any who is everything okay, Joe?
All right, not my car.
Did you have a delivery?
A package?
Captain John Luke Picage?
That was a little breathy because as you can hear, my dog.
I mean, it's like, it's like a guy, it's like a non vet hearing a car backfire.
Anyway, you can stop it.
I don't know how to.
I got to tell you.
I try to love my cat.
I always think about how much I would love to remove its voice box.
I love the purring.
The meowing is constant and incessant.
It can't eat enough, and it's becoming an issue, frankly.
I've tried.
And on cue, there goes the downstairs techno music starting.
My downstairs neighbor, I go the other day, techno music starts.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, but to answer your question, yeah, I got a package.
It's my mailman.
The same mailman can never seem to fit the stuff in the book.
It almost annoys me because every other day rings the bell.
That's not a big packet.
And the dog starts barking and stuff.
And it's like, dude, can you just leave the goddamn thing on the stoop?
I know he's doing the responsible thing.
I shouldn't get annoyed with it.
Yes.
On this one, I side with the postman.
I do too, but I'm still irritated because you got to listen to that.
Oh, also.
Oh no, that is my address.
Okay.
So what is the deal with this car with the proud USC parent bumper sticker?
That Jaguar I got for $1 ,500 flat all in.
So I bought it because I said I wanted to get a beater car to kind of go from point A to point B.
Right.
It's got a hell of an engine in it.
It's in wonderful shape.
It's beautiful looking.
And it was $1 ,500 bucks.
And I own it outright.
Do you know why it was $1 ,500 bucks?
I mean, it's an old car.
So it's like, it's only worth about at the most three grand in a resale.
Okay.
And I just found a good deal on it.
All right.
But I ran the van and did all that crap.
And it's in good shape.
She's clean.
She's clean, baby.
That dog will hunt.
So it's just a great little car to ride from, you know, around town in.
All right.
Once I get my license, which is next week, I think I finally get to go to take the test.
That's great.
And you're, you're only 41.
42.
So why I've had a license in the past.
Folks, I would also like to say, speaking of, as we said in our ad, we're both listening
to Pet Cemetery, read by Dexter.
And we're going to definitely do that on the show.
Joe and I, I'm calling it now.
Joe, don't see it with anyone but me.
I will see it with you.
I'm oddly excited to see it, even though I kind of know it's going to suck.
I don't know.
It's going to suck.
I'm trying to be optimistic.
I haven't been excited about anything at all in years.
I mean, look, the producers of it continue to reign terror throughout the, the horror movie
community.
Yeah.
They did it.
Now they're doing this.
They're behind the child's play remake, which I posted about this on Instagram the other day.
Like, could these, could the people behind this remake get it any less?
Yeah.
Like they're all proud.
Like a list actor voicing Chuckie.
It's like, oh, so you don't want Chuckie to be scary at all?
Right.
It's just like, who is it?
They didn't say it.
Yeah.
That's what I want to hear.
It's like David Cross voicing Chuckie.
Is he a list?
You know what I mean?
No, but it's not going to be David Cross, either.
Although he did voice.
No, he was, he didn't voice one of the chipmunks.
He was their manager.
Yeah.
It'll be, it'll be like, you know, like Amy Cideris as the voice of Chuckie.
That's something I never got.
So David Cross, and I don't know the man, portrayed a, the manager of the chipmunks, Alvin and
the chipmunks.
And he goes on Conan and he's like, this fucking movie is a piece of shit.
Blah blah blah.
And it's like, dude, you did it for the money.
Yeah.
No one is faulting you for that.
I mean, I'm sure people are faulting David Cross for doing that.
But I think more and more people are understanding you have to do ads.
You have to put your music in commercials and movies.
If you want to make a dime, they're not making anything off a Spotify or anything like that.
So like, well, I just, it always rose me the wrong way when somebody goes in and starts making fun of the movie.
They're in.
You can turn it down.
You needed the money.
And when you take the money, you're obligated to perform.
And if they ask you to promote.
Look, I think David Cross, you know, became a victim of his own hubris.
As I've said before about most celebrities that get sort of attacked in this position
and whatever, you know, he got, he got hit pretty hard for that joke he made.
Yeah.
The Asian joke.
It's like, dude, when you walk around telling everybody they're stupid.
And if they don't vote a certain way, they're wrong.
And that you're smarter than they are and all that shit.
It's like people, oh, we're going to revel in.
Look, nobody's mad at Ray Romano if he makes a movie like that.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Because he's right.
He's just like, yeah, man, I got blast.
Have you watched Patelton?
The fuck is Patelton?
Oh, that's right.
You don't have Netflix.
Although we'll get to that in a minute.
But every time I log into Netflix, filling up my home pages, Ray Romano and one of the duplasses,
the one who has the therapy appointment before mine.
And it's called Patelton.
The movie where like Romano's going to die or whatever.
I think he's going to die.
I mean, to me, that's just a title that just makes me laugh.
And Romano knows how to pick him because he did one of the funniest titles ever.
Welcome to Mooseport.
But Patelton is like a dark movie.
I think there's a comedic edge.
I don't know.
I mean, look.
It's been on the home page for weeks and I haven't seen a single person talk about it.
So I'm sure it's not great.
Let's talk about Netflix because I am in a position where I could potentially get my subscription back
because they did pull the bird box footage.
Do you think that the head of Netflix, Chip Netflix, listens to this podcast and that's why you did it?
Yes.
All right.
And it's Sandy Netflix and it's a woman.
Okay.
Is the head of Netflix.
Find that hard to believe, but go on.
It seems like if it's a big corporation, it's probably run by a man.
And I know they'll come after me for saying that, but I believe we're gonna go to the other direction.
I believe it's a woman, but her name is in Sandy Netflix.
You know, who knows, but I do find it a coincidence that I talk about it the next day it changes.
That's true.
So I mean, you know, maybe it probably cost them a thousand dollars to do it.
I will say I have two friends far up the ladder at Netflix.
Okay.
So maybe one of them listens to the podcast.
Yes.
They might.
Speaking of Netflix, I mean, I got to take you over to Pat's movie corner, but I got to do more
than my share.
I'm piling them up, especially after a week in a cabin.
You do three and I'll do brief reviews.
I got to check some of these off my list.
Now it's triggering my ACD.
They're overflowing from my phone.
Why don't you keep, listen, here's what I'm asking you to do.
Why don't you keep the extras because I'm soon not going to have any.
Because my schedule is picking up a bit.
So I'd rather you cover my ass when I don't have any with your extras.
Happy to.
Yeah.
Instead of wasting them now.
Well, I don't consider wasting.
I've got more than I could ever do, frankly.
Look at this list.
What do you do all day?
This is what you do all day?
Well, these have been building up forever.
Because you limit me to three.
You limit me.
I don't limit you to three.
Your role was Pat's movie corner is three.
And it usually works out nicely for the segment.
Also, sometimes I put them on here twice and so forth.
I just want to clean up this list.
Sounds like somebody got sloppy.
I don't know what that means.
Folks, let's take you over to Pat's movie corner.
I'd like to kick this thing off with one of the worst movies I've seen in a long time.
And this thing was for my consideration.
Last year, it was critically acclaimed.
It's a picture called Don't Worry.
He won't get far on foot.
Now, hey, that's the worst title I've ever heard.
The Joaquin Phoenix thing.
Don't worry.
He won't get far on foot.
Pick six words and take them out of the title.
That's too long.
All right.
It's Joaquin Phoenix.
He plays an alcoholic paraplegic cartoonist, that old tale.
True story.
Jonah Hill at his worst.
If you dislike Jonah Hill, if you dislike the current,
holier than now, like smelling his own shit, Jonah Hill,
you will not believe this performance.
He is playing a gay man.
It all takes place in the 70s.
He's got like open silk shirts and flowing hair.
He's also in rehab with Joaquin.
And then Jack Black, the only person bringing any life to the proceedings
as the guy who's driving the car when Joaquin Phoenix gets paralyzed.
And does he say things like, sorry, you're in a wheel skadoosh.
He did say wheel skadoosh, which I thought was out of place.
And was dressed as a panda at the time.
Now, this movie, here's what it is.
A man in a wheelchair drinking himself nearly to death.
Once in a while, he will draw a shit cartoon.
This man is supposed to be like a world famous cartoonist.
He had big fans, Robin Williams and all these people.
And they show you some of these cartoons.
And a model for this would be American Splendor.
When you see the cartoons in that movie,
and when you see that guy's work, you're like, that's pretty awesome.
In addition to it, just being a great movie.
The guy's not a cartoonist in American Splendor.
Harvey just wrote the comics.
What's his name drew them?
Yeah, but you know, you see the material.
It's what I'm saying.
Yeah, crum, yes.
And crum's a great movie about a cartoonist.
This guy's named John Callahan.
There's a reason you never have heard of him.
And I am sorry.
I know the man was in a wheelchair.
But he draws, what Wikipedia here says,
off -color newspaper cartoons.
So you see a montage of like old women walking up to him
and spitting in his face.
I mean, like, your cartoons are disgusting.
You see these cartoons.
They're the most innocuous, lame,
poorly drawn unfunny shit you've ever seen.
What's his name?
John Callahan.
And everybody in the movie talks about him like he's a genius.
Like, John, you're a legend.
We love you, John.
And the cartoon suck.
Jim Davis, sir, you are not.
Charles Schulz, you are not Bill Waterston.
You are not.
These are probably the only three cartoonists I know.
Gary Larson.
They've got a bit of a far side vibe to them.
They suck.
You know, and maybe if I read a book about them
or looked at them,
but everything you see in this movie, you're like,
am I supposed to believe this is setting the world on fire?
It's one of those things where they try to act like this
is having some sort of impact when you know it didn't
because you don't know who the guy is.
But most of it is just people crying and drinking
and being miserable and AA scenes that go on forever.
Rooney Mara is in it as a love interest.
That's like the most underwritten female role I've seen in a movie.
Well, I mean, listen, it's about time they started
underwriting Rooney Mara's fucking roles
because I mean, you want to talk about death on screen.
She is no good.
And it's like watching an interview with Bjork.
You're just like, what is going on?
Is there a personality in there anywhere?
Everyone in the movie is at their worst.
There is a reason this started to be bandied about in the Oscar race
and then nobody talked about it after it came out.
But it was kind of critically acclaimed.
It's like sappiest shit.
And I just didn't like it.
I only like Jack Black.
And what makes it all the more depressing
is that it was directed by Gus Van Sant,
who is a once great filmmaker who has really lost his way.
He makes a bunch of very mediocre to crappy movies
and has a handful of good ones in there.
That's Gus Van Sant.
I think, yeah, his early movies up through Good Will Hunting
are pretty good.
They're all right.
And then there was decades of like, you know,
that movie with Matt Damon and KCF
like walking around the desert.
You know, there was a...
The Columbine movie.
The Cobain one was terrible.
Oh, I don't know.
Well, I'm gonna follow this up with something
that's really gonna piss off people.
Now the house music is annoying me.
It's every day.
Yeah.
And every...
But once a week, I text him and I say,
hey, man, the musical allowed you mind.
And he goes, yeah, no problem, dude.
I'm so sorry.
Turns it down.
And then thinks that that means the next day
he can turn it back to that volume again.
Gotcha.
It's irritating.
The other day, I come out of the house.
There's a woman there.
I don't know if it's a sister or a girl he's dating.
Whatever.
She's sitting on the front stoop having a drink.
What show am I to knock that?
No.
And I texted him and he wasn't there.
He had to text her to tell her to turn it down.
Because she started blaring music at eight o 'clock in the morning.
Twelve o 'clock, I finally texted him.
Like, dude, please.
It's like really loud.
Four hours, this is.
And so finally, I go downstairs around five
to walk the dog for the second time.
And I see her.
And she goes, she goes, oh, was the music too loud?
And I go, yeah.
And she goes, wow.
I mean, I got a text at 12 to turn it down.
I was like, what a bum.
It's 12 o 'clock.
Get out of bed.
And I go, yeah, I work nights.
And she goes, oh, my bad.
And I'm like, yeah, yo, I only ask you to turn it down
when I hear a fucking techno soundtrack
behind the TV show I'm watching.
Yeah.
That's when I ask you to turn it down.
What a fucking asshole.
That's a ballsy move to come back like that.
It's very loud.
Although it, you know, it may just be the acoustics of the place.
Who knows?
Well, the other day she was like, yeah,
the thing is, it's weird.
I can barely hear it in the next room
from the one I'm playing it in.
And I go, what do you mean?
She goes, well, I'm playing it in the bedroom
so I can hear it out here.
And I'm like, yeah, don't do that.
Right.
She's like, yeah, I don't know.
And I go, yeah, I have speakers in each room.
Yeah.
For $15.
Go to the dollar store and get a wireless speaker
for each room to sync your phone up with.
Right.
Don't, you don't blare it for one room
for the entire house.
Or get one of the photo deals that you just move around.
How hard is that?
Those are $50 tops.
So I don't know what to do.
I'm kind of at a point.
You know what, Helian?
I'd love to hear your opinion on this.
I'm debating going to the landlord
and saying like, look,
I've asked the guy several times.
He's always very nice.
But this isn't what I signed on for.
And it's not really fair.
Right.
But I also don't want to do that
if the right move first is to go to him
and be like, hey, dude, I got a really level with you here.
You can't play at that loud ever.
I don't know if that's what I do first
or the fact that he hasn't taken the hint now
after several discussions about it
that it's just like, well,
they sound like drug addicts.
But you may have to go to the landlord.
But is that like a punk move?
Yeah.
But you've tried repeatedly to handle it on your own
and that's what you got to do.
But then what happens?
You know?
Because I even said to him,
I go, why don't we do like a level test
and we'll know like what level not to turn it over?
Mine and yours.
Yeah.
And he's like, no, we're good.
Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
Like, okay.
Yeah.
What's he look like?
Like a nerdy, straight -laced guy.
Like he's like apparently he's like a financial advisor
or something.
But he's home a lot.
Work hard, play hard, baby.
Playing music a lot.
Yeah.
Probably a bit coin investor.
So I don't know.
Anyway.
All right.
I'm going to follow my with my movie corner.
I'm going to give you something that will piss off
everybody that's mad that I made a slide.
If you work in that last one.
Do you remember when we talked about the crane boy
in the movie, mysteries episode of Frazier?
I do.
And you said that's one of those ideas as a writer
you're driving to work to the writer's room.
You can't wait to get there.
Yes.
To pitch it because it's so perfect.
I watched an episode of married with children.
Okay.
Called Wabbit Season.
That is one of these ideas.
All right.
Here's the plot of the episode.
Owl is going to have a nervous breakdown
from stress at work.
Uh -huh.
His doctor says.
Stress being a shoe salesman?
Yeah.
Okay.
His doctor says you have to get a hobby
to bring some like, you know, solace into your life.
Some peace.
His hobby is he starts a garden in the backyard.
Yes.
A rabbit starts eating all of his vegetables.
And from that point on it is albundi descending into madness.
Into an elmer -fud like madness.
Uh -huh.
To catch this rabbit.
By the end of the episode there's a scene where he shoving
a stick of dynamite into a giant carrot.
Okay.
And he blows up his own house.
It's crazy.
He blows up the house?
He blows up the house back in it with the dynamite.
Then they have the house next week.
And then it's just back next week.
They do that again.
Was that show that much of a cartoon?
Yeah.
It was crazy.
I mean, I remember - I've seen quite a few, but I don't remember that.
It's an excellent episode.
All right.
It's insane.
And then -
Hear that?
Now there's a hammering or a fucking gun.
Uh -huh.
And then there's the - they had the audacity to have a joke in there
where they actually make fun of Kelly.
Because he's going to shoot the rabbit with a shotgun.
Yeah.
And Kelly goes, Daddy, whatever you do, be careful.
Because the rabbit will put his two fingers in the hole
and into the shotgun will blow up in your face.
Uh -huh.
And then everybody laughs like, what an idiot.
Cut to a scene of him putting dynamite into a carrot.
And it's like a foam care.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah.
All right.
I got to see this.
I enjoyed it thoroughly.
It was absolutely absurd.
Yeah.
I mean -
I - I missed that.
I missed that from comedy, you know?
Yeah.
There is no silly comedy anymore.
It - because people think they're above it.
And I hate it.
Um -
I'm going to tell you what else I watched.
I watched a picture called Suburbicon.
I've heard of it.
I've never seen it.
So yeah, I - the first day of the cab and I -
I spent with my - my - my dear friend,
you're a acquaintance, perhaps a little more than an acquaintance.
My friend Ian.
Ian Friedman.
A acquaintance.
He's my friend.
I think he'd prefer acquaintance.
I saw on the other day, I was shooting a comedy central
and he came down and talked to me.
All right.
But, uh, we get up to the cab and we watch these two movies
back to back and it was just like, we had made the two worst choices
that anyone's ever made.
Um, Suburbicon is - I mean, I - I had plenty of time
during the movie to read the Wikipedia.
It had such a convoluted story of how I'd got to the screen.
But after blood simple.
So we're talking like 1986.
The Cohen brothers, that's - I think that's 84.
But there - so this would have been 85 -86.
Cohen brothers were going to do a movie called Suburbicon.
Which was, you know, basically what this movie is,
which is kind of like a super fucked up double indemnity type thing.
They never got the script where they wanted it and they abandoned it.
They started writing a project about a black family moving into a white neighborhood in the 50s.
They never got that script where they wanted it.
Somewhere along the line, whenever they started working with George Clooney,
they became friends.
Apparently he asked them, do you guys have any old scripts that you haven't used?
They're like, yeah, we got tons.
Okay.
He reads these two old scripts that the Cohen brothers decided were not good enough to film.
One Suburbicon won a race, you know, race issue movie.
And decides he'll combine them into one script.
And George Clooney himself will rewrite the Cohen brothers,
merge these movies and make them work.
Because surely the Cohen brothers couldn't do it.
Obviously, Clooney's your man.
He's the new voice of Chuckie.
Perhaps.
Right.
You know, he's the guy, he's the new Robert town.
You bring him in when a script just won't come together and he fixes it perfectly.
So, look, I love George Clooney.
I don't even hate him as a director or a writer.
I think he's fine.
But, you know.
No, and I actually think he's a legit director.
Like, he's a guy that actually wants to direct.
He learned his shit.
I like some of this stuff.
Like, you know, whereas like, I say, like,
Idris Elba is directing him.
It's like, why is every, it's like, people just tick that as a box.
Yeah.
No, it's been going on for a long time.
Maybe it'll be good.
I mean, I won't be, maybe he'll be another clue.
But I just see, I only pick him because it seems like every actor that becomes
at least even marginally successful in the mainstream.
The next thing you know, it's like written and directed by Elizabeth Banks.
Sure.
You're like, what?
Because she's a woman.
Well, yeah.
But besides that.
And for Idris Elba, I assume you're upset because she's...
She can't run a budget.
She'll be spending the whole damn thing on shoes.
Look.
Let's talk about Suburbicon.
Suburbicon stars Maddie Damon.
And I would say his worst performance.
He's wildly miscast.
It stars Julianne Moore, who was an actress.
I loved in the 90s and always my heart sinks when I see her now.
I hear she's in a great movie that just came out.
Some new indie that I'll probably check out.
But fired from, can you ever forgive me?
I saw that.
I mean, for me, her worst is when she's doing that boss in accent,
which you did on like 30 rock and stuff.
It's embarrassing.
But it's those two.
And it's Oscar Isaacs, who kind of comes in for a very small supporting part.
Well, Oscar Isaac, he's got to stop.
He's doing too much.
He's in too much shit.
And Adam Driver is about to tick over that line too.
Yeah, absolutely.
You can't be in everything.
Absolutely.
Please.
Anyway, the movie starts.
There's this very funny character actor.
I didn't recognize playing a male man.
He's whistling his way through the neighborhood.
Hey, how's it going?
How's it going?
It gets up to the doorway.
This African American woman answers the door.
And he's like, eh, and like trying to keep it together,
but he's really like freaking out.
And doesn't want to give her a male.
And it's like this very tense, kind of awkward, funny scene.
And I'm like, OK, interesting.
That's not what I thought SuburbanCon was about.
And I started looking it up.
So sure enough, they come.
And this is what I found actually offensive about the movie.
Is they start to deal with the realities of a black family moving into a white suburban neighborhood in the 50s.
And almost immediately abandon it for this other story about Matt Damon plotting to kill his wife and his wife's sister.
Yeah, I thought that's what the whole movie was about.
That's what it should have been, but instead he drags in this other story and gives it almost no screen time.
So you're like, well, now is the...
Sorry, I cut you off, I'm sorry.
No, it's just...
That's the gross thing about it is that, OK, either...
This is a very serious and interesting subject.
Like, deal with it or do a double indemnity style noir type movie.
My question is...
The two do not taste good together.
My question is, is the reason for that blending of themes to say, can you believe these people lived in a world where it was weird to have a black family on the block, but murder was palpable?
Is that what it's supposed to be?
No, because it's not like in the 50s murder was palatable.
It's not like murder was any cooler now than it was now.
But they almost don't deal with that family in any real way.
And then at the end, they have the two little boys, the white boy and the black boy playing catch over a fence.
And you're like, no, you didn't earn this final shot at all because you didn't do that movie.
You did the crime movie.
And I actually thought the crime movie was kind of a cool story.
When it opens up, Julian Moore is playing Twins and I almost just turned the thing off.
I can't.
Nope, I'm dead.
One blonde, one brunette.
And the blondes in a wheelchair.
And I won't spoil it in case you want to watch it.
But Matt Damon basically, there's some foul play and so forth.
Their kid in the movie is very good, a very good little actor.
But everyone else doesn't quite work.
The tone is all over the place.
And really that Cohen brother's tone, that Fargo thing is theirs and theirs alone.
Many have tried and almost every have failed.
It's really hard to do that like their thing.
And Clooney is just not up to the task.
So they were right to leave these movies on the shelf.
I don't think they should have been dusted off.
The movie was critically banned.
And it got a D minus from audiences.
And audiences always rate things very highly because they're dumb.
But yeah, it's not great.
It's not great.
Yeah, anything where anybody's playing Twins anymore.
Look, it's not impressive anymore.
No.
It was more impressive when John Claude Van Dam did it because you know how they had to do it.
And how technically hard it was.
Even though it was just two of the same guy.
Or back to the future when he's playing the whole family.
Or whatever.
It's still that.
And not a professor like that.
Back then it was so impressive.
Now it's like you could shoot one of those roles in Denver and the other one in Los Angeles.
And then they would make it look like you're in the same room.
Right.
It's not that impressive anymore.
It's not necessary.
You could also just change another actor's face to have your face.
Yes.
So it's just, it's, it's, it's a little, it's a little much.
But anyway, I'm only going to do one more because I have a pretty big scary,
or a screaming end that I want to get to that was not the Netflix thing, believe it or not.
The Paul Lind, Holly Wien, special.
We were talking about doing this as a commentary video.
But I think it will work better if I just kind of tell Pat about it on the air.
Because he's never seen it.
But yes, folks, Paul Lind from Hollywood Squares has a Halloween special.
He was contracted in the 70s to do a special per year with CBS.
Because back then you could do that.
That was like a gig you could get.
You could just be a guy that never toward or perform.
Right.
But you would get specials.
That's right.
It's good saying.
Yeah.
So his is called the Paul Lind, Holly Halloween special.
Featuring the likes of Tim Conway.
Pinkie Tuscadero.
Who is Pinkie Tuscadero?
From Happy Days.
I remember the actress's name.
Fam is only for her name, I would say.
Yeah.
I mean, she's her real name, I forget.
But she was Pinkie Tuscadero.
Or in fact, in the credits of this thing, it says like so and so Pinkie Tuscadero.
Last name.
Like.
Oh, wow.
Like she was really cashing on that.
Fonzie fame.
Tim Conway is in it.
Betty White is in it.
Just how you like to go by Joe Veterinarian from Better Call Saul.
Derosa.
Yes, exactly.
I'll also do.
And you know, I'll say Joe consultant on crashing season one.
Right.
Derosa.
I also go Pat Ben Frywater from season one episode nine of Camera Cross Rody's Walsh.
Right.
But, you know, people know me.
And my vet has a name, by the way.
What is his name?
Caldera.
He's the last name, yeah.
Doctor Caldera.
Oh, Doctor Caldera.
Yeah.
What's your first name?
They just call him Caldera.
You don't ask, you don't want to do some character work?
I like the mystery of it.
It excites me as much as it excites the viewers.
Anyway.
Oh, and then finally in this cavalcade of stars of the day.
Kiss.
Okay.
Does not one, but three musical numbers on this special.
How long is this thing?
It's about an hour.
Which, I mean, they're really lean and heavy on kiss.
Well, I'm sure Paul then was a big fan of kiss.
Every single sketch.
Now, people, I'm not one to judge books by their covers.
Sure.
But Paul then was gay.
I mean, it's debatable.
It's his gay.
It was, it was, if you read about him, he was frustrated.
He couldn't be openly gay.
Right.
He was gay.
But even if you didn't know that, it was a fairly safe assumption that he was gay, man.
Every sketch centers around him with a woman fighting over him or him fighting for a woman.
That's the plot of every single sketch.
Yeah.
And not with any sort of wink to camera.
Not with any sort of like, you know, not like, it's not like he hits on the woman and then looks in the camera and goes,
couldn't you just die?
There's none of that.
It's just, you know, because I guess they thought people, I guess people were in that level of denial back then.
Not him.
I mean, the public.
Yeah.
Including a sketch where at the beginning of it, he sets up that he wants to be the rhinestone trucker.
Okay.
Cuts to him hanging off a semi in a white sequence suit and he goes, I'm the rhinestone trucker.
Like B -52 style, you know.
And then that's a sketch about him and Tim Conway, almost fishing over it.
Hurry up and bring your rhinestone trucker.
Yeah.
Fist fighting over Pinkie Tuscadero.
Okay.
You're supposed to believe that Pinkie Tuscadero would fuck either of these two.
How cheap is this special?
How does it look?
Is it on a set?
Yeah, it's on a set.
It looks like, you know, it looks like all those, those like Bob Hoopsman.
It looks like the way those specials all look.
Okay.
None of them looked extravagant.
Do the audience laughing?
Yeah.
Okay.
Big studio audience.
I can't tell if it's a laugh track or not.
This thing is just, it's, it's wild.
Yeah.
And then he does a thing at the top of song.
It's a variation.
You were telling me, I was telling him about the song.
You said it's a parody of the song he did and what?
Yes.
Bye bye, birdie.
Kids, what's the matter with kids today?
Yeah.
So he does a Halloween song about kids.
And he goes, I give them goodies because he's singing about giving them like Halloween candy.
Right.
I was, I portrayed Conrad Birdie in, uh, bye bye birdie.
It's sort of the Elvis Presley role.
Key role in the show.
I played Conrad Bane in the play of his life.
Is that right?
Yep.
Um, that's it for me for movie corner because I, we're running a little long time and I want to
do a screaming in.
But, uh, well, I'll do my third one, which is my favorite television show of the year.
Uh, I think it's a masterpiece.
If I may, I think that it's one of those few occasions where everyone is talking about something
and they're right, you know, usually you watch it and you're like, you fucking idiots.
This show is incredible.
It is called pen 15 or penis.
Uh, I guess, you know, how you type the word penis into a calculator or a phone.
But I don't know these girls.
Maya, Maya Erskine and Anna Conkel.
They are comics.
Um, I assume, I assume sketch type comics.
Maybe they're comedians as well.
Um, I know a little bit about the development process of this.
I know a few people who work behind the scenes and they worked for years and years to get this thing right.
It takes place in the year 2000 when they are both in, you remember that Conan sketch in the year 2000.
They spent me a laugh.
Sorry.
Anyway, uh, it takes place in the year 2000.
I was in high school like 95 through 99.
So this was hitting me pretty hard.
Um, it is these two girls who are about 30 years old playing themselves at 14, 13.
Mm hmm.
As they come into puberty and so forth.
But all their co -stars are actual children.
Right.
And, you know, there's tons of comedy to be mined from how filthy they are and how they're like,
there's all these slow motion shots of like 12 year old boys with the wind in their hair.
That get kind of uncomfortable because it's like a 30 year old woman staring lustily at a 12 year old boy.
Right.
There's a lot of sick comedy to be had there and all that stuff is very, very funny.
The dialogue is pitch perfect, the music from the time, the clothes, everything like really takes you back.
There's an episode about masturbation that is easily one of the most uncomfortable half hours of television I've ever seen because even though it is a 30 year old woman,
she's playing a 13 year old girl and there's like a close up of her vagina throbbing like a, you know, like a cartoon almost like.
Wow.
There's crazy shit in it.
And even as I'm saying this, it probably sounds like it's like a super fucked up to crave thing.
But it's very sweet as well.
And I might have just been my mood.
I found myself crying uncontrollably at several points.
I watched all 10 episodes in one day.
I did have a week of free time.
I'm trying to decompress a lot of work.
Nicely even in a cabinet in the woods has nothing to do with this whatsoever.
Sure.
And, you know, I had been working nonstop for nine months.
But I was maybe sorting through some shit, but Heather watched it at home.
Heather wasn't high school in 2000.
And she was about these girls age.
And my God, she had the same reaction.
She was like, I'm bawling, I'm laughing.
I think it is absolutely incredible.
I, of course, hope it gets a season two, but I'd be worried they'd ruin the thing.
It's just a truly perfect thing.
And it's only five hours of your time because ten and a half hours.
I think it's incredible.
I heard you to check it out.
I will check it out.
Sounds funny.
You're so dismissive, Jim.
What do you want?
It's so fucking dismissive.
I haven't seen it.
What do you want me to say?
It sounds funny.
Oh, watch it.
I was trying to bring a little like, who's afraid of Virginia Woolf?
Action to the couch.
Well, you should have said something like, big daddy says.
That's cat in a hot tub.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
All right.
Screamin' in 24 hour news psycho.
But the 24 hour had a thing in it, too.
24 hour news psycho.
What did Karen want to call it again?
Terrible.
I thought that's what we incorporated it in with.
Was it like, Screamin' in, Terrible 4 hour news psycho?
No.
Hers was particularly bad.
What's the other news network?
Like, it was like, she's like MSNB Scream.
Yeah, I think Karen was literally like, call it hatchet news.
Yes.
How are you, Karen?
I miss you.
I saw Karen the other night.
We had a blast.
We did a show that my friend Brian Cook has called Guilty Treasures.
Karen sang the Cheryl Crow song.
You sing a song that you love that you don't want.
Sort of a guilty pleasure.
The first tip.
Did you know do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do the bad day.
Yeah, that's not any use this band.
You're in my favorite mistake.
Yeah.
That's not.
I'm like quite a few Cheryl Crow songs that's not one.
I love anything but down.
Which is a great song.
I didn't know, I liked it so I heard her sing it.
I was like, I never noticed.
I was like, I never noticed how cool that song is.
It's got that organ line in it and she's like, yeah, right.
I think, you know, I don't throw the, throw her music on,
but Cheryl Crow is a great song writer.
We had a good time. I think Santoria was a lot of fun.
Anyway, folks.
Yes.
Rotten Tomatoes came out.
I mean, this is almost like the jussies smaller thing.
This is just an ongoing thing with these Captain Marvel reviews.
But Rotten Tomatoes has deleted hundreds, hundreds of reviews
from the user reviews, from the website concerning the Captain Marvel film.
I think few things have done more damage to modern film than Rotten Tomatoes, if I may.
That's fine. Listen. I was the victim of fake reviews on Amazon
and my album ratings went from four stars to one star because of a trolling campaign.
I've been there.
You and Captain Marvel, same brother.
When I reported it to Amazon, I was told, look, we can't get into that game.
We can't get into the game of we're going to determine if we think this review is fake or not.
If they're saying they don't, this is kind of the risk you take with something like this.
Basically was the response.
Not the greatest thing to hear, but I dealt with it and it was what it was.
Captain Marvel, it seems odd to me.
It seems odd to me.
Here's why I'm not picking on Captain Marvel, but it seems odd to me that even the good reviews of this movie
are saying it's not a good movie.
Even the good reviews are saying, is it not great? Sure.
Does it have a lot of problems, of course?
I read you that Peter Travis.
Exactly. These are the good reviews.
In conjunction with this, it had a much lower audience score than the critic score,
which has happened to tons of movies on Rotten Tomatoes.
Sure.
And vice versa has happened also.
So for Rotten Tomatoes, suddenly to step in as the great Disney machine that is absorbing every fucking studio in Hollywood right now,
and basically trying to have their fingerprints on everything that ever gets produced in this town,
seems a little fishy to me.
Their Rotten Tomatoes suddenly deletes hundreds of user reviews and says,
we had a major glitch on our site. Those were incorrect.
They absolutely did not have a glitch on their site.
Yeah, it's just what's weird.
I mean, I just went through all this.
Disney's buying 20th Century Fox and like no one knows who their boss is over there.
Like it makes for a hellish work environment. I'll tell you that much.
Yeah, so, you know, people, and it's a monopoly, isn't it?
Like at some point, don't they say that's enough?
You can't control 50 % of Hollywood.
Look, that's the one reason I might not re -subscribe to Netflix,
because I think they are perpetuating monopoly.
I just saw, Jesus Christ's eye to yourself has a new TV show with them.
I'm like, who, what, what a list -nominated actor is not working with these people right now?
You're talking Netflix.
Yeah, yeah.
He's a DJ and it's a comedy. Is that what the show is?
Yeah, because you know how funny he is.
So I'm on SNL, so I know exactly how funny he is.
I mean, I really like you, Dresel, but I -
What are you two?
I, Netflix is becoming a big problem too in my opinion.
And, you know, at this cabin I had Netflix, Hulu and Prime.
You know, that was my TV and I got to kind of look through and I was like,
what is going on on Netflix?
There's just thousands of -
There's like five new shows a week.
That's not healthy.
They set -
Well, they announced last year that in 2019 they were going to release it was something like 75 things.
Yeah.
It was an insane number of stuff.
What is pen 15 on Prime?
Hulu.
Hulu, okay, good.
See, Hulu, I mean, look, they're all corporations at the end of the day, but Hulu,
I've only watched a couple of Hulu shows and I've been disappointed with almost all of them,
but they seem to be taking a step in the right direction and putting a lot of care into what they do put on the air,
as opposed to just chucking a bunch of shit and hoping to land.
Well, I would agree with that and I would also say that Hulu is not trying to so -
grab up every single player.
Right.
They always get the really good, like anytime they get a new movie, I'm like,
that's that really good, interesting indie movie I wanted to say.
Netflix, it's like, it's like there's got to be like a goddamn Saudi prince somewhere in the shadows.
Sure.
Where are they getting this money from?
You're not going to like where that money goes back to.
I can almost guarantee you.
Nothing against the Saudi princes, I don't, I don't think.
I don't know.
I don't know who's doing what these days.
I don't know the side we're on.
Today, I saw Twitter, Donald Trump Jr. defended Chelsea Clinton.
I saw that too.
What the fuck is going on?
It's, I mean, let's not even crack open that camera.
But the world is ending.
Let's get to our movie.
Harnuar.
Culture is definitely ending, but the world is also ending.
But speaking of good culture, Harnuar.
And speaking of an app, by the way, that, and again, I mean them agreeing to sponsor us,
I don't even think it came from us talking so much praise about shutter.
I think it was a coincidence, but.
I don't think it did either because I didn't see any personal notice in the ad.
No, there should have been a little love.
Maybe we'll wave your 499 subscription fee this month.
I'm just kidding.
I'm di -tees the shutter people.
But for 499, you get, you get what feels like a carefully curated assortment of things.
And it's always way more stuff than you could watch in a month.
It's not like they got three movies over there.
But the Joe Bob shit is so special.
That first 13 movie marathon.
Yeah.
It's just fucking incredible.
And you know, how long does it take you to watch 13 movies?
I still haven't finished the whole marathon.
But so worth your time.
And this was there, you know, maybe first or second foray into documentary filmmaking.
Jordan Peel produced it.
And it is called horror noir.
And it is about the history of black history of black horror.
And black creators and writers in the horror genre.
And I mean, the overall arc is a triumphant one.
Because they talk about how they started out being like sort of the gag characters in these movies or the throwaway characters.
You know, they were either somebody who got killed right away or they were sort of these wide eyed like freaked out natives that were sort of warning the white folk about
you know, what was going on around these parts.
And they were there was very stereotypical.
And certainly these roles weren't uplifting ones.
Well, and you always talk about and they go into it in this movie too.
The very stereotypical mystical black older woman who knows all the secrets.
Yes, yes.
And I was so happy that they touched on that.
Yeah.
And they talk about how it kind of like that's where it started for black people in horror cinema.
And where they ended up was Jordan Peel winning an Oscar for best original screenplay.
First black writer in history to win for that.
And much deserved.
And it's just an incredible journey.
And some of the most and if there are interviews with Stacy, not Stacy.
If I may, I'm sorry from the craft.
I'm blanking on her name now. Rachel true.
Rachel true.
Yeah.
Do you hear that clapping?
Maybe they're watching a game.
Let me correct.
I really want to quickly correct myself.
Jordan Peel is not a producer.
He's one of the talking heads that discusses.
Yeah, he's in it.
Ernest Dickerson.
He produced the Lorraine Bob at Documentary, which I also watched on Amazon.
Ernest Dickerson's in it.
Love Ernest Dickerson.
The best guy.
Listen to that guy talk all day.
The guy that played Kin Cade in Nightmare on Elm Street 3 and 4.
Yeah.
Arguably my favorite of any Nightmare on Elm Street character.
Tony Todd who put a portrait.
Candyman Keith David who was most people know as Mary's stepdad and something about Mary.
But also the guy at the end of the most disturbing movie sequence of all time in Requiem for a Dream.
Oh, yeah.
It's just a wonderful, wonderful.
And there are these insights and commentaries that I was completely unaware of.
The most fascinating to me was learning that black audiences saw some of the universal error horror films as commentaries about them.
Like then they talked about the creature of the black lagoon and the woman is saying, you know, here's this creature trying to steal and kidnap the sacred blonde white woman.
Right.
And he's got big lips.
You know, and he's a monster and he's, you know, and I'm like, wow, that's fucking fascinating, man.
Like I never do that.
That's what I loved about it is, you know, two things.
A, it goes to show you that this is a real thriving time for documentary film because this movie was probably made for,
I mean, aside from licensing film clips, there's almost, it's just people sitting around chatting.
In the same theater.
Yeah, they just, they got about a budget of five grand on it.
Yeah, they bring in guests who I'm sure were just, were like, yeah, I'd love to come down and talk about it, you know.
And it feels that way.
It feels like people talking about their genuine experiences.
All the actors who played these quote unquote token roles in the 80s.
It's very interesting to see them say like, you know, it's stuff you never think of when you're a kid watching horror movies.
But like Rachel true, who, you know, she's, she's also had a lot of very valid complaints lately that they'll do these crap,
the craft reunion shows.
And she doesn't get invited.
And the other three girls do, which she has finally been invited back because of the up, uproar and congrats to Rachel true that that has happened.
Yeah, it just sucks that she had to.
Yeah, I agree.
Cause a stink, you know.
But, well, good.
No, just that she talks about how I'm making sure we had her name, correct.
But she's making sure she's talking on this movie that basically her roles, whenever she got these roles in these horror movies.
And they all talk about this experience.
Your role was saying, are you okay to the white lead?
Is everything okay?
Are you seeing scared?
Is everything all right?
What's going on?
And they, you know, they probably should have cut together some big super cut of that happening a thousand times in these movies.
They show you a couple.
But it's like they just talk about what a bummer it was.
You know, a few of them have a good sense of humor and it's like, you know, I was caching a paycheck.
I didn't care.
I was in front of the 13th.
But it does really suck that every time they get the part, it's like, oh yeah, I'm the helper.
I'm the one who gets killed first.
I'm the one, you know, they go into all these horror movie tropes that black people have had to deal with for years, black actors.
And I really loved hearing all their stories and the different viewpoints on it.
And then coming into their own more and, you know, something like Candyman where you have the first kind of black Freddy.
You know, of course you had black ill and they go into the black exploitation days and all that.
Yeah.
But, you know, that was a very cool and exciting thing.
But then they talk about the problems with that movie.
They're like, why is he going after his own kind?
He was lynched by white people.
Why isn't he going into the, right?
The wealthy parts of Chicago and killing the white people.
Well, that's what I found fascinating or most fascinating about the movie was seeing the two, the duality of opinion or that were the, or compare, or contradicting opinions, if you will, or varied opinions on some of these movies.
Because they show Candyman and you'd see Tony Todd talking about what a breakthrough this was for somebody like him and to be in this movie and the importance of it.
But then you'd see other people say, you know, it bothered me that in Candyman he was in love with a white woman.
Yeah.
You know, like it was interesting to hear the different perspectives on that.
Some of the people in the movie were like, you know, I was just happy that finally we were in there doing it.
Yeah.
And other people were saying, you know, it wasn't quite enough for me at the time.
I wanted a little more.
But people under the stairs got tons of praise unanimously.
Well deserved.
I mean, we talked about that on the show and that movie blew me away with how relevant it was and how cool it was.
Not a black child is the lead of that movie.
Yeah, and the black community prevails at the end against these white monsters.
So that one got a lot of praise.
And then also two for once it was a white, you know, the natives are on term in this sense.
But the local was the kid with no tongue.
Right.
Basically in that role or that position.
And it was a white guy finally helping the black people out instead of the other way around.
So it's that movie got you like unanimous praise throughout the documentary.
It's a very kind of quick breezy fun documentary.
But it really paints a great picture of progress in this genre in race and horror movies.
So a specific area of film, but that's how these documentaries would have to be here.
They'd be a 10 hour special.
So to me, I got the whole picture of this and how difficult progress is and how when you take a step forward,
you have to kind of look past a few of the other steps that maybe didn't get addressed.
I loved it.
They touched on Eves Bayou, which is an amazing movie that almost nobody has seen.
I never thought that was just like a heavy drama.
You know what I always thought that was like like a Jason's lyric kind of a thing.
Like I never had no idea it was this sort of dark movie.
There's a ghost element to it.
Samuel Jackson is awesome in it.
And Ebert used to rave about it constantly as why I saw it.
And I just loved the shit out of it.
I was surprised it was so heavily featured in this documentary.
But lots of great things to put on your checklist, your watch list,
shutter has a lot of the movies that are discussed in the documentary.
So you can just check them out once you hear about them.
A particular sort of blank spot for me is black exploitation horror.
I've seen a lot of the black exploitation action movies.
Your shaft, of course, your coffee with all the Pam Greer's.
Right.
Cleopatra Jones.
I've seen all of those.
I love those movies.
But I have seen almost none of the black exploitation horror films.
Blackula screen, blackula screen.
Black and Stein, I believe was one of them that they said was not very good.
But I own Dr. Black and Mr. Hyde.
So yeah, watch that for the show.
I would love to check some of those out.
And then of course it builds to get out.
And just what a breakthrough that was besides being a great movie.
Jordan Peel's like I made this for black audiences.
I'm glad other people watched it.
But what happens is now nobody's scared me more to green light a movie about black people.
About with a black director because they were always like relegated to the sidekick role.
And now I think that conversation after get out is like,
let's maybe make all our horror movies this way.
I think you saw quite a heap of them coming out right after the first purge and all that.
Well, us 100 % score on Ron Tomatoes right now.
Yeah, weirdly, the only review I really looked at was on the Onion AV Club.
And they're like, it's brilliant, but it's a complete mess.
And I was like, well, whatever, I'll certainly check it out.
I heard it's a little confusing.
And I want to see it because sometimes in a horror movie, that means Susperia.
Yeah.
And sometimes in a horror movie, that means Susperia.
You don't even.
So I want to see in what way is it confusing.
You know, is it not well constructed or is it?
You know, are they leaving a lot to interpretation?
But, but you know, hey, congrats on an opening, you know, opening strong or whatever.
I can't wait to see it.
We'll review that for the show.
We will absolutely review that.
I think that's like April 1st that come.
I think, well, that empaths cemetery are in the same like a couple of weeks.
So definitely try to see both of those early because those will be 100 % definite views,
especially now that I'm on a little hiatus from work.
I'm going to be seeing a lot more movies in chat.
We'll wrap this up, Joe.
But horror noir.
Just a fantastic documentary made with a lot of love.
And about a really interesting subject that really helps you look at a lot of your favorite horror movies in different ways.
For me, like when they got into the poltergeist and all that shit, you know, that actor was like, yeah, you know,
the guy's great in the movie, but he was like, yeah, I'm just going to sit there like, why aren't I the dad?
When will I ever get a dad party?
Right.
And you realize you've almost never seen that guy again.
So, and that's a movie I've seen a billion times, you know, it's so it's like diversity, but sure.
And it's frankly, frankly, it's annoying with the new pet cemetery because they made Pascal black, the Pascal character black.
And it's like, and all I think of what I see that is, well, why couldn't the family just be a black family?
Why can't the neighbor be Morgan Freeman?
Yeah.
Instead of John Lithke.
Like there were, there were more, why can't the wife be black or the dad be, you know what I mean?
It's like, they're significant roles they could have given.
It's almost, it's almost, I felt like that was the exact thing that this documentary was sort of focusing its sights on.
Oh, there's one black guy in the movie and he's the one that gets killed right at the beginning.
And he's the one that mystically helps the white people from the other side.
It's literally everything the documentaries talk about.
Well, and still, even your most social justice type people will be like, see we've got diversity because there's a black eye who has three lines in your show with all white people.
It's like, no, it's not really how it works.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anyway, Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram, Joe DeRosa comedian on Facebook, more food, videos, Hogi's heroes are on the way.
They'll be coming to you very soon.
A new story in Penthouse this month called Menu Change.
I am at the Vegas Topgolf facility on Friday, the 29th and Saturday, the 30th of March, one show per night.
And I've got several shows coming up in April.
I'm going to be again doing a show for bonkers and Minneapolis.
I forget the name of the casino right now, but if you Google Minneapolis, my name and bonkers, you'll find it.
I will be at the Valley Forge casino in Pennsylvania.
I believe it's the third week of April.
And I will be at Moon Tower.
Also, at the Moon Tower Fest in Austin, that's the third week.
I think the other one's the second week.
Something like that anyway.
Folks, check out uninformed the podcast featuring Bill Burr myself at patreon .com slash Burr.
I am at the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram.
I may be joining Joe at that Vegas show.
Who knows if you're out that way.
Come see us both.
Check out those two movies, Pat Cemetery and us when they come out.
I don't think we have a next one yet.
Or we're going to do the remake of Hills have eyes.
Yeah, that'll be next week.
And that's it.
Thank you folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.