I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, where sometimes we talk about the movies you want to hear,
and sometimes we talk about the Pope's exorcist.
Spoiler alert.
The Pope?
Yes.
Might not be a great movie.
Spoiler.
Look, it might not be a great movie, but I feel like I like it more than you, I'll say
that much.
Really?
I mean, look, I didn't walk in expecting a classic.
Sometimes you've got to adjust those expectations, but having watched a lot of the Russell Crowe
as Nicolas Cage direct -to -video stuff, like I'm sure this part where they originally went
out to Nicolas Cage would have made more sense as he's Italian and Russell Crowe is not Italian
at all, but look, I had some fun with this one, and we'll get to it.
This was in theaters by the way, this did pretty well in theaters, in fact the sequel
has already been confirmed, which is why, spoiler alert, you get that mission impossible
ending when he's walking off to the next adventure, it's practically playing like back in black
I mean, they had played lots of music in this one.
See, I thought when Russell Crowe, 300 pounds, dressed in sort of like Marlon Brando, Island
Doctor Moreau, priest outfit and a hat, driving on a Dumb and Dumber scooter to Faith No More,
I thought, I bet Joe's going to like this, but no, I was wrong.
Well, we'll talk about it.
It's an interesting film, but I will say, yet another movie that has joined the ranks
with Hotel for Dogs and Women Talking as one of the worst titles I've ever heard for a movie,
The Pope's Exorcist.
Again, I got to disagree with you, that to me suggests that this man is better than any exorcist,
and that's all I need to know.
Pat, if the pope likes him?
It wasn't until I watched it, I thought he was exercising the pope.
I thought that's what the movie was about.
When the trailer came out, that's what I thought, that he was like working out with kids and like
testing, and then finally it was like, no, no, no, the pope's been possessed.
That's the issue.
But no, in fact, the pope just gets all the most funny dialogue.
The pope is actually a really funny character in this movie, I thought.
Yes.
It's a little tongue in cheek.
There's some intentional humor, some unintentional.
It felt like a cage, but it's a crow.
I never thought we'd see the day where crow started to have a sense of humor about himself
and his career, but I think we are reaching that point with him.
And I'm kind of here for it, I got to say.
Yeah, thank God.
Yeah, guys aren't throwing telephones at people anymore.
Well, here's a positive news story.
Jamie Foxx was seen in public.
He was on his boat and he waved.
Okay, good.
And he seemed...
I didn't know what the hell was going on there.
He seemed like healthy, like he didn't seem blind, not that blind.
You can't talk anymore.
I mean, not that blind, not healthy.
I'm just saying, you know what I mean?
He doesn't seem like he lost his eyesight.
He waved, you know, like, I don't know, he's got his shirt off, he looks good.
Like, you know, that's a positive.
I hope he's all right, you know?
Yeah, for sure.
I'm a fan.
So, you know, let's hope he doesn't appear on his first talk show
and he thinks he's Ethel Merman or something now.
You know, I hope he's okay.
Like, you know, I hope he's back to his normal self.
Absolutely, absolutely.
I root for people.
Pat, do you know that about me?
I'm rooting for Matthew Perry.
That's the guy I want to see the big comeback happen with.
I really do.
I want to see Perry back in like snappy, smart -ass form and something.
Joseph, I just listened to Matthew Perry's autobiography.
It's a rough one.
It's a rough ride.
Did you hear it?
You heard it too?
I've listened to the whole thing.
I had to, I listened to it and I had to get rid of it because I was like,
this is touching and deep, but it's too, this is too much, man.
It's really, it's really heavy.
I absolutely love that.
It's called friends, lovers and the big, terrible thing.
The big, terrible thing, of course, being addiction, alcoholism.
I mean, people called me Chandler in high school.
You know, I always liked the guy a lot and related to him and the character.
You know, he talks about how the character was a lot like him.
Just keeps making quips.
So nobody sees the vast hole inside of him.
And that was me to, to a great extent for a lot of my life until
eventually I had no quips left.
I was like, nope, I'm just depressed and I got to figure this out.
And that will be the name of Pat's book.
All out of quips.
I'm all out of quips.
It's remember we used to have to do ads for quip, the mechanical toothbrush.
Barely.
What happened to that?
It did hundreds of ads, probably made $50.
These countries, I mean, these companies come and go is quip still around.
Yeah, I went on, on the good Christian fun podcast and I talked shit about head gum
and how we basically had to ask them what our listenership was and then leave and go
do our own thing.
And he left it in the show.
So like there's a head gum podcast where I'm just freely shitting on head gum.
I did say I love Amir and I love those guys.
I think it's just the nature of doing business with these podcast companies.
And he hooped.
When I hit play on this Matthew Perry audio book, he ain't talking the same anymore.
His voice is like in slow motion.
It's got like he's got marbles in his mouth.
I had to listen to it at like a 1 .4 speed just so it sounded like Matthew Perry.
It's well written and yet there's times where he just misses the mark.
He's repeating himself.
He takes two shots at Keanu Reeves.
Who he says he wishes was dead that he's since gone back on and said,
I don't know why I said that.
I'm sorry.
But it's a really great book.
It's a great look at addiction.
And for all the people who are like, how are you making a million dollars a week for years?
And you still feel the need to do alcohol and drugs to this extent.
He was doing 55 Xanax a day.
55 Xanax a day and his life was actually better than we remember.
He was dating Julia Roberts in 1994 as like the quippy guy on a NBC sitcom.
Julia Roberts, he had it.
He truly had it all and that's what people don't get about addiction and about depression.
It doesn't matter in the slightest.
And I think his book did a really great job of just showing you that no matter what you have,
these diseases are just waiting to take you down.
I really enjoyed the book.
But yeah, come back for him would be great.
They talked about him working with Adam McKay in the book and it sounded like that might be
fruitful but I don't know.
I think people just see him now and they get bummed out, unfortunately.
I know that was the case on the reunion special.
He's sharper because he said he's on that medicine and that's kind of
affects his, I think that's the thing that makes him sound a little slower and whatnot.
But I've watched interviews with him since that book came out and of course,
it's an audio book.
It was probably recorded far before it was ever released.
He seems much quicker and like his interview with Bill Maher was great.
And I watched him do the like five GQs, five things I can't live without,
whoever the hell does those videos.
He's funny in it.
So I was like, he's still able to do it.
I'm sure he is.
He's just got to get back into fighting shape.
That's all.
And he said he's writing screenplays and stuff.
It's hard to say you wish him well when a guy literally has,
he talks about how he had himself a house built because he liked the house in
the first Dark Knight movie.
The guy literally truly has it all and you just want to reach out and help him.
It's just the classic story of addiction.
I really love actors, directors, et cetera, reading their own stories on audio book.
I just can't get enough.
I don't even care who it is.
I listened to Jessica Simpson.
One of my favorites was I'm Glad My Mom Died by Jeanette McCurdy,
who I had never even heard of, but she was on iCarly.
It is one of the best sort of memoirs I've ever heard.
And I love how brave the title is.
I'm glad my mom died.
Her mom is a nightmare.
The classic stage mom.
And yeah, if you have audible, I can't recommend it enough.
It's better than Perry's.
It's like a super well -written, sharp, funny book.
I was going to say, is it funny?
It's, you know, it's the darkest of comedy.
McCurdy, she might be Irish.
She doesn't mention it, but it felt Irish to me,
which is that like just gallows fucking humor.
But I loved it.
Loved it.
All right.
And then I have to go to that real quick.
Because I only got one for the corner,
but I got a scary stuff as we're talking about audiobooks here.
Thinner, one of my favorite Stephen King books
and one of my favorite Stephen King adaptation movies.
I love thinner.
It's not great, but I really enjoy the film.
And my favorite part about the film is arguably Joe Mantegna.
So I was delighted to see that Joe Mantegna reads the entire audiobook.
And it's great.
Joe Mantegna has got a great soothing voice.
It's a great spooky ghost, you know, Stephen King kind of ghost story.
Great for those night times.
You want to doze off to something a little dark, a little fun, but not too much.
And Joe Mantegna reading it is an excellent experience.
I highly recommend the audiobook of thinner, ladies and gentlemen.
There you go.
And hell, while we're here, and I'll cut out some of my movie corner as well.
As You Wish, written by Kerry Elwes, is the story of the making of The Princess Bride.
I listened to that on a big drive this week and absolutely loved it.
He's got almost everybody involved.
Rob Reiner, you know, Mandy Patinkin, Christopher Guest,
everybody you want to hear, Robin Wright Penn.
They all come on and share their recollections of the making of The Princess Bride,
which is one of my favorite movies of all time, about to be released on Criterion 4K.
That's a really great sort of oral history book.
And a lot of fun stuff I didn't know.
Then I listened to The Church of Baseball,
which is Ron Shelton's book about the making of Bull Durham.
I like Bull Durham.
It never blew me away the way it does some.
I haven't seen it in a very long time.
But to me, the celebrity memoir read by the celebrity is what makes Audible the best.
I'm excited to do Brian Cox's next.
But I also really love like a script to test audiences to like the legacy of the movie
type journey through the making of the film.
And those are two of the best recent ones, As You Wish and The Church of Baseball.
If you like those movies, add those to your wish list over on Audible as well.
Make no money from these people.
But happy to shout out when something is done well.
Beautiful.
I'll just do one this week and we'll get to the film at hand.
If you're in LA, or specifically Santa Monica, the Arrow Theater,
which is a beautiful theater part of the American Cinematheque,
is doing a 70 millimeter fest.
What is 70 millimeter?
It is, if you think of a piece of film as like that little thing with the spools on the side,
imagine doubling it in size.
Not just 35 millimeter, but 70.
That means much like IMAX, although it is different.
You get a much bigger, wider, clearer, more colorful picture.
Most, if not all theaters are not equipped for 70 millimeter.
The last kind of big release was Interstellar.
They also sometimes do Paul Thomas Anderson's movies in a 70 millimeter release in LA theaters.
Phantom Thread had one, Inherent Vice had one.
But they're hard to come by.
The Arrow does a festival every year.
Yesterday, I was supposed to see The Untouchables in 70 millimeter,
and I felt like dog shit.
I was really upset that I could not go.
But I'm definitely going to Malcolm X coming up.
I'm so pumped to see that in the largest, most beautiful screen possible.
They have Boogie Nights, which I have seen in 70 millimeter and is well worth it.
It's also incredible sound.
It uses every possible channel.
Um, if you're a movie nerd, you owe it to yourself to see one of these.
And I saw probably the best movie you could ever see in this giant format.
A movie that was done in this format.
Originally, Lawrence of Arabia.
I had only seen Lawrence of Arabia on VHS with the halfway through switching tapes.
And it looked like shit.
Let's be real.
I always said, if I'm ever going to sit through this like nearly four hour movie again,
it's going to have to be on the big screen.
Seeing it in 70 millimeter blew my mind.
It looked like it was shot yesterday.
You see how Spielberg got everything in Raiders
and through a lot of his career from Lawrence of Arabia.
It feels like another indie movie.
I forgot how hilarious Lawrence himself as played by Peter O'Toole is.
He's like a complete cock.
He's so smug and such an asshole to everybody.
But at his core, he only wants what's right and just.
He's an amazing character.
The movie is really funny.
It's an epic.
I heard some grumbling about people like Anthony Quinn
and other white actors playing Arabs in the movie.
But it's the time folks, you know, they did this regularly.
Look at the original West Side story.
Casting was often done in a way that today we would find inappropriate.
But it was almost a hundred years ago.
I don't know what to tell you.
Lawrence of Arabia is justly considered one of the all time great films.
Spielberg says it's his favorite film.
And that to me was the biggest revelation.
Having just watched all the Indiana Jones, how much of an influence it was.
But if you're going to see it in 70 millimeter,
you know, there's a few chances left to see it in that format here in LA.
But otherwise, you might never get that chance.
Just make sure if you're going to see it again, you see it at the theater.
Because that's the way to do it.
It's also the kind of movie where a three and a half hour movie,
you might get distracted by your phone.
Go see it with the big intermission.
Go see it.
And please go see the 70 millimeter format stuff while it's there.
I mean, who doesn't want to see Malcolm X?
I've never seen that even in the theater.
So I'm very pumped about that.
If you're out here, make a make a day of it.
It's fun.
I only have one.
I finally watched my 4K of heavy metal.
Why have I not been watching heavy metal all the time?
What an awesome, awesome movie.
God, man, it's it's it's just awesome.
It's just nuts and dirty and guns and violence and fucking and cool
rotoscope cartoons and awesome music and cartoon divas in it played in that bar.
It was just fucking awesome, man.
The sequel, unfortunately, I heard is terrible.
Heavy metal 2000.
I'd love to see a live action shot for shot remake of the original heavy metal movie.
They could never do it because of all the sex and everything now.
But with Jack Black, I'd love to see it.
I mean, that sequence where John Candy is like the little white kid
that transforms into a large black man and then fucks like across the galaxy.
Yeah, yeah, I watched it on LSD.
I watched it just a few months ago and I fucking loved it myself.
I had never seen it.
And I think heavy metal 2000 is included as an extra on there, Joe.
So I haven't seen the new one either, but worth the shot.
I'm sure the music is like corn and Static X and stuff is my guess, but I don't know.
I looked it up.
It was like.
I think it's like monster.
There was some cool bands like Monster Magnet.
And I like Monster Magnet, but then it was like, yeah.
Anyway, Rob Zombie, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Check out heavy metal if you haven't seen it.
Apparently they've been trying to make a third one forever in love and robots, love,
sex and robots, whatever it's called on Netflix is the unofficial third.
Yeah.
Heavy metal installment and it's cool because it's one of those movies when,
you know, you watch the special feature, you know, a vignette or feature,
whatever you want to call it.
And, you know, a lot of really cool people like heavy metal.
It's, you know, and a lot of cool directors and it's just a cool movie.
I recommend heavy metal anyway.
Okay.
Let's get to much to my surprise.
What sounds like is going to be a bit of a dividing movie here.
The Pope's Exorcist.
Yeah, I look, I mean, I've been watching, uh, Joe Bob and I have been kind of disgusted
with the movie.
He's movies he's getting beyond the door or three.
He did the other night, like people don't like beyond the door.
I didn't even know they made sequels to the thing.
He did shark NATO, you know, the sci -fi original it's, it's sad to me.
I don't want to see him doing these movies.
Now the Pope's Exorcist to me feels like the type of movie Joe Bob should be doing
because I think it works both as a bad movie and a good movie.
I gave it a three out of five on the letterbox, which I guess ranks as a C, but the truth
is I kind of enjoyed myself more than that.
I just couldn't see myself in get a better rating.
I like a fat Russell Crowe wearing weird sunglasses and the weird like bad ass Pope
outfit putting him on that little dumb and dumber scooter.
I thought it was a stroke of genius.
The music in the movie.
I think that's what the real guy did.
I think the real guy that it's based on rode around on that little scooter.
I mean, he was clearly a character.
I don't know if he had this great taste in music where he's listening to like Faith No
More and the cult and all these like kind of alt 80s and you know, alternative music
and stuff, but it just kind of works.
It's, it's two paint by numbers.
I mean, the story is just simply a little boy who gets possessed by the devil.
They call in the Pope's exorcist and he goes and does it.
You know, it's, it's, that's it.
That's the movie.
He, he goes, he performs the exorcism with the help of another weaker priest, just like
in the exorcist.
They both have their deep dark secrets about things that have happened in their past that
of course the demon exploits.
Just like in the exorcist.
Yeah.
And then surprise, surprise, they get the demon out.
And then literally does set up a franchise and there's already going to be more where
he goes and exercises more people.
The possessed kid has things get written on his stomach and blood, just like in the
exorcist.
Look, this movie is, I'll get to what I liked about it.
Here's what my biggest issue with it was.
This movie to me is like the guys that wrote this, they had the exorcist on
and then they threw on the DVD of them, Emily Rose and when I, and they were just
writing shit now, like, oh yeah, then you do that.
Then you do the thing where they climb on the ceiling.
Got it right on the stomach, right?
We got to learn the demon's name because that's how you'd beat it.
Okay.
It was so just like every single turn you're like, guys, for Christ's sake, uh, the, the,
the, the trope I had the biggest problem with in this.
And I don't know when they're going to fucking learn.
And the great was Ralph Innocent from the witch.
Is that his name?
Ralph Innocent?
Is that the actor's name?
The dad in the witch.
Oh, I don't know his name.
The guy from the office.
Uh, I don't know his name.
I'm sorry.
I know who you mean, but I don't know his name.
He's the voice.
And he's not in this movie.
Oh, he's the voice of the demon.
Yeah.
And as soon as I heard the demon, I was like, oh, that's.
You're right.
Ralph Innocent.
Yeah.
I was like, that's Ralph Innocent.
I didn't know his name either.
I had to look it up and he's great.
But when are these movies going to learn every possession movie?
Guys, the thing that is so awesome about the exorcist and what makes it so scary,
the voice of the demon is done by, I forget the lady's name.
She was an older actress.
Mercedes McCambridge.
Yes.
Who said in an interview.
She went off the wagon for the exorcist.
She started drinking so she could get the husk in her voice she needed.
And like, so she could like go there.
So she's like, I drink eggs and then smoke six cigarettes and we'd record like.
And it's so fucking scary sounding.
When are these movies going to learn?
They also did it in.
Carnival with where they had the lady from she devil and kindergarten cop.
The short lady, Linda Hunt.
Yeah, she's the voice of management and her voice is scary.
Like she just makes her voice scary and it's a rich voice and it's great.
Just have a scary voice that doesn't match the child's body.
That's all you need.
Like this thing where it's like, we're going to throw it through the modulator
and then add two octaves below to it.
It's like, how many fucking horror movies are they going to do this in?
How many horror movies are they going to do the modulated octave drop voice?
Like, it just doesn't, it's not scary.
It's just not fucking scary.
That that really.
It's up there with it's up there with the cheap CGI.
You know, like there's the scene in this where he realizes the boy is possessed
because the kid's eyes like double when he's looking in the kid's eyes.
And I started laughing and I was like, if I had a friend here
in an Italian accent right now, I would say bad CGI.
That is the mark of the devil, whatever.
Because it's like it's again, it's like how many movies we can do the bad CGI trick.
Oh, look, their face gets weird for a second.
Remember that in Devil's Advocate?
Yep.
Yeah.
Remember that in Jacobs?
Yep.
Yeah.
No, I remember in all the movies they did it.
So no, it's a total greatest hits of these of these possession movies.
It's a total paint by numbers.
Greatest hits unquestionably.
What this movie has those other ones don't.
Is Russell Crowe and Russell Crowe, you know, for a very long time was considered
one of our greatest actors.
He's not as bankable as he once was.
So he takes his talents to kind of lesser fare.
This to me is like when James Mason or Christopher Lee or any of these like great actors
would eventually turn to the horror genre and just start doing great work.
The same great work they've always been doing just on kind of a cheesier scale.
And it creates an effect that I love.
It's somebody who's slumming for sure.
But it's somebody who's like, look, I came to play.
If the big leagues won't pay me to do my skills anymore, I'm going to do them down here.
And bringing that level of talent to be a true B movie like this
can sometimes have really great results.
And I thought that this for the most part was just really fun.
When he goes to see the Pope who's played by a pretty famous director, actually,
Franco Nero, who Tarantino loves.
I wrote down some lines that had me howling.
He says, and I'm not, I'm, I wrote it down verbatim.
The Pope says, this boy's possession is a progressing very fast.
Yeah.
His possession is progressing fast.
A possession is not like jaundice.
You're possessed by the devil.
You're immediately possessed.
It was such a stupid line that I like gasp and laugh.
And in the same scene as the Pope is sending off Russell Crowe,
we hear over narration, the Pope saying to him, be careful.
This a demon sounds very dangerous.
Yeah.
What demon isn't Pope?
What demon isn't?
It's a demon in their defense, Pat.
They do explain that their levels of demons, uh, the higher up this demon is the king of hell.
His title is the king of hell.
Uh, yeah.
And the king of rock.
They, they, they get around to, uh, but there's some very funny.
There's some very purposefully funny moments in the movie.
It's funny when he's like, when the young priest is like, I read all your articles.
And he's like, did you read my books?
And he goes, no.
And he goes, they're, they're good.
They're very good.
And then they call that back at the end with the, with on screen, he wrote a dozen books.
They make him a little bit of a narcissist.
They make him a little bit of a guy who's like, uh, you know, who thinks he's hot shit.
And why wouldn't he be?
He's the Pope's chosen exorcist nails the line.
I loved how campy they made his villain, the Cardinal, the guy who's opposing to him.
They made this guy so far over the top.
Like you couldn't even believe it.
It's very, very funny.
Halfway through that, like seeing where the other priests or whatever, for some reason
they're all in Italy.
They've got the most American Cardinal guy.
He's like 25.
It didn't make any sense.
No, chastising him.
I got to make it a point in that scene.
I'm like, is this guy even in the church?
Who is this guy?
This is crazy.
Yeah.
He seems like a spy or something.
Cause he's so over the top.
And then they, um, they do the, uh, the Crow nails the joke at the end when they,
after they get through the entire exorcism and the other priest is covered in blood.
And he's like, you look like a shit.
I was like, that's, that's actually a funny line.
It made me laugh.
Um, yeah, now this is one of the things I liked about the movie.
I really enjoyed Crow's humor.
He played the part with a lot of charge and every review, even the bad ones point that out.
Um, but I like that.
And this is a thing that a lot of possession movies won't do and don't do.
I like that.
That becomes a little bit like a Da Vinci code kind of thing where like they find that
catacomb and they go into it and there's like all the skeletons down there.
And he's like, they're all extra.
It was kind of like Indiana Jonesy when he's like, they're all exorcists.
Like this, this man was under the influence of the devil.
When he told the Pope to start the crusades and all that stuff, he was possessed.
That's why the demon wanted me here.
He's going to try to possess me.
So I go back and influence the church to do wrong.
And they bring the, the coverup of the, the molestation scandal into it.
Like the, the, you know, the devil's influence on the church or whatever.
I thought all that stuff was really, really cool.
Uh, in the end, I mean, they, so you go through all the motions of the,
of the paint by numbers, as Pat said, exorcism stuff and, you know, come into down to come
into me, take me the priest is like, Jesus Christ.
But then in the, in the final throws of the third act, they end up back in that catacomb
and they just say, fuck it.
At this point, even though this is supposedly based on true events, the demons come out
of the priest as two women from the past lives of these two priests.
And the priests fight the women as physical demons and make them for some inexplicable
reason explode by putting a cross to their head.
Topless lady demons.
Yeah, it's nuts.
It's fucking nuts.
It is like, I also liked that it's rated R rated movie and they have the kid do some
creepy shit.
The kid grabs his mom's tits at one point, uh, you know, they have them say some gross
stuff.
I'm like, all right, like finally a fucking R rated exorcism movie again, you know?
And you know, the kid, you know, it's a very cheap special effect.
Have the kids say incredibly fucked up and, and profane things with somebody else's
voice coming out.
It's just kind of fun to see and it's cheap and easy.
You know, it's not anything that requires a lot of CGI.
Um, the director Julius Avery, his biggest movie by far is overlord.
And then his career has kind of just been puttering around since we talked about doing
overlord five years ago on this show.
And I've still never seen it.
I would love to do it.
I saw it, but, um, that makes sense.
Overlord, that makes the ending of this makes sense with overlord because overlord's
fucking wild.
Uh, it's a fun movie.
You'll like overlord.
Um, but, and then he, you know, the, he goes back home to Rome and the, the new cardinal
under the Pope or whatever, like rings him down into that, like underground operation.
And it is like, here is, I mean, it's so funny movies anymore.
They're set up like video games where he's like, he points to a map and he goes, here
is the location of every place on earth.
The Lord is not welcome.
And, and Russell Crowe says to the young priest, too big of a job for just me.
You know, do you, do you feel like, you know, do you want a piece of this action
in so many words and the young priest says, yeah.
And the guy goes, let's go to work.
And then Russell Crowe goes, let's go to hell.
And, and then it's a final shot, as I said earlier of him strutting the street.
It's crazy.
I think you liked it more than more than you realized.
I think I'm coming around on it.
I mean, it's fucking nuts.
Here's my thing.
I watched like prisoners of the ghost land and I'll give tries sometimes to these like
super low budget, Nick Cage movies.
And they are always too bad.
They are not so bad.
They're good.
They are so bad.
They're bad.
They don't work as, oh my God, like the room, like this is so bad.
It's hilarious.
They also don't work as good movies and they don't work in any way in between.
That's most of these types of movies.
This movie to me, I get how dumb people might think it was a great horror movie.
I get how smart people might think it was just the right kind of stupid to have a good time at.
And I think that the filmmakers were kind of going for that.
That's a really hard thing to nail.
And I think, although this is no masterpiece, don't get me wrong.
I think they nailed how to be a really good B movie in this day and age.
And I think when we look at those movies of James Mason, Christopher Lee, all those type
of actors, these big like Shakespearean actors, even somebody like Von Sydow doing Flash Gordon
or something, they start slumming it.
They want to cash in and make some money near the end of their careers.
Russell Crowe is no different.
But when they come to play and they come to say like, I'm not going to, no offense to Bruce
Willis, but I'm not going to just kind of sleepwalk through this performance to make my money.
And of course, I'm not talking about what happened with him later in his career where he
sleepwalking because he was not doing well.
Right.
But he definitely did a lot of movies where he just wasn't trying and he's like, look,
they're paying me.
I'll show up fine.
When you get an actor who still has that twinkle in his eye and still has that passion to act,
and he's like, I'm going to give you the same performance I gave you in The Insider.
I'm just going to do it in this piece of shit.
I think it can often make a really fun time at the movies.
And that is all Pope's Exorcist seems to be aiming for.
It gives it to you.
And I'll say this.
I will happily see The Pope's Exorcist part two.
Happily.
I'll see it.
I feel like we might have a John Wick on our hands here where now I like John Wick part one
quite a bit, but it was a sleeper hit.
But when I first saw the ads for it, it was a wholly dismissable film.
I was like, who cares?
This is a fucking action movie with Keanu Reeve.
I don't care.
And then you see it and you go, wow, okay.
And then the sequels start coming.
You're like, oh shit, all right.
I think this could turn into something.
I mean, if they went for broke, what excites me about a sequel is if they went this fucking
sideways at the climax of this one, I'm like, what the fuck are they going to do on the next one?
Like, they're going to clearly make it even bigger.
So I am curious to see where it goes.
All right.
You know what?
I'll I'll I'll you've turned me around.
I'll hog up for Pope's Exorcist.
I'm going to watch it again.
My hog is for sure up.
And if you want to rent this, it's already $4 .99 on Amazon, just out of theaters.
My guess is it'll be on Peacock in a month or something.
Peacock tends to get all this low budget horror.
But look, a real solid entertainment as far as I'm concerned.
And just Crow playing Italian is funny to me.
I mean, the whole movie.
It's just.
It walks.
It walks a delicate line a lot better than much bigger movies have done.
You know, it stays in the pocket.
And I think it's largely a successful little horror movie that's got a good sense of humor about it.
We'll be back.
As you know, we'll be back with Renfield.
We're going to do a Q &A with you guys that we'll have Emily look for.
So think of some questions we've never been asked.
Um, we're doing Renfield, which is on Peacock for free.
We're also going to be doing Super Mario Brothers, which I have seen.
And Joe is not, but that's going to be on Peacock and early off.
So, you know, um, watch for those.
I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
I'm on the good Christian fun pod this month, talking about contact the movie with Jodie Foster.
Uh, and that's all I got Joseph.
Joe DeRosa comedy on your social needs, uh, all live tour dates starting in September,
going through December at the moment.
Uh, uh, Joe DeRosa .com for ticket info and show info, uh, dates are being added consistently.
Um, well, so go check out that salsa windfall song.
Keep your eye out for the full length record and come to Joey roses in New York.
You're here, Joey roses, NYC .com.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.