Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for tees and seeds, 21 plus to wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Rewards up due to expiry. Gamling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Hey, it's me, shakable, breakable, unmistakable Clutch app.
But don't break me! Break free in Borderlands 4!
The newest, fastest, looter shooter you can play with friends!
Everything's better with friends! And I will totally know!
Preorder Borderlands 4 now!
Rated mature.
This is a headgun podcast.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell, it's your favorite podcast about the horror movies
and sci -fi shows, for the pimps in the hoes, the sisters in the bros, all of those people
that listen, keep glistening, keep glistening, snakepliskin.
I'm escaped from New York, Joe DeRosa, and that's Patrick Walson.
And welcome to a special Good Friday episode of We'll See You In Hell, the podcast that
lets you know that if you don't follow our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ, you are going
to hell.
We will see you there.
We are recording this on Good Friday.
Good Friday when the Lord gave His life for thee and then came back two days later on
Easter Sunday and we'll be happy to have you back then as well, but it drops on a Easter
Monday. Yeah, so the shows you're probably have a raging Easter hangover, peep sugar
all over your cock ring. Uh huh. Uh, thinking, you know, who's bonnet did I get in last night
If you catch my drift bonnet, is that an Easter thing? Easter bonnet. Yeah, like little
girls will wear them. They used to wear them back in the, you know, meet me in St. Louis
days. Where Easter bonnets in your Easter bonnet. Meet me in St. Louis. Yeah, Judy Garland.
You know, I heard she got in quite a few bonnets. We're quite a few people got in her bonnet
back in the day. Yeah. Well, she was a pillhead. Let's call it, call it what it was.
Now, they're doing a movie about her, yes, with, and, uh,
Shell Williams.
Wait, no, that's that she played, uh, uh,
Maryland, Maryland.
Oh, yeah, that was a boring fucking movie.
My week with Maryland, more like my year in the movie theater.
No, who's playing Judy? I forget.
Judy is, uh, Renee Zellweger.
Oh, yeah, that's right. That's an odd casting.
But then you remember that Renee Zellweger's face looks like it was
take it off another human being at this point. So she kind of looks like Judy Garland now.
I gotta say I would like to see Martin Short as Judy Garland. That's what I wanted.
I would like to see Martin Short as Judy Garland playing it with his Jerry Lewis impression.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with a loss in the whole time. Is there a worse, you know, of your major holidays,
your top 10? Is there a worse holiday than Easter, a Lamer holiday than Easter? I've never had a great
one. Never had a great one. What would be great about our Lord's crucifixion other than his
glorious resurrection? That's what Easter is. Yeah, I'm saying what would be great about that
other than his glorious resurrection. I mean, if you're the type of psycho or sicko that wants to
revel in a man being nailed to something, well, then that's on you, Pat, but I can't help you there.
I just feel like the food sucks. There's never a good party. No, the food's, it's ham. It's great
food. I don't need a ham. I love ham on a Sunday afternoon. I made a ham on a Saturday afternoon
recently. You were here. I had a piece of ham. It was good. I've just never had a go. The only real
Easter memory I have would be my dad throwing me against a wall in my basement after I had moved out
of the house and then driving in two separate cars to Easter being my sister and my mom and my dad.
And then we got there my dad walking around going yeah, well padded to drive separate because he's in a
He's in a bad mood today to everyone at my Easter because he threw me against a wall was why I was in a
Why did he throw you against a wall?
Because he was like when are you gonna move along and I was like well, I don't live here anymore
I guess I can come over on a Saturday, but then somehow this conversation wound up with me throwing against the wall
Then the whole rest of the day was a lot of like careful what you say to pad, they'll get
upset.
Oh wow.
Now it's kind of a great Santini vibe.
I don't know what great Santini is.
Bobby Duval as an abusive father.
Look, that's not a movie about a magician.
I always thought there was about a magician all these years.
No, there's no magic except the magic on the screen.
I mean, woven by the great Bobby Duval.
Yeah, he's great in that moment.
Bounce is a basketball off his son's head, if I recall.
That sounds like a terrible Easter pet.
My memories consist of Easter egg hunts
and candies and things.
Yeah, I guess.
Never getting thrown against a wall, never being mocked
in front of the family by my own father.
Yeah, you wouldn't expect to see it on an Easter Sunday.
I wouldn't expect to see it on a regular Sunday.
No, but that's what I remember.
I did used to have egg hunts and things of that nature but also kind of lame if I'm being honest. Well
yeah because if you're not five an egg hunt is stupid but even if you are five it's like oh good I
I have you know jelly beans that are melting in my hand Christmas you have 10 new toys. See our egg hunts
at our church where they do them often had uh sorry I was gonna make a dirty priest joke but I don't
I don't want it because these were nice priests.
Yeah, they made my church.
They did a thing, like you'd find something
that dollar bills in them.
It was fun.
Okay.
You know, when you're sick or whatever.
Probably taking right out of the collection plate.
Yeah, yeah.
Probably.
Sick.
Sick people.
What's been happening, Joe?
I guess we should get to it first,
get on with the show and get on with the,
JOOOOO! SHIPPING LOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
or a stitch of weed, or a bump of cocaine, or a needle of arrow.
Yeah.
I have smoked about a total of five cigarettes over the two weeks, which is not bad.
Not bad.
I've been on that you only smoke when you drink.
I guess that's not true.
Well, I noticed sometimes now when I go out socially, the discomfort hits such a mass level
that I have to go outside and do something to harm myself and I don't want to cut myself
just yet.
Right.
But if cigarettes didn't exist, that's what I would be doing.
So those are the only times I ever smoke, but since I haven't been drinking.
And I haven't been on a diet for the last week.
And I got a cholesterol test back Monday.
My cholesterol was a bit high.
It's supposed to be 200, I was at 258.
So not medicine high, but you know, and not like alarming high, but high and I gotta get it down. I
Guess because who gives us your yolks cut your cheese up your fish. Haven't had any
And a piece of fish. Haven't had eggs pork
Or cheese all week
Been using cholesterol -free mayonnaise to make some tuna salad. No bread. No sweets. No sugar. Oh, man
is disgusting. Well, I didn't ask you that, Pat. And if I want
it, your fucking opinion, I would ask for it when you were a
member of the mayonnaise committee. Well, I thought this was
supposed to be a discussion podcast, where and we discussed
things more like a disgusting podcast. I'm fed up folks with this
world we live in. What's your last week was our big world
podcast. We'll get off the world this week. Um, not much. I mean,
and I might as well just get us over to Pat's movie corner.
Already?
What are we, 15 minutes in here?
We're not even, I think about 11 minutes in.
All right.
You've nothing in your week.
You want to talk about how you haven't been drinking?
Or have you been, you sneak?
No, I haven't.
It doesn't get easier.
I want to drink all the time.
Right now, I'd like to be having a drink.
But that's about it.
You know your days are long.
They're boring. If I'm myself going to bed earlier waking up early very little joy. Yeah, um
Yeah, I think it was
Humphrey Bogart who say doesn't understand people who doesn't drink who don't drink
Because when they wake up, that's the best they're gonna feel all day. Yeah, I know the quote well
So not you're often quoted him for saying that yeah
It's true. Yeah, it's a miserable day
Nothing picks up. No, you know, I mean, I guess you get a little
You know, I found an N64
Sure in a thrift store two days ago for $25 that was exciting
Then that's gone now though. I mean, I still have it, but the joy is gone
I didn't even play it. I just bought it
Yeah, and I set it up and I didn't even turn it on
So I mean, that's where I'm at
Yeah, I mean, it came out more sad than a than a triumph for
really. It sounds terrible. It was supposed to be sad. And you
didn't have one of those? No, that's the newest addition to my
collection is the N64. I had one of those as a kid. I didn't
have one now. All right. Or college kid, I should say. Got some
new video games over here. Mortal Kombat and I LA Armageddon
for the PlayStation 2. One of the great Mortal Kombat entries. Tony Hawk
Pro Skater for the N64. Again, haven't played it. 1080 snowboarding for the
N64. Again, haven't played it. Rogue Squadron for the N64. Haven't played it.
Well, I'm glad you kept us from heading over to Pants Movements. Got some great
stuff here. All right, let's go, all right, I saw red sparrow, red sparrow,
starring Jennifer Lawrence. I mean, it was weird. It was basically like a woman,
especially it was a weird movie for now. Every bit as weird as death wish,
because she was basically a woman, not sort of a Russian spy, who was groomed
to seduce and pleasure men.
And there are classes that are shown in this movie,
where they're basically being trained
to lean into a sexual assault and take it.
Right, because then you can get better info for them.
It all felt pretty uncomfortable.
The story was very convoluted.
At some point, it reminded me of a tinkertail or soldier spy,
the most boring movie ever made.
The most boring and unconfusing movie ever made yeah, you know, it's that movie is
But that movie I felt like this movie is smarter than me and I
I just don't get it and that's fine red sparrow. I felt like this movie is dumber than me and
They just kind of aren't telling the story well and it didn't really do much for me. There was
You know, I had heard it compared to Paul Verhoeven
Who's an insane director that I love a lot of his movies you know showgirl starship
troopers robocop you love showgirls earliest I like trash and I like his version of
trash he also did hollow man which was you know a Kevin Bacon getting invisible so he
could sexually assault women basically was the plot of that was that a good movie no
hollow man's very bad but uh it had the same kind of feel there was a lot of nudity in it
the surprising amount of Jennifer Lawrence nudity she was I mean she's an incredible looking woman
She has a presence. I like watching her. But as we dip into the two -hour 20 -minute range, you know, I
Saw I can't recommend it. I saw about
25 minutes of this film. Yeah, I
Was waiting to go in to see another movie that will review that's my drain going off
I don't know if it's picking up on here, but I was well, I'll explain why I saw only 25 minutes on it on the annihilation
podcast, but
But I saw about 25 minutes of this movie as I waited to see a annihilation.
And that was enough for me.
I got in one rape scene, which 25 minutes in is, you know, there's probably more coming
if they're throwing them that quickly at you.
Yeah.
I didn't really care to see more where that one.
Jeremy Irons comes out doing this Russian diplomat character that literally looks like it's
a sketch on mad TV. He's holding the cigarette upside down. Yeah, it was both like broad, like a
malkovich, but also you could tell he was very bored doing it. It was absurd. So as a over -the -top
performance done in a boring way, which was very strange to say. It was absurd. And then I'll
his character does everything except say as you a medic and say yeah the cows come home or
you know one of those things. I think he said something pretty close to that. It was it was not a good
wasn't a bad film it just wasn't a good film right what I what I saw 25 now yeah no I saw the
hole should back. I don't think it didn't get any better. I saw ready player one but I imagine we'll do
that on here. We should do that on here. We'll do that on here. I saw Hellrager
judgment, which we're probably not going to review on here. I'm not watching
anymore. Hellraist. I know. You've made it very clear. How was it? Not good. Yeah. It
got a little bit closer to what I love about the first two films than most of
the sequels did. Right. But that's not saying much because there's been so many
bad sequels at this point. It had moments that were interesting. It had some ideas that
were fine. It was much, much too layered. There was too much going on. It very much felt
like a movie that felt like, you know, it felt like these things always feel anymore.
Like these sequels a lot of the time feel. They took a script for something and then they
He turned it into a hell -raiser movie,
which the director claims he didn't do.
But that's what it felt like to me.
Enough, if you're listening out there,
hell -raiser producers and writers.
Enough with the cop storylines.
Nobody wants a cop murder mystery storyline.
That's its own thing.
Don't, as they say in the comedy writing business,
don't joke the joke.
We're already doing a horror movie
about demons from hell.
Don't add a serial killer storyline to it. It's too much.
I've only heard it's a joke on a joke.
Huh? I've only heard it's a joke on a joke.
Yeah, you're joking the joke.
I've never heard it put as joking the joke.
Why, I don't know. What do you want from me, Pat?
I didn't want you to give him wrong information.
I'm sorry.
But you get what I mean.
So it was, you know, I'm...
Does pinhead ever get arrested?
Do they ever put like cuffs on him
and take him down to the station?
There's a there's a scene that's very like cops like where they pull him out of his trailer. Yeah, and his wife is his demon wife is screaming for the cops to let him go.
Uh -huh.
She's spitting at the camera. Right. So yeah, and I just didn't think that fit.
I think it fit.
And then the movie ends with this spoiler alert. The movie ends with this.
There's this woman that keeps showing up to the pinhead and the and the auditor who's
one of the other centabytes throughout the film.
And you don't know who she is or whatever, but she's dressed in this like sort of white
leather get up with like strap on shoes, like white shoes with toe, toe exposed shoes with
strap.
You know, like a very modern outfit.
Then at the end of the movie, you find out she's like a rep from heaven.
And she's basically like, you're not going to bring this serial killer to hell.
You're going to let him go because we need him out there to keep people believing in us.
So it's just too much.
It's like now the director is doing the whole like heavens actually corrupt too, see, which
is dumb.
Right.
And boring and basic.
And then also you're like, the centabytes wear this like otherworldly clothing and this woman
from heaven is dressed like they're the gap, like she shopped it like the gap business or whatever,
you know, it's ridiculous. It's just not. Maybe she was trying to blend it. Well, no, she only
appears to the demons. And then at the end of the movie, Pinhead gets turned back into a normal human.
And that's his punishment is that he's now a human, which completely betrays
the pinhead mythology and not that it hasn't been betrayed before, but that's
not that's not what the story is like so it's just it's just bad. It was just
bad. I'm sorry to hear. Yeah me too I was excited to see it and I waited two
years to see it yeah so anyway all right well I got some for Joe scary stuff. Wait
Don't you have another oh wait ready player one that was it
That's that's all I saw okay, so then we'll do that on an episode. Yeah, okay. I got you
Hey, well then let's take it to Joe's scary stuff stuff stuff. Drop drop drop
What do you got bitch?
Shout select which is a nice little
You know not quite at
But what's the collector's edition?
The screen factory.
Yes.
They're not quite at that level with the special features, but Shout Select does a nice job
of picking movies.
I believe they did the Bill and Ted series, which I bought and still have not watched.
But I also got the Burbs.
Beautiful.
New a dish, great print, great horror comedy, really good like 45 minute documentary with all
the key players except Tom Hanks and Gary Fisher and Bruce Dern.
Yeah.
That's a lot of Feldman.
You tell me this the other night, he goes, he goes, the entire cast is in this documentary.
I go, really?
And I go, Hanks, he goes, except for Hanks.
And well, and also Fisher, because she's past, I go, okay, so Bruce Dern, you go, no,
he's not in it either.
He didn't get Dern.
I go, who's in it?
He goes, it's a lot of Feldman.
Yeah.
It's Feldman.
It's Dern's wife and the stars and stripes bikini.
in the interviews now, she puts it back on.
No, all right, and it's a lot of Dante,
Dante, Dante, Joe Dante, Joe Dante, yeah.
You know, it's good.
And then the other features unfortunately
you've already seen on the documentary.
So you start to watch the commentary
and you're like, you just told me this story.
I hate when they do that on Blu -rays, frankly.
Like, they'll have an interview with Joe Dante
that's 10 minutes long.
but then most of the interview, like 95 % of it, is in the documentary. So don't put the interview on that.
I don't get it. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, but I mean, they probably do that commentary six months apart from the interview,
so they don't remember it.
I mean, this one had the Dottie interview was in the documentary and then they put it on there like it's
a special feature. I didn't expect to complain about this, this Blu -ray, but it was a minor quibble.
If you're a fan of the Burbs, there's tons of great stories.
They talk about Corey Feldman having a lot of porn stars on the set.
He was 15 years old.
That's barely mentioned.
They gloss right over it.
It was a different time, folks.
It's a different time.
Rick Ducamon also not in the documentary.
Pretty much nobody from the cast in the documentary.
Rick Overtin.
Overton.
Yeah.
Or is it Dukeamon?
Or is that Rick Ducamon?
Dukeamon.
Let's get the mixed up.
There's two guys.
One's Rick over to one's Rick Duke of it. That's Duke of them. Yeah, Duke him and died and they said that he
Had a very filthy sense of humor that all often didn't gel with the entire cast
You know the role was offered to John candy
Is that right? Yeah, he passed because he said no, I'm not playing another like fat guy role
Right like I don't want to play the fat guy again boy, but what a great movie that would have been it would have been fucking fancy
How'd you know that I never heard that?
I don't know I just know it
But look, I think Dukehamon is tremendous in it, but I can only, you know, it's like
the kingpin scenario.
What would the other version have been?
Well, this candy and Dukehamon are not equals.
I mean, no, but Dukehamon's really good at it.
He is.
He really plays the dumb guy very, very well.
Yeah.
And I just mean a farly carry Keaton kingpin
That's a true
Which is better scenario who knows I think the one we got
Keaton wait care in the in the alternate kingpin carry is is big earn, right carry is bigger and Keaton is
Harrelson and farly was the omniscience and were they ever gonna dress that Keaton is about 20 years older than
and I'm sure they weren't.
Didn't you, Gary?
I'm sure they weren't, and they're supposed to be the same age.
Yeah, well, I mean, it could have been a whole different thing.
But yeah, but I love the burbs.
I would, I'm interested to see, you know,
what of course would have loved to see
what the John Candy version would have been.
I think it was right around, right after that was when
Candy did like only the lonely.
I think it was when he was trying later, but yeah, yeah,
he was like, I want to be a leading man,
like just because I'm heavy doesn't mean,
I mean, Jesus you want to talk about ahead of his time right Christ almighty, you know, like the late 80s
And the guys like why can't I be fat and be just regular, you know, JFK for crying. Oh, he's fantastic
Well, I take that back. He's not fantasy. He's it's interesting to see him in that role in JFK
But he's not fantastic and at that accent is not I like it. I like the role. I don't I'm not buying the accent
You got to do that.
Well, that's how it was written.
He's doing it in kind of a 50s movie style, I felt.
Right.
I guess.
I watched on YouTube.
I had seen it before in A &E, like this hour -long tribute to John Candy.
It's fantastic.
If you look up tribute to John Candy and it's about 50 minutes on YouTube, it's fantastic.
I really like Jack Lemmon and Jeff K.
I do as well.
Yeah.
He told a story on the actor studio that his...
He goes, he goes, they just stoned, just kept tearing the lights up, brighter, brighter,
brighter, brighter, brighter, brighter, I'm doing the scene, I'm sweating.
Wouldn't you know what the damn paper caught on fire?
That's how hot the damn lights were.
Wow.
That's the story he told.
That was the same episode where James looked and said, what's your favorite word?
And he looked at his wife and said, can I?
And she nodded, yes.
And he went, uh, cock, suck, I'm out of the fuck.
All right.
But it was, it was bleeped, how did you know?
Because they, I don't know, they didn't bleep the sucker in the fucker or the mother maybe.
All right.
I really, I really should not on trial.
You've got a lot of challenges today.
I just, it's something that occurred.
Now, Mr. Derosa, you claim.
How can you have heard the word Cox, I could clearly, through the beak.
Did you see that interview with Bob Hoskins that was making the round this week?
No, why is that making the rounds?
It was from like 1990 or something, probably like Roger Rabbit Days
and Hoskins on some British talk show.
I don't know who posted, but it got a lot of traction
for some or whatever reason.
No, it didn't seem to be.
All right.
He talked about being hammered on the set of Super Mario Brothers.
Oh, I just watched a whole dot online doc about that
by the gaming historian, which is he does these really great,
like sort of biography style history videos about video games.
Yeah, you know, whole thing about the Super Mario brothers and how like they were just apparently fucking wasted like
There was a there was like a car accident when Lengels. I was driving
I recently read an article about it that was fascinating. It seemed like a a true disaster. Yeah, but
Anyway, Huskins is like, yeah, you know, I get a call from my buddy Brian DePolma and
And he says, a old chap, let's go to dinner and we go to dinner and he says, I want you to play Al Capone in my untouchables movie.
Yeah.
And I said, Al Capone, we're brought into Palmer. Where do I sign, mate?
So anyway, you know, he goes, I got to tell you though, I did ask Robert De Niro to do it.
If he doesn't do it, will you beat my backup for me? Will you be on call?
I said I understand you got to go with De Niro and I'll be I'll be your on call man
So some time passes
Then De Niro does the part. I think all right. I didn't get it. I get a
Card at my house one day a check inside for two hundred thousand dollars
It's a card from Brian De Palma saying thank you for being my backup man
Wow, well, I turned to my wife. I said hey, Brian you got any other parts
You don't need me to play.
And like a huge laugh for the audience.
It's kind of a soft punchline really,
but it's worth a watch.
It was a great story.
They don't even let them talk for that long
on these talk shows anymore.
Now you just watched like a long great story, well told.
It was nice.
There's an interview I found recently.
If you go on YouTube, you can find it.
If you look up Joe Pesci Letterman Goodfellas.
You talked about it last time and I watched it. I did. Yeah. Oh, Jesus. Wow. That was a week ago. More
forgetful without the drink. Uh, do you watch it? Yeah. Do you like it? I loved it. It was
fucking great. Great interview. Uh, okay. I'm going to plug for Joe scary stuff. You know, I'll stick
with the theme here. Um, and many of you horror collectors out there are probably already familiar
with this. But arrow, arrow is doing some really great re -releases of films. Uh, they're, they're,
We're doing a lot in the -
They're doing Robin Hood Prince of Thieves, right?
Oh, God.
Jesus.
Come on, man.
That reminds me, did you ever hear the Bob Hoskins interview,
where he was supposed to play Robin Hood?
No.
And they said you have to go with Kevin Costner.
Yeah.
He didn't get a check.
He just didn't get it.
It was awesome.
Is it gonna play Robin Hood now?
No, Joe, I'm doing your story you just did.
Well, I know, but
Hoskins is such a better choice for the role of Robin Hood a British man. Yeah, Hoskins a British man that looks like super man
Well, I guess he'd be better fake for Friar tough. Yeah, what are you talking about? Maybe little John at least he's British
Friar tough by the way my drag name is Friar tucked
folks. Folks. Let's just say you want the seats in the rear. If you want to see the
full view. Anyway, we were at a arrow. Arrow. They're doing a lot of stuff, you know, much
like screen factories doing. They're re -issuing a lot of old horror movies and doing very nice jobs
with new packaging and special features and things. I believe Arrow did the reanimator
anniversary reissue that just came out and the reanim -bride of reanimator. So check those out,
man. If you're not, I don't see them often in stores, which is why I think it's good to plug these
things. I don't see a lot of the screen factory stuff in stores. Usually, unless you're
at a fries electronics or a place that sells some sort of more esoteric DVDs and blu -rays,
I don't really see these things. I've never seen them at a Best Buy or anything. Go on Amazon
and look these things up. Or go directly to their websites and get them.
Probably should go to the websites. That's the first thing Trump's done.
Yeah, that seems like a good idea is try to get to the bottom of why Amazon the largest company in America doesn't pay taxes
I was like now you're doing something worthwhile Trump
But it's probably just some personal vendetta. He hasn't. Well, he's doing it so he can be like look how they didn't pay that taxi
That's what he wants to do again, but hey, whatever you really that's how the scene with that that Trump what's that you really Gandalfy need that Trump
I
Phil, go get the head out of the drumster, little Phil, and go whack the guy, Frankie.
That's right, Gandalfini.
It's really good.
You should breathe heavier, though.
Yeah.
About the boom, about it being, we should still watch it like, because you'll love it and then
you'll eat your words.
We forgot to mention what we're talking about today, which is mom and dad, the Nicholas
Kage, Selma Blair vehicle about parents who one day snap in a town or I guess across the world.
They never, no, yeah, it's widespread because there's national news stories.
Right. And they turn on their children and try to kill them.
It is available on iTunes right now for 99 cents and you can download it on any of your major sites.
Yeah. I thought this movie was a blast.
I loved it. It was one of the sharpest, it was the sharpest horror movie I've seen since
Get Out. It has the strongest social commentary I've seen in a horror film since Get Out. It's
cage being self -effacing and wild. Uncaged. Yes. Blair delivers on all fronts. The kids are great.
and all plants, 10 ricks in shows up, what more do you want? I mean, it's a great movie,
it's a lot of fun, it's funny at times, it's tense, they hit this concept from every conceivable angle.
And I just thought they did a great job of depicting the dynamic of the old and the young in this
day and age. They made the kids look like total fucking pricks at the top of the movie where
you want bad things to happen to them because they're so arrogant and so snottie. And then
by the end of the movie, you think that the parents are the kind of gross people because
they're complaining about this life they opted to have for themselves and make for themselves
And now they're mad at it. So it was a really really great commentary on both sides of the age gap and I thought it was I thought it was awesome
Funny movie. I mean, so a lot of times with these movies. They'll have a great premise like this Truth or Dare movie coming out
I think it has in theory a great premise. Haven't seen it. Maybe it's great
But it looks like the executions probably not gonna be on point
There's a lot of great horror premises that have been wasted through the years. This is a great one
I had not seen and they did everything they could have done with it
Yeah, they used every part of the buffalo. You got cage as we talked about the other day
I mean, he really creeps it up in this thing even when he's supposed to be being a nice dad before he snaps
He's still kind of weird and creepy. That's what I found strange was I understand not wanting to make him like
Ward Cleaver or something, but I bet it was cage who was like I think this guy should be a piece of shit before he turns
And then the directors, there's a long, long line of stories of cage insisting on something
performance -wise that might hurt the film.
Yeah.
Like that one we saw where he did a brand -on impression for the last 30 minutes.
What was that?
Oh, and I didn't see that movie, man, by its dog, man by its dog.
Um, but, uh, yeah, I mean, he's, he's going for it.
Uh, I think if there had been a little more of a arc between the old dad and the new dad,
it would have hit a little harder, but it was kind of funny to see him in these flashbacks
like pounding beers and talking about getting laid and shit like that to his son.
But then again, maybe the flashbacks were warped and supposed to be, you know, through this
new lens of seeing your dad is crazy. Yeah, that's true. So I don't know. But yeah, there is a
funny scene where he's like sitting with his eight -year -old drinking beer. And he's like,
son, that car was a pussy magnet. And his eight -year -old is like, dad, Jesus. He's like, sorry,
girl's girl mag son girl that's my Jimmy Stewart. See, see, it was a girl mag
She's not here. She's in your house
What's that from
It's a wonderful life. He says that your money's not here. It's in Joe's house and and so does he's house and
You know that I don't remember that line, but it sounds they were movies. It sounds accurate
There's an angel, an angel, God is weighing.
That's right, so, so, that's right.
Let's do, give me a Jimmy Stewart ordering at a restaurant.
Any, give me any restaurant.
I'll do it, I'll do, I'll start with the,
where's that Pinto or black beans?
No, I give you the restaurant, you give me the right,
let's play the, get improv game.
I thought I was gonna be Jimmy Stewart
coming through Chipotle.
No, I'll be, I'm saying we could both do it,
But I'll give you the restaurant to order you give me the restaurant to order
Then it's like a game. We're at two different restaurants. God damn it Pat
What do Jimmy ready Jimmy Stewart ordering at McDonald's go see?
Well, I'll do a 20 -piece chicken nugget because I got to get my grandkids later and they like it and their fingers and dipping sauces
I
Quarter powder with trees. Yeah, can you do it without onions because I got I kiss the wife and she smells it on my breath and
She doesn't let me kiss her again. This is
Devolving into Adam Sandler's old or Dana Carvey's old man characters. Yeah, I'll do
44 ounce a diet doctor doctor pepper diet doctor pepper. That's that's fun to say and it's fun to say
Okay, look, it's hard to do for an extended period.
No, I'll do Gandalfini ordering at a restaurant.
All right, Gandalfini ordering at Chuck E. Cheese.
I think I'm a whole pizza and another whole pizza.
And another whole pizza.
And then another whole pizza.
Is that rat edible?
Speak ill of the dead much.
Speaking of which, I like another whole pizza.
Well, come and write up Mr. Gandalfring here.
See, they are war.
It's a Chuck E. Cheese connected in the end.
It's a Chuck E. Cheese where celebrities work.
Yes, I ended you.
Well, look, I'm going to read through some of these questions that we got.
I requested them.
You need to remember on our next episode for us to talk about our, that was off, Mike,
our field trip last week.
Oh yeah, we'll talk about it on the next episode.
I'll tease it, I call that a tease.
Absolutely.
And one of these episodes this month will be shout outs,
but not this one.
All right, here comes some questions.
So wait, so this is a new segment of Q and A.
We've never done this, so let's give it a name.
I thought what the hell, we'll, we'll go, okay.
Okay.
Queue and ache.
Queue and aides.
That's scary.
Oh, God.
Well, all right.
Queue and ache.
I'm just doing a shitty crypt keeper.
Queue and I call this one Boo and Slay.
Okay, it's Boo and Slay.
Just your thoughts on Nicholas Cage
and his evolution in general.
as Ashley Davis and he was my favorite actor from age 10 to 30 and now I can't
really support him on these journeys. I don't see everything he makes but that
sweet spot of 10 years where he was like he was doing some truly like they
talk about brave acting which I always find to be a real shitty thing to say when
are risking their lives. But like him in Moonstruck, it's pretty brave. It's an insane performance
that should have wrecked that movie, but somehow worked perfectly. He did shoot like that
all the time, like the rock. You're like, does he? What is he doing? Is this right? But it makes
them all so much more fun. And that element is missing from action movies now. Raising Arizona,
the greatest community performance for me, I've ever seen. He's great in that. And then let's not
I don't forget leaving Las Vegas.
He's tremendous in that movie.
Honeymoon and Vegas is the funniest,
like if you're talking about a traditional romantic comedy,
that might be the funniest romantic comedy performance.
Oh, that's the prequel to leaving Las Vegas, right?
That's why he goes with them, he was still pretty good.
If you've never seen Honeymoon and Vegas,
holy shit is that movie funny.
Most of it is due to Cage,
but it's just a great story very well told, love it.
My favorite cage performance is matchstick, man.
We've discussed it.
Love matchstick, man.
Yeah, I feel we've talked about the man before.
How much Coke was given to Cage prior to filming
as Alan Hallett, a lot of it, a lot of it.
I would imagine, right?
Are you guys gonna do a live show anytime soon?
I think we gotta organize this, Joe.
We gotta organize this.
Well, it seems that our numbers are strongest
in Chicago, Los Angeles, and San Francisco, or San Diego.
It's one of the sand towns out here.
We're gonna do both.
Let's just start with Los Angeles and Chicago.
How have we not done one in Los Angeles if you are from either of those if you live in either of those cities
And you want us to do a live one right to us
You know on the Facebook page or on Twitter or on Instagram or email or whatever and let us know and you know
Give us an idea of
Can we get one of these things going?
Great we'd love to
Joe did you notice the grant Morrison cameo and mom and dad he was on the news
as Stanley Burns. I don't know who Grant Morrison is.
I don't know who Grant Morrison is.
Oh. Well, wait a minute. Now I got it.
Now I got to look up Grant Morrison.
I know the name. I'm not looking up.
Who is your dream Coke binge celeb?
Whether they have the cage -like Coke vibe or not.
So basically, who would you most want to do a bunch of Coke with?
That's a great question.
And I guess you got to say living or dead,
but I mean, I couldn't hang with the
like the blues brothers, you know, I'd be dead, but my vote would probably be
acroid and bluesy on the side of the blues brothers, I think would be a blast.
I would pick, you know, my favorite comedian of all time is George Carlin, and he was a big,
big fan of the cocaine late 70s. So I'd go with Carlin. Grant Morrison is a comic book writer.
Oh, okay, he wrote all -star Superman.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, that's where I knew his name from.
It's from comic books.
But I can't remember names ever.
But that's cool.
No, I didn't notice that.
But that is very cool that he was in there.
Okay.
We got...
Did you ever think about doing stand -up as your career?
I assume that's for me, but it's funnier to ask you, funnier to me to ask you, yeah.
When I moved out here, I thought I want to either do performing all -in or writing all -in.
I do not feel like people tend to succeed if they have their toe in 10 different pots.
Maybe that was right, maybe that was wrong, but I didn't do stand -up till much later.
never never seemed like a viable option to me. I don't have the, you know, I can't tell the same
story over and over and over. It drives me crazy. But I loved it for the brief time I did it.
Well, remember that next time we're at a bar.
Okay, are either of you pumped that tool is finally in the studio working on a new album?
Job nope
Yeah, it's funny. I was never my bag really. I liked tool for a long time
I heard sober on
Sirius XM the other day, and I had heard that song. I ain't heard that song since it was big
Yeah, but I haven't heard that song in forever, and I remembered like oh, yeah
Remember when I wrote I ain't heard that song so it was big reservoir dogs. Yeah, that's right
I heard the night the lights went out and Georgia. Yeah, yeah, I ain't heard that song since it was
Yeah, it's the first time I realize it's the wife killed child or whatever he says
But I was listening to it and I was like, oh, yeah
Remember the time when we thought manor James Keenan was like super cool and mysterious. Yeah, and then he started
Showing his face and doing interviews and you're like this guy's a dildo right like I'm just not a fan of the guy anymore
Like that I liked his wine documentary because I thought it was interesting that he has found success in the world of wine
I mean, and I love the Tim and Eric segments in it, but I hated like how much he was trying
to also be funny and how every scene was like him and Pat and Oswald or him and some
comedian, he just came off like not cool to me for some reason, I don't know, did it annoyed
me.
I hear you.
One more.
We'll do some on the next one.
I'll do one more.
I'll do one more. Can we get your best Nicholas Cage? We've been doing a bit of them, but we should each do one on the way out.
All right, I'll do Nick. Give me a restaurant to order from the Olive Garden.
Now you're a bottomless show. That's Jimmy Stewart. It's both. Is it truly bottomless? Or is there in fact a fucking bottom?
That was, that was a good like late 90s catch. Yeah. Okay. Give me a restaurant.
Shaky's pizza. Hey, man, I'd like a Shaky's pizza. And if you could get it out here,
too sweet, that'd be great because I'm real fucking hungry. I would have liked more
are screaming on to some sausage and a pepperoni. You think you can do that?
Oh, because that's our show, uh, Joderosa Comedy on Instagram. Sometimes Twitter,
the penthouse column is you let me down, look out for that. And hopefully, hopefully,
I will have some interesting news coming soon that is TV related. And that's all I can say.
Yes, I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh show living
Biblically is on Monday nights on CBS at 93830 Central folks.
We will see you next week with a picture called an Iolation starring Natalie
Portman. So see it if you haven't and we'll see you next time.
We'll see you and hell that was a hit down podcast.