I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast that talks movies, well the podcast doesn't talk, but we are on the podcast
talk.
And boy do we talk.
We talk about the issues that matter to you.
You ever see that Garth Brooks video where he's like, here's what we're going to talk
about on my new Facebook page, we're going to talk about fun, we're going to talk about
excitement.
It's it's a hilarious video, but he's not being like ironic, right?
No, he's like, you're not going to believe the fun we're going to have enough.
It's clearly like somebody was like, Garth, you need a Facebook page and he's like, I got
to do a big intro, like he didn't know what it was or something.
It's worth a watch, it's what it's really ludicrous and Garth Brooks is just a man that has always
made me laugh.
It's a very interesting cat.
The fact that only two musicians have done the, at least that I'm aware of, have done
the alt persona thing on a giant scale and their Beyonce and Garth Brooks, remember Chris
Gaines?
Who was Beyonce's?
Sasha Fierce.
Was that, but I was pissed about that because I had gone through most of the steps to legally
change my name to Sasha Fierce.
And then I was like, well, I guess somebody beat me to the punch.
But with Joe, what are you doing with Beyonce?
This, my monitor was almost going to fall.
I had to fix it.
What the hell do you, what do you care?
I mean, you're going back, you look like Ray Charles over there.
You're going all the way left, all the way right.
People at home can't see it.
You don't got to, you don't got to expose the magic.
I think people like to know what we're up to.
It's so funny to me when people ask us to watch a video of us doing this, which I know
you do on your taste buds and stuff, too.
I guess I get it, but, well, taste buds were in a room together and it's edited.
It's like, and it's dynamically edited.
This is literally two guys on Zoom, yeah.
Yeah, I don't think you, I don't think you want it, like you think you want it.
Also, the idea of like having to get dressed up to do this podcast is stomach churning
to it hurts.
It hurts.
But wait, Sasha fears that was, was that really an art persona?
I thought there was just like an alias, like kind of like how Wu Tang, like method man will
be like hot nickels.
You know, or something, but no, the series that's one of his nicknames are like cool Keith
does that where he's like, I'm Dr. Octagon and then I'm Dr. Do.
But it's not like, I mean, there's, there's symptomatic differences, but it's not like,
like with Garth Brooks, he dressed up in a costume and did a behind the music as the guy,
like that was insane.
Joe, Sasha fears is the fun, more sensual, more aggressive, more outspoken and glamorous side
that comes out when Bay is working and when she's on that stage.
So she just named herself when she's in a different room.
And I don't think she does that anymore either.
I think it was like she just called herself that for one album.
I haven't heard the new album.
Look, people aren't going to like this.
I find Beyoncé to be a trifle overrated.
I prefer Rihanna.
I find when Beyoncé sings about sex, it feels like a put on.
And when Rihanna sings about sex, it sounds like she's getting fucked
in the recording studio while she's singing.
I believe her more.
I agree, I agree.
I've never been a big fan of Beyoncé's terminology with sex.
The jelly I never cared for that time.
That's what I'm saying.
It's like she doesn't, it doesn't come natural.
She's like the 40 -year -old virgin or something.
She's using terms that nobody else uses.
Yeah, it's like when your 12 -year -old friend is telling you, he knows what sex is.
Yeah, now don't get me wrong.
I know that Beyoncé has probably made love before
and she's probably very good at it.
Look, I'm even willing to find out and report back
if Jay -Z is okay with it.
I'm just saying Rihanna comes off like just a dirty freak.
And I like that.
I like it dirty.
Beyoncé always seems like maybe I'll do a song where I'm a dirty freak
and I don't like that.
Yeah, I always kind of felt that with Janet Jackson too.
Like it never felt as honest.
Okay, interesting.
To me, it felt like she was...
It was like, well, I'm supposed to sing about this now because I'm this old.
So like, you know, but I never bought it.
I never, you know, I bought her more in the rhythm nation vibes.
Yeah, I remember that song.
All the girls at the party look at that body shaking that thing.
Like I never did see, got a nice package all right.
I think I'm going to have to ride it tonight.
Oh, got a nice package.
Yeah, okay.
That's what I'm saying.
It's the same thing.
Now I agree with you on your Janet Jackson.
It's like, you've got a nice package that I'd like to ride.
If somebody said that to me, I'd say, fine, let's go.
But I would also say, that's the sexiest way.
You could phrase that, you know?
Bitch.
I wouldn't say that to her.
No, I know, I'm kidding.
I'm definitely not going to try to mess this up.
She just asked to ride my package.
So I'm not going to insult her.
I have a shout out to do here to Rebecca.
Laws.
No mits.
I think it's how you know, mits, mits.
Anyway, she was a middle man.
I guess it's a hyphenated last name.
Oh, okay.
She was at the live taping.
And she just sent me a package.
That's why I thought of this of an old PlayStation that she had,
because she knows I'm a game collector and a bunch of games.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Rebecca, it's an OG PlayStation.
It's the first PlayStation.
I have one, but I'm happy to have a second one.
I always want to have more of this stuff.
I love it.
She sent me all this as a gift.
And then Pat, she didn't leave you out.
You got a card.
Oh, God.
All right.
Have you opened it?
No, she said ask me if I would mail this to you.
Oh, please do.
So text me your address when you can.
Because I don't know it either, Rebecca.
You know, text you.
And then I'll, I'll mail you this card.
I also got a card.
I don't want to rub in that my gift.
Oh, so.
But we both got cards.
But only one of us got the gaming system.
Old video game system with all the games.
Yeah.
If it makes you feel better, the games ain't great.
Let me say that about a gift.
She, she was like, I have these.
Do you want them?
Like I was like, yeah, I was always thinking.
But it was like an NFL 2000.
You know, it wasn't.
Okay.
You, you know, you weren't getting any of your games.
Literally.
You know, you know, no, no one, no tech in in there.
There's a tech and demo, I think, in there actually.
But yeah.
But no, thank you, Rebecca.
I can't.
I'm just teasing.
I really appreciate it.
And.
I actually really like it more.
When I received games that I might not have bought.
Because it's easier to add them to the collection.
It's like the collect, you know, there's.
When you.
I get Christmas.
I asked my mom for stuff that I wouldn't necessarily buy.
Yeah.
You know, otherwise, you're just asking for.
You're just buying it for yourself.
You know, I'm saying.
Yes, I do.
I do.
You get it.
I got it, Joe.
What's new with you.
I've had whooping cough.
Since the last.
Before I even got the last five podcast.
But no code.
No.
No, not.
Literally whooping cough.
It's.
It's back.
I had.
I had Covid.
When I left New York, I immediately.
The first time I had Covid was a couple weeks before it broke.
And it was right.
When I came back from doing the pod live in New York.
And then the second time I got it was right.
When I came back from doing the.
Interesting.
How you took.
My opportunity to answer your question about how I'm doing with.
your state of affairs.
That was a long choice.
I'm saying I had COVID.
Yeah.
Maybe.
And if you think you didn't, did you get tested?
I did get tested.
Okay.
I didn't have COVID.
No, I've whooping cough.
That's what I have.
Okay.
I don't even cough.
I've coughed several times on the podcast here today alone.
I think they actually thought you were going to yell at me.
I mean, I'm definitely not here in whoops.
Well, it's on its way out.
But.
Excuse me.
So anyway, I've had, I had that.
I was really sick for a couple days.
And then the cough just kind of lingers.
It doesn't go away.
Right.
Um, you can't go around any kids or anything.
It's highly contagious.
Uh, and it's bad for kids.
So you couldn't be around kids either.
Let's be real.
Yeah.
Yes, the law.
Well, some Megan's lunch.
I don't fucking.
Pat.
I'm a little woozy today.
Okay.
A little foggy today.
But, um, the, uh, yeah.
So like I miss my godson's birthday, which kind of sucked.
Um, yeah, you know, I wasn't able to hang out with a friend of mine who just had a kid.
Um, you know, so that's, that's kind of the annoying part of it.
But.
Aside from that.
Pat.
Yes.
I've been on a local cholesterol diet.
I got diagnosed with high cholesterol.
Okay.
I've been eating a lot of vegetarian meals.
And, uh, if I do eat meat, it's something like this, like a turkey.
Or a fatty fish.
Was it crazy high?
Where were you at?
I was at one night.
No, I was at 194 at 200 is when they're like, you have to take medicine at 194.
They're like, look.
You don't have to take medicine.
But if you keep fucking around, we got to give you medicine.
So.
Up to you right now.
And I was like, let me try to do it the right way.
Uh -huh.
It was time for a change anyway.
I had to cut back on the booze and change the diet.
And I am dropping some weight, which feels good, you know, so.
Good.
Yeah, I'm off.
I'm off drinking and weed, uh, as of today.
Saying I'm doing a, uh, extended sober October.
But I might push it even further.
Just.
But I'm saying it right here.
Yeah, yeah.
No, you've said it many times on the air and we've seen how it goes.
Well, you know, I say it and then like, I get divorced, you know, and then I go, you know,
what?
Oh, just go a week.
Just see if you can make it a week.
You make it a week and make it another week.
You know, I'm doing our October and it's starting today.
I'm ready.
I'm not even nervous about it.
I know, but I'm just telling you, any therapist will tell you.
Hey, everything built to do this.
Every institution with get with abstaining tells you.
Don't do exactly what you're doing right now.
Just go the first week and then go.
I made it.
Now I'm going to go another week.
Well, I'm doing it.
All right.
I'm going.
What was the show one day at a time?
Was that about sobriety?
Yeah, go one day at a time.
That's all right.
Was that show about sobriety?
Uh, it was about trying to stay sane in this cookie.
Crazy world we live in.
Who was on it?
Joe, by the way,
still hasn't seen sopranos watching too close for comfort right now.
I didn't know you were going to blow up my movie quarter.
Oh, well, Joe, you can still talk about too close for comfort.
Uh, I, yeah, I will never see the sopranos.
And I like watching old sitcoms.
But even that's that weird.
I mean, that's a, that's a real rough one.
Well, I, listen, when I, when I say I'm watching it,
I put it on and fall asleep to it because it's like a good fall asleep show.
It's a terrible sitcom.
Are you laughing at all?
Once in a while,
Ted Knight does like a super Ted Knight thing and it's very funny.
Like there was a thing,
there was a plot line where his wife was reading like a 50 shades of gray type novel.
And he was like chastising her for reading it.
And then like finally, he picks it up and starts reading it when he's alone.
And he's, as he's reading it, he's going, he's going,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
So like, that's funny to me.
It is.
But those, those moments,
you'd be shocked at how few and far between they are.
It's very,
if I would have written that,
I would have had her reading this book,
and he's all pissed off about it.
But then she starts learning some new shit.
And she's like throwing down in the bedroom and we see it all.
She's Ted Knight just getting fucked.
She makes a joke about that.
Yeah.
And then they end the episode on a joke about how now he's interested in the book
and wants to make it a night to remember.
That's the last line of the thing.
But the plot of the episode has nothing to do with it.
It's not even,
it's not even a plot point.
The episode is about a completely different thing.
This is just like the opening and closing joke of the episode.
Right.
Okay.
Like, they don't go in any direction.
You think so.
So they did an episode where Monroe played by Jim J baller,
who was diagnosed with AIDS in the final season when they changed the name to the
Ted Knight show.
Always a strange move in the seventh season of the show.
Is that true?
That's when he was diagnosed as HIV positive.
Yeah.
He didn't come out with it until years later.
Probably because Ted Knight would have said,
get him off this set.
I don't know if Ted Knight was a homophobe,
but I assume he.
I don't know.
I don't think he was a homophobe,
but he was.
I definitely think he was a tight ass.
Sure.
They said he didn't really like Rodney Dangerfield on the set of candy shack.
Because they were like Rodney is kind of that guy and Ted Knight is kind of that guy.
And he just wasn't into it.
But.
But anyway, um, he.
So there's an episode where Monroe gets a computer and it's, you know,
it's the 80s.
So they used to do plots and everything where like.
Computers could do the impossible.
So like throughout the episode, Monroe's going like,
I hook the computer into the national weather satellite.
And you know, this is like pre nobody's got to own him at this, but nothing, you know.
Yeah.
Anyway, the first gag with the computer is Monroe is like,
I crunched all these numbers with the stock market and like,
and then I reviewed them with an analyst and this, this can't lose.
The stock can't lose.
And Ted and it's like, you know, you're an idiot.
And you can't trust a machine and whatever.
And then Monroe buys stock.
And, and, and it immediately goes up.
So then Ted night, of course, is like.
Give me 200 shares.
Give me to it, you know.
And, and you're like, here we go.
Here's, here's your plot.
This is, this is, we're off to the races.
And then.
Monroe, right after Ted night buys all the shares.
Monroe talks about how he, the program he used for the stocks was the same program he used to fit to crunch the finances for the household.
And all the finance numbers are wrong.
So it's like, it's like, Mrs. Rush, you spent $1 million last month.
And then he's like, this is the same.
I know it's correct.
It's the same program I used for the stocks.
So Ted night does like huge Ted night.
Right.
And he's like, so my stocks, you idiot.
Tell my stock.
And like, but you think that the joke is going to be that Monroe is saying the stocks are 275 apiece, meaning $2 .75.
And then because he used the program wrong, they're $275.
And then the plot will be Ted night just spent.
What's 200 times 372 or 275.
Towards, what are you serious?
It would be like $5 ,000 some dollars.
Right.
No, 50 ,000.
Wait, what is the, what is the math problem here?
What's $2 .75 times 100, $2 ,700.
And it's $27 .5.
No.
Yeah.
$2 times 100 is $200.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
Anyway, Jesus Christ.
Sorry, dude.
I'm something.
By the way, why are we doing math when discussing one random episode of because you think that because you think this is because I'm explaining to you what you think the plot is going to be.
Yeah.
He thinks he spent $200.
$400.
And he's watching this with two calculators and a visor.
The calculators both spilling out receipt paper out the back.
You can't make the numbers that up.
You think, you know, and then you think that the turn is going to be that he spent $4 ,000.
Right.
And then he's got to get the money back, but he can't get it back.
So now he's in the stock market and the whole episode is the up and down.
It's been right to sell for less based on the one show.
Yeah.
And that's not it.
It's just he sells the stock immediately.
And then they move on to another hair brain computer scenario.
It's just not a good show.
And he's.
What is he?
He's the dad of Jim J. Bullock.
No.
Ted Knight is a cartoonist.
Who is the.
He's a super job for a sitcom.
They've done it a million times.
We can't see the drawings.
Cosmic cow is the car the character he draws.
He is the patriarch of the family.
He lives with his wife in a duplex.
And he owns both.
And then his daughters rent out an apartment in the other side.
Okay.
Is he gay on the show?
No.
He just a sexual.
I think he goes out with women once in a while.
I think if I'm not mistaken.
But is Jim.
I mean, is Ted Knight, like calling him a fruit and stuff?
Or is it not three company stuff?
He's raised.
No.
That was that was three company.
Yeah.
But three three company was like a sex show.
Like this is a.
This is a.
Like family friendly a sitcom as you can get.
From that time period.
It's terrible.
It's not a good show.
Yeah.
But it goes to show you what a different world we lived in.
Ted Knight was a god damn celebrity, dude.
And like all he ever did was Mary Tyler Moore.
This and catty shack.
But like his celebrity was so strong from Mary Tyler Moore.
This fucking show ran five seasons.
And then when it was ailing in the sixth season, they reworked the thing.
And they they boot the two daughters.
How fucked up is that?
They were on five seasons as regulars.
And they just dropped them from the show in the sixth season.
And.
And then him.
His wife, Muriel walks in and goes, well, my daughters are dead.
And they just go on with the show.
Yeah.
And then so like in the last season, him, his wife, Muriel and Monroe,
for some reason, because because he was like the herbal.
They moved to another city.
And he gets a new job.
Yeah.
And they rename it the Ted Knight show.
But then in syndication, they changed it back to two clothes for company.
It's a mess.
Yeah.
And then it only got canceled because he died.
Hard attack.
Uh, he looks like a heart attack.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, he's like actually pretty fit.
And he does a lot of physical stuff.
Okay.
It's kind of.
He just looked like a guy who enjoyed a good tumbler of scotch at the end of the morning.
Right.
Yeah.
I think he was a real square man.
Okay.
I think he was like.
I think he's the judge from Cadyshire.
I think that's what his deal.
Yeah.
Like, you know, he likes to get, he likes a game of golf.
Sure.
You know, quite even get home with some cocoa and the wife on Saturday.
You know, that kind of thing.
That's the vibes I get.
All right.
Anyway, it's a bad show.
Well, find those sitcoms comforting.
Joe has plunged us into the movie corner.
And I will just take it from there.
Uh, I'm going to hold off on Pearl.
Because I think Joe and I are going to do Pearl.
But I rewatched heavy month.
By the way.
Heavy.
A lot of work coming up.
Dude.
The monsters.
Pearl.
Hell razor.
We could do clerks three.
Blonde.
Just came out.
This NC 17.
Yeah.
The thing that moment.
Row.
The great.
It was about.
But row.
Yeah.
Like a SNL sketch that no one gets.
Or last.
Put all about Jim.
Jet.
On row.
Uh, I.
So you know what I rewatched was top five.
Not a good film.
I disagree.
Wow.
I think it is maybe.
And this is very faint praise indeed.
But it might be Chris Rock's best as a writer director.
I mean, there's not a lot of competition.
I think it works as a film.
It's funny.
There's really funny cameos.
From a lot of funny comedy folks.
I don't know.
I kind of dug it.
I love the scene.
The strip club scene at the end with all the cameos is super funny.
And then you got Jerry Seinfeld talking to a giant ass stripper.
And he's accusing her of stealing his money.
To about her.
And then she goes.
Look at me.
I'm wearing a G string.
Where would I.
Where would I put your money?
And he goes.
Do I have to say it?
A laugh for me that got a rewind.
Do I.
Very, very funny.
I don't know.
I had some laughs.
It was pleasant.
It might just be missing comedy in general.
But like.
I like Rosario Dawson.
I like Chris Rock.
Yeah.
I like.
JB smooth.
You know.
There is a very funny extended sequence where Cedric the entertainer plays.
Like the guy who picks you up at the airport when you're going to do stand up.
And he's like anybody in Florida, you know, you need anything in Florida.
You call me on the man as named Jazzy D.
And he's, you know, the costumes funny.
Cedric's usually pretty family friendly.
And this is him being like a sleaze.
Then Chris Rock is having sex with these two women.
And then one of whom is Haley from living Biblically great to see her.
Pretty much nude.
Not great to see her.
Period.
Pretty much nude.
Who was Haley on living Biblically?
Haley was the girl got stuck in an elevator with with Tony Rock.
I don't remember because I was dropped from the series, but.
She was very, very funny.
She played like kind of a psycho ex.
Okay.
But um.
Yeah, this.
Chris Rock is having sex with the two women.
That said, Rick set up.
But then Cedric comes walking in to join them.
And then you got like Cedric getting double blown by that.
It's all just very funny.
My favorite.
Line of the Cedric beat is he's acting like he's the cool guy in town.
And he can get you whatever you need.
And he's got the hook up.
And then he's leaving Chris Rock's hotel room.
He sees that he's got wooden hangers in the in the closet.
And he's like, look at you with the wooden hangers.
Look at you.
Could I could I take a couple of these?
And he leans over and he goes,
oh, they got them locked up there.
They're onto your boy.
They got the hangers locked up and walks out.
Very, very funny bit.
I love set of the entertainer in the movie.
I don't know.
I like the film.
It made me laugh.
Top five.
Check it out.
I'll revisit it.
I.
I remember not liking it that much.
But now that you're saying all these parts.
I'm remembering.
Oh, wait.
No, I think I did actually like that movie.
There's funny shit.
I mean, especially compared to.
Comedy of the last several years, you know.
Yeah, I mean, that's got a big part to do with it.
You know, it's.
It's.
It might not have stood out as super great at the time,
but it seems pretty funny when you watch it now.
Well, speaking of comedy series,
I'll stay on TV is my theme for the for the corner today.
I.
I finally.
I didn't finish it.
But I finally have watched dark.
Dark.
Garth.
Marangi's dark place.
Loved it.
Um.
It's okay.
It's not great.
Uh.
It's funny.
It's not not funny.
It's not not well done.
It's not not well.
I mean, that crew.
You just you can only get so bad with that crew.
Yeah.
Um.
I think though it does itself a great disservice.
Okay.
Yeah, and hopefully this by showing so much of the episodes
of the fake show.
The funny parts.
The funniest parts or the commentary?
Yeah.
Like watching them talk.
So.
Like when it's showing like,
I you're being like being like,
it wouldn't be done today,
you know, like and all that stuff,
like,
like, you know, like, to me, that is the funniest stuff him talking about how nobody would
be able to handle how intense this show is, of course, that's, that's the funniest.
And then like, when it cuts to Matt Berry, and he's like, the bloke couldn't remember
a line.
Yeah.
He'd act across from a peach half on half days, like, like all that stuff is the funniest
stuff.
And they show so little of it.
Yeah.
Um, the show, the part of the fake show is funny.
The one thing I don't like, though, is they kind of, as, as we say in the biz, Pat, they
joke the joke a little too much, like, it'll be like, you're already doing like a spoof
of something.
So just like, let it be the spoof, but then you're putting jokes into the dialogue of the
spoof.
And you're like, yeah, but a guy writing something like this wouldn't put that joke into it.
He would just write a really bad show.
So it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it bites off of, it takes a pretty big bite, um, and,
and some big swings.
But obviously it's, it's, it's a, it's a good show.
I just wanted it.
I think I, I think I was just disappointed because I thought it was going to be all that mock
humanery talking heads thing.
And it's very, very little of that.
But, um, my guy, but there are some touches in it that are so fucking funny, man, like, like,
the fact that, um, Matt Berry's voice is completely dubbed for no good reason, like they
do in a lot of those shows, those old horror shows, um, I took the, I took that as being funny
because he has such an excellent voice.
I think the joke there is like, why would you disguise this man's amazing voice?
Well, it is his, with his own voice, though.
Yeah, that's, that's what's funny about me.
It's like those, it's like those 70s, like hammer horror movies, like, it's not
just that you see it a lot in Italian horror from the 70s and 80s.
It's like somebody is speaking English in the movie and they're redubbed in English with
their own voice.
It's very odd, but, um, that was funny.
My favorite joke and the whole thing, though, is in the opening credits of each episode,
when it'll say like music, music by, so and so, and then it'll say based on tunes,
originally whistled by Garth Marine, he's such an ego maniac, like every part of it,
yeah, stick with it, stick with it.
I mean, I like it.
I don't dislike it.
It's whatever, six episodes or whatever.
I thought it was really funny, but, you know, it's, it's no toast to London, it's no Alan
Partridge, but it's very fun.
I rewatched, oh, by the way, real quick, did you know, in watching this, I went and looked
for toast of how toast of Tinseltown, which is the newest season of toast, cannot wait.
Yeah.
London.
No, cannot wait.
Guess what, babe, it's been out for like a year or you just can't get it over, you can't
get it here.
Well, that's always the case.
It's, I mean, nothing.
It's not even on Britbox.
I subscribed to Britbox and so on that either.
That's always the case with British show.
You just got to wait till it randomly pops up.
I, I watched the first season of back.
The peep show guys show, and then I watched the second season like eight years later, and
I had no idea what was happening.
So the second season is out.
We can see that because I still have seen the second season.
Yeah, no, they're on Amazon, you might have to pay for it.
I, you know, actually, I watched back when I got AMC plus to watch the end of Better Call
Saul.
They weirdly had both seasons back.
Okay.
Anyway, I rewatched just friends.
I was just, I don't know, looking for something dumb to occupy the time, and I remembered
it being kind of funny, and it is kind of funny.
It's boy, for, to show you what people found funny, this came out in 2005.
So like, yeah, well, I guess that's almost 20 years ago, which is so disturbing to me seriously.
Oh, yeah.
But this thing kicks off with Ryan Reynolds in a fat suit, fat makeup.
He was, you know, he was fat in high school, so nobody ever liked him or whatever.
I guess they were doing this pretty recently with the rock too and central intelligence, not
that long ago.
But there's a lot of jokes about him being fat.
He's in love with Amy Smart.
Amy Smart played the object of teenage boys desire for 15 years.
She was the love interest in so many college comedies, road trip.
And I like her and she's funny and certainly a likable actress.
It's just amazing.
The career she had, Starsky and Hutch, rat race, outside providence, but actually hanging
in there, I don't know that she really acts.
Last time I saw her was in crank and I love crank, but she, maybe she just had kids or something.
I don't know.
I like Amy Smart.
Ryan Reynolds in this is funny.
Every line Ryan Reynolds delivers, he's doing it like Chandler on cocaine like it's Ace
Ventura acting.
And I guess he's toned that down a little bit, but he's funny in it.
Julie Haggardy is in it, who I always love as his mom, who's, oh, oh, from Airplane.
Julie Haggard.
Yeah.
Okay.
Loss in America.
Oh, yeah.
Anna Ferris is very funny in it as like a Britney Spears type.
It's a very convoluted film.
He plays a guy who gets attractive and makes some money when he gets older and then goes
back home with Britney Spears because he's a music producer or something.
It's very convoluted.
But there's a lot of wear.
I remember this and he's like dating her, they get married and then he meets the other
girl, right?
No marriage.
Oh.
There's no marriage.
Okay.
But the plots they would have in this thing, like the amount of times I used to try to like
sell movies during this time, they just wanted a big comedy book like Good Luck Chuck.
The premise was he's the guy who after you date him, the next person you meet is your husband
or is your life partner.
That was a game cook movie.
If you had some stupid hook like that, that would be your movie.
So in this movie, the amount of times everyone's like, oh, no, bro, bro, did you wind up back
in the friend zone again?
It's like all that just desperation where they just don't trust the movie to just be a movie.
There has to be some big book.
That's what ultimately ruins just friends, but it's also the kind of movie where like if
somebody slips and falls, it goes, boy, it's very broad, but the stuff in it that works
and is funny, it's pretty funny, so they're pretty good comedy.
I'd like to just break down me and Pat's friendship in a nutshell.
Yes.
And just by using the just friends, the text exchange we had, yeah, Pat texts me watching
just friends, certainly plenty to say there.
Yeah.
He said, hey, man, you usually can't go wrong with Reynolds.
He's always pretty funny, supportive with Pat due to me, Joe watches the too close for
comfort, won't watch the sopranos.
It's just you just you just hurt me.
Why can't you support me when I watch a bad off the kindness want you to spend your time
better?
Just friends is 95 minutes.
You're watching a hundred and twenty six episodes of people's for comfort.
You want to hear something dark?
I've gone to sleep, woken up eight hours later, and it's still going like God knows what
I'm absorbing as I sleep, but excuse me.
But the I was wrong about the marriage, but I am right about correct.
He's like going out with Anna Ferris, and then he falls for Amy Smart, right?
Or no, he's not dating Anna Ferris.
He he's kind of like babysitting her.
Oh, okay.
That's what.
But she thinks they're together because she's playing a psychopath.
I don't know.
Okay.
It's probably last on my list for today.
Thank you.
Universe.
Jesus.
Thank you.
Buddha.
A lot.
Thank you.
Whoever it is, you.
When good blessings happen.
Finally, we have another good Star Wars TV show.
Star Wars and or is excellent.
It is an excellent show.
I know I praised Boba Fett in the past.
But it was up and down.
The further I get away from it, the more I kind of realize that.
Obi -Wan was, you know, more or less.
And it's decent times where the times when it wasn't being a complete train wreck.
Andor is awesome.
It's everything.
Fans love about Star Wars.
It's serious.
The stakes are high.
The robots and aliens talking robot and alien language.
Everybody else is English.
It's like, this is what we're here for people.
There's no dumb comedy in it.
It's Star Wars, man.
It's like it's awesome.
It's just so well done with a really impeccable cast.
That was the star of Andor.
The guy from Narcos.
Okay.
I forget his name.
I want to say Diego Luna.
Well, Diego Luna may have been on it.
Let me check.
Do scars guards in it.
You're right.
Diego Luna.
Dad scars guards in it.
He's awesome.
It's just awesome.
And there's no thank God.
Fucking cameos of fucking comedians.
And like gags and Joe.
It's like it's a God damn show that takes itself seriously.
It's awesome.
And has Andor been mentioned before on in the Star Wars world.
I know Andor has.
Andor is the is Cassie and Andor.
That's his name.
That's Diego Luna's character's name.
He was the character.
He was the main.
He's the male lead in Rogue One.
So these this series is all the events that lead up to Rogue One.
Rogue One is the attack on the Death Star to get the plans.
So they can blow it up in a new hope.
This is how basically his character joins the rebellion.
I had no interest in it.
I was like, I don't care.
Yeah.
It's going to be drawing boring.
And then I was like, wow, I'm very wrong.
It is really, really good.
Almost plays like a fucking.
Plays like an almost like a Jack Ryan series or something.
It's very like spy espionage.
It's fun.
It's cool.
It's a good show.
All right.
I saw.
It's really bummed me out.
The 40th anniversary.
A poltergeist.
We're getting to this age now that jaws was the fucking 50th anniversary.
Like a tragedy.
Poltergeist remains my favorite horror movie.
It just does.
I don't remember the last time it came up on the show, but we were like,
maybe it was you was like, I bet if you watch it again, you disagree.
No, I watch it all the time.
And it's my favorite.
Brought our friend Lizzie to go see it.
She'd never seen it.
She was very touched by it.
She was worried she was going to be scared, but she was very moved.
She's because she's into spirituality and the afterlife and all that.
I just love the film.
I can't get enough of it.
I think it really does boil down to spending that extra time with Craig T.
I think it's going to be in Joe Beth Wilson and the family and giving a shit about them.
The end of the story.
That's what that's what we're missing for modern horror and modern movies in general.
I'll tell you what else we're missing.
Yes.
I experienced something in central park the other night.
Sounds like it's going to take place behind a bush, but it doesn't.
Yeah.
It just brought me back to like.
This is I remember this.
I remember this kind of fun chaos.
Out in the world.
I went to the.
Global citizen festival.
I only went to see Metallica play a bunch of people played.
I unfortunately had to see what is global citizen.
What does that mean?
It's like a festival where they raise awareness for humane causes.
You know,
Okay.
Anything do less than raising awareness.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, wait.
People are suffering somewhere.
Cool. All right.
Let's go watch Metallica.
It's yeah, it's like they raised money, I guess, too.
You know, so it's, you know, it's one of those things. But anyway.
I had to see Mame skin, which was just horrific.
What are they?
It's, it's the most comprised thing I've ever seen since new kids on the block.
And their biggest song is a cover that.
You.
That's a cover.
They have another song that's big.
That's like on every Instagram video.
Okay.
So terrible.
They're it. No, that song's actually tolerable.
But I mean, they're just so they're all wearing the high heel boots.
And every, you know, everybody's perfectly manicured and perfectly tattooed.
And they all do their moves.
It's just, they just suck.
Yeah.
Anyway, had to see them before Metallica.
There was a bunch of other people that performed that day.
But we went late.
So.
Because the goal was to see Metallica.
So anyway.
Somebody gets it in their head that that people witness in Metallica want to hear Nancy Pelosi speak.
This made national news.
Uh -huh.
She goes on stage.
And what's the deal?
She get big fake boobs Nancy Pelosi.
I don't know.
It's odd.
But she did, right?
It's like, I keep seeing that disgust.
And I'm like, I think she has huge tits.
But it just became a big story.
And then when you see her now, she's got like Dolly Parton's.
I think she got fake jugs now.
And Muzzle.
I don't care.
But yeah, I don't give a shit.
Yeah, I'd like to see him.
Maybe she got him for the Metallica concert.
She was like, maybe I'll flash the boys and they'll think I'm fun.
Dude.
So she gets booed.
Yeah.
Then they play a video of.
They play a video of.
COVID and all the damage COVID did.
And everybody that's died from COVID.
Then they play a video of president.
Sorry for the siren.
Yeah.
Let's get it loud as humanly possible.
Please.
Jesus Christ.
You got to get out of the city for a while starting to get to me.
Then they played a video of Joe Biden's wife talking about all the good work they've done.
That all.
That Metallica takes the stage.
Sure.
They open with creeping death.
A song about the plague.
That has a breakdown where the chant is die.
And the entire audience in Central Park.
Tens of thousands of people were chanting die in unison to Metallica.
Minutes after they played the COVID video.
Of how many people died.
It was nuts.
It was awesome.
I'm not making any sort of political statement.
I loved the chaos of it all.
I loved seeing a politician get booed.
I loved seeing Metallica open with that song without any worry of like,
is this going to strike the wrong chord with anybody?
Uh -huh.
Maybe they opened with it because they were like, hey, we sing songs about the plague.
You know, like I don't fucking know, but the point is is I was like, yes.
This.
This is what it used to be.
Yeah.
Like the squares would get booed at the rock show.
And then the metal band would come out and play the song that wasn't really appropriate for them to play.
Yeah.
Everybody just got into the spirit of it.
Like, I just don't remember the last time I've witnessed anything like that.
Where agenda was so completely separated from emotional enjoyment.
You know, right.
And it was just awesome.
It was just an awesome, awesome experience.
Uh, and they still brought the heat Metallica.
Oh, yeah.
I've only seen them once.
I saw them open for Stevie Wonder.
Just a while.
Even it was an outside lands that it was a festival.
So, okay.
But, uh, yeah, they were great.
I actually just started listening to, I was listening to kill them all the other day and stuff.
And I'm like, yeah, I like this shit.
It took a long time.
But I like it now.
They're awesome.
Yeah.
You got a, you got a lot of fun stuff to delve into.
Anyway, folks.
We come now to the main topic of discussion.
The show.
Let me just check really quick.
I don't think I had a.
What the hell do they do with my phone?
Oh, uh, I don't think I had a scary stuff or anything for today.
Or for this episode.
They just want to make sure.
No.
Okay.
Oh, well, this is an interesting news.
I go real quick.
Yeah.
Uh.
I hate to break it to you.
But Jonathan Lipnicki.
Uh -oh.
Is.
Uh, has announced that he's.
Taking a career hiatus from acting.
Oh, hiatus.
When did he announce this?
1997.
Uh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I missed.
This isn't as good as I thought.
I missed the headline was misleading.
The story is he said I wasn't a very good actor for a very long time.
And that led to a long break from acting for me.
That's what it was.
Oh, that sucks.
So.
Now he thinks.
Uh, I didn't get that far.
Okay.
So.
But, uh, god damn it.
I thought that was going to be really funny.
And then it just wasn't.
Oh, well.
Uh, folks today we're talking about.
And this is a little touchy for me because I'm friends with two of the guys in this fucking movie.
Don't worry.
Darling.
Who are you friends with?
Well, there are two stand -up comedians in the film, Pat.
Your friends with Nick Croll?
Never heard you mention them.
Nick and I did comedy in the city together.
Yes.
As an old pal.
Uh, and as a small role in the field.
Seaf Ali is also in this.
Who's a goose.
I'm actually better friends with.
Okay.
He's in everything.
Uh, he's an old.
Everything.
Yeah.
Good kid.
Not see the guy in something.
Uh, but I saw him.
Actually, the day I saw Don't really worry.
Darling.
I stepped off stage at the stand.
And he was standing there.
And I go, Hey, what brings you to town?
And he goes, I'm here for the premiere of Don't Worry Darling.
I go, Ah, I just saw it today.
You were one of the only things I enjoyed about it.
Who falls it aside?
Why is it policy?
Why is that policy?
Yeah.
He doesn't want to hear that.
Right.
The fucking movie.
But he doesn't want to hear that.
He was fine.
It was fine.
I don't live in your little fucking.
Suck each other off fake paradise.
No, you don't.
You don't got to do that.
But you don't got to say, I hated the movie.
I didn't say that.
I said, you were the one of the only things I enjoyed about it.
And I said, and I will say this about the film.
And I stand by this.
Well, wait, I have two things to say, actually.
I stand by this.
The day I saw it.
Yes.
You're going to be shocked by something about to say.
The day I saw it, my take was this.
And I said, I talked to a see for a while about this.
And I was saying.
I felt like.
Way too much was jammed into the third act.
I felt like that wasn't the writers fault or Olivia Wilde's fault.
I felt like I could see the executive notes on the screen.
And I felt like they made them.
Like shove all this bullshit into the third act.
Because it was 10 ticks too close to wanting to be an Oscar nominated film.
If they had moved 10 ticks in the other direction and just embraced it as horror.
That thing could have had the most fucking dire ending on it.
Probably the original ending.
I'm assuming.
No bullshit hope or anything like that.
It could have just been what it the fuck it was for the first two acts of the movie.
And I and through the first two acts of the movie.
I felt that.
It was making it was made a statement.
The statement was a bit hackneyed.
I don't mean the statement on gender is hackneyed.
I just mean the way in which they were making the statement was.
We've seen this before.
We've seen the like surreal reality that's based on the 50s.
That's a commentary on the way women are treated.
We've seen that before a few times.
So this so the execution of the statement was a bit stale but.
I thought for the most part it was pretty well done.
I thought it was all very well acted and I thought that.
I was interested enough with everything going on to see what was happening.
And then in the third act comes your twist which you know is coming eventually.
And the twist was palatable enough.
But they didn't let the twist just stand on its own two feet.
It was the twist.
And then it was more stuff.
And then it was a variation of the twist.
And then it was a chasing.
And it was a hopeful ending.
And there was one thing after the next.
And this is one of the.
I talked him for like an hour about the movie and I was very respectful.
I wasn't really shitting on it.
But I was I was really like.
Wrapped up in this third act and I said you know one thing that was bothering me in the third act was.
So so spoiler alert everybody.
The big reveal and don't worry darling is that.
Florence pew is actually.
Is is married to Harry styles but you find out.
There are a couple in action in our reality.
And that in our reality, he their marriage is very bad.
And he against her will.
Subjected her into this virtual reality program that they both live in now where they actually have a picture perfect 1950s marriage.
The problem is is she's too strong willed and she's too independent.
And she she realizes what's going on.
And she discovers that that's what's happening.
So.
So basically what you're faced with is this entire movie this reality they've been living in is is a virtual reality.
One of the thing my biggest problem with this movie is.
Why.
Did Chris pines character who created this reality.
Allow for the dragon to be missing so many scales for the arrow to get shot into.
It's like there are things built into his virtual world that will allow the world to be destroyed.
If someone chooses to do so, why would you do that?
You wouldn't do that.
You just wouldn't do that.
No clue.
I.
I found the movie very obvious.
I think that like what you're saying about it being studio notes.
Olivia wild after book smart would probably get the director's cut treatment.
You know, you probably get that do whatever you want.
Also, I just don't want to stand up for Olivia wild for some reason, but I mean.
This movie to me, it's it is a valley of the dolls.
It is steppered wives.
It is a lot of these kind of movies we've seen before.
Sure.
Not saying you can't update it.
It's it's a very strong premise.
Because you can read so much into it, especially with what's going on today with women's health.
With the Supreme Court, et cetera, there's a lot to be said here.
I just don't think it's said it very well.
This is not like, you know, I think what happened was and.
You know, it's it does suck because if this was just some faceless director, we wouldn't be discussing her probably.
But I think that you get a book smart, which is a above average team comedy.
Fine.
But then you get this like, oh, she must be able to do everything now.
That's Hollywood.
That's the way Hollywood sees it.
You do one hit.
They're like, she can do anything.
I would be is going for like.
Meaning that it does not it's not in control of the script is not smart enough.
Or funny enough or dark enough or interestingly or interestingly enough.
It just kind of sits there.
It was done in Palm Springs.
You know, I like Palm Springs.
I like how it looks.
It was clearly very influenced by like Edward Siserhands is my thinking the whole everyone going to work at the same time and everybody's long looking.
I'm so tired.
I'm going to interject.
I'm so tired of that shit.
I'm so tired of that.
This movie does a lot of that.
There's a lot of that hacky.
Look, it's a it's a routine.
You know, that if I see one more fucking movie with an overhead shot of breakfast being prepared in in jump cut steps.
Yeah.
To symbolize that the routine of it.
I just can't anymore.
I'm like, come on, man with this shit.
It all felt super familiar.
I think them going for those.
For me, when you see them in the present day as like,
it's just quick flashes of them as a couple in the present day.
That stuff got laughs from the audience I saw it with.
I don't think they earned that really.
I think Chris Pine is a really strong actor.
And I think he would make a great villain.
But I just didn't feel they net like like what you're saying.
He let too much go.
He weirdly because.
The movie has to kind of hide its cards a little bit.
But he's not super menacing really.
It just kind of to me, everything just kind of sat there until the end.
And then they tried to resolve everything too quickly.
And it didn't work.
You know, I really did not like the film.
That's interesting because I thought they tried to resolve it too quickly when they when I thought the first ending was happening.
Yeah.
Then by the time the actual ending happening, I was literally like.
I was literally like shifting in my seat like come on.
Yes.
Like my god, we need a seven minute chase through the desert right now.
Like what?
It's just by the way TV shows are now a movies are now doing with virtual reality.
What we were just making fun of too close for comfort doing in the eighties with computers.
Yeah, you can't do that with virtual reality.
Yeah, virtual reality doesn't look real.
It looks extraordinarily fake.
In fact, it looks.
Leagues behind would even a PS5's graphics would look like.
Right.
Or even a PS4 or even even a PS3 at times.
Like.
It's not this exponential you can do anything you want in any second thing.
It's not like it's just all bullshit.
So it's like.
I'm kind of getting tired of these shows coming out in these movies that are supposed to be very rooted in our world.
But then.
Take something that is part of our world.
And.
And exploited in a way that is just completely unbelievable.
Like 100%.
And.
People can say.
Joe Jesus Christ.
It's a sci fi movie or Joe Jesus Christ.
It's.
It's the point.
It's fake.
What.
Okay.
But.
It's not fake.
It's making a very.
It's making a very real commentary.
Yeah.
It's making a very real statement and it's based in a very real world.
Ours.
Right.
So, so.
Make.
Make it sort of believable.
Then.
That everybody can have a seven minute chase scene through the desert.
It's just stupid.
Also, well, yeah, I guess you couldn't see what another person's doing.
And I got that, nevermind.
But like, so, you know, I don't know.
I thought just to speak to what you were saying, Pat,
about it's making a statement.
It's not in control.
It's not smart enough.
I don't think it's making that smart of a statement.
Yeah.
I think it's it.
I think it's a valid statement.
It's not making it well.
Like she kept talking about how this movie is all about female pleasure.
We don't see, well, if you wild did, we don't see any men come in this movie.
It's all about female pleasure.
Shouldn't we shouldn't it be about male pleasure?
If they're forcing you into a alternate reality world against your wishes against.
She shouldn't it be about the man coming?
She tried to make what she tried to do.
She tried to make a movie that was about the patriarchy, patriarchy,
that also made you question, but look what the woman gets out of it.
Yeah.
So you'd feel conflicted and it does none of that.
No.
Every man in the movie is showinistic.
It's obvious from the beginning of the movie.
Aside from the fact that they all like love to make their wives come for whatever reason.
But it's all very obvious from the beginning.
There's a there's a sick, sick toxic amount of showvinism going on in this place.
Yeah.
You know, and and and and and basically because it bites off so much more than it can chew.
So it reduces it's the statement of the movie to to again, in my opinion,
a very tight one that we're all very aware of.
Women are mistreated by men.
Well, yes, we know.
That's terrible.
So tell me something about that.
Take me on a journey about that.
Right.
This doesn't do any of that.
This just shows that a guy can be so selfish.
He would put his wife into a coma.
So she can like cook him eggs.
And yeah, and why what was the deal?
Like he was a doctor.
What was her issue with him?
You know, like what why was their marriage so unhappy that he had to do this?
It was just simply he lost his job, which they mentioned very briefly.
Oh, okay, I miss that.
She he lost his job.
He's kind of a fuck up.
They allude to that.
Yeah.
She's a doctor.
She works a third.
She works 30 hours shifts as an ER doctor.
Uh -huh.
He wants her to be in his life more.
She's not receptive or able to because of her job.
Uh -huh.
She loves her job and puts her job first.
He's an asshole.
He's going to do this to her.
Gotcha.
I mean, the the movie's biggest issue by far is Harry Styles,
who is about as commanding a screen presence as Zach Efram.
He's a nothing.
And, you know, I think he was bad.
I didn't think he was bad.
I thought he sucked.
He brought nothing to the table and maybe it's because I was thinking of what Shia LaBuff would have brought.
And that would have been intense.
It would have been intense.
Now, do I think that a guy who's shooting dogs and beat women should continue to work?
No, I don't.
But I do think we could have found a better actor than Harry Styles here.
I just, I got nothing out of it.
What was your take on the red plane, Joe?
I have no idea.
No idea here.
Again, it was, it was another thing that the writer or the director or both of them injected into this movie
because they thought it would be this think moment.
Yeah.
And guys, I'm sorry.
I know book smart is a good movie and it's funny, but let's call spades, spades here.
That's also an extremely derivative movie.
It is, it is a point by point remake of super bad.
I mean, for critics, like Olivia Wilde, like this is kind of her bag, I guess, is, you know, she's good at observing and mimicking, which is what a lot of directors nowadays do.
Yes.
I don't think there's a lot there for original vision.
I didn't think Florence Pugh was great.
I thought Crowell was great.
I enjoyed, I enjoyed seeing him in a darker role.
Olivia Wilde was, was, was very good in it.
Yeah, Chris, Chris Pine.
I could take her leave, Chris Pine.
I kind of feel like he's, I don't know.
I like him, but I just never give a shit.
Like, I'm like, oh, he's here.
Okay, cool.
Yeah.
I mean, it is hard to care about a guy who's like more beautiful than most women, but he is playing that kind of a guy.
So I didn't really mind it.
But as I talked about on the live show, in the case of book smart and the case of this movie, there was a lot of behind the scenes about who gets the writing credit.
And I think that Olivia Wilde is trying, it's like, being a director is not enough.
She wants to be the writer of things as well.
But I think the script is what really fucks this movie.
A friend of mine was talking to me about how the Truman show works because we know right off the bat what's going on.
And we're going through this adventure with Jim Carey.
This movie waits on the twist for so long that there's really no tension generated.
The tension's kind of coming from what's happening, but we don't care enough.
And we also kind of guess it from watching the trailer.
I, I didn't guess the, I didn't guess the exact twist.
Yeah.
Oh, it was, oh, it's virtual reality.
No, no, I did kind of think throughout the movie.
This is going to be like the village.
They're going to be like, you're, they're going to leave.
And there's going to be this our world right over there, which is basically the same.
It was what it is.
It's just instead of a secluded, you know, environment.
It's, it's a virtual reality one.
But like the look, this all said.
This is the part that I said at the beginning.
I was like, you're going to be shocked to hear this.
I don't necessarily think it's a bad movie.
I just think it's a kind of who cares movie.
I don't think it deserves the, the attack it's getting.
I mean, that's a person that's clearly vendetta shit with critics and Olivia Wilde or whatever.
But like, I don't think it's a bad movie.
I don't think I think it's like a C minus.
It's like, yeah, like who cares?
Like it's kind of a lazy black mirror episode.
Yeah, I saw it called white mirror, which was kind of funny.
I mean, there, there are like randomly two black people in this that I heard were essentially cut out of the movie.
And it's a very white.
It's a very, but that's, it doesn't really tackle the issues.
It brings up is my main issue.
I think when you say a C minus, it's an average movie.
I agree with you with the C minus.
But to me, a C minus is a bad move.
There should have been.
There should have been dialogue in this thing.
Yeah, it was, it's, it's so, it's so shortsighted.
That the, that the rationalization dialogue only goes as far as Chris Pine is a good man.
He provides for us.
Yeah, don't ask any questions.
That's just so lazy and so shortsighted.
There should have been stuff in here where he was going look around.
Don't you see all races living equally?
Look around, like you know what I mean?
It should have been so much more sinister.
Yeah, that would have been right.
Yeah, playing on and and deepened him.
He's got sort of a, you know, not a less of a one note villain thing.
That would have been a good addition to the script for sure.
And, and the whole thing too, where he's like,
I've been waiting for someone like you, someone to challenge me.
Yeah.
That was never followed through on.
Also, why would you want that if you, if your whole goal is to not be challenged,
which they hammer home in every scene.
Why would you want that?
But okay, I've been waiting for someone like you to challenge me.
So then where is our scene where the evil villain boss kills his wife and goes to pew and
I said, you're the queen.
Where is the, the, you know, Vader seducing Luke to the dark side and will rule the galaxy together part.
That should have been in there.
But instead, no, the wife kills him.
And Chris Pines wife kills him and then goes, it's my turn now.
And it's like, okay, man, well, you're just doing like a girl power move at the expense of your story here.
There, there's no temptation in that.
There's no seduction in that.
No.
It's just, it's just, you're just giving the female character a leg up because you.
And, and, and she's awful.
Like she's not even doing it for the right reason.
So then it's going against the credo of the movie.
It's just a mess.
It's just kind of a mess when it, when it comes to what it's trying to say and how it's trying to say it.
After I read the, the wiki on it, I, I was kind of turned on to a lot of pages that just asked.
What is going on with some of these plot holes and their big ones?
So this one I'm going to read to you now, where is Jack Harry Styles going all day when he's at work?
He tells Alice he has to leave every day just to make enough money to keep them in the simulation.
But I thought their whole issue beforehand was that he was unemployed.
Where did he get a job?
Does he work for Chris Pine?
Why would you ever give up your girlfriend's doctor salary just so she can hand you a drink at the end of the day?
My take.
My take on that was this is designed for men that are losers that feel it's not fair.
Again, it's for in cells.
Make this statement in the statement is never made.
It's not even insinuated.
Man are angry about the shift in society where women now could have the upper hand.
That's never said.
It's never said it's never even hinted towards.
It's literally just supposed to be this guy is mad that his wife is outdoing him.
Yeah.
Like and he loves her so much that he's selfish.
I mean, I would have loved to see him with that where he's pleading about how much he loves her.
Right.
Again, I think you kind of get that in in the virtual thing.
And then he's dead, but he's not dead.
And then and then his ghost coming up to her before she exits the simulation.
Yeah.
I didn't understand that.
Like no.
No.
Yeah.
It's just it's a movie that needed another couple drafts or something.
But I think the elements are in place for a better movie.
It doesn't really coalesce.
I think Joe liked it slightly more than me, but I mean, this is just a very skippable movie that has a pretty obvious point to make.
And doesn't land it very well.
So it's just kind of a misfire for me.
I forgot.
I have a third friend of the movie.
Caper Lance and it as well.
She's very good.
And she's known like Caper Lance.
She was.
Yeah.
Her and Croll are great in the film.
I thought that not much of the film.
No.
I thought that I thought that they had a lot of really, really immense talent on the screen.
And it was kind of wasted.
I didn't.
Man, I was dying to.
But I didn't.
I didn't ask.
I'll see if when I was talking to I didn't get into like, so look, so what's up, dude?
Yeah.
I didn't do any of that.
They just talked about the movie.
Yeah.
She just had like 40 people.
I'm not.
I don't know if she did this, but probably 40 people that worked in the movie just released a statement
that there was no problems on the set of the film.
It's like guys.
Let it go.
Like.
Yeah.
These sets have problems all the fucking time.
Well, apparently pews beef was that her and styles were disappearing all the time.
Yeah.
Right.
Which is.
Not cool.
But I mean, at least it's like, but even that, it's like.
Oh, so she was jerking off at work.
Like, you know what I mean?
Right.
She was fucking off.
And we will never know.
Okay.
That Olivia styles as the boss of a production.
Wow.
A while.
Excuse me.
Is fucking her employee.
Harry styles.
A younger man.
During workout.
How was that?
Any.
How was that not fall in line with all the stuff we're not supposed to be doing?
I think.
You can't argue it.
I mean that you can.
The age thing nobody cares about that, but you can you can certainly say you're not supposed to be fucking your subordinate.
That's just what it is.
However, if people were to actually get upset, you'd have to look at the thousands of male directors who have fucked their younger female stars.
Absolutely.
It is a double standard, of course.
I mean, obviously.
Whatever.
I mean, however much time Olivia Wilde spent on the film she should have spent some more time is all I can say.
And.
I just got very little out of it.
And it's a frustrating experience.
You know, it just there's something about the movie that's.
Frustrating.
It's not satisfying.
It's not.
You can tell everyone leaving the theater was just kind of shrugging.
And that's.
That response tends to annoy people more than just a movie sucking.
It reminded me of a comedian who gets on stage that thinks he's saying something.
Yes.
And we've got a lot of it's Hannah Gatsby.
This movie is Hannah Gatsby.
Who folks.
And yet another startling turn of utter hypocrisy has signed a new deal with Netflix.
Yeah.
There's your new psycho.
Can't believe I buried that lead.
Unreal.
Now that's crazy.
I agree.
I tweeted.
I took it down.
But I tweeted the other day.
At this point, I wouldn't be surprised if Hannah Gatsby came out as straight.
And then I just took it down because I was like, I don't need this shit.
No, you don't.
Anyway, folks.
We'll be back in the next episode with.
We're not sure yet, but we'll be back with something.
Joe to Rosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Please go to Joey roses in New York City.
Joey roses NYC dot com for all info there comes see me on the road please.
All in for info and shows at jodorosa info .com and huge announcement live show.
Happening in Florida in December.
We'll see you in hell one night, one show Thursday December.
or it's like the 7th or 8th, whatever that Thursday is.
Paddy Walsh and I will be in clear water.
I think it is, Florida.
Uh -huh.
If you want tickets, all the info is on my website.
Not a ton of seats, but more seats
than we had at the New York show.
Go to joderosanfo .com to get your stuff for that.
And thank you to everybody that came out
to the New York show.
Yeah, New York show was awesome.
Can't wait to see those you in Florida.
I hope we're hitting a different group
than could come to our shows in the past, which would be great.
I'm the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.