Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to Will see you in hell, your favorite podcast that talks about horror, sci -fi and fantasy film.
We do the commentary sometimes, and then we also review them.
How do you like that?
This is your episode.
I believe this is your final episode for March.
We got a lot cooking today.
We're going to bring you some shout outs at the end of the episode.
We're going to talk about a little film called Hell Razor 2 subtitled Hellbound, Hellbound,
Hellbound, Hellbound, Hellbound, Hellbound, you know who sings that?
No.
Breeders.
Pod.
First album.
Great album.
Okay.
A lot of people think that Breeders phenomenon started with last splash, it ain't the case.
I believe you.
Pod is a good album, I don't remember that song, but it's called Hellbound.
Oh! You don't say! Also as one of the sexiest songs ever written, O -O -H exclamation point used
to great effect in the movie May, which is a fantastic, an underrated horror film by the lucky
McKee. Hold on, slow down. Made? May, M -A -Y. M -A -Y. I don't know the film. I thought you were talking about
made with Vince Vaughan and John Favreau.
No, have you seen May?
I did, no, I don't, no, you've never heard of it.
I'll learn it too, it's fantastic.
Who's in it?
Anna Ferris, and then the rest of the cast is kind of unknown.
Oh, this is one of those zuckered things.
Nope.
I think a scary movie spoof kind of thing.
No.
It's a horror movie with some comedic elements,
but Leslie Neilson, Kevin Hart.
I've seen these.
They're both in there, yeah.
I've seen these films.
They're good.
I like the ones with the Wayne's Brothers best,
But yeah, but they but they they're still funny after they leave. Have you seen I mean of course
I've seen scary movies the scary movie franchise. Have you seen like little man or white chicks?
I've I've caught pieces of them in passing
White chicks. I remember had
Surprisingly funny or parts in it that I thought it was gonna have yeah
Little man is
This little man looks rough.
I would imagine why chicks have some laughs.
I love like an I'm gonna get you, Succa.
I love I'm gonna get you, Succa.
I mean, I don't know why I look down my nose
those other movies.
I guess because it's a man being computer -generated
to look like a midget, but.
Well, no, like a baby.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He poses as a baby.
Oh, it's a midget who poses as a baby?
Excuse me, little person.
Yeah, yeah, he's like, well, it's not,
he's not even, he's like, they, they, they, computer generate them to be like the size of a baby,
and then he pretends to be a baby for, to, to what end? To rob people or something?
It's all part of that big, big mama's house and all that stuff.
I like big mama's house. So do I, but there was a big string of movies at that time period where it
was a lot to do with being disguised, to pull a thing off or whatever. That was big.
I think master of disguise.
That had some laughs in it, I'll tell you that.
It featured, I blink and dancing too,
I like to move it, move it,
which I laughed at for 10 minutes.
And the fact that his name is Pistachio Disguise.
Yeah, it's very funny.
You told me that and based on that, I watched it.
I didn't enjoy it.
No, it's bad, but there are a couple laughs.
But so May is a horror movie about disguises?
Not about disguises at all.
It just features early breeders songs can in ball the big for the first one. No, no
Completely wrong in everyone
But I highly recommend may I thought I had talked about it on it before maybe I haven't it's it's what it's a true
You know somebody's like you got to see this little known horror movie nobody's ever seen this thing the shining
And you know like come on may is a good like no one truly has seen it and it's really good truly no one truly
All right, I'll check it out
What else did Lucky McKee do?
He did like that.
Pat, I've never heard of the movie, let alone the director.
Well, he's done a lot.
He did like the woods and Lucky McKee.
That's up there with pistachio disguisey.
No, he's a talented director.
He did that red that Hank Ketchum adaptation.
The Bruce Willis movie.
No, red.
Different red.
Wow, this is getting like, who's on first over here?
Well, there is a Bruce Willis movie called red, you know, I know with Morgan Freeman and Helen Mirin. They may read too
Yeah, I know my mom bought me both for Christmas when I had never seen either and said these movies seem right up your alley
Red one ain't bad
Red one ain't better. I traded him to I traded him for credit to buy another thing that I wanted
So he actually has not made a big movie
He did may, all cheerleaders die, which I also saw, which was pretty good.
Never saw it.
I know it, but I've never seen it.
The woods, which I saw, that was fine.
Never saw it.
The woman.
They're just, they're two generic titles.
Oh, the woman.
Is that the one about the feral woman that they try to tame her?
I have that on my shutter.
That watch list.
Was a rough film.
Yes.
I saw it.
It's rough.
Yeah.
But anyway.
May is the jewel of that crown.
I'd like to see the woman. It was on a recommendation list of shutter films.
It's pretty good. You're right. I mean, from what I recall, it's very disturbing.
Now Joe, what's new? What's happening? Well, I think we should begin.
Are you saying that we should get on with the show and also on with a Jew,
You didn't cover your face that time either well it was a low deep I was proud of it as opposed to when I really put some
Passion and feminine and that's one of the funniest scenes in space balls when the Jewish princess is in the jail cell singing
the like railroad. Yeah, that's that's really one of the funniest fucking scenes in the movie. Also
in vacation, Chevy Chase sings one of those old spirituals as well. What is he he's driving?
thing, and it goes swing, swing, swing, cherry up, and it goes coming forward to carry
me whole swing low, cherry up. It is a slave swing. It's a crazy bit, but I love it.
Swing low, cherry up. That's funny. It's new. Not new. Not much. I'm playing a lot of
video games. Okay, a lot of video games, a lot, a lot of video games, but they're keeping me busy.
All right. You know, working on this, well, working on a thing. I don't want to talk about it just
yet, but, but, you know, hopefully it's good. And that's, that's about it, Pat. I'm trying to,
you know, just kind of make it through each day without screaming at somebody.
Sure.
I get that.
Or cutting myself.
Uh -huh.
I've never been a cutter, but I get it now.
Let's put it that way.
Well, I'd rather you scream than cut yourself, Frank.
Sure.
But, uh, but that's about it, man.
I wish, you know, I wish there was more exciting news for you, uh, but, you know, the town
is eating me away from the outside in and from the inside out so I you know I got nothing
much like the characters in hellbound hellraiser 2 yes which I look forward to talking about
today because you really you had some thoughts on this film yeah it upset me I didn't like
it and spoiler alert it's the first film we've done that I did not finish and I know that's
It's not very responsible of me, but I don't know what else to tell you, life's too short.
Now, you've criticized people that will walk out of movies, including me, especially when
there's a review online.
I'm over that.
I do feel if you're a paid movie critic, I've only seen this from a few different critics.
I think it's wonderful.
I got news here.
You're a paid movie critic.
We make money.
Yeah.
No, you're a paid.
We probably make more money, not that we make shit loads of money doing this, but we probably
make more money doing this than the average movie critic that's probably it does which is why they're
all so deeply on it but um no I I mean I just I couldn't do it I I I um I've been trying to do
what they call self -care what the millennials call self -care oh well that's a good group of people
to listen to and just not wallow in uh misery so I deleted Facebook and Twitter from my phone we can talk
about Facebook. I didn't I did it prior to the big news, which shouldn't have come as a shock to
anyone. But I believe Facebook and Twitter for my phone. I don't miss it. I feel happier.
I'm not drinking. I'm not smoking. I'm not doing anything. Right. And it's scary at first. You
don't have that pacifier. But then after like two days, you feel much better as we just discuss.
Yeah. No, I've been off the sauce for a few days myself. Yeah. I was never a big weed guy. No sauce,
no sigs for a little time here. And that's, uh, you do feel better. Yeah. And so I, you know,
I start to feel a little better and a little more positive and I sit down last night and I'm
an hour into Hellraiser 2 and I'm like, fuck this. Why am I doing this? Well, it's just a horror movie.
It's not, you know, I, well, we'll talk about it. All right. Talk about it. Uh, so yeah, but I mean,
In big news this week, Facebook, I guess this is, you know, good for, what does it scream
at N?
No, it's, it's deadlines from the, deadlines from the 24 -hour news psycho of scream and
end.
That's what it is.
How about MSNB scream?
Let's just stick with scream and end.
The scream and end is the worst of them, I think.
It's it's better than whatever the hell you just said. Yeah, how about
Scream and be scream
It's too much Pat. Okay. You got to let it go. Screams. Yeah
No, I
You know Facebook has been revealed to have sold all of our data to the the Trump
campaign
The fact that people would do these quizzes like
OMG, I'm most like Marge Simpson
And you give them all your personal information
To find out which Simpson character you're the most like or whatever it may be
How you ever thought that Facebook was a trustworthy side? I don't understand the people who are like well
I'm getting off now. It doesn't matter. They have your info
Will say you can find me at Instagram. Yeah, guess what honey? Facebook owns Instagram, too. They own everything. They own you
You're done. We did it. We all fucked up
I look I said it for years. I've said it not to pat myself on the back, but I will. I said it for years
I said it years and years and years ago about Twitter. I go everybody is trudging
Headfirst into this thing. They're not questioning it one fucking bit. This is the new smoking. This is what it is
This is just like when cigarettes came out and it was like isn't this so great?
It's such a cool trend and fad and whatever. Nobody stops and fucking thinks
So here we are. We got what we deserved. We're all fucking guilty. I'm including myself in that. Yeah, and you know, we're
Here we are people wonder why and you know, you got to promote shit
So I keep them and that's like the only reason but for me you just get them off my phone was the big thing
If I want to promote something sit down on my laptop send a little post and move on with my day
I'm not sitting there going like because it does as we've discussed it makes you
terrified and makes even though the world is shit it makes you think that the
world's gonna end like in a minute everyone is everyone is at at a 10 yeah and
it's not it's not people are at a 10 during Nixon people are at 10 during George
W people are at 10 during Reagan it's like he's gonna fucking relax a little bit
here yeah nobody saying that anybody likes what's happening but you also got to
keep shitting perspective, man. Keep your fucking head on straight. Um, just
don't need it. And then the, and then all these stories like we've talked about
this as well. But like stories designed to anger you. And they know that when you
click on them, they know, like, Oh, this guy, I'm a guy who likes that feeling or
doesn't, I don't like it, but you're drawn to it. You become addicted to it.
Rage culture, outrage culture, fuck the media to fuck the media. You can't, there
There is a team where you cannot like Trump
and also still hate the media.
There is a team.
Fuck the media for what they do.
Of course, you know, I love all this shit about,
they're not shit, I mean, it's a good thing
about like kids being concerned about their safety
and everything and like the media being like,
aren't these protests that these kids are doing
at schools wonderful because of the shootings and everything?
It's like, hey guys, how about you stop running
fucking footage of the shootings 24 hours of God damn day and making every lunatic that
grabs a gun and brings it into public feel like the fucking super villain he wants to
feel like they never take any fucking responsibility. God damn it. Now I'm all worked up. All the stories
now are like I saw one from a very major. It might have been The New York Times or something
but it was like shooters family says he was love sick. Right? Like he loved a girl who broke
is hard or something like what are you are we supposed to feel bad are we supposed to
sympathize what what's going on and uh you know the local news is worse I watched the local
news last night CBS local news I believe a every but every man is a either bowtoxed out freak
or just some like old bad looking dude and every woman looks like a porn star yes and you know
So this woman last night had like hot dog collagen lips.
Her eyes had almost crossed due to the plastic surgery.
Giant fake tits falling out of her blouse.
And she's like, and there's another shooting
in studio city.
It's like, what's going on?
LA is the worst of them.
And then they said, I'll be careful now
because this video might be disturbing for you.
And I watched the kid that was sitting in his backyard
on his cell phone, 22 year old blackhead with a fiance and two children, get shot 20 times
by cops because they thought his white cell phone was a gun.
I watched him get shot at his house.
They, Jesus Christ, this is, and by the way, they'll show, they'll show something horrific like
that.
And yet, and yet if, if someone in that same video says shit or ass, they'll believe it.
If fucking children running everything, it's ridiculous, it's fucking ridiculous, everybody's
at fault, the world is terrible.
Now I'm on a 10, I didn't want to be on a 10, but now I'm on a 10.
I wrote a poster thing on Instagram the other day, like there's a selfie circle that they
were advertising on Instagram and it's a little mirror, like a light illuminated circle that
you put on your phone.
Yeah.
So you can take better selfie.
I mean, almost stupidest fucking thing I've ever seen in my life.
So I take a screen cap of it, I post, and people wonder how slash why Trump is president.
Right.
Meaning it's this kind of self -indulgence that makes someone want to see an egomaniac get
into the White House.
Right.
This woman, woman I use the term mildly because I couldn't tell if she was a teenager or
not. Okay. But you know, so she could have technically been a girl. I don't know. But, you
know, she was old enough to engage in a conversation, I guess. But she writes to me, glad you pointed
out only one woman here instead of signaling out all women for the horror that these men
are committing. So then a guy writes to her and goes, I don't think this has anything to
to do with women number one, number two,
you realize like a ton of white women
voted Trump into the White House, like that's a fact.
Then she goes, thank you for mansplaining.
So then I write, I usually don't jump into this shit anymore,
but I write, I go, look, nobody was mansplaining
and I never mentioned women, but in here's my little dig.
You see gender too much, stop it, you know what I mean?
Because I love flipping it on somebody like that.
Sure.
Then she writes back, oh yeah,
Yeah, it's a real man -centric post.
I see a lot of men in there also, it's not funny.
And I go, it wasn't meant to be funny.
It was meant to be a commentary.
You'll understand how commentary works one day
when you get older.
And by the way, this isn't man -splaining.
This is you being a child.
And then thankfully, many people like that comic,
including the majority of them being women,
which was interesting.
There's also always the option folks to not follow, not watch.
She doesn't even follow me.
That's why I responded.
She doesn't even, I don't even know how she saw the thing.
It's like, let me get this straight.
You have time to look on the feeds of people on Instagram that you don't even fucking follow.
And then you're going to get fucking irritated.
You're going to seek this shit out and then try to come at me and then come at me with a thing
you're making up.
So let me get, so because there's a woman in the thing I'm criticizing now, that's sexist
Somehow like and because a guy says to you, I disagree. That's man's point. Look what the fuck is going on
What the fuck is happening? Pat, you got me real route up over here. I got it calmed down
It's a rough time. I feel like I need to go back and say you know, you can look like a porn star and you can have all kinds of
Botox and whatever you have and whatever you want to do and still be a
Great newswoman. I'm I'm just saying that's all that happens in Los Angeles and I
It's hard to believe that all of these women are at the top of their their fields, you know, and then that's being judgmental
But and it's the guys it's like when you watch date line
the the woman correspondent on date line is a gorgeous blonde woman and
Every male correspondent is like other than well, there's Keith Morrison who looks like the you know the grim reaper
He's like 85 with like deep crevasses in his face right and then there's a
the guy who's like 300 pounds, you know, falling out of his suits who looks like he just
downed a half bottle of scotch before they held action. It's a double standard I'm trying
to point out. I'm not saying if you're a hot woman, you can't be smart. I don't even know why I
need to explain this. Probably nobody even win here. But you're also not saying to be fair, you pointed
out that the men in LA news also bowtocks the shit out of their face and whatever. Yeah, it's
that weatherman looks like Jack Frost, do you either get that or you just get guys who
are just like old fox and and they don't care because they're dudes.
It's, there was a time, there was a time and Pat I'm talking a long long time ago.
Maybe nine, ten months ago where we would have all openly criticized the sexualization
of a news anchor. Yeah. Times have changed pet. It's not that error anymore. It's not. And when I
moved here 10 years ago, I was shocked at the weather women. The weather women would always be
an unbelievably gorgeous Hispanic woman that looked like some like a Telemundo presenter type woman.
Right. Like crazy tight and short skirts and crazy cleavage. And I was like, wow, the weather here,
I guess, you know, and it became a battle you can tell between the stations who has the hottest weather woman
That's why people choose their news, right? But now
And I have watched local news and forever, but now it's bleeding into the person actually bringing you
Stories of people being murdered and and the president news and things like that. It's crazy. I feel they need to explain or justify
Something I said yes when I said she could have been a girl
She looked to be at least 18 that's my point 18 19 right my reason
and more of my reason for saying that is,
she didn't strike me as a mature person.
So if you're not gonna act like I'm a sure adult,
I'm not gonna refer to you as a man or a woman.
I'm gonna refer to you as a fucking child
or a boy or girl.
That's what I was trying to get at.
Anyway, I presented an interesting issue yesterday
to you, Joe.
You did?
I did.
Well, this was this when you said,
when you walked over with your penis out of your pants
to my desk while I was trying to work,
and you said it was an erect penis
And he said, Joe, I need to see you.
My office something's come up and he pointed down at it.
I wasn't going to bring that up.
I didn't hear a lot of complaints from what I recall.
Joe said, maybe I can help you put it back down and did so.
Let me get this straight.
You need help putting this down.
Yeah, I want to I want to promise this by saying that I have not seen
aisle of dogs. But okay, so this is Wes Anderson. Now this is, by the way, just because I like
to point out when you do a segment incorrectly. Yeah. This is what deadline should be.
Well, it's supposed to be horror news. Well, it's, it's, it's horror fantasy sci -fi. I'd consider
aisle of dogs a fantasy movie, but movie related news. Okay, fine. That's like that as a social
relevance. At the beginning, we're doing deadlines, right? Yeah. No, I know, but you, but then you
Do a thing about Twitter selling our information are we're Facebook. I won't be boxed in I won't be put on a box
So I haven't seen Isle of dogs. I am a guy who
who likes Wes Anderson and thinks that he has made a couple great movies, Rushmore
Bottle Rocket, Ten and Bumps. Might just be the age when I saw them. But you know, I usually
like what he does. He's undeniably an original artist. He tends to make the same movie over
and over, but they're beautiful and interesting movies. Sure. That are usually pretty funny.
Now he was criticized. I would say rightly so for having the widest movies ever. I mean,
Everyone in his movies are white.
Sure.
Not 10 of bombs you had your Danny Glover or say there's efforts that have been made.
But so now after all this criticism, you have all these all white castes, all white castes.
He makes a movie set in Japan, right?
I love dogs, which again, I have not seen and might be wildly offensive.
I don't know.
But it pops up, I love dogs being slammed for cultural appropriation.
So what is the man's supposed to do?
What is anyone supposed to do if you're if you make an effort now and you know
Today they had this interview with this Japanese actor who was like west was asking me a lot about Japanese culture and having me help
Whatever and they put that out as I guess damage control, but the guy is trying to make an effort to broaden his horizons
Not right about what he knows, you know right about something he doesn't know, which is a scary field
And then if you get that wrong, then you're fucked there too, it's it's I know I don't know what people are supposed to do and then and create a feel fuck the media. Yeah, fuck you media. I'm not talking about podcasts. Right. I'm not talking about people that right. I'm not talking about real journalists. Okay. Uh, that that right think pieces or whatever. Well, no, I am. I guess I'm not sure the worst.
Yeah, I said that. I said that wrong. Look, God bless if you write a men's fashion spread for GQ or you know, you write an article about, you know, uh, what's that makeup shop in the mall, Sephora. Sephora, you know, for, for glam magazine. That's how I know you don't have a girlfriend. Yes.
Yes.
Well, also, you've seen the multiple holes I've drilled into my wall.
Yeah, I'm also sitting in the Twix -2 full -size gaming system.
I'm not talking about anybody that does anything publicly.
I'm talking about these people that are out there trying to tell the public how they should
feel, or think, or nudge them in a certain direction, which is most of the media.
and it's fucking disgusting, man.
It's like, stop it.
It's just a story for them.
It's yellow journalism all over again.
You're all William Randolph Hearst.
You're all fucking alarmist.
You're all disgusting people.
And I don't give a fuck.
If you're sitting there going, you know what, man?
Look, I don't make the rules.
I just follow them.
All Nazis march for Hitler.
Fuck you.
I'm tired of the fucking excuses.
You're either part of the problem or you're not part of the problem and if you're the person I'm referring to right now
You're part of the fucking problem. Stop it. Stop it. They won't stop it. This doesn't matter. They're not gonna stop
They just they throw these grenades up because everybody clicks on them and then but you wind up getting people upset about things
They haven't seen they don't know they don't understand and it's it's already happening, but it's killing creativity
and it's making people fearful of anything they want to attempt to do, which puts a lot of
constructions immediately on the work you're trying to do. And to not praise Wes Anderson,
I mean, and again, this movie could be Mickey Rooney and Breakfast at Tiffany's. I don't think it is.
I highly doubt that that's the case, but I just feel like we're, you know, we're getting heading
down a dangerous path. We're in a bad path. And you know what, dude?
killin' creativity is horrible, but fuck killin' creativity.
These people are killing people's lives.
It's like, they don't understand the weight of what they're doing.
They're giving, they're putting the potential fate
of people that have professional lives
in the hands of 22 year olds and 23 year old bloggers
that just wanna break in so bad
That they'll take two hundred bucks to write these bullshit hack fucking articles because they have no real experience
You can see it in the writing you were talking about today in the car where you were reading that movie review
From a major publication on the east coast and it sounded like a fucking 10th grader wrote it
Yeah, because they're hiring these kids because they'll work for pennies and they'll and they'll they'll do all the sensational is shit
And they'll compromise their morals and all this stuff and then their parents are all cow -towing to them and
There's an M &M thing where he talked about how the source would go after certain rappers,
well they went after him, would go after certain rappers because just because they didn't
like them and would give them lesser mics and M &M was like, you're playing with people's
lives here.
You know, dude, and I've been down that road, dude, I was down the road with my own album reviews
when I was getting trolled a couple years back where my album ratings online went from
from five stars to two half star reviews.
Right.
Overall, I don't mean there were half star reviews involved.
Yeah, you can kill a career with the internet.
And it's like, dude, I know what it's like
to deal with this man.
So it's like, you've got to fucking stop.
But this dumb, fucking country we live in thinks
that everybody should have equal access to everything.
And I'm not talking about freedom and all that kind of shit.
I'm talking about how a guy that has never attended film
school, uh, or ever attended, uh, even a film class is allowed to rate a movie on Amazon
the same way that a fucking Roger Ebert .com can rate a movie on Amazon or on Rotten Tomatoes
and whatever.
That's what I'm talking about.
There is no filtration anymore for any of this shit.
It's fucking nuts.
It's nuts.
I don't understand.
Well, in Tomatoes, you'll read a review that's generally positive.
It'll have the negative, whatever it is, splat on it.
You'll read a review that's very critical.
It'll have a big juicy tomato on it.
I don't trust that side anymore.
I asked Joe to see a movie last night.
I know the writer of it.
It's supposed to be an extremely almost
like a happiness level uncomfortable weird movie called
Flower.
And I'm still excited to see it.
I like movies about difficult subjects.
Except unless Hellraiser.
Sure.
Well, this is, by the way, just so we remember,
Happiness is my hell razor dude. Those are the kinds of movies I refuse to see understand that yeah
But you know, I text Joe you want to go to this movie
You know, it's got a half a star on Roger ebert .com. I said I couldn't go but I said bummer because it apparently got a half star
But that so that is one person right who is not Roger ebert by the way the greatest film critic of my lifetime
We don't know who that is. I don't know what Roger ebert .com is but it's
It's enough to have people's opinion shaped
and it's making for a much less interesting culture
where everyone feels like they have to agree on things
and your opinion on movies can brand your racist.
But as we saw with Black Panther, as we saw it,
ghost busters in the case of women,
where they go after critics for not liking something,
you must be a racist, you must hate women.
I think it's just getting scary.
It's getting scary.
It's getting and and here's why here's why that's the reaction now
Because it did start with a bunch of assholes. Yeah, it did start with a bunch of trolls that hated women and and hated
Anybody that wasn't white or hated anybody that didn't love guns or whatever the fuck it was
Yes, that's where it started
But now it's spread into anybody that just wants to sort of talk in the gray area is getting clumped in with that and what's crazy to me is
If you want to break it down politically, the left hates the left right now and the right
hates the right.
So I'm not sure what's going to happen, but it seems like there's a small sect on the
left and a small sect on the right that are somehow making the most noise for everybody.
Most Republicans don't like Donald Trump, yet he's president and it seems like that's the
whole party because he's the face of the party essentially.
Most liberals can't stand the fucking PC police,
yet those are the only liberals we ever hear from.
So I'm not quite sure how this small demographic
from each group is seemingly controlling
the climate of everything, but they are.
And I think it's because they're essentially
the stay -at -home parents from the 80s
that would write letters to like Nabisco
because they advertise too much sugar
in the cereal, the kids or whatever, these are the people.
The average person who's got rationale, who's level headed, who's logical, who has things
to do, even if it is just playing video games, is like, yeah, I don't have time to like
go get into all this bullshit.
That's why you and I take the shit off our phone and go out.
But the people that stay in it, man, I think getting off Twitter will make this stuff seem
less of an issue than it is.
But it was getting to just be creep and it's the kind of thing where you talk to your parents or something about they have no idea
It's even going on and that's honestly a better way to live your life
It is and if we can get those people to spend more money
There could be hope for the entertainment business, but until then we're at the mercy of these children
But I mean it's it's no nobody is is making up their mind for themselves nobody is watching something if if people say it is bad
had, there's no interesting discussion going on at all and you know, when I read reviews
of a movie that's coming out or whatever, I'll read two or three reviews and I'm like,
they're all just the same thing and people are waiting for stuff to go up and rot in tomatoes
so they can say, people used to do this when I was a movie critic, they wait to see what
the consensus is going to be and then join it because they're scared of being the one person
and being like, I thought this was great
or I thought this thing everybody loves sucked.
So that's how you get everyone kind of whispering
amongst themselves like, but shape of water sucked dick, right?
Like, we're a fish dick.
Why is everyone saying this thing's amazing?
You know, it's a frustrating time.
We spent too much time on all of this, but -
We're 36 minutes in.
Holy cow.
We haven't even swung by.
Let's quickly swing my past movie corner.
Do you think that we will do an Isleation on this show,
which has been heavily requested?
We probably should we can do it. It's a good one to discuss probably and it'll have to be in April some I have to get to see it
But yeah, I've been talking about it with Heather since we saw you think we'll do I mean, I'd love to do it
Do you think we could do a perfect host on this or the perfect toast because if you if so I'm gonna
I'm not gonna talk about it, but it's David Hyde Pierce
It's technically a horror film. I'll watch it. We'll do it
Okay, so April we'll do annihilation and the perfect toast. That'll be two of the episodes
All right, and so yeah, I saw an eyelashin. I also so I'm watching currently
On an awesome documentary called Wild Wild Country, which just got on in that flick. Yeah, that's the duplash film, correct
The duplash brothers they had to put their names on it. Yeah
They had nothing to do it. I mean, unless they shaped it had something to do with editing or something, but who knows
It it starts a little slow, but it is about a cult
In Oregon that moves into this like 40 person small town and
Sets up shop and becomes this giant thriving cult and
They're presenting themselves as agriculture type of people and then you realize pretty quickly there's they're like
Extreme sex orgies and open marriages and stuff like that and it's getting more and more interesting
with each episode. I don't even know what side I'm on half the time. But it's, which is a great
sign of a good documentary. I'm really into it. I recommend it highly. It's very interesting.
All right. I'll keep it short. So, a horror movie called The Windmill. The Windmill.
I found it on Shutter. I think I found it on Shutter. I'm really enjoying the Shutter app. I just can't
I don't remember anymore what's on which app between Shutter Prime, Hulu, and Netflix.
But the windmill, it's about a windmill, I kind of figured that out.
An Amsterdam where there's an evil ghost that's there and he kills people for their sins.
It wasn't great.
I watched it solely on the fact that the monster looked cool and I was like, oh, this sounds cool.
Like a demon that hunts people at this windmill in the wilderness of the Netherlands or what
I was like, this sounds fun and wasn't that good.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that was kind of that.
Um, I watched Christof Kislauski's blue, you know that blue white red trilogy, they're
I've heard of it.
I know.
It's a, it's a French trilogy that like growing up was the movie that every critic jizzed
over this, this trilogy from this French filmmaker with Juliet Binoche.
Pate forever.
I've never seen him.
I was like, you know what, it's time to check off some of these classics.
I own them.
I hadn't even opened it, it was fine.
Yeah, it's like most criterion stuff.
Yeah, I got two more in the trilogy, I got a watch.
I love criterion, of course, and I like how it looks,
I like the packaging, I like the collection,
but I was like, well, let me look through the supplements
of this, there was a 10 minute interview
with Kierstoff Kizlowski, where he talked about a shot
where they dipped a sugar cube in coffee
and the sugar cube filled with coffee.
And he was like, I figured that an audience would not watch,
this is not a French accent, and he was speaking in French.
I don't know why I'm doing this voice,
but I'm gonna continue with it.
I figured people would watch five seconds,
but actually I got it down to 4 .5 seconds
that they would watch a sugar cube go into a cup of coffee.
Eight seconds, you get walkouts.
So we had to find the sugar cube
because let me show you.
Oh my God.
He did, you sit through this.
Yes, you'll sit through this.
Well, this one, this stopped me
from watching the supplements,
but I couldn't believe what I was seeing.
So he goes, now as you can see now,
he dips a sugar cube into his own coffee.
He goes, it takes 10 seconds to completely fill with coffee.
So what I did, this thing went on and on and on,
and I love criteria and I support them.
I only entire collection on Blu -ray,
but this is why people give the collection a bad thing.
Remember when you were a kid and you'd go to the toy store and the new
He -man came out or the new transformers or whatever was a turtle guy
But yeah, Ninja fine Ninja Turtle. Yeah, and it had a big beautiful box and it was the most amazing in the world
And you said I wanted your mom will go. It's a piece of junk. It's just another piece of junk
That's the criterion collection for grown -ups. It's some degree
I mean, when they do put out a movie that you love,
there's nothing better.
Look, breakfast, club, whatever.
That's fine.
Yeah, some of those toys I loved,
but my point is, is they really win
with the fucking packaging.
Right.
It's the most gorgeous packaging on planet earth.
You're like, I have to own this,
or I don't like movies.
I know.
I'm a poser if I don't own this.
And then you buy it and you go, most of the time you go,
yeah, it's pretty cool.
I don't know, I lost the arm.
I don't have the gun part anymore.
That's the truth.
Tom told me this, and it was almost like the first time you get stoned or something,
but I was like, tan or something, my mom goes, pat.
The Ninja Turtle that you want to spend your harder and allowance on is the exact same
as these other Ninja Turtles you have.
What the hell is that?
Why is my phone ringing through my TV?
Joe, I don't know what to tell you.
What is going on anymore?
I didn't tell the phone to do that.
Why is it doing that?
It rings through my iPad now, too.
I didn't tell it to do that.
Look, I'm betting it's got something to do
with your fucking Alexa.
I can't believe as paranoid as you are,
you have a fucking Alexa in your house.
Alexa's not connected to my Apple shit.
How do you know?
She's not.
Alexa.
Alexa, are you connected to Apple?
She wouldn't even answer.
She's not speaking to you anymore.
But she's saying, you know, when she pointed out to me, Pat.
Alexa are you talking my mom? Oh, all who confused him like her name is Alexa. No, it's it's not
See there she there she doesn't know she knows she knows that I don't know that
so
When she just said they're the exact same piece of plastic with an orange
Bandana instead of purple and of course you cut you should know that when you're a kid
But it hit me like a ton of bricks. I was like I've been spending all my money on the same thing over and over and over
Then they realize kids were getting wise and then you get the turtle that you can open his shell and store the
Nunchucks and the shell out of now I got to get that but
We're doing the same things we did when we were kids with toys. That's exactly right with these blue razor
Whatever you're trying to fill the hole with. Yeah, and then you get it and the holes not filled folks
Which my hole was filled. It's Friday. Hey, there's still time. All right
Right, the call by the way that I just got entitled to receive a prize, this is, it's
funny.
Somebody said, have you noticed since Trump got elected, you get way more courtesy calls.
And I was like, you know what, it's weird.
I do.
Is that connected?
And then we find out the Facebook thing.
Yeah.
And then I get a call just now.
You've been selected to receive a prize.
Anyway.
All right.
Look, let's get to our movie at hand.
And I told you about that, that protein bar I bought that, that I saw on that point.
I had another one. I went up to Arrowhead. I was up there with some friends and I was supposed to get some more supplies
So I bought some more supplies and now I get daily ads for Hershey bars in my Instagram. It's fratting
Hellbound
Hellraiser 2 hellbound Hellraiser 2
Look the first one I guess because we watched it in a commentary format and it was you and I sitting and watching it
I also thought there was just a better story, a better movie.
I mean, the story makes no sense in Hellraiser 2.
Hellraiser 2 is a, it's a lot of fun, in my opinion.
Fun.
I look, I love Pinhead.
I love Pinhead.
Pinhead has not been in it when I left.
Do you saw him get the nails dug in his head
and then he's been out of it for an hour?
You did not watch an hour of the movie then.
There's no way.
He comes in, he comes in at about the 45 minute mark.
That's probably where I got it.
So what I, what I told you a lot, you didn't see any of the plot, shouldn't the plot have kicked in at the 45 minute mark?
The, I mean, it's just simple story telling, but here's what I was watching that eventually set me over the edge.
I already was not having a good time by any means and felt myself sinking back into a depression.
I was starting to slowly emerge from. Right.
And there's a guy lying on a blood soaked mattress covered in maggots.
starts screaming and cutting away at his chest, cutting himself up and cutting away at his
dick at one point.
I don't, he doesn't cut his dick.
I'm gonna go back, but hold on, is this the scene where you shut it off?
I gave it another 15 after that.
Okay, so you watched roughly 22 minutes of the film.
Oh, I got out at 44 minutes.
How do you know?
Because you can tell.
You pause it and check.
So you check the number.
It was 44 minutes.
You're sure I watch beyond this scene, but then the woman comes out and then she digs her hand in the back of his head and the
Pukes and maggots and they're screaming and they're I was like this is
Not for me as I said to you
The on the texting last night. Hey, that's the only scene like that in the movie
That is the controversial scene. I couldn't explain I didn't feel like I'd over text last night to explain the whole thing
That's the scene that was cut out of the R -rated version.
It was included in the unrated version.
Well, I really wish I had seen it without.
There was still plenty of people getting ripped apart
by hooks and so forth.
Yeah, well.
This is not for me, and you were just talking
last week about you don't like torture,
but now you like Hellbound, Hell Rise or two.
I just don't understand how you watch a movie like Happiness,
and you see Philopsy more often's come hit a wall,
and that's fine.
So I see come every day, sometimes twice a day.
You got a, you got a, you got a, you got a main, you got a comedic storyline about a
pedophile. Right. That, that, you can sit through that, but, but, but, you know, the,
the bloody skinless woman is too much. The bloody skinless woman was, you know, gross
whatever, but this guy, cutting away at himself in the maggot, it was the tonnage of shit
and then he needs to puke when she puts her hands or, I was just like, give me a fucking
break. It's that seems a little much. I agree. I don't love it. I do think the
first film was a better film overall. I used to not think that. There was a time
my life where Hellraiser 2 was my favorite horror movie ever. I cannot believe it.
And I met Doug Bradley in a bar once. Yeah. And I said, Hellraiser 2 is the best
horror movie ever. And he said, you're wrong mate. And I said, no, I'm not. It's the
best hard movie ever. And he goes, you're wrong. Best hard movie ever brought a Frankenstein.
You can ask Robert England Hill agree. And as he went to Cypher's beer, I yelled, shut
up and take the compliment Bradley and then he laughed, which was a big moment for me in
my life that I made pinhead laugh.
But as I get older, I recently re -watched the film as well because I knew we were going
to be talking about it.
I mean, you didn't see the real plot of it as they go down, they have to go down into
hell.
right? Trying Kirstie and the blonde -haired girl are essentially trying to write the wrongs of the
first film and Julia, who's the evil lady from the first film, is trying to basically command hell
and take over and the centabytes are still after Kirstie. It doesn't make a lot of sense. No. It doesn't
make sense why they let certain people go. It doesn't make sense why they're still after Kirstie.
It doesn't make sense that Frank, Uncle Frank from the first film dies while he's in hell somehow.
Yeah, in hell you're dead, I thought.
That's what I thought too.
It doesn't make sense why some of the centibites are sort of these like just sort of like judges,
like you know, you know, unbiased judges, like if you're evil, then we take you and if you're not,
then we don't. And then the doctor becomes a centibight. And then he's just like a Jason
or Freddie Krueger style monster with one line or two, which I don't care for. Like he's like flying
around on this demon thing. And he's like, the devil, is he or no, no, he goes, the surgeon is in.
And I recommend amputation and then like cuts a guy's like arm off or whatever.
I would have loved a fucking whip at some point.
It goes, it goes really off the rails at the end.
It gets nuts and it doesn't make any fucking sense.
They disregard the rules of the first one, like suddenly, like in the first one, the box
sends them back to hell, but in the second one, that doesn't work for some reason and it
doesn't make any sense.
She also fulfills the bargain of the first movie which is if you I didn't know what I was doing with this box
If you leave me alone I'll get you Frank and that's their deal
And she does and then they still try to take her at the end of that movie
So the first one doesn't painfully make a lot of sense either but it makes way more sense, right?
I you know and part of it
I think was just watching it with you and not
Being home alone watching it, but I enjoyed the first one
I thought it was a well -made horror movie,
but if I'm gonna have my face just mashed into depravity
and torture, I have to be rooting for something,
there has to be some sort of story,
there has to be something getting me from A to B.
When I'm 45 minutes in, watching this nauseating scene
go on and on and on and on,
and I don't even know what I'm looking at
or why I give a shit, that's a problem.
It's because he needs blood on the mattress to resurrect Julia's body needs that much blood
Well, he needs blood and he doesn't want to kill somebody so he brings that guy who he knows if he gives him a knife
He'll cut himself. How about you shave over the mattress? No, you need you need because the because the blood is the victim
So yeah, he's basically trying to keep his hands clean of murder
That part makes sense to me. It's gross
He says right here on the parent's guide
and I am to be a man violently cuts his chest
and crotch with a razor blade, extremely graphic,
glorious scene in the film.
All right, I didn't imagine the crotch cut.
I don't remember the crotch cut.
I mean, this was also your favorite horror movie at one point.
I don't remember him cutting his dick.
I for some reason.
You don't see him is dick, but you know,
eventually when you're like,
how long am I gonna watch this guy cut into
his maggot -ridden body, then it's like,
oh, I guess we'll take it up a notch
and he makes some swipes in the dick region.
Oh, I thought that was just him cutting his stomach now. He does that too. Right. We're wrong.
But like, you know, like hostile, we've discussed hostile on the show before.
That was at a time where I did not even like horror movies when that movie came out. I didn't,
I was a pussy. I didn't want to watch them. And I went to see them theater and was honestly like,
I don't know. I'm going to wind up leaving this or something. But sure enough, I'm rooting for
these guys. And there's a whole story to it. And it's basically a sex comedy in the first half hour.
Right, and you're really like oh my god. I hope they get out of here. There's that hell hell raised with a franchise
Seems to be just like just watch this fucked up shit. You you sick, but who are you rooting for in a happiness?
Well that happiness is not a horror movie. I know but I'm saying you know is and that's not one of my favorite movies either
But I do love the movie. I can't deny it
there's also 10 stories going on and happy. And they're all horribly depraved happiness is essentially a depraved, you know, Woody Allen movie, but it's got a light touch to it in a weird way. And it's it's black comedy. I mean, hell, hell raise or two is I just don't know how anybody could get anything out of it unless you're a gore junkie, which I am definitely not.
Well, I'm going to go out in a limb here and say, and I'm going to get a lot of pushback
on this from fans, I'm sure, but Clive Barker, excellent writer, yeah, kind of ends there.
Well, he didn't direct us. No, or writer, but he was behind this, he was still part of the franchise
at this point. Hellraiser one, again, a classic, but if you really were to analyze it on the same
level that you analyze like an exorcist or something like that.
You're going to find a hell of a lot more plot holes and hiccups than you're going to
find in a film like that.
I've read the Hellbound Heart, the book that it's based on.
He's an excellent, excellent writer, or at least was at one point, the Scarlet Gospels,
which was the latest, there's a new Hellraiser book now coming out that he didn't write,
but he like oversaw or something, but the Scarlet Gospels was the last official release, I believe,
and it was dog shit. It was terrible. You know, Nightbreed is a shitty movie. Nightbreed is a
fucking boring, bad movie that makes no sense. Have you seen this fabled director's cut of it?
I tried. It's brutal, dude. I've never seen Nightbreed. I've heard that it's a lost masterpiece,
this uncut version, I haven't seen it.
It's not, it's a bad movie.
It's not good, it's corny.
There's a cornyness to it where, you know,
Lord of Illusions is not great.
That baccala?
Yeah, you know, midnight meat train,
which is based on one of his stories is not great.
Brad, good.
You know, so I think Barker's a great writer.
I don't think that always carries over into film form,
whether or not Son of a bitch forgot to mute the TV yeah that doesn't always carry
over into film form whether or not it's the writer himself that's making the
movie it's like Stephen King suffers from the same issue Stephen King a lot of
the time when he's involved with the movie it's not that great of a flick right and
hence the shining mini series versus the the Polanski shining Arbina or the
And I'll ask you what's his face, Kubrick shining.
And then also too, a lot of Stephen King stories that they try to adapt into films end up
being kind of shitty because you're like, yeah, that works as a short story.
You've stretched it now in 90 minutes, two hours, you've added all these other plot lines
to it.
It's stupid now.
I mean, a great counterpoint would be Shawshank Redemption, which is a two and a half hour
move.
I'm not saying it can't work.
Yeah, you know that the the the again hellbound hard is a great novella hell razor is a is a I I would say great horror film
It's got its problems, but it's solid. I really love the and I'm a fan of the franchise before anybody wants to crucify me in this
I have seen
every
Hell razor movie
And I have seen them with immediacy like when they went to direct a video
I was at the fucking blockbuster video in Austin, Texas
this, the day they released Hellseeker or Inferno,
whichever one came first, to see it.
So I'm die hard.
I rented the latest one.
The day it was available, I'm fucking iTunes, I rented it.
So I liked the franchise.
I believe in it, but I can't sit here
and say they're fantastic films.
Would you say two is the second best?
Now I would.
Yeah, I think they get progressively,
Well, no, I say it goes one, two, four, three, and then after that, it's a kind of take
your pick.
The real Roger Ebert himself gave Hellraiser two, one star.
Really?
Yeah.
For the same reasons, you're saying like he thought it was disgusting and shit.
Yeah, I mean, just he's like, it's just one horrible visual after another with nothing
nothing really tying them together fair enough fair enough and he was you know
usually pretty open about that star pretty open -minded about stuff I remember
him giving dark city four stars chose fascinated I like dark city it's a cool movie
I wish I had it on blue ray versus DVD but I'm not buying it again anyway folks
that's our show that's it we had to do our shout outs oh shit you know I made a dome
Ed, you reminded me. No, I'll do. All right. Because you did the, uh, you do the ad.
I do the shout outs. It's kind of how we, how we've been doing it. While Joe's bringing
this up, I'm on Twitter and Instagram kind of at the Patrick Walsh show, living
Biblically Monday nights, 938, 30 central on CBS. Uh, I'm also sort of on Twitter and Instagram
Joe DeRosa comedy and then a penthouse monthly column you let me down. All right, shout -outs.
Guys, can't thank you enough for your Patreon support, for all of your support.
We're always taking it back by it. It's very touching. And here are your shout -outs for the month of March.
I don't know if you guys know
I'm not sure if you guys know
I don't know. I like some of the shirts. I saw I like the Zippo man shirt Matt Crawford Jenna Richard
Deming Brian Callis Tim Drain Michael Madrigal go to Mr. Shoot Records. If you're ever
in Lancaster, Pennsylvania, Richard Howinstein, Bretton Frazier. Wow. That's weird. Bretton Frazier.
Okay. Frazier. Almost like Brendan Frazier. Sean Luke Physioc Damien, Karen Kilgaris.
Oh Karen that's a dear friend from my favorite murder make sure you listen to that podcast you download it you support
We saw her do it her and Georgia do it live at the Orpheum theater on Friday night fantastic
Just a fantastic show and the love people have for them is infectious. I got chills with the way they were cheering for the our friends
It was fun, man. It was really fun. Go listen to my favorite murder
Uh, Jack O 'Steel, Tyler Sanderson, Joey Mueller, Shelby L, Dan Hepang, sorry, Dan, Dan
Hepanoids, Nathan Baskett, Blake Chanel, Gary Myron, John Paul Reese, Sy Rod, Dylan
Ellen Larr, Phil Burrell, Edmund Dillon, the blank magic ninja, Scott Pauline Serile,
Byron Morton, no, Brian Morton, excuse me, Patrick Baxter, Adam Maxwell Kent, Nick
Muscara, Casey Sturgeon, Chris Marsh, Daphne Kellogg, Ryan Martz, Tristan Avery, Hunk
Matthew J. Brown, Julie Aguyer, I believe.
I hope I said that right.
Aguirre, maybe, or Aguirre, yeah, the wrath of God.
Charity Ferguson, Hank Gustafson, Nick Walther, Alex C,
Alexander Stein, Tyler Keetley, Emily Marvel, Heather Anderson,
John B. Wat, dear friend of mine.
Check out John's store on Etsy.
John, I'm sorry, I'm forgetting the name of the damn store,
But check out John Wadsdorn at sea makes horror memorabilia. It's very cool
Mori Benjamin Nicholas Burns
Heighton Davidson Alex Nelson Will Pittman Jeremy Derek Clark Alex Shipley Joshua Taj Bozeman Sean Pinnock Amanda Liebson
Timothy Lesto
Nope, Timothy let's go
Shane Nazarian
John King
Clayton Stamper
Smelly Bubbles, James Nassmon, Holly Barnes, Jeff Some Confidence, David Bellinger, Tyler
Zach, Kurt Ziegler, Hunter McDonald, John Wolt, Justin Bohaguer, Adam Bembenek, Manny
Rios, Demonio Rubio, Brandon Gash, who does some of the art, correct, on the Etsy store
for our Etsy store, which is called the Hoghouse store.
Thank you, Brandon.
Edmund Agabo, Paul Pickerel, Jake Ferote.
Chris Lindt, Tony Quinn, Rob Lines, Danny Rudd,
Jacob Barrett, Jordan C, Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler,
Joshua Christensen, Barbara Allen, Jonathan Face,
Rebecca Cohen, Chris Bowen, Mike Gibbons,
Donnie Joyce, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson,
Jennifer Smith, Hader Ismail, Connor Denahee, Michael, Steven Calpa, Kevin Swiss to Wits.
Kevin Swiss to Wits. I think I said that correctly. Thomas Koza, Anthony J. Guajardo,
Annie Johanison, Timmy Kaye, Sean Florent, Dolores Martinez, Megan Librand, Scott Blickensdurfer,
Alic Walker, Brett Wemmer, Tristan Carlson, Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo,
Weston Thomas Havidio, that's the one, how do you say it?
Remember the one that's all the consonants?
Yeah, Havidio did?
Vittavitch or something?
I'm sorry buddy.
Sorry man.
Please recent us the parenthesis.
You've sent it to us, sorry.
I sent it again.
Because we lose these messages.
Jared Blair, Josh Smallridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Griffith, Emily Florence,
who runs our Hoghouse store and our Facebook group page.
Thank you, Emily.
We love you.
You're awesome.
Sean L. Jordan Parker, Dave Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim DeAngelo, Jonathan Galatt, Michael
Michael McBee, Carla, oh, Stephanie Power, Sterling, Abrigo, Jaronne, Jaronne Sanderson, Diego
Campos, Stephen Maso, Zoe Blascovic, Aisley Kivinsland, Dan McLeod, Lorenz Bunganiers,
Alejandro Salgado, Papa Spouche, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda
Alzamora. Jason Weibel. I said PPGs. That is my friend, Mike Curry. Hello, Mike. That's
a blockbuster video inside joke. We used to work at blockbuster video. Drew Spindler, Andrew
Koval, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melanowski, Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Ben, Misty Zavar, Brandon
Inak, Dajne Wilford, Johnny Ferg, Mathias Paujo, Michael Gold, Danielle Deuer, Eric
Lamora, Steven Reese, Kevin, Marcinic, Erica Branding, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge,
Zach Showendorf, Will Potorff, Natalie Craig, Anthony Kyle Kinsland, the man whose name
and we cannot speak.
Ony Babaduk, Scott Patton,
Reed Esthetic, Brian Bollarier,
Robert Pearson, Max Unwraff,
Brian England, and John Weisengruber.
Wow.
It's incredible.
Incredible.
It's moving assortment of people.
I can't believe we have that many fans.
It's lovely.
It's very, very touching.
Guys, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you.
That was a hitgun podcast.