I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell.
It's time to get busy with the men in the shizzy.
I am Joe DeRizzi.
Oh boy.
Uh, I'm Pat Wolfe.
We don't need the judgment right off the bat.
You might not need it, but you got it.
Sometimes, sometimes, uh, what you, you can't always get what you want.
But if you try, sometimes you might just find that you'll get what you need, honey.
That's the Rolling Stones.
Yeah, I was doing Mick Jagger when he sings it.
You can't always get what you want, honey.
Yeah, it's interesting.
It's like, is it a Southern?
Is it a British?
Is it a weird black affectation?
I don't know.
It's the affectation of a man who fucked 15 year olds and some seemingly just skating clean from it.
I'm, uh, I read each morning the highlights of the Kevin Spacey trial.
Speaking of fucking 15 year olds.
Ain't looking good.
It's so weird.
He's got like Elton John.
I'll be like, yeah, he, you know, he, he slept over at our house after a party once.
And then it's like Kevin Spacey was weeping during Elton John's testimony.
It's like, what?
Have you read any of this stuff?
No, I read, I mean, I read the thing about the, you know, the kid that was like.
These, these, well, I'll tell you what I read in a second, but go ahead with your thing.
They just got these character witnesses who come forward and they're like, yes.
Uh, he had dinner at my house once in 2008 and he didn't rape anyone.
It's like, what?
So then the lawyers wisely saying, do you understand that people can be benevolent on one hand and then an asshole on the other?
Like, especially famous people.
What are you talking about?
It's like, well, Kevin Spacey was nice to me once so he couldn't have assaulted this person in a hotel room.
Out of your fucking mind.
People who are nice are nice always.
I read a headline regarding the trial and it was from.
Jay Leno headline.
It was, it was from an outlet.
That wasn't siding with Kevin Spacey.
It was from like a liberal news type outlet.
And that certainly wants to chastise Kevin, you know, that is not that is not trying to somehow legitimize Kevin Spacey is what I'm getting at.
And yet, yet this is how they still print the headline because these disgusting pigs still need to get their clicks.
Kevin Spacey accuser admits to laughing about the incident.
And you're like, what, what is that?
Like, wait, what?
Yeah.
Or joking about the incident.
And then you read it and it's the guy saying I would joke about it to cope with it as a means of self therapy because it was tragic.
And I'm like, this publication is on the side of the guy, the victim.
And yet they still have to write it in a way.
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
I'm going into a back room.
Maybe you can't hear this gardening shit, but that's all I hear.
Oh, boy, this guy.
Oh, boy is my intro.
He's he's doing like a like a Super Dave cam right now.
You don't have to pay any attention to it.
Well, it's you think the gardening distracting.
It was like the like, you know, you know what they do the thing in a show where they put the camera inside the bowling ball.
That's what it looked like.
And they want to show you the bowling ball action.
Anyway, they're on the side of the damn victim and and they still have to type it or advertise it through the headline in this way that you read it.
And it sounds like accusatory about the guy like like victim admits to you.
You don't have to use the word admits.
The word admits is admits is a word that insinuates.
It's not a positive word.
You don't go.
They admitted to this.
That means usually you're guilty of something.
And I just I just can't stand it.
I can't stand that.
There is no dignified press left.
It's all gone.
And in this country, at least they all write from a clickbait perspective, regardless of what the story is.
Even if it's an objective story, it could be something as objective as this woman was murdered in cold blood.
The story could be that objective.
There's no two sides to it.
This happened.
It's very black and white.
Blah, blah, blah.
And they'll still write the headline of like, you know, you know, murder victims, family admits that she went out after and you're like, don't stop.
Why are you you're only writing it like that?
So I click on it thinking,
oh, what happened?
What weird thing did they spin to make it sound
like she wasn't murdered in cold blood?
And you know what I'm saying?
It's crazy.
It's fucking sick.
It's really sick.
I agree.
I try not to click on anything anymore.
I'll go, are you gonna feel better
having learned some tiny piece of gossip
about some celebrity you don't care about at all?
No, they've phrased it in such a way
that you're like, oh, really?
She said this, but you don't care.
You know in your heart, you don't care,
so don't click on it.
That.
Not a good state of things.
What are you doing?
You doing standup?
You doing your little jokes?
I don't care for the phrasing.
No, I'm not on tour again until the fall,
which I'll be plugging at the end of the episode.
But no, what am I doing?
I am batch recording all of my podcasts
in anticipation of the month of August.
So I can.
Yeah, Joe's like, hey, can you record eight
on Monday, July 21st?
Yeah, I guess I can.
Sure.
I'm gonna try to go on a soul searching
introspective road trip in August
and maybe shut my phone off and not talk to anybody.
I believe, Pat, that I have earned it.
I believe that I deserve it.
I rarely say that.
I don't know.
I'm just gonna drive.
Long December and there's reason to believe.
You're just listening to Long December over and over.
Is that counting crows?
Yeah.
That'll be first on my playlist.
Maybe this year will be better than the last.
That'll be a playlist entitled Road Mix.
Starts with - Road Mix number three.
Long December followed by, of course, Turn the Page.
There I go.
Turn the page.
Joe wishing on shooting stars,
looking out at a lesser canyon, not the grand,
a lesser canyon.
Sleeping on the hood of my car.
Yeah.
Hands behind the head staring up at, yeah,
Wayne's World style.
20 minutes into trying to sleep,
someone comes up and takes your wallet,
just leaves.
That'd be a funny gag in something.
The guy goes on a road trip,
it cuts to him doing that on the hood of his car.
You find out he's only been driving for 15 minutes.
Immediately.
Yeah.
I don't understand camping.
It just seems like people are just gonna rob
and kill you at this point, you know?
I used to not be scared of it.
I don't know why I am now, but now I'm just like,
you're just gonna sleep with your belongings
in the middle of nowhere and hope for the best?
I don't, I'm not gonna do it.
In defense of camping, which I don't do,
I get what you're saying, but in defense of camping,
the only belongings are camping belongings.
So who gives a shit?
What are they gonna steal, your compass?
Oh, they stole my new thermos.
Like, who cares?
You're not bringing your Sonos out there,
you know what I mean?
Or maybe you are bringing your Sonos.
You could, you bring a speaker, you bring your wallet,
your pocket knife.
You're not bringing your watch collection.
All right.
But I understand why you feel that way,
and the reason you feel that way, Pat,
is because the society is crumbling.
I mean - It is.
When you're watching, here's where we're at, people.
Here's where we're at.
When you're watching Tucker Carlson
dress down Mike Pence,
and Tucker Carlson is making some decent points
about why are we sending tanks to the Ukraine?
Our cities are crumbling.
And Mike Pence is kind of going, it's not my problem.
I'm like, I don't know what the,
I don't know what's happening anymore.
I know we've said many times -
Where are you watching?
It's all over the place.
It's like a big, it's a viral clip.
It went crazy viral.
So he's doing like his Twitter talk show now,
Tucker Carlson.
I don't know what it's from.
It's him and Mike Pence in front of a packed house.
You'd think these two guys are lining up on stuff, right?
Yeah.
And Pence is real,
and did you think Pence is gonna come out
in heavy support of the Ukraine?
He went over and met with the guy.
I thought that those guys would hate each other.
See, Pence, it's an interesting phenomenon
because none of the Trump people like Pence.
They all wanted him hung.
And I think if Mike Pence is anything, folks, it's not hung.
Okay.
And they also don't think he's a good leader.
They would never vote for him.
The people on the left hate Mike Pence.
Who's supporting him?
Who likes Mike Pence?
That guy in the Ukraine,
that John Stewart president they have over there.
Oh, okay.
The comedian president?
Yeah, he likes him, apparently, I think.
All right.
But then you got Tucker Carlson going,
every city in the United States is deteriorating,
which he's right, it is.
So it's a real mind fuck.
You're like, I don't,
you don't know how to feel about any of it.
You're just like, I don't know what's going on anymore.
Like, I don't, you know, used to be real clear.
Gore Vidal, Bill Buckley.
That was it.
You're like, all right, I know where that guy stands.
I know where that guy stands.
And let's listen to them go at each other.
You know, it was the guy in Nixon,
Forrester, Nick, what was Frost?
Frost and Nixon.
It was a real clear cut who you were,
you understood who each guy was.
Like, I'm anymore, I'm lost with this shit.
Would you see if I released a movie called Alf Nixon?
And it's like Alf with note cards preparing
for his interview show,
the one where I saw I'm interviewing Dennis Frans,
but he's actually got Nixon on in the seventies.
It's out, he's in a suit, he's got a stack of note cards,
he's sweating.
And they're like, five minutes, Alf.
And he's like, I know, god damn it.
You think I know I'm interviewing the president?
And it's, are we seeing a more serious Alf
or is he making his cracks and quips and all that?
Did that not sound serious to you?
Yeah, this is Alf at his breaking point.
I'm saying when the cameras roll,
what Alf are we getting?
That's the beauty of it is that it's that kind of thing
where it's like sweat and stress,
but once those lights come up, it's all Alf.
It's all magic.
He turns it on.
I can't say I wouldn't watch it,
but I can't also say that there's any character
in pop culture I might hate more than Alf.
I mean, I hate Alf.
Well, the opposite of you.
I know, a lot of people are.
I mean, he's based on Rodney Dangerfield.
You love Rodney.
Yeah, what the hell are we talking about here?
Yeah, yeah, Rodney's great.
It's like saying you like sandwiches.
Alf's based on Rodney Dangerfield.
Why don't you like Subway?
Because it sucks.
But for a kid, Alf is your Rodney.
No, Rodney was my Rodney.
I saw it back to school when I was 11 years old.
It changed my life.
I'm gonna go then go watch the Alf sitcom
with this depressed, four -eyed dad
stumbling around the kitchen, moaning the whole time.
It's a miserable show.
If you like to laugh, you should.
You know who's popping up a lot of...
The mom?
Where do you think any of them are?
We know the dad's dead.
Where do you think the other ones are?
We never heard from the rest of that cast ever again, man.
They just disappeared.
Not true.
The nosy neighbor was Jerry's mom on Seinfeld.
Okay, but the family cat.
Tilt your mic down just a little bit.
The mom, I can't even picture in my mind right now,
to tell you the truth.
Or the son.
Tilt your mic down just a little bit towards your mouth.
No, no, no, just on the stand, I mean,
just so it's pointed a little more at your mouth,
just because of the way you're sitting in this new chair.
Thank you.
But it's touching my mouth.
That's good, that sounds good.
No, the mom, the red -haired, I'll put it in the chat.
Hold on.
You know the mom.
I'll know her when I see her.
Mom from Alf.
I gotta tell you, as much as I hate the internet sometimes,
Google is truly amazing.
Type anything in, you'll find it.
I know how it works.
In case you didn't know, just letting you know.
Here you go, hold on.
I guess you got it.
Shared a file in the meeting.
You clicked a picture of Alf's mom.
Your coworker shared a file in the meeting.
Did you get the file I sent?
Potential security issue detected.
Oh boy.
Let's download it anyway.
Probably could have just Googled it myself,
save some time and energy.
Yeah, okay, I got her, I got her.
Yeah, Kate.
Look, she made zero impact on that show.
Oh, it's forgotten.
I couldn't tell you one thing
about this woman's personality.
Is she a neat freak?
Is she sarcastic?
Is she, I mean, obviously she married
below her weight class.
What do you mean by that?
She's a hot lady and her husband is a chode.
In real life or on the show?
On the show.
Oh yeah.
She's got, I mean, this show destroyed people.
She did four things after Alf.
Like, I think these people were like, I'm done.
I'm done in the business.
It's, I mean, the stories are so miserable.
But you gotta, who else was on the show?
Max Wright, we know, we saw Max Wright in other things.
Andrea Elson, the daughter.
Unfamiliar.
I don't understand it, you don't remember the daughter.
Really, you don't remember any of these people?
You love this show.
I remember Alf and Willie.
And the kid, cause I was a little boy and I related,
but I wished that I could have lived with Alf,
but that's about it.
She left the business in 97.
Benji Gregory.
Yeah.
The kid.
Murder, suicide.
He left the business in 93.
With a bullet.
Actually, he was on the Back to the Future TV series
of the cartoon.
He did 13 episodes of that.
Did he voice Marty?
Insane.
No, somebody else did.
Here's what's insane about the Back to the Future TV series.
Tom Wilson did the series.
Okay.
He was Biff.
He now is,
he now will do,
he'll do Back to the Future stuff now.
Like, you know, reunions and stuff like that.
But he did the goddamn TV series.
It's like, you're willing to do 26 episodes of a cartoon
as Biff Tannen, and then you start getting mad
when anybody asks you about you were Biff or whatever.
You know what I mean?
Like, I'm like, you did.
Like, if you're the guy that's like, I've moved on,
you're not the guy that also does the cartoon.
You know what I mean?
Well, I didn't know he was the guy who was like,
I'm not talking about that.
Oh yeah, he was staunchly.
His stand -up act, he ended with a song,
and it was like kind of funny,
but it was like, I'm gonna answer all the questions
in this song that everybody wants to ask me all the time.
And that was like the hook.
What's Michael J. Fox like?
Is he nice?
You know, like all, because he wouldn't do,
that's why in those like Back to the Future,
like the Blu -ray set that I'm sure you bought,
that we all did.
Yeah.
He's not in any of the extra,
he's not in any of the interstitials materials.
Because he was like, I won't do it.
Like, he won't, like he wouldn't do it.
Now he does it, now he'll do stuff,
but he wouldn't for the longest time,
because he was like, I am, you know,
I guess I am more than,
I'm not saying he shouldn't think that way,
but it's just weird to do the cartoon.
And Crispin Glover's whole deal was,
he wanted an outrageous amount of money to return
for part two, correct?
Yeah, I'm starting to wonder if Crispin Glover's,
you know, I was always on the Crispin Glover team.
Yeah.
With that scenario, the way he described it.
And then the more I hear about it, I'm like,
I don't know, dude.
Sounds like you tried to hold them over a barrel.
They told you to fuck off.
And then they put a guy that's -
Legendary nut.
Sort of looks like you in old man makeup.
And then you tried to sue them for use of your likeness.
And granted, when I first saw the movie,
I thought that was him.
That's right there.
You lose Crispin Glover,
there should have never been a Back to the Future 2.
You can't have, it's like,
that's where the series falls, starts to fall apart.
But anyway, it is, I don't know what side of it I fall on.
I do know this.
You can't get to where Spielberg is without,
you know, you gotta be a pretty,
that's not a position in Hollywood
that like really great guys get to.
You know what I mean?
It's just not.
I mean, Back to the Future was a mechist,
but Spielberg produced.
But yeah, that -
He points the finger at Spielberg
more than anybody, I believe.
Doesn't he?
Yeah, right.
I mean, Glover was no star.
Glover at no point in his career has been a star.
So I think he probably should have just accepted that
and enrolled with it.
But he was also a maniac.
You don't put a maniac as the fourth lead
of your family film.
You just don't do it.
He was great.
Perfect.
But you were pretty damn funny playing those.
Are you gonna see the Back to the Future Broadway show?
We just talked over each other.
We're doing that a lot these days,
we're talking over each other a lot.
I don't know why.
I mean, I gotta talk at some point, you know?
You're talking 100 % of the time.
Oh, please.
So I gotta get in there somehow.
Are you seeing the Back to the Future Broadway show?
The balls.
Well, by the way, it wasn't a criticism
that we were talking at the same time.
I was just saying, we're doing that a lot lately.
You like to turn a lot into shots at me.
What is that?
Why do you do that?
It's easy, it's there.
Why do you shove the people that love?
Stop.
I don't know.
You don't need to shove love, Pat.
I know, I know.
I want you to get a sign that says that.
I actually have a ticket to see it next week.
Oh, okay.
I am not in any way.
I hear it's fantastic.
I am not in any way excited about it,
but I'm gonna go see it and hopefully it's good.
Okay.
Are the, speaking of the Ukraine and Mike Pence earlier,
are people fleeing the Ukraine?
I don't know.
Because there are so many attractive,
but damaged looking young Ukrainian women on the apps lately.
Um, it seems like 50 % more damaged Ukrainian women
on the run have infiltrated Tinder
and are looking for men with money.
Do you think, and don't judge me for this question.
Sure.
I'm just speaking to the sick society we live in.
Do you think that those women were already on the apps
and that there's a percentage of people out there that said,
I know how to exploit the Ukraine thing.
This is an opportunity for me to stand out on the apps.
I'll get more clicks and interest
if I say the Ukrainian thing now.
I'm sure.
Maybe, yeah.
It's just the nature of the beast with anybody
in any situation like, you know, people take things
and use them to capitalize, but yeah, I don't know.
Um, I mean, I'm sure people are, they must be fleeing, right?
I mean, I would think, I mean, some people are trapped.
Right.
The Ukrainian gals online tend to be of the,
hey, I need somebody with money.
I need somewhere to stay.
I have a young child, please help.
And that's not really where I like
to start out a relationship,
is in the complete red zone.
I like to work my way up to the red zone.
But, yeah, I don't know.
I don't know, but they're out there
and they seem to need shelter
and Tinder does not seem to be the smartest place to look.
But what do I know?
Millions have fled the Ukraine.
There's refugees when a situation like this happens.
So millions have fled.
But it says, the part I was unsure about is to exactly where,
but it's like meaning the United States.
It says for the most part,
it's all fleeing to neighboring countries
because that's an easy, you know,
if you're in peril, you can flee across a border quickly
or much more quickly than you could to the United States.
So I would say that my theory could be pretty accurate here
that people are just going, oh, I'll put Ukraine and say,
say, you know, kind of make it almost look as if
I'm linked to the tragedy directly,
or more directly at least.
And that'll get me a little more traction on here.
But I hear you, it is kind of a,
it's not the best place to start with a first date
with help me please.
Help.
You show up and they're like,
yeah, so I'm from the Ukraine.
Just needed a little bit of help.
You know, it was getting crazy with Putin over there.
Yeah, you don't sound like you're from the Ukraine.
No, I said, Queens, you misheard.
Okay.
You must have misheard me.
I'd like to date a girl like that.
Like a show girl with that.
They're not really around anymore.
Yeah, where are all the show girls
with a Queens accent anymore?
Where have they all been?
Well, they were in every old movie about like old Broadway.
And then they were in Woody Allen movies
50 years after that,
but otherwise they don't seem to exist in the real world.
That's a good point, damn it.
Woody Allen, it'd be like a movie set in 2004
and Mira Sorvino would be like,
Woody, what time does the curtain go up on the big show?
I gotta tell you, I don't blame Woody for that one.
I think that's all Mira.
He's renowned for not really telling actors what to do.
He's very like, I don't care if you even get the lines right
as long as the idea of it is there.
I think that was Mira going,
I wanna try something here, follow me.
And he was like, okay, whatever you wanna do, maybe.
Maybe you're right.
You're going to the movie,
I don't have anything for the movie corner today,
but I have a hefty news psycho in its place.
But you do your movie corner
and then I'll do my news psycho
and then we can all have a good time.
All right, I saw,
you know what I'll do is the Blade trilogy.
I watched Blade one in glorious 4K,
then Blade two, then Blade Trinity,
which I had never seen.
And the OG Blade, I'm fairly certain we did it on the show.
I find the movie very funny, very fun.
I love the chemistry between Snipes and Chris Christopherson,
who apparently became dear friends off stage as well.
And Blade just feels, it feels like you could make Blade
today, I know they are making Blade with Maharaja Ali,
but I can almost guarantee that the old Blade,
the 1998 Blade is gonna feel more current,
more up -to -date, more exciting
than this Blade we're about to get, the new one.
It's like ahead of its time,
it's better than the current Marvel movies.
It's just great.
The opening blood raves.
One of the most memorable scenes in all of Superhero Dumb.
This guy who directed the original Blade,
really never directed again.
He, after this, did A League of Extraordinary Gentlemen.
I've always enjoyed that in that film as well.
I've enjoyed The League of, people hate it,
but I think it's a fun movie.
I have not seen it, but it caused the director,
Stephen Norrington, to say, that's it.
He and Sean Connery got along so poorly.
He kind of went the no comment, classy route.
Sean Connery said, this is why I never want to act again.
I'm tired of working with idiots.
That was his comment about Stephen Norrington.
And he never acted again, that was it.
He never acted again,
Norrington never really directed again.
Rumor has it that he's doing a Mad God type thing,
where he's creating like a full feature film
with miniatures in his home.
And I hope that he does.
I mean, I don't think the guy's Tim Burton,
but he's got a great visual style.
I love the way the first Blade looks, feels.
I love Snipes in it.
I love everything about it.
I just, you know, people, Blade doesn't come to mind
when you think of superhero movies for whatever reason,
but to me, it's definitely in the top 5 % of superhero films.
I love the OG Blade.
Two, you get a slightly lesser story.
There's not much going on in two,
but you get Guillermo del Toro.
The visuals on display,
he's a guy who comes in with something to prove.
Apparently this movie had a bunch of big fights
behind the scenes as well.
Norrington turned down Blade II,
Guillermo del Toro turned down Blade III.
This has been a very problematic franchise.
They can't get anybody to stick around.
And from what I hear,
and from reading the IMDB pages and stuff,
it's because Wesley Snipes gradually over time
has gone completely insane,
until Blade Trinity, when he fully lost his mind.
But I love Blade.
I love Blade II.
Guillermo del Toro was always slightly overrated to me.
I like his movies.
I love Pan's Labyrinth.
I think people go a little too far,
especially when you watch them all back to back.
It's like, yeah, the guy loves creatures, you know?
He makes weird looking creatures.
Can we all just calm down a little bit?
But I love Blade I, I love Blade II.
Blade Trinity gets a terrible rap.
But it's not a terrible movie.
Written and directed by David S. Goyer,
man who did Training Day.
If I, can I interject?
I think, by the standards of the day,
it was a bad movie.
I still think they were too -
I think that's what's going on here.
Yeah, too harsh on it.
But you compare it to now,
Blade trilogy would have a 99 % on Rotten Tomatoes.
Trinity, yeah.
Or Trinity, excuse me.
No, that's totally the case.
As is often when you return,
like I bet if I watched the league,
I've never seen the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen.
I bet if I watched that now, I'd be like,
this is pretty cool.
Same with Van Helsing, which I've never seen.
And it's supposed to be terrible.
Things that were allegedly terrible back then,
they don't hold a candle to today's terrible.
They really don't.
So Blade Trinity feels like a pretty average
superhero movie.
It's got more comedy than most.
You got Ryan Reynolds quipping a lot,
but that just seems like Deadpool
or any other movie that comes out nowadays.
You got Parker Posey, who I always love to see.
You got the gay dude from the Christopher Guest movies
playing some sort of vampire psychologist.
Who?
Michael, the Fran Drescher husband from the sitcom?
That's right, that's right.
I forget his name.
So it's like this really funny supporting cast,
Jessica Biel, who obviously gorgeous,
not bringing much acting jobs at the time,
but she's improved.
You got Patton Oswalt, you got Natasha Lyonne.
It's weirdly like an indie comedy cast.
And they're doing most of the heavy lifting.
Snipes famously, anytime his face is not on camera,
he had his stand -in do it,
which is very obvious throughout the film.
Wesley is barely there.
Allegedly he was stoned throughout the entire production.
Huge clouds of weed coming out of his trailer.
And that comes across in his performance.
Him and Kristofferson thought that Blade doesn't need help.
Why are they giving Blade all these sidekicks?
Blade is a man who works alone,
and if he's gonna work with a partner,
it should be Whistler, Kristofferson.
I personally agree with them.
But Blade Trinity's really fun.
If you only remember it as being a piece of shit,
be given another shot, it's kind of fun.
What I would say, I love the Blade trilogy.
Yeah.
I almost wish we would have just done it as an episode,
but oh well.
I love the Blade trilogy.
The Blade trilogy is a perfect example
of how you pace yourself with a franchise.
The first one is about Blade and establishing Blade,
and establishing Blade's operation,
and Blade fighting a very worthy adversary,
vampire, played by Stephen Dorff.
At the end of the movie,
Blade's right -hand man Whistler is supposedly dead
or whatever, and you realize, oh,
they're keeping Whistler alive in Romania
or wherever the hell it is.
Cliffhanger ending, boom, you're out.
Second movie, let's up the ante.
Now there's a new threat, you've got the vampires,
but now there's a vampire strain who feed on vampires.
So Blade has to kind of work with some vampires,
and he hates it.
Beautiful, here we go.
Crazier effects, little bit bigger, whatever.
Third movie, we're ending it.
How do we end it?
We're gonna have him fight Dracula, the ultimate vampire.
It's so perfectly paced.
And then also third movie is where
we're gonna bring in some ancillary characters.
We're gonna build the team out.
We're gonna set up things that might lead to a spinoff
or whatever it is.
It's so perfectly paced.
If they made that movie now, which they are making it now,
this fucking thing is gonna be, you know,
it'll be like, and by the way,
we're doing Super Mario Brothers today.
I never mentioned that,
but this ties into it, what I'm saying.
This fucking thing would be right out of the gate.
He's gonna fight Dracula.
There's gonna be the vampires that feed the other vampires.
He's gotta fight both kinds of them.
He's got a whole team.
This guy's got a story, that guy's,
it would be so goddamn overstuffed.
They'd pull out every stop right away
and then go fuck it.
Let's give them an avalanche to deal with
and if it does well, we'll work out how to go bigger later.
And then they have to go bigger later
and they can't and it sucks.
And there's nowhere to go.
It's, you know, it's really incredible to me
how these modern takes on these franchises
have lost all concept of pacing.
It's insane.
It's fucking insane.
Well, they think if they don't give you
the full come in the face money shot
right out of the gate, that you will lose interest
and you won't come back and it's like,
we gotta give them everything that's cool
about this property in the first movie.
And what winds up happening is that none of it hits
because it's just overkill.
None of it hits.
Blade, you're like, who is this dude?
He's cool, he's funny.
I wanna know more about, but you're absolutely right.
You're just dealing with Blade.
But it's not the, you get the origin story
but we're not spending the entire two hours
on Blade and his mom and that stuff.
It's very quick, tasteful.
If you're in, you're out.
You get why you should care about Blade
and then you move on to the action.
It's great.
I completely agree with you
about how everything is paced out.
And it's a shame.
It's a shame that this new Blade,
we're already shitting on it before it's even come out
but I just don't think it's gonna work out.
Everyone involved has tried to quit this movie.
I mean, granted the Blade franchise was troubled too
but everybody's like, no, I'm not doing the script, sorry.
That's like where the Blade movie is at.
They're like on set and everybody's like,
we can't shoot this, come on.
The new one you mean, this new one?
Yeah, the new one.
Well, and also Marvel has already misstepped
with a horror superhero vampire piece with Morbius.
Didn't work.
Right.
So I have a feeling all the -
And they wanted, sorry, they wanted Morbius for Blade 2.
I didn't even know Morbius was part of the Blade world.
Well, I promise you too, with the way these big studios work,
all the horse shit they couldn't cram into fucking Morbius
they're trying to now cram in.
It'll be like the day of shooting
and they're running over going,
we wanna put this scene in, let's get this scene in.
It's ridiculous, it's ridiculous
the way these studios operate.
Speaking of which -
Yeah, and then putting people in the end credits and stuff,
it's just like, to me it makes me feel
when I go to a superhero movie
that if I didn't see the previous 15 that I'm lost.
So the big, like the most popular entertainment now,
superhero movies, I still have to feel
like I'm not a part of it when I go
because I missed the last however many that came out.
Just a drag.
Well also, every superhero
can have an emotional triumph story.
That's the, I promise you they exploit that
with the new blade.
They did it in The Flash.
They did it, they obviously do it with Batman
over and over again.
Most of the Marvel superheroes, they're doing it.
It's like, I'm just so tired of it.
It's just like, all right, we get it.
They pulled themselves up from the tragedies of their youth
and became hero, we get it guys.
It's not always that, it's just not always that.
And it's really boring and really stupid.
And I wanna talk though, this new psycho I got here
is about, you know, I said earlier about,
you said Blade Trinity is not a bad movie.
And we were saying, well, by today's standards,
it's not a bad movie.
By the time period it came out in,
by the standards of then,
people expected a little bit more from their movies.
And what I find interesting with that concept in mind
is I'm reading, I read reviews of things now
and the reviews that are supposedly good reviews
are not good reviews.
You know, look, the best case scenario, or excuse me,
the best case example of this would be the Rex Reed review
that I read about Book Club, the next chapter,
which was very, very funny, very funny to read.
And we love Rex Reed here at the We'll See You In Hell
podcast, God, I would love to meet that guy
and try to get him on here.
That'd be so incredible.
But you know, I think it's, even though it's Rex Reed
and we, you know, I get it, like the whole gag is that,
you know, the joke is that he is a sort of insufferable,
not insufferable, that's a mean word.
I'm not trying to say that about him.
That he is an, let's call him an intolerant critic
and he hates most things.
And even when he likes something, he shits on it.
I realize that's sort of unique and indicative
of Rex Reed himself.
But I do think there's a weird thing happening
where, you know, it's like you read these reviews
of these movies that have come out
and they're supposed to be the quote good reviews
and they're not good.
And then because we sort of gauge everything
by Rotten Tomatoes now and the aggregator,
you know, a half decent review now counts as a good review.
And then a movie that you're scratching your head about
over how it has a 99 % or whatever it is,
that's how that happens.
So I looked up the Rotten Tomatoes score of Barbie.
I am fascinated by this Barbie movie.
I will very temporarily hear, and by the way, people,
everything I'm about to say about Barbie,
these are my words, they're not Pat's words
because I realize I might step on some,
if in case I say anything controversial, fine.
I'm owning what I am saying right now.
I read the full plot synopsis of Barbie this morning
on Wikipedia, it has a 90 % as of now on Rotten Tomatoes
from the early reviews.
I read the synopsis of Barbie on Wikipedia this morning
and Walsh, for the love of God, you're moving around
so much, it's really distracting.
What's going on over there?
People, we show you behind the curtain here
at We'll See You in Hell.
You're moving chairs again?
I'm setting it here so it doesn't move.
I mean, I don't know what to tell you.
All right.
It's hard though, because the screen is going sideways.
It's a busy day here at the
We'll See You in Hell offices, people.
Anyway, by the way, I haven't just been talking
this whole time, Pat stepped away,
and I'm only bringing that up because he made
that little snip earlier that I talked too much.
He stepped away, that's why I've been talking
nonstop for four minutes straight.
I was kidding and I'm having stomach issues.
That's okay.
But continue talking about Barbie.
I don't judge.
I'll be right back, but I'm enjoying the Barbie.
I haven't even seen Barbie, I wanna see Barbie.
You say whatever you want about Barbie.
I don't know anybody in the film.
I just wanna wait to read the reviews until you're back.
Okay, all right, be right back.
So Barbie is the plot synopsis,
and honestly, I try not to be one of these people.
I've already gotten into several arguments in public
with people over Indiana Jones.
When some bonehead says,
oh, the dial of diversity, or oh yeah,
because he's a straight white male,
they had to replace him with
Greta, not Greta, Phoebe Waller,
Bridge, and yeah, because Kathleen Kennedy hates men.
I'm like, shut up, it's not true.
You don't understand the movie, you're dumb.
I'm not threatened by a strong female character in a movie.
I don't know why you are, and I especially don't know
why you aren't in Indiana Jones movie,
when every fucking movie has had
a fucking strong female lead in it.
Why, suddenly that's a problem.
Anyway, I try not to be this guy.
Or that guy, I should say, but people.
I read the synopsis of Barbie, for Christ's sakes, guys.
I mean, what are we doing here?
The synopsis is that in Barbie land,
all the Barbies run everything, okay, fine,
and they have stereotypical Barbie,
I think is Margot Robbie's character,
and then they have President Barbie,
Kate McKinnon plays weird Barbie.
They have different Barbies, and all the Barbies
run the society that they live in, okay, fine.
The Kens all hang out at the beach and be pretty.
Okay, fine, who cares, I don't care.
That's kind of what Barbie is, right?
Barbie's supposed to be like the woman is in charge,
and Ken is the plaything.
That's kind of how the dolls work,
or at least that's how I always understood it, fine.
When Margot Robbie and,
this is the part of it that bugs me,
when Margot Robbie and, what's his face,
fucking Ryan Gosling who plays the main Ken.
By the way, the Kens don't have signifying names.
It's just Ken one, Ken two, Ken three.
Are we trying to be better or are we not?
That bugged me.
I'm like, so the Barbies have titles and things,
and then the Kens are just one, two, three, four, get it,
because they're just playthings.
They're just anonymous things
that are there to look pretty.
It was wrong when men did that to women.
It is wrong.
The way to write it is not to do it in reverse.
It's obnoxious, it's gross, I just don't understand.
Maybe I'm an asshole, whatever, who cares?
I'm not gonna make a federal fucking case out of it.
Anyway, here's the part that really bothered me.
When they go into the real world,
Ken sees that the patriarchy in the real world,
not in Barbie Land, runs everything,
so then he goes back to Barbie Land
and gets the men to revolt and take over everything,
and then the women are subjugated
then into lesser positions in the society of Barbie Land,
and then Barbie comes back and gets the women to also revolt
and they take back over.
Gang, what the fuck are we doing here?
You set up a reverse patriarchy, so is that matriarchy,
at the beginning of the movie
with the Barbies running everything
and the Kens being the little pretty dolls, right?
Then they go into our world
and they see that there's a patriarchy,
so then the Kens in the Barbie world revolt
and take over the Barbie world
because they don't want to be oppressed,
and then the Barbies go, well, how dare you,
and then they revolt and take over again from the Kens.
Isn't that exactly what the fucking commentary
of the movie is saying is fucked up?
I don't understand, because in the Barbie world
it's women running everything, it's not fucked up,
and the men shouldn't want a better role in society,
the very commentary of this movie is fuck the patriarchy,
so why are you saying fuck the patriarchy
by going we're gonna create a matriarchy
where then when the men say this is fucked up,
we feel oppressed, we're gonna say they're wrong.
I don't understand, and I also don't understand
why you're taking this brand that people,
for whatever fucking reason love,
I'm not a Barbie fan, I don't give a shit about Barbie,
and immediately turning it into half of that brand,
the Ken dolls, are evil and stupid.
It's like why, why not give them any, I don't, whatever.
I haven't seen it, I know I haven't seen it.
There's a pretty detailed.
I am, because this is making me so upset,
but anyway, the bigger point that I'm getting to is this.
All I'm saying, people, is I'm not saying
the patriarchy is not there,
I'm not saying the patriarchy is right,
I'm saying it's fucked up, and the way to prove
that it's fucked up is not to just do that now in reverse,
it's for all of us to be better together,
especially when there are men saying
I wanna help everybody be better.
It would be different if every man
was still stomping his feet, that's not,
and saying I don't wanna listen, that's not the case.
Some men do that, not all men.
Anyway, okay, so.
Every review is referring to this
as like a feminist screed.
Yes.
I'm sure there'll be all kinds of think pieces
about it going forward.
So here's the bigger point that I'm actually getting to.
I'm sidestepping into the plot of the movie.
I go to read the reviews, like okay,
well this thing's got a 90%,
let me see what the critics are saying,
because this thing must be a fucking masterpiece.
This is what a good review sounds,
now I get it, I'm only reading excerpts
because it's Rotten Tomatoes,
but this is what a good review sounds like now.
This is the bigger issue.
My bigger issue is with critics
and the way things are reviewed now.
While it's not as biting or sharp
as it imagines itself to be,
Barbie's plastic parade of camp and goofy hijinks
slowly give way to the kind of tender insecure emotion
that Gerwig is so damn good at.
That's your blurb, it starts with a criticism.
A fascinating movie, even if it is occasionally
a little frustrating.
What a gorgeous and fascinating mishmash this is.
These are the good reviews, what are we doing?
Why is the majority of good reviews I read right now
like backhanded fucking compliments?
Well it's not perfect and it's certainly a mess at times,
however, there's enough in there that it's worth your time.
What?
Yeah, it's this thing of we can't say anything
negative anymore, which extends even to criticism.
So they'll bend over backwards to find only positive things
to say about a movie or a show, even though they're critics.
And then Rotten Tomatoes itself spins average reviews
into positives and negatives into averages,
so you're never getting the actual viewpoint
of what the opinion on a movie is,
you're never getting the real thing.
But that's all people do, oh is it any good?
I mean it's got an 86 on Rotten Tomatoes,
somebody tells me that it means less than nothing to me.
Because it's just not real.
I'm gonna call out one critic for this line,
well she's gonna make your skin crawl.
Maura MacDonald, I think that's how you say her first name,
my apologies if I'm saying it incorrectly,
from the Seattle Times, this is her, ready?
Yes, Gerwig's Barbie is delightfully more than canuff.
More than canuff?
Yeah, because enough starts with E -N,
and if you put a K in front of it,
it spells can. That's fucking horrible.
Yep, and it's also this little shot at like,
we don't need Ken, yeah.
All right, so then go have a fucking movie of all Barbies
then if you don't need Ken, you need him for something.
You need him for something, you need him for something.
Even if it's to shit on him, you need him for something.
Well, it's a very weird thing to suddenly pretend
like Barbie is this feminist statement too,
that's never been what Barbie was about, ever.
They took, sorry, I'm sorry, go ahead, I'm sorry.
No, it's about a girl with unrealistic
and perfect bodily dimensions,
teaching our daughters from a very young age
what they must aspire to but will never be able to reach.
They took a doll that epitomizes everything wrong
with the presentation of image to young women
in the United States of America, and elsewhere,
and tried to somehow say,
this is now a tool of femininity, or feminism,
and it's insane to me.
I mean, it might be a great movie, I don't know,
but for Christ's sakes, let's stop pretending
like it's this virtuous excursion,
and I guess that that's kind of the point,
but I don't know, I don't know.
I just, I feel like it's like if you made,
you know, I don't know.
It's like if you made a movie about Speedy Gonzales
and somehow turned it into this really hardcore
comedic commentary on the state of affairs in Mexico,
you know what I mean, or unjust treatment at the border
or something like that.
I don't understand, why is this the vehicle
for the other thing?
Why are the two worlds colliding?
Barbie is like an Olsen Twins movie at best,
and Greta Gerwig has turned it obviously
into something much greater, and again,
it might be really good, I don't know,
I haven't seen it yet, but I just don't understand
why you take this and turn it into that.
I don't see why the two things need to go together,
I don't see the point of bringing them together
outside of Mattel is trying to do a Bud Light here
and really rebrand themselves for all the problems
potentially or inadvertently caused in the past
with this product, but.
Well, Mattel also just announced yesterday
that after devoting $30 million in development costs,
meaning this movie hasn't shot a piece of film yet,
but Netflix pulled the plug on the new
Masters of Universe movie, having not shot a thing.
So I don't know what's going on with these places,
I think what the big issue is,
is that nothing can just be what it is anymore,
everything has to be a statement.
I think just making a movie about Barbie
and how she's hot and it would have looked a lot
like the Charlie's Angels with Cameron Diaz,
just like showcasing hot women,
it wasn't ever gonna be that,
but I also don't think we have to keep acting like this.
Again, I haven't seen it either,
but yeah, acting like this is like the latest feminist text
that we all need to aspire to or something,
it is getting a little crazy.
I agree.
I'm going to see Barbie, I hope we do it on the show.
I agree with nothing can just be what it is,
and Masters of the Universe is a perfect example of that.
Guys, just let it be fucking He -Man and have She -Ra there,
and have She -Ra be She -Ra and have her be awesome.
Nobody's saying don't do that.
But to backseat He -Man and then be like,
wow, the show's really about She -Ra,
it's like, or Tila, whatever the fuck her name is,
now I look like an asshole.
They'll have it abroad.
This is new Masters of the Universe.
The new one, the Kevin Smith one.
This is a brand new thing.
No, this is a new thing.
No, no, no, I know, I know.
But I'm just talking about the last thing they did,
and it's like, okay, so you overly injected
the feminist stance into Masters of the Universe,
a show literally called He -Man.
Okay. He -Man.
And now it's in Barbie too, and it's like, okay,
so just let these things be what they are.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't wanna sound like an asshole.
I'm not mad about a feminist statement in a movie.
If you're gonna redo them,
if you're just gonna redo everything and remake everything,
then why are you also updating and changing everything
to fit this weird moral code?
Because then you're not redoing it.
Then why, it's all the more reason
to come up with something new.
Yes, and I guess what I'm saying is,
you can still have those elements there,
and you can still course -correct
without spitting on the thing.
Make Teela a stronger character.
Make her a more present force.
Okay, you don't also have to kill Prince Adam.
It's his show.
Can the guy have his show?
You know, you bring Seinfeld back.
You know, guys, we're gonna give Elaine
a little more of, you know,
a firmly -footed feminist character in the show.
Okay, we're also gonna kill Jerry off
and make her the lead.
No, you don't have to do that.
Let it just still be the Seinfeld thing.
Like, I just don't get it.
Anyway, you can make things equal
without making men the villain every time.
You know, you can balance things out more
without making men a piece of shit,
is something you could think about doing once in a while.
And that's what we're here to do,
is stick up for the men.
And today, we're talking about two Italian men
who live in or near the sewer and work as plumbers.
Their names are Mario and -
We're also talking about Super Mario Brothers.
Listen, folks.
Their names are Mario as portrayed by,
for some reason, Chris Pratt,
and Luigi as played, for some reason, by Charlie Day.
You've got a huge cast of characters.
You got Keegan, of course, in the mix.
He has to have a role as Toad.
But this is one of the first movies
where I've already been there for the,
let's dust this off and remake it thing once.
So when I was 13, they made Super Mario Brothers
with Bob Hoskins and John Leguizamo.
I was big into Nintendo at this time
and the Mario Brothers, and like everyone else,
I thought this movie was an absolute piece of shit.
Maybe it'd be good if I watched it now, I don't know.
The new Mario Brothers, I was like, who cares about this?
But sure enough, it's become one of the biggest movies
of the year.
It's parents taking their kids, blah, blah, blah.
Kids are loving the shit out of the new Mario Brothers.
Sure, that's a good kids movie, yeah.
It's a little kids movie, in my opinion.
I mean, it's a tight 90, and I was bored
out of my fucking mind by the Mario Brothers.
The kids in the theater were losing their shit
the entire time, and it's one of those movies
that I just felt like is for a much younger audience.
The jokes didn't land for me, the story,
they separate the Mario Brothers within five minutes.
It's a let's look for Luigi movie.
Let me start with the positive.
This movie does, in the right way,
exactly what I was just complaining about,
Masters of the Universe doing in the wrong way.
The classic thing with most Mario storylines in the games
is he's gotta save the princess,
or he's gotta help her while she stays over
to the side in her castle and doesn't do anything.
Sure.
Only a few of the games actually really bring her
into the mix as a playable character,
such as Super Mario Brothers 2 being
the most famous of those.
And she's a great character in that game,
she's my favorite character to play with in the game.
I like what they did with the princess in this.
They're like, we're gonna make her part of the adventure,
we're gonna give her, we're gonna make her
a strong character, we're not gonna make her helpless.
I thought that was great.
I thought they just did it in a really well -done way.
And it made me just look at everybody equally
and respect everybody, and I liked it.
I thought that was really, really well done.
You can't help but point it out
because so many people do that sort of thing
in a pandering way.
And to see it done in the right way,
I was like, yes, yes, this, this is how you do this,
this is really good.
Another positive I'll say about the movie is,
well, it looks gorgeous, number one,
but number two, it, better than any other
of these nostalgia movies I have seen,
it puts, it injects the Easter eggs
of the entire Super Mario Brothers franchise
so organically into this movie,
I was like, that's really well done, man.
They really, really did a good job.
And these things, every scene, there's something.
They use the music the right way,
the way they shoot certain sequences,
so it's from the side and it's kind of like
you're watching him go through a level of the game
is really cool.
The way they incorporate Mario -adjacent characters
like Spike from Wrecking Crew,
Jumpman, which was his name in Donkey Kong,
they just, they just did that really, really, really well,
like the little kid Icarus Easter egg.
That said, the movie is completely over -stuffed
with plot devices that would have given them
a really cool place to go in a sequel.
Now, it's Super Mario Brothers.
If they want to make a sequel, they'll make a sequel.
I don't think they will.
Mario, or Nintendo, excuse me, is notorious for like,
hey man, we do it the way we feel like doing it
and tough shit, like, you know, like,
there's a reason there's never been a Zelda movie yet.
There's a reason why they did this,
they did this live action outing once and that was it.
There's a reason why they don't put a Mario game out
every year as they easily could.
They know how to protect their brand
and give you just enough that you want more.
I don't think they're gonna make a sequel.
I really don't.
Well, no, that's not true,
because there's the Yoshi Easter egg.
They will.
Yeah, the very end is the Yoshi Easter egg,
so I guess they are.
But also, given the content of the games
and the fantastic element of the games,
I guess they could probably do
whatever they want in a sequel, the sky's the limit.
But I'm watching this thing and I'm like,
guys, you don't have to bring Donkey Kong
and Donkey Kong Country into the first Super,
we're here for Super Mario Brothers.
And I get that Donkey Kong is what spawned the character,
the game, I mean.
But he's not part of the games after that.
He's just not, except for Mario Kart.
Mario Kart's another thing they brought into this.
And I thought it was gonna be a quick little nod,
and then it's like, no, like,
the karts are gonna actually play a pretty significant role.
They bring Super Smash Brothers into this.
I'm like, guys, save something, save something.
Yeah, I agree.
I followed this stuff all throughout my childhood.
I actually knew it pretty well,
and I was immediately bored
because they didn't explore anything enough.
They just introduced 15 things that we all remember,
and they're like, remember this?
And that's about it.
In a 90 -minute movie,
you don't ever really feel like a story is being followed.
It just kind of keeps bringing up new shit.
And it does look really cool, visually.
But I just couldn't find anything to care about
or latch onto in any way.
I like the Jack Black character as Bowser.
The little song about Peach is very funny.
I hated that so much.
I am so over.
I like Jack Black, but I am so fucking over.
I mean, to me, he's all that kept me watching.
I am so fucking over every single thing he does.
They have to incorporate his goddamn heavy metal thing
into it, and in some way, he's got to do his skittity -dee -dee -dee.
That Peach's song,
if he could have said fuck for no reason in it,
like he does in every Tenacious D song,
he would have.
I'm just like, god damn it, guys.
It's not even a musical.
Why does Jack Black have to sing a fucking song in this?
Enough.
Whatever keeps the kids liking Jack Black, I'm fine with.
To me, it was one of the few comedic highlights of the song,
I mean, of the movie.
I didn't mind that at all.
But the movie did not make me laugh.
Not that it needs to,
but it's like the humor was very little kitty.
As far as them making another one,
this is now the third highest grossing animated film
of all time and the 15th highest grossing film ever made.
So they will make more.
The lesson that they have learned, honestly,
is why work hard on a cool story?
You just kind of got to give people the nostalgia
they want.
And to me, it felt like watching a friend
play Mario Brothers,
which is one of the most boring things you can do.
Watch somebody play a video game.
I didn't care.
I didn't believe in the brotherhood of Mario and Luigi.
I didn't have any emotional connection.
I didn't think it was fun.
I really did not like the Mario Brothers at all.
I thought that...
I disagree.
I think that they utilized the elements of the game
and what drives the games and the stories of the games
in the movie well to make a pretty succinct story out of it.
However, the execution of it
just wasn't that interesting.
For instance,
instead of giving me
a seven minute Super Smash Brothers fight
between Donkey Kong and Mario,
give me Mario going through one of the Mario worlds.
Show me the treachery of that.
Like he's got to go through the fire world.
Have him at the end have to go through the castle
like he does in the game and all that crazy shit.
She puts him through that obstacle course
at the beginning of the movie where you're supposed...
It's all the classic Mario obstacles.
And then none of them really happen.
There's the other part where she shows him
how to use the flowers to get the fireball ability.
And then he never gets it.
He gets it and it fizzles out and he doesn't get to use it.
There was just a lot of that.
And then the final fight is just him
and Luigi back in Brooklyn against Bowser.
And I like that the invincibility star
is like what gives them the power.
And I thought that was cool.
But yeah, I don't know.
I really liked the movie up until they end up
in weirdly in the mushroom kingdom.
And that's when I was kind of like,
they're not really doing anything with this.
They're just kind of there.
Yeah.
I did like the sort of Wizard of Oz quality of it.
He lands in this weird place
and he immediately meets basically a munchkin, Toad.
And Toad's like, let me take you to the castle.
But I was like, getting to the castle
should have been something.
But I felt like it was all in fast forward
because we got to get the princess into this thing
so he's going to go right to the castle.
And him and Toad immediately will trust each other.
So we don't have time to get...
Mike, there could have been all kinds of...
But again, if this is a movie geared towards an eight -year -old
or even younger, six -year -old
who doesn't have the time or attention span
and wants to basically see the video game
plastered up on the screen,
well, my hat's off to them, they pulled it off.
It's leagues better than any Nintendo -related film
that's ever come out before.
It's way better than The Wizard
and it's way better than the Bob Hoskins version
of Super Mario Brothers.
I still question why they got the two most Anglo -white men
to play Italian people, but you know,
this is yet another one of Hollywood's great contradictions
that doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, it says they scrapped Pratt's original accent
for sounding too similar to Tony Soprano.
Charlie Day's during production, they said,
hey, you gotta lose your accent too.
Directors told him it sounded too similar to Goodfellas,
to which Charlie responded,
all right, I think you're wrong, but fine.
So Charlie was asked to record his dialogue
many, many different ways
and then the directors selected the version
they believed would be best suited for the film.
That's the vibe the movie gave me.
Hey, we've cast you to play Luigi.
Give us 10 different takes of each line
and then in the editing room,
we'll decide what your voice will be.
It's just a drag, you know?
I agree with that, I agree with that.
I also think, you know,
in the vein of the John Mulaney joke,
but it's just like, what a waste of millions of dollars
that you could do God knows what with.
Make another movie, make a better movie,
feed people that need food, whatever it is.
What a waste of millions and millions of dollars
that you feel that any kid on earth,
maybe, just maybe cares that Chris Pratt is in it.
Everybody after Chris Pratt, nobody gives a shit at all.
You got Anna Taylor -Joy playing the princess,
she's a great actor, she's great in the role.
Thought it was Emma Stone.
Huh?
You would never know who it was
because you wouldn't know it was Charlie Day
playing Luigi, you wouldn't know anybody is in this.
Yeah.
But my point is, it's like,
the Anna Taylor -Joy thing to me was truly fascinating
because I'm like, you felt like you had to get
the hottest up -and -coming actress out there right now?
Like, you could've got like,
you could've got like a Net Benning
for a third of the price, probably,
and she would've been amazing,
and nobody would've cared.
She wouldn't, you know, it's like.
Yeah, you're telling a kid,
like, remember the Queen's Gambit?
And your daughter's like, no,
I didn't watch the Queen's Gambit.
It makes no sense, it never has made any sense.
So, anyway, my hog is not down for Super Mario Brothers,
but it's not up.
I'd say for the kids,
I almost said my hog is up for the kids,
which is a problematic sentence.
But you get what I'm saying.
As far as a kids movie goes for a six -year -old audience,
then yeah, I think it does the trick.
But I think it was, its intentions were to reach
to a much greater scope than that.
So I'd say my hog is straight out.
It's not down, it's not up.
It's just kinda eh, who cares?
I don't have kids.
I don't care about kids.
So I'm gonna review this movie
based on how I liked it, which is not at all.
I definitely could see why a little kid
would enjoy this movie,
but there's nothing here for adults, really.
It's not funny.
The nostalgia shit, it's not like I was like,
oh, I remember that when I played Mario.
I just didn't give a fuck.
Didn't care about the story, didn't care about anything.
Visually, it looked sorta cool.
But my hog could not be more down
for the kids and for Mario Brothers.
Folks, that's the episode out this week for me.
The new Salsa Windfall album, full album.
Please check it out.
It's called Artificial Birth.
The single is Mouth on My Money,
both available at all digital platforms.
August 4th, the album is out.
I also am on a huge tour starting in the fall,
or starting next month, actually.
Jesus, God, time is flying.
I'm going all over the place.
September 16th, I'm in Avenal, New Jersey.
September 21 to 23, I'm in Toronto.
November 11th, I'm in Philadelphia.
November 17th, I'm in Pittsburgh.
November 18th, I'm in Buffalo.
30th of November, Denver.
December 1st, Phoenix.
December 3rd, Salt Lake City.
And more shows might have been added since this recording,
but please come out, joederosa .com
for all information and tickets.
Thank you.
I'm on Instagram, at the Patch Walsh.
You can hear me on the Good Christian Fun Podcast,
discussing the movie Contact,
and the Miss Pat Show is now on BT Plus.
We will be back with a review of
Mission Impossible, colon, Dead Reckoning.
We will see you next time, and we will see you in hell.