Hey, look at that. It's your January bonus app. Yeah, fuck yeah, everybody.
Oh, you're looking good. Gonna sing you a song.
We don't take now.
That's the twist. I know. You did that earlier for me. Yeah, we recorded five golden minutes
of this podcast and Joe just deleted them. I worried about something. He said something provocative.
Yeah, sometimes I said, hey, Joe, you ever heard every other episode of the show?
Where you're passionately arguing to bring some slur back.
Oh, that was the depiction of the drawing that guy just did of us.
Yeah, that's right. It was like, I'm not, you know, Jesus Christ, I'm not that guy.
I mean, it comes up a lot. Come on, everybody.
Come up in that voice. It does. Yeah, we were bantering earlier. I was teasing Joe about his
Bill Haley in the comments album. And I was asking if, you know, on a Saturday night,
he dips a hand into the big thing of grease, slicks his hair back, enjoys a strawberry milkshake,
and twists around his apartment to Bill Haley in the comments before hopping on his moped.
And I said that I had it into the night. I do, but I'd say Zima with two jolly ranchers in it.
Yes, it was funny earlier. It was funny earlier. Really funny, actually. You'll never know.
Joe, just, I wasn't even consulted, just deleted five minutes of my life.
Well, you've made that call before. You've stopped and said, we got to delete this right now.
And I go, okay, I don't give you any shit about it. I just say, okay. I thought, yeah, thanks a lot.
I appreciate it. Now slurs that we should still be allowed to say. I'm kidding, folks. I'm kidding.
We're here to do the bonus app. I'm a little overwhelmed.
I'm going to Dallas smart to do shows. And I'm looking forward to it. And I'm not plugging,
but I will be in Dallas. And as I've already said on other episodes, you do a 10 gallon hat when
you're down there. Belt buckle. Okay. I have a whole outfit I break out for just for Dallas. All right.
We just had Patrick Duffy on the cool kids speaking of Dallas. He was fucking hilarious.
And then what I'll do is, is I'll have, I'll have, after, after, particularly, edgy joke.
Yeah. I'll lick my fingers and I go, that's a tangy real.
Okay. All right. You know what I mean? Sure. That's some barbecue. I'll say that.
I have all kinds of catch phrases just for Texas. I'd, I'd maybe work on them a little on the,
flight down. They work. I've done them for years. They, they always work. That's a tangy rib is not
great. Well, you got it. You do it after a, like a dirty joke. Right. Yeah. I got it.
You know, well, you say a little extra cream and that day to Sally. Something like that. Yeah.
That's good. Yeah. But anyway, I'm going to Dallas. And, uh, and I was supposed to come right back on
Sunday, but my friend, I get a text yesterday for my friend, Sal Volcano of the impractical jokers.
Big fan. You're on Twitter sometimes. And I'll tell him he said, hi.
Anyway, he texts me. He goes, hey, man, we had a fallout. Do you want to perform in the jokers cruise
next week? So I'm going from Dallas to Tampa to get on a cruise liner to do comedy on the way to the
Bahamas. Beautiful. In practical jokers. Do you get off the and have fun on the islands?
Are you staying on the cruise ship? Uh, I think you get off. I assume they let you walk off the boat
at some point. I don't think they're like, everybody stays on import. You know, do they do pranks on
the ship? Uh, are they like, we're going to, we're all going to die. And then it's like just in
practical joke. Yeah. They have, they have like a thing that shoots water. We sprung a leak.
Every man for himself. And you knock, you knock a child over the rails. Sure.
And they go, we're kidding. Sure. Yeah. Uh, I don't think there's pranks. I think there's just a lot
of comedy shows. Great line up on this thing. Oakerson, Jay Oakerson, Dan Soder, Steve Bern, a lot of
friends, Nate Bargatzi, a lot of friends on this thing. It's going to be fun. Sounds like a blast.
Yeah. So tomorrow, though, I leave for, for about two weeks and I'm a little overwhelmed, which
reminds me that Monday, that Sunday, I get, well, I get back on a Sunday or the week I get back,
the episode might be a day or two late, but we will try to get it out on time. But, uh, I apologize. I
did not anticipate being away this long and it just popped up yesterday. It's okay.
Is it okay? It's okay. Do you have any, do you have any, uh, criticisms about that?
No, I said, it's okay. Yeah. All right. Well, you said it with it. You push yourself so hard, you know.
You just, you push yourself so hard. Who me?
Uh, that's sarcastic. You know, kind of about what? I'm just, I'm yanking your crank. I'm jerking your
gear. I'm in a soft space right now. Folks, Joe and I, uh, are here. We're bringing your bonus up.
It's January. We got it in under the wire. It's not under the wire. It's a day in January.
It comes out. It doesn't matter if it's the last day. That's true. Well, people bitch.
People bitch. Right. Right. Right. The seventh. That means you care. That means you care. Start
episode is Joe and I really digging into those Oscar noms. Who's, who's nodded for what?
Who's nombed for the other? Um, I've brought an entertainment weekly, which used to be a pretty
solid magazine. And now let me read you the, the headlines from the Oscar magazine that a professional
writer wrote. What stars will be born? Will Glenn close in on an Oscar? Stop it.
Who's the fave or it to win each category? But favorite has a you like the movie, the favorite.
Oh, good. These are, these are terrible entertainment weekly. They're terrible. And you used to be
better than this. Uh, I don't know that they were much better than that, but they did. I mean,
I was a kid when I subscribe, but they always had great articles, great stuff. We're going to be talking
about, and I'd like to keep it kind of strictly to the Oscar movies because we can talk about the ones
that didn't make the cut on the, on the podcast itself. There's more than enough to dig into on this
podcast. I think we take it through the major cat, the major five categories. Oh no. I, we're going to
go a little deeper than that. Why? We don't have a host yet for the Oscars. Joe, have you thrown
your head in the ring? Uh, yeah. It was thrown right back at me. Folks. I needed your Twitter.
With this climate we're in, you couldn't pay me to host the fucking Oscars. I bet, I bet they could
pay you to host the Oscars. You couldn't get me on that stage. I bet they were like FBI background
checks on people. It's true. Nobody seems to want the gig. No, why would you? Then they're like, oh,
we'll get notorious, uh, sweetheart, Ellen DeGeneres. I remember thing I've heard Ellen
Genres is one of the worst women in all of Hollywood. She's throwing that out there. Yeah, no, I've heard
it. These people, I mean, there's no one more to face than an actor. Joe, what is happening? My phone
keeps digging because I had it on, I had the sound dog. You think maybe you could silence it for your,
your, your podcast, your professional podcast? Well, I didn't know the rear was turned on. The only
reason it was turned on is so I knew when you got here, I'm here, baby. And I forgot to turn it
off. I'm sorry. Sorry. I feel like we're in a raw place going into this. Raw. I don't feel good.
I feel fine. I didn't feel good yesterday. I don't feel good today. I feel, uh, sort of where there's
black mold in my apartment or something. That could be black mold. You're in a new apartment.
I don't know. And the thing is, it's never going to do anything permanent because you're always out
of the apartment very quickly. So whatever the problem is. Judgments from years from. You're not going
to seep into your long lot of judgments from your side of the table today. We're on a lot of judgments.
We're on a couch. All right. Let's start by talking about the best picture race as a whole. Now, Joe,
what, what do you think about the changes made to this category through the years? Do you feel it was
a good move to add the best animated feature category? Because I think they always have maybe one
exceptional animated film, maybe two in a great year. And the other three, you're like, what?
And I think that it's kind of bullshit. And if the movie is truly worthy, they nominated for
best picture anyway. Same with foreign language. Roma's nominated for best foreign language and best
picture. I don't think it's going on. I don't think best. And I don't think animated or foreign
language should be in best picture. Agreed. Because they get their own category. Agreed. And they're also
God forbid a fucking comedy. And there are also academy events around the world. This isn't the only
one. Yes. So I think like if a movie is not made here, what was Rome, Roma made here?
I mean, I know it wasn't made in a day, Roma, but even Roma fell, folks. Roma was not made here.
No, it was made in Mexico. Yeah, I think the movie should have to be produced here to be in the
contender for best picture. But even if it's animated, I don't think animated should be able to jump
into that ring. Yeah, I mean, I'm going to look this up here, but I guarantee three of these nominees,
you're like, that's not even a good movie. So best animated feature,
feature, bodici, Incredibles 2, which I heard was fine. I love dogs, which was worse than fine,
but looked great. Not a good movie though. Mariah, I don't know what that is. Ralph breaks the internet,
didn't see it, but like we talk in the best picture. And also Spider -Man into the Spider -Verse,
which I hope to discuss on this show someday. I know everyone in the world feels that it has earned
that spot. And many feel it earns a best picture nomination. I strongly disagree.
I think almost, and look, there's exceptions to any role, obviously, but I think almost any time
a superhero movie is nominated, it's stupid. Well, this is the first year they said that
a superhero movie has been nominated for best picture. In the past, people thought the dark night
was, but it wasn't. That was the year they decided we should open this up to 10 movies so we can
have more of the public's favorites as opposed to just artsy favorites, but frankly, 10 is too much too.
You look at the 10 titles, you're like, these are the best we could do. It's not the best. It's the best
of what they deem as cool kids stuff. So that's what it is. Don't use cool kids derogatorably.
That's my bread and butter. But yeah, I mean, come on. Look, a modern age superhero movie to
me getting nominated now, to me is almost like if you're nominating an animated feature.
So much of it is fake and not happening. I completely agree. And there are people like, come on,
man, really? Like, and they're so, they're so pained by numbers. It's just like every single superhero
movie follows the same exact fucking thing. It's like at least when Heath ledger won, it was for like
this weird, dark, like, heat version of a superhero movie. You know, like, it made a little more sense.
Like, well, this year, you know, I think many would say this is a special exception with black
Panther. It's a touchy subject. That's our first nominee we can discuss. I feel like
this movie to me personally, although I appreciate respect, love, it's place in history,
in having a movie with a black superhero. I realize how important, how cool that is.
It has been done in the past. I don't know why this was treated as the first, but
to me, it felt like largely just another one of these superhero movies. It ended with a big action
climax, blah, blah. It had a little more on its mind, but I found myself just as kind of checked
out by it. And I can freely say and admit it's because I don't like any superhero movies. But to me,
I don't think any of these movies should be in the best picture discussion at all.
And the same for me goes with black Panther. I agree. I found it particularly
glaring and out of place, because when you read the list, it's placed next to Black Clansmen,
which is infinitely superior movie, which is in your comparing it, you know, because of the titles.
But yeah, if you want to talk about a movie with it, it has something to say about race.
Well, that's my, that's exactly my point. And Spike Lee has made countless other films with all
black casts that are far superior to Black Panther. They could have, they could have, drive them as
days you'd be doing the right thing for best picture. You know, as usual, Holly would got caught with
the tan in the fucking cookie jar. They got called out for the, for the fucking bullshit, spineless
racist. They truly are. And they're scamored and nominate and, and praise the thing that was
right there that they could quickly praise and try to get themselves out of the water. That's,
that's all that there is to it. You know, it's Tyler, look, I'm not a big fan of Tyler Perry movies,
but that fucking guy's been making movies for 20 years, you know, and they're sitting there going,
we've never had an all black cast do well financially. What the fuck are you talking about?
His movie is obviously not destroyed. They make tons of money. What are you talking about?
Last summer girl's trip made $200 million on what appeared to be a $2 million budget.
Yeah, yeah, certain movies get assigned these places of reverence that I'm not sure that
deserve. And what it does deserve is sort of adding a very credible Black superhero and a movie that's
just as good as the others, in my opinion, it's just not my genre, but that's, that's a big step
and that's very cool, but it's they're not the first. And this is the first kind of on this success
level, which is great, but that's not really what the Oscars were supposed to be. This movie before
it was even released, they were saying was going to be a best picture nominee and it almost sort of
wielded that to happen. I don't know that it's earned. They were, they were not, not we're going to,
they added a category this year. Most popular film that people were going to vote on and so many
filmmakers came out and were like, really guys, like, are were the people's choice now? Yeah,
and they pulled it, which made them look even worse. Yeah, they didn't even have the conviction of
sticking with their new category. However, if they did, that's a place where Black Panther should
absolutely be. It was, it's one of the top 10 highest grossing movies of all time. But keep in mind,
by the way, everybody, keep in mind, this academy that is so concerned about race and progress and
forward thinking and change fired one of the only black hosts they've ever had on this fucking thing.
Correct. And about two days. So they're full of shit. But I agree with you, Black Panther is no
better or worse than any other Marvel film. I'm also not a big fan of the Marvel films and I'm
even a fan of the DC films anymore. Yeah, I do think it's a cool thing for kids and people in
general. I agree with everything you said. I just don't think it's a, you know, to me, it's like
nominating the last Jedi as best picture. I was like, I love solo. I don't think it should be best
picture. My favorite, but, you know, completely agree. I think the places where it should be nominated
and probably is if I look through them are costume design. Some of the most incredible costumes
I've seen, cinematography, you know, all kinds of set decoration, art decoration was all
incredible. And Michael B. Jordan, to me, this was the performance where he kind of came alive.
He's always kind of a sleepy actor to me. But I thought he was awesome as the villain in this and
actually so good that he made Black Panther himself seem kind of a boring hero in my opinion. But that
might just be me. So I'm moving with a lot to recommend. Not sure how it made it into this category.
But let's segue over to Black Clansman. For me, when I really looked back and scrolled through,
I watched a ton of screeners over the last couple of weeks. I've seen pretty much everything in
the discussion, all the best picture nominees. To me, it's not even close. Black Clansman is the
best movie of the year. The band and the best of these options. You don't think it's, I think it
100 % is. Oh, no, I, that's my pick as well. Yeah. Black Clansman's my pick. I found it riveting.
I found the story amazing. I love the script. It was classic Spike Lee. The end sequence with the
footage of present day real life David Duke and the white nationalist rallies and stuff like it was
a very, very moving picture. I thought he hit the race argument from a bunch of different angles
as Spike Lee always does. I think it's his best film since Malcolm X. Malcolm X is in my 10
favorite films ever made. So my picks for Black Clansman. I'm excited that Denzel's son is an awesome
actor. It's almost like we're going to get another Denzel now. Yes, he's a great actor. Awesome. Everybody
in the movie is great. The woman who I thought was a lock for best sporting actress not even mentioned
the sort of villain of the piece, the wife of one of the Clans. She's great. But yeah, you know,
to me, this is his best since I would go further. I've loved, I've really loved the ton of Spike
Lee movies, but I would say it's his best since 25th hour, which to me was a similar movie that told
it's awesome story and told it amazingly well and beautifully shot and acted, but also had a lot
on its mind. That movie was about 9 -11. This movie is about today and how it's not so different from
the past. But Spike Lee is probably the smartest filmmaker working today. I think the fact that he is
so smart means that when he misses, he misses so much harder than most because he's taking such
bigger swings than most. And the man is never one best director, which is kind of hilarious in a world
where, you know, like we give these awards to Kevin Costner, let's say, for Dances with Wolves. But
he's the best we got. I hope he keeps making movies in this vein. He kind of lost his way for about
a decade, and I think he's back in a big way. I didn't happen to everybody. Scorsese, he kind of
went off the course for a little while there and, you know, Dupalman, you know, everybody kind of does
it, but but I agree. I think clansman, clansman's my pick. What else we got on the list?
And there's no chance of winning, but it is my favorite. Next up on the best picture nominee list is the
favorite with a U. And one of my favorites of the year. This is not my genre. This is a, you know,
a period piece. Queen Anne in the battle to be the Queen's kind of number one bitch basically,
almost in a pimping ho type if you want to use a parallel. And the Queen is played by Olivia Coleman
from Peep show. She, it's just an awesome performance, a very funny performance, pretty sad. And then
you got racial vice and Emma Stone kind of vying to be her, you know, second and command basically.
Racial vice is awesome in it. I always like Emma Stone. I feel like she overstretched a little
in this, but I did think she was really good in the end. And it's just like a nasty mean vulgar,
trashy, fun movie and funny. It's really funny. It's really great. It's wonderfully shot by
the guy who did the lobster and Yorgos Lenthmus. Also, if you've never seen dog tooth, one of his early
movies, deeply disturbing, awesome movie. Very David Lynchy. Check it out. And this film, unlike his
others, is quite comical and funny and even light and farcical in places. And then it takes a
gets real dark. I thought we were going to get out clean on it, but it gets real dark. I think
Olivia Coleman, who I always loved on Peep show, deserves the nomination. She got, I think she's
got a shot at winning. I mean, she's really, really tremendous in it. She's showing some reason
that nominated her for actress and the other two for supporting. It's just one of these random
things. She would have easily won supporting. And it is a supporting performance. She's, everybody
does a great job, but she was truly wowing in it where I was like, that was a performance from her.
I was like, this is what used to get nominated. Like somebody going through the range of emotions
on camera and like, you know, also being able to physicalize disabilities and all these things.
I'm like, she's fucking incredible in this. Yeah, I loved it. And Nicholas Hout is really, really
funny in it. Also getting no mention, but like, as soon as you realize who it is, which takes a few
minutes, because he's dressed like a dandy or a fop kind of with a count makeup, just an incredibly
funny performance. Like, it's like, I've never seen Barry Lyndon. This is what I imagine Barry
Lyndon is like, except without you. Yeah. You know, he's so funny in it. And the the amount of times
you hear the C word in this movie, I mean, talk about a period piece. Folks, I, it's, it's, it's, it's
truly magical. It's a word that sweeps me off my feet. And they use it, they use it tremendously
throughout this film. And just, you know, without, without, and not sparingly, mind you, it's very funny.
The, it's, it's just a great, it's just a great movie. It's, I, the one thing I found odd about it was the,
I, I was trying really hard to figure out the decision for this. Did you notice the use of the
wide angle lenses in every scene where he'd have like that, clearly like a wide angle lens,
like, or panoramic in the up way up in the corner of the room. Right. I, I didn't get what that choice
was. I think it was, they'd stuck out. Like, you're like, oh, that's a weird shot that just covered
the entire room. It felt to me like just showing off. But also it's like, if you spend that much money
on those sets, you probably want to show as much as possible. That's a good point. But I dug it,
I dug the way it was shot, directed, acted. Um, and that's, you know, I, I've grown into them a
little, but my least favorite genre, rather than a biopic is British period costume dress.
I hate a period piece. And this really shakes it out. It's not what you expect.
Next nominee is Green Book. I discussed it on the podcast recently. You've not seen a question.
I have not seen Green Book. I think Green Book, you know, it's, it's embroiled in all sorts of
controversies now. Some I have read about, some I have not even gotten to because everything is such controversy.
This one, some of it is warranted. I realized. But, um, if you look at it as just a movie, I thought it
was entertaining as shit. Well, the writer wrote the thing about the Muslim chance or something.
Correct. And, you know, there's, they didn't, they didn't consult the actual Black man who the
movie is based on. They only got the story through the white man. And it's definitely feels like
one of these movies that to be fair, Hollywood has been awarded with Oscars for a century
where a white guy kind of saves the Black people. That, that's a kind of movie that's been catnip
to Oscar voters since the thing started. And the black guy, the Black character is sort of,
I assume, reduced to, because this is what they usually do in like a driving misdaisy or something.
They reduce the Black character to like the sort of wisdom post. I mean, honestly, yeah, that teaches,
that enlightens the, the problematic white. Yeah. Yeah. The rainbow quote a one best picture in like
1993. It feels very dated. The fact that one of the fairly brothers directed it, I think even adds
to that. It, it just feels like a, the kind of movie that would have swept the Oscars undeservedly
in the 90s. And now it's winning over the Academy again, just like it's been doing forever.
Fairly didn't direct it or bother. He produced it. No, fairly direct. Are you sure? And
co -wrote it. Okay, you know, the fairly brothers pulled his dick out in front of Camden. Yeah,
she thought it was funny. Correct. And there was a joke between friends. Correct. Peter Fairly classic joke.
A joke I'm playing on you right now. I don't know if you read this. The fairly brothers of, in
fact, become so unfunny. He meant this as a comedy this film. Well, that would be funnier if
Green Book was not up for, didn't win Best Comedy at the Golden Globes. One best comedy. Correct.
And well, he even raps the one best drama. Well, what else was nominated for Best, we don't have time.
Well, just we got to stay on course. No, Green Book is surprisingly funny. And as I said,
if you look at it under this lens of like a movie to watch with your dad and your wife or your
girlfriend or whatever, it's perfect for that. It just feels like a movie you'd watch on a Sunday
night with a cup of hot cocoa or something. Yeah, you're a cup of hot cocoa. You know, it's a little,
it's a little sanitized. It's a sanitized, would you say, for Christmas? It's a little sanitized.
I think that's what people's problem is. No, you get to Joe. So sanitize. Yeah. God, that's good, Joe.
But, oh, I'm sorry. I don't write on a big TV show. I would say the movie's well worth your time.
It's not a best picture movie. And of course, everything going on behind the scenes is not ideal,
but I'm just talking about the movie here. We discussed Black Panther Bohemian Rhapsody. Joe and I have
discussed it. We loved it. To me, loved it, but like again, we're talking about a movie that's just
frankly ridiculous. It's not a best picture film by any stretch. No, I love the movie. I wept.
I was not in favor of the film. Yeah. Given the press that was leading up to it, I lost interest in
seeing it because of everything they were saying about how they were changing the story and all that
stuff. When I got this, and I haven't been a Bryan Singer fan in a long time for many, many reasons.
But so when I got the screener, I watched it out of curiosity, you know, and you know the rest,
I cried and we loved it. And they watched it again with my mom and cried. But it's not a best picture.
I mean, this thing is a really good version of like an MTV. Yeah, if it were on,
or something, you'd be like, this is awesome. But it's it was a theatrical release.
It is probably if I'm being honest with myself, one of my favorites of the year just because it was so
purely enjoyable. But I do think Malik, I wouldn't be mad if he got best actor. Sure, although he's
sealing his own grave. He's lying to everybody saying he had no idea about Bryan Singer. As if his agent
wouldn't mention it or somebody wouldn't mention it. Complete lie. People see right through it. But
yeah, May got a bunch of shit too. The Singer stuff probably dropped after the voting was closed.
So the movie has a chance. It's it's won a lot of big awards. No, the Singer stuff dropped before
the movie even finished production. But now the stuff that people are taking seriously this week
just came out. It was like a fresh reminder. It's just a re but it's just a re -ash of what came out.
Then I know, but people are already in forgiveness mode with him and this kind of brought it back.
She'll have to back in your face if you want. Yeah, boy.
Roma, you have not seen Joe correct? No, you know, any any one of those like
gritty, heavy family ethnic dramas, it just doesn't it doesn't ring my bell. It doesn't
matter what the ethnicity is. It's just at any time I see that thing where it's like
the family. If they're not white, you're you're around. If it ain't white, it ain't right.
Now I've said it for years. No, but you know what I mean? Like any one of those gritty maybe.
Like the I'm Italian. They would always make those about Italian families.
Right. Brooklyn, like, these small films about a struggling I like Super Mario brothers.
You know, like Vampire and Brooklyn for instance. Right. I don't like that type of film.
It does. I don't enjoy it when it's the only type of small family movies I like are comedies.
When it's heavy drama, I'm not into it. Well, look, I was so even though I had heard from everyone
it was great. I was so not pumped to see Roma that I I eventually one night because I would drive
home. I would drive up to the store and like be like, I'm going to see Roma and then not go.
The other night I got in my car, backed out of my driveway, looked at myself in the rear view mirror
and was like, you're not going to go watch a two and a half hour movie right now in a four in language.
I pulled right back in the garage and went back in the house. I just thought maybe I'll never see it.
But then I did what everyone told me not to do and I watched it on Netflix instead of the theater.
Everybody says the Dolby sound is incredible. There's not really that much sound in the movie.
There must have been an amazing mix, but I don't know what people are talking about.
And then the images, you've got to see this thing in the big screen. So I watched it. I'll say I
liked it, but I would rather it have been 250 of the coolest photographs I've ever seen in an
art exhibit called Roma. And I could walk through and check it out. Look, I would have preferred it to
this movie. I thought this is what I keep saying about these directors. You want to paint pictures,
go paint pictures. You want to you want to take photographs, go take photographs. You want to
make a music video, go make a music video. But I'm tired of movies being praised because they have
beautiful imagery. That's that's one component in a good movie. Well, it's not a whole medium. Of course,
you know, I always say it's truth at 24 frames per second. I say that all the time. But I had a
professor in college who was who would say a movie is not a good movie unless you can turn the
sound and the dialogue and the music off and watch it and still love it and follow the story.
That's when I would say to him, I'd say, you know, what about Woody Allen or Quentin Tarantino or
you know, David Mammett or all these wordsmiths. And he was like, well, they should be doing the theater
because film is a visual medium. I didn't I didn't agree with him, but I this was a guy who always
was the guy who had the theory that almost everyone in every one of your favorite movies is gay.
And he could argue any of them. His best was John McLean. He argued John McLean being gay forever.
Hilarious man. But regardless, I don't agree with him. However, I can't dismiss how amazing
these images are. There is nothing wrong with saying a movie looks gorgeous. Blade Runner 2049
looked gorgeous. It was not a good movie. I'm not saying Roma is not a good movie. I have not
seen Roma. What I am saying though is I'm getting tired of hearing about it. It's movie after
fucking movie. People said it with Blade Runner. People said it with about the bad bunch. People
said it about I'm going to fucking drive and all that shit. You know, I hate it. What's the bad
bunch or bad batch? The movie. But I mean, people say these with it, but it was visually stunning.
And it's like, look, you'd never you'd never listen to a record and say, oh my God, it's so well
produced that I love it. You would listen to a record and you go, wow, amazing production. The song
is written well. What a performance. You would put all that together. So a movie has to be the same
thing. It has to be script. It has to be the vision. It has to be what you're seeing on the screen.
That's why I said, bohemian rap city, love the movie. Not a best picture nomination. Give me a
fucking break. Whereas you look at a movie like the favorite or black clansman. They're expertly
directed. They're expertly acted. The scripts fucking move and are with and they have wit and
pace and they twist and they took it's great. Every part of it is there for you. I agree.
I mean, but you know, you have not seen Roma. No, I know. I'm going off of the concept. I understand
the concept. I think, you know, what you were saying is true a lot of the time, but it's selling this
movie short. I would say this movie, I mean, this movie is two and a half hours. It's black and white.
It's entirely in a foreign language. It's got a lot of strikes against it in terms of like coming home
from a hard day at work and wanting to watch it. Sure. But I will say I'm very glad I did. I
basically took an intermission. I watched it in two chunks. I shut my phone off. It's that kind
of movie. And I was a little regretful that I'd not go see it at the theater because it's, you know,
it's as opposed to being a movie. It's like art. It's why they what they used to call the art film.
But I thought it was a really beautiful movie. However, it starts to get bogged down in misery and
tragedy about an hour into this thing. And then you see some just horrific shit in this movie and
it's miserable to watch and long. So, you know, you got to be ready for that. That's a fourth strike
against it. It ain't an easy watch. But it's timely. I love that. Basically, it was like, let's show you
a couple of years in the life or less than that of this kind of made that would slip in between the
cracks that nobody would ever pay attention to. I like those kinds of stories. I think Roma absolutely
deserves to be in the best movie of the year discussion. But, you know, was it my favorite? No.
I've, I occasionally like an art house film very seldomly. I talked about how much I liked
Nosferatu last week. But, you know, I remember seeing Pi in the movie theater just fucking hating it
for all the reasons I just rattled off about. Right. Anyway, I'll check out Roma. I mean, but, yeah,
you just, you know, your description of what transpires is everything why I've never watched those
family movies. Somebody dies. It's very sad. You get depressed. I mean, this is too much. What you're
asked to watch at a key moment in this movie. I don't wish on anybody. And I'm not even counting the
five minute dick flopping karate scene. A half hour in a just a naked guy dick flopping around doing
karate. Which I was like, all right, glad I didn't watch this with my mom as I originally almost did.
Our next picture, and I know you and I have both seen a Joe is vice. Adam McKay's vice.
Ridiculous. Ridiculous. The movie. I said it the moment. I mean, 10 minutes into this thing. I said,
it's just shit. Oliver Stone. It's, it's like an Oliver Stone rip off but 20 years too late.
Weirdly, it's like this whole style of filmmaking is going out of fashion. And it didn't feel new and
fresh. It felt like forced. And we've seen it way better and awkward at times.
Look, I thought the performances for the most part were very good impressions to me.
Yeah, you know, make up an impressions. You know, I'm a fan of everybody in the cast.
But I mean, this I texted pad halfway through watching and I go, this is film school shit. Yeah,
you know, there's like, there's like an over a voiceover saying like, who knows what Dick Cheney was
thinking in this exact moment? Unfortunately, we can't just break into a perfect Shakespearean soliloquy
to capture all the emotions we feel in life. And then of course, they do it. And I'm like,
this is this is making my fucking skin crawl right now. This is so corny. That moment to me felt like
like a commercial like, you know, like the level of writing was like watching a commercial for a
product like a peanut butter and they'd be like, and I wondered what that would sound like. And they
show you a little snippet. Yeah, yeah. But it went on forever. Like, if memory serves that scene where
they're talking Shakespearean lasted 45 minutes because it was so cringe worth. I don't know how
long it actually was. But I was like, God, this is embarrassing. And then Adam McKay is trying to
be this like sort of submersive submersive. Sorry, what did I say submersive? I mean, he was trying
to drown the viewer. Well, that too, that's a subversive filmmaker that, you know, and he's trying to
pull all these like sort of like, you know, as, as you said, Oliver Stone, like kind of young
Scorsese, like these little, these little flashy tricks that guys used to do before him and better.
And then every single fucking person that comes on the screen, who you know, by the way,
right? You know, every one of these people, they were in the White House for fucking or 10 years ago,
mostly all alive. You know, he does, he does like the pause, or he doesn't pause the frame, but
but he puts the tight, their name up on the screen and their position. And it's like, dude,
I watch the favorite spoiler alert, spoiler alert, spoiler alert.
I watch the favorite. The Queen has a goddamn stroke halfway through the movie. They don't even explain
it to you. All of a sudden, she's just got half a frozen face. And you're just like, I guess
she's really sick. Like, that's it. You got, you got, you got fucking dandy fops walking around.
And you, and they're not telling you what their names are. This fucking movie, like Rockwell shows up
as George W. And it's like freeze frame across the street. George W. Bush.
By, by president for eight, it's like, I know who it is. Sam Rockwell was like, hey, my name's George
Bush. Like, it was that, that level of obviousness over and over and over again to me. The few,
the few tonal swings it went for that I liked number one, when the credits rolled halfway through.
No, that was funny. And they were like, oh, no, this is how it could have ended if Dick Cheney wasn't an
asshole over them. That was clever. You know, it's kind of a Monty Python trick, but I've not seen
that where the credits come up during a movie and go on for so long that you sort of believe him
for a minute. But here's the bad thing. When the credits started to roll, I was like, oh,
good, because the movie was not holding my interest in anyway. Oh, and he does that hack fucking thing
at the end where Cheney turns to camera. Yeah. And it's like, I did what you wanted me to do. Yeah.
You, the people hired me. Right. Oh, it's so overdone and terrible. It's, it's high school theater
shit. So now we haven't been enjoying ourselves for two hours. And now you're going to yell at us and
accuse us of something as well. I also didn't care for the, the like he kind of picked
Adam McKay seemed to sort of pick or I guess you wrote the script, right? He did.
He seemed to sort of pick who he wanted to demonize and who he didn't want to. Right. And it was like
Cheney's an asshole. Longer be wrong. Yeah. But it was like the whole thing about like look at this
bastard. He, you know, he sold his own daughter out. You know, and, and, and let his other
daughter stand up against gay marriage and his other daughter's gay. What a piece of shit for
compromising his ethics. And then they show the colon pal thing where he basically lies about the
information they've gotten and which scares the shit out of everybody. Right. And he's like colon
pal would later say it was the saddest day of his life. It's like, no, he's a fucking asshole too.
Sure. Like, well, why does he get off the hook? So, you know, I don't know. This movie was W all
over again. It was, it was, you know, and W's not a good movie. It was about exactly as good as W,
which is to say not much. And what's frustrating to me is Oliver Stone's gonna make movies at about
that W level until he dies. He's lost his touch. Maybe he's got one more great one left in him but
will he get the budget to do it? Probably not. Adam McKay is leaps and bounds above every other
comedic filmmaker writer director working in this town has made as repeatedly made movies and before
that sketches that made me cry laughing. And I don't laugh that hard ever. But the guy has an amazing
track record largely with largely with feral. But for him to just say like, it's these, it's these awards.
It makes people sick in the head and they give up their true gifts and spend their life chasing
these stupid awards. That mean nothing. Instead of sharing with the world, their gift, which in
Adam McKay's case, is being one of the greatest comedy writers and directors in my lifetime.
He is just going to waste that now and make middling dramas probably with Steve Carell because they're
both doing the same thing. One behind one in front of the camera. Give me that Oscar and neglecting
their true gifts. And I think it's sad. Oh, and the god damn thing at the top like the key at the
beginning of the graphics. Like, you know, given the Dick Cheney's the most secretive leader on earth,
we, you know, we couldn't get all the information we wanted. But we did our fucking best. Yeah.
Oh, it just tries so hard. The stupid shit where they show like the model of the Oval Office
and they're putting the placeholders of the cabinet in and it's going ding, ding, ding. Right.
It wasn't a fan. Quick horror fun fact. In 1992, I'm going to ask you, Joe, you probably know. I
gave you too many hints. In 1992, this became the only horror movie to win the top honor at the
Oscar's best picture. What year? 1992. This movie sounds the way. Yeah. The only horror movie ever
to win best picture of the Oscars. But the actress just got what was the, well, that's the second. That
was the first horror movie to win a best picture nomination even. Okay. Horror is even more
neglected than comedy. And I'll tell you this, folks, whether you love or hate hereditary and I
understand both reactions, I myself can't think of really any other movie this year that I remember
more vividly than hereditary. And I thought it was pretty fucking awesome. But whatever side of the
nominated for best actors, what the fuck is wrong with you? No, I agree with that. And quite frankly,
I didn't even like hereditary. It should be in this fucking category of over at least the third of
these nominations. It's because, you know, the Academy probably, you know, right when you got to that
party scene, everybody was like, let's shut this off. And it is disturbing and unsettling. But
the horror genre can't be completely neglected. You're getting amazing performances.
Like because the kid eats the peanut butter in her hand. It's beheaded knowledge. Well,
that's not the party. See that's after the party. That whole party scene plus the drive home is
most tense. I've ever been in a, been in a theater in five years, bro, for that 30, 30 minutes.
It's about 15 minutes. 5th Joe. But you know, I mean, what are we doing here? Trying to have a nice
conversation. I bet, I bet that, that whole party, she's at the party a long time. You're forgetting
that part. Listen, guess who wasn't high as a kite when he saw it? It's about 50 because here's
why I know that. The movie's like 2 30. I bet I'm not a time it. I'm not. All right. But when you
describe that scene to me before I saw it, I was like, oh, shit. So when it started, I was like,
here comes this 20 minute party sequence. And I was like, that was like 10 minutes. They were in and
out. I was counting party drive home. Yeah. I'm counting head on the side of the road getting eaten by
ants. I'm talking the next morning when the mom goes out, finds her headless daughter in the car
when she's going to go run errands. All right. Well, that's, that's, that's quite a few. You're
into the next day. Yeah. I'm just saying that chunk of that movie. I mean, it's shut up. The
obnoxious teenagers in the audience. But I'm losing my point. Tony Collette, easily one of the best
performances male or female this year, I would say easily should have made this list. And I think
it's kind of offensive that she did. She should have. It's, it's disgraceful that a movie like
Mandy doesn't get any recognition from these fucking people. That is one of the most visually spectacular
things I've seen. And it's got a great script. And it's tremendously acted. Mandy, I would
love to see get some love and cinematography sound, anything like that where I knew it didn't stand
a chance, but where I think it most deserved the nomination was for Nicholas Cage. That bathroom scene
of him with the vodka. People would have snickered when they showed that clip at the Oscars.
But by the end of it, it's like, no, fuck, like this is this is what acting can be. That's,
that's my favorite scene of the year. Him drink a vodka in the bathroom. I fucking loved it.
Cage deserved it, but didn't stand a chance. Collette did stand a chance. And I think it's kind of unfair
that they, they shut her out. A star is born is our last nominated movie. Yeah. And see any yet, Joseph?
Didn't see it zero desire. Couldn't care less. I bet you would genuinely like it. It's really hard
not to like. And it's more. I would. I almost care. I bet you money. You'd like it. It's really
entertaining. And it's not really what you think either. It's, it's a good movie. All right.
To me, a star is born is the most again, though. It feels like it's 1992 again. You know,
it's like when the bodyguard and all this shit was out, like a star is born.
Yeah, honestly, one of the better movies I saw this year, but like it just being a top everyone's
list and Lady Gaga being on top of everyone's list, I don't know. I did think it was extremely
entertaining. And did that kind of adult romance genre that almost doesn't exist anymore,
unless it's a 50 shades of gray movie. And did it up right. The music was good. It appealed to
everybody. The performances were great. And then the side performances are what brought, bring it home.
Sam Elliott and Andrew Dice Clay. Love the movie. I think it deserves a spot. So for me,
what do I think will win? I think Roma will win. And I think black clansmen should win. Joe,
I would probably agree with you, even though I haven't seen Roma. I feel like there's so much
buzz around it. Then also given the controversy about it being the Netflix movie that made it in for
the first time. Right. I feel like Roma might take it. I also, I also think Green Book might take it.
But I think it's got a shot. They'd be there to be an uproar, but it's got a shot. Black clansmen
deserves it. What is your opinion of easily the most controversial best picture winner of the past
10 years or so crash? Did you like crash? Yeah, I enjoyed it. I like crash. Yeah, I liked it. What do you
mean by contour? Like people were, people were and still are furious and consider it one of the worst
movies ever to win best. Crash? Crash. It's a pretty tight film at the end of the day. I mean,
the Boyle's racism down to us. I mean, every one of those segments is basically you take like a racist
joke and you just you just turn it into like a sketch. But like everyone that broke back mountain should
have won because that was the big cause that year. I love broke back mountain. I like it a whole lot
more than crash. I I wasn't furious. Crash to me seems like exactly the kind of simple -minded movie
about race that the Academy always votes. And we'll probably vote Green Book as well. You know,
I think it's got a very good chance. I think Roma will win. Well, what one last year?
I used to care so much and now I care so little when I watch what one last year.
The hell was even nominated last year? Look it up, Joe. While I read the best director nominees,
they are as follows. Alfonso Cuarón, Pada Roma, Adam McKay, believe it or not, for Vice, outrageous.
And McKay the other night had searched Vice on Twitter and was going after anyone who had made a joke
about what he was like, hey, fuck you, man. We don't need your negativity. And I'm like, dude, you're
going after Twitter trolls. I get it, but stop it. That's my advice. By the way, what statement are
you making, Adam? The guy is not in the fucking White House anymore. Correct. You know, it's like, I don't get
all right. Yeah, we all know. We all know the story. It's awful. You know, like, you're not doing
anything about present. Yeah, forget it. God damn it. Yorgos Lentimos Spike Lee, baby, and Pavel
Lowsky for Cold War, which a dude at work saw and hated said was pretentious. I have not seen it.
For me, you know, a lot of times these awards are given to somebody who's deserved it for a long time.
I don't necessarily think that's fair because they don't always deserve it. However, in this case,
the long -time person who should have won one by now and the most deserving nominee, to me,
is clearly Spike Lee. Wow. And guess what? I go back to last year. Yeah. And it is, in fact, the movie
I'm most defended by waiting best picture. Which the shape of water. Oh, to me, the shape of water is
one of the worst ever to win ever to win the crown. Most awards in one or the most in one,
one, four words was nominated for 13 Oscars. Just criminally insane. Not even close to the top of
Guillermo del Toro's filmography. Not even close. Last year also featured Dunkirk. Oh, Dunkirk,
I like Blade Runner 2049 darkest hour. Blade Runner was up for best picture. No way.
What are you even looking at, Joe? I'm just reading pictures. Look at your Netflix kill.
No, I'm reading pictures that won. You're all over me today. Reading pictures.
Francis McDorman won, lectured everybody on diversifying casts. She consistently appears in all white
movies all the time constantly. What else was known? You see, everybody today was like, I vow to work in a
movie directed by a woman in the next year. All these people are putting this up and I'm like,
what if you don't get a role in a movie? What obnoxious assumption? Well, obviously, I'll be in a movie,
so I'll do it with a woman. It's like, I find the whole business crazy. I can't explain that
very much. How many women got nominated this year? Zero. Folks. Zero. I can explain that very easily.
That is the fucking scumbag actors ploy to get a job. Yeah. It's so transparent this
shit. It's so gross. All right, shape of water was nominated. Yeah, that's like the think a director
will be like, oh, come over and then they got a job. You're right. Call me by your name was nominated.
Darkest hour. Dunkirk. Get out. Ladybird. Phantom thread. The post and three billboards outside
Ebbing. How would announce you've hired a woman to direct your movie instead of pledging to and
putting it on the women almost half the episodes of my show this year, 22 episodes were directed by a
woman. It was very easy to do took chances on people who'd never done it before, but it was very easy
to do. You don't see me talking on Twitter about it. You do see me talking my podcast about it. I'll
give you that, but it took me a long time to bring it up. Joe, I think you'd agree with me. Spike Lee
deserves to win. I would hope so. And I can almost guarantee it'll go to Alfonso Quaron who already
won for gravity a much lesser movie, which shouldn't have won best picture either. And I believe it did.
But I mean, Spike just deserves it. And if this was Alfonso direct. Roma. Oh, he directed Roma. Yeah,
but he also directed gravity a few years back and won. Oh, gravity. I hate gravity. I liked it. Okay,
I don't know why we're not talking about it at all three years down the line. I didn't hate it. I just
was like, who cares? To me, best picture, I think Ebert used to say this to. It should be decided five
years down the line or 10 years down the line. It's the only way to know. But people are always and we've
been talking about it ourselves. What, but is it really a best picture type movie? To me, you know, it
shouldn't be that way. It should be people choosing their actual favorites. And also not from
a pre -selected stack of DVDs that you get because a movie that they didn't send out a screener for
has to my knowledge never been nominated for anything. You have to play the game, spend a lot of money
and send out these DVD screeners to people. And it's kind of shitty. You're buying people. Like,
you get on the list of for your consideration by sent by marketing yourself and sending out DVDs.
That's not, it shouldn't be the way we decide the quality of something in my opinion.
No, no, it's, I've seen people I know personally try to campaign for their own,
you know, they get considered for something and then they, they started online campaign to get
an actual nomination. I mean, it's, it's nuts. Yeah. It's nuts how this all actually works.
You know, so whatever. Listen folks, we, we, we, we were an hour in here. We didn't even get to
the actors or anything. I think a second episode is, is in order. And I think your February bonus
app is going to be Oscars part two because they don't come out to late at February anyway.
Maybe even March. We'll get it to you early in the month. It's got plenty of time to take our picks
to the track. Yeah, we'll get it. I think they're late October, February. So we'll get you,
we'll get you on part two of this in early early, early ish feb. And, uh, what do you think of that?
I like it. We'll, uh, we'll see you back on the regular podcast and we'll see you in hell.