Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hi everybody, Joseph you all know we're gonna talk over this movie correct we
were worried that you wouldn't and you would hate our guts. Pat stand up for
this part. It's the first ever live the live recording of we'll see you in hell.
We've been working on a lot as we might as well show them off. Have you guys heard
the podcast before or you just listen that's if we reach one person that's all
that matters.
Two.
Thank you so much.
Amazing people are here at 8 .20 in the morning.
Yeah.
That's awesome.
And give it up for Fangoria for bringing us out and having an awesome podcast network.
Yeah.
These prizes sound like they are worth more than the price of admission, so you're already winning.
But bomb horribly and you'd already be winning.
Yeah.
And we will.
I have to appreciate the level of maniac that comes out for an 8 .20 screening of maniac
cop.
Well, I assume their maniacs just scrolling the newspaper for other maniac events
Maniac cop okay, sure I'll do them the people in the theater that's that's all they're doing all days looking for screenings of maniac cop, too
So maniac affiliated
Are you guys excited to watch this?
Let's get the energy up
It's 8 .20 in the morning who's drinking we're drinking already we've we've had a couple down here already
Has everybody seen many at cop tour, are there any newbies?
Okay.
We want to have a good time this week.
It's great movement.
You were at Silver Bullet last night.
You were blown away by Silver Bullet.
This movie is going to fuck you up.
This is really going to...
You're not going to know what to do after this.
Go to sleep.
I want to tell a really quick, just intro...
the horror fest story. We should share a quick horror fest story. Go ahead.
And for those of you listening at home, this is when you want to queue up maniac cup too,
so you can watch along with us, right? So we're, uh, that's not going to work because,
yeah, for who cares? All right. Uh, so I'm in the hotel last night, the front desk, this, this
90 -year -old man walks in and, uh, he goes right up, I'm just in the middle, I'm in the middle
checking and he walks up he goes, excuse me. Can I have this cup? Just takes a
plastic cup. The clerk's like, yeah, it's a plastic cup. He goes, no cups in my
room. Astounding. Not a one. And the guy goes, all right, I'm sorry. And he goes
here, they wanted me to give you this envelope. And he goes, what the hell is it? And the
guy goes, I don't know. They just told me to give it to you. The guy goes, what's in
And the guy goes, I don't know.
And he goes, all right, but I'm taking the cup, okay?
He's like, yeah, we get on the elevator.
It's me him and another guy.
Hold right up.
Just dissertation about how there's no cups in the room.
Sure.
And I go, I go like this, I go, not even.
And he goes, not even in the bathroom.
And I go, that's amazing.
That's what I was just gonna ask you.
Not even glass the bathroom.
And then he goes, you gonna eat breakfast next door tomorrow?
It's very good.
And I said, I don't know.
I got to do this screening at 8 .30 and he goes, oh, Christ, God bless.
And he gets off the elevator and the other kid goes, bartender from the Shining.
Yeah.
He's here.
And that was like one of the most chilling characters in the Shining is like a sort of cat -skilly
zinger, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
The twins from the Shining are here as well.
I have not yet seen them or met them.
Anybody who's seen them?
Okay, great.
I would love to.
everybody keeps saying they're very sweet. I look forward to meeting them. Do you have a good story?
I know you do, Pat. Well, I woke up this morning and I had a night bag. Oh, you know,
whenever you bring on a trip. And I had a little tiny pocket cologne from a previous trip where I might
have thought I would get laid and didn't. So I had this little thing and it had gotten loose in the
bag and my toothbrush that I kicked my day off with at 7 .15 was coded in cheap
sample column and that's what I'm tasting even after drinking a bloody
Mary. I taste horrible column. That's my story. Now you got another one. Can I tell
the other one? I'll tell you. Okay. All right. There's a way better story that
I made love to Robert England last night.
I made sweet love to Robert England.
Did everybody like the horror -themed rock songs before the screening?
Today, a little Abercadabra, black magic woman?
Abercadabra, does that really count as horror?
It's a got a mysterious, mysterious theme.
I'll give you an out of horror.
Pat and I had fun doing a little ad -lib down here where Santana was trying to explain
that he was saying it was a black woman that did magic and they kept they wouldn't let
him emphasize the right syllable. He was hidden black way too hard and they were like Carlos,
baby. It's the 70s man. No, I like her man, I like it.
All right guys, let's all just yell and get our energy up and let's get into Maniac
Cup 2.
How about that?
So on 3, 1, 2, 3, scream Maniac Cup 2!
Let's do this.
that tapered off very quickly how you doing Joe I'm well good I'm well I'm
surprisingly awake I like this that you can get food in the theater is this your
first time in an I don't know I went to one in Austin that I loved what did you
You see, I saw Aloha, which is the worst movie I've ever seen in my entire life.
Aloha, the Bradley Cooper movie?
Sure.
Anybody see Aloha?
Just terrible, wasn't it?
It was a romantic comedy and you couldn't follow it.
Sorry about this incident.
Little trailer for Carrie.
I forgot how scary that shot was.
Cissy Spacek. What are your thoughts?
I love her. She's great. Of course.
She's great. Where's she been?
She's in stuff all the time.
I'd like to see a sequel to Carrie now.
Cissy Spacek, like old Carrie.
What we got it called the rage Carrie too.
No, but that was a new Carrie.
Yeah.
I'd like to see like Carrie.
She's in a nursing home. They're all mocking her. She sets it on fire. I think it's a great idea.
There's those there's a tiny twins
We're sitting very close to the screen
Is this too close for you? No, I'm all right. No, it's too close to you. Oh
Oh, God.
What a cocksucker.
So this is Maniacop too, or as it's known in 2015,
regular cop too.
So I'd like to start with some political humor about it.
You see, because cops kill people all the time.
Take it easy, Pat.
that. Straight up a nice up the middle podcast here. I did it was a sharp commentary. Thank
you. That's from my daily show packet. I think I like about the Alamo theaters. There's
the first theater ever went to that did these like old school retro bumpers. Now every theater
does it. But Alamo, I think, started it. What they could use is a let's go out to the lobby with
the singing candy. Yeah. Yeah. What I could use is another screwdriver. All right. Here we go.
We're in. It's happening. This is your recap of maniac cop ones ending.
By the way, is this a dream note from a studio if you're a writer? We want the first six pages to
just be the last six pages of the other movie.
Yeah, and we'll pay you again.
They also show the entire sequence
of the maniac cop getting shipped in the shower.
They show the exact same sequence.
That's not in part one, is it?
It is in part one.
It is?
Yeah.
I thought it was only in part two.
I love the hand.
I want it more ugly on the face in maniac cop one.
You get it.
You know, we got a couple tears.
I learned in my research I did on the drive -over here that this movie was not
theatrically released. It went straight to video and HBO. Many at COP2.
Many at COP2. Yes. Four million dollar budget straight to video. I'd like to
point out to that we're under two minutes into the film. We've already seen three
people go up on harnesses through the air. Yeah. I love that. Somebody gets
punch they fly through there I love it I love it too. Bruce Campbell man's man is
real now now you think the physics of that works that you could be stabbed by
a rock if you drove into it fast enough I don't know I hope to never know I believe
a real man goes off the side of the truck here when it goes into the that's a
real guy that's very impressive great stunts in the maniac cop series well he
died so wasn't that wasn't that great a stunt look that's a real guy man I know
Joe that's one of those we got one take to do this don't fuck it up yeah but
I don't like water that was him flying through the air
All right, now we're into that.
That's how you open a picture, folks.
Here we go.
This was kind of like going by the Evil Dead 2 Evil Dead model.
It's almost a remake because there's a lot of very similar elements,
but it works as a sequel as well.
You know what, Pat?
I don't agree with that at all.
I believe this is a true sequel.
I guess I'm just saying because they show that entire shower sequence,
which I was just baffled by.
Hey, I'm never complaining about a second play of a shower sequence when I'm in in prison.
Yeah, I was watching this on the plane on your iPad and I'm like, okay, this should be pretty safe.
There's a 20 -minute strip club sequence, so I'm angling the iPad to the window, hoping no one sees it.
And I finally shipped it back and I'm like, okay, now we're safe.
20 -minute shower man's ass stabbing sequence.
right. It's like, well, not that not the kind of stabbing you think we mean. No, no, no,
in an old male prison. Sure. Robert Davie of Goonies fame. Yeah. I once was in a bar in New York
with the guys that host Red Eye, which was a Fox show that used to have a lot of comics on.
And I was absolutely shit faced. And after we left, they said, do you know who you were just
drinking with that was Robert Dove of Goonies.
I was like, I recognize Robert Dove of Goonies.
I was like, I talked to that guy for 40 minutes.
He was yelling at me.
Matt Cordell, not an icy cold name.
It's a terrible name for like a, Freddie Krueger.
And then you got Matt Cordell.
Jason Voorhees, Matt Cordell.
Sounds kind of like a dick.
Yeah.
Well, he is a, he's a maniac is what he is.
He's a maniac dick Charles Napier.
Charles Napier was in every movie from 1970 through 1985.
Who is Charles Napier?
He was one of the not see, no one of the cops
and blues brothers, I know that much.
And he was just in a lot of like Robert Altman movies.
OK.
He'll kneel down when he say, he's holding him out
when he's hosting the strip club.
No, the show.
I love the guy hosting the strip club.
I guess they just told him to improv.
You'll see when we get there, he's like,
Isn't she beautiful? I was watching it with subtitles and 80 times the subtitle was isn't she beautiful folks
It's like come up with something new to say
Isn't it look at her isn't she beautiful? I
Got chat away. I auditioned to DJ at a strip club once. Oh, wow
I was 22 and the guy that ran it the guy the like the main DJ fucked me out of the job. How so?
he like would tell me to do stuff and then I'd do it and he'd be like you don't
ever want to do that. And I was like I get it. It's your turf in here. He didn't
want me getting any of that sweet stripper stripper play that I guess he was
getting. Was that a low point for you? Not getting the callback for the stripper
DJ audition? It was a high point that they even brought me in for the first interview.
I didn't care. Okay. Driving to work the other day to my writing gig told my
like the guy Carpool with, we're doing a screening of maniac cup too for my podcast
and he goes, never seen it, not familiar.
But what else did William Lustig direct?
New William Lustig, no fucking clue what maniac cup one or two was though.
That's odd, isn't it?
It's a big Lustig buff.
Do you know what else he directed?
I know he directed maniac.
He also directed Uncle Sam.
Oh, Uncle Sam wants you to die.
That's the tagline.
hologram boxes uncle Sam once you I think it's just dead. Yeah, you know the
media cop's tagline. No, it's the best tagline ever. Ready? Yes, you have the
right to remain silent forever. That's good. It's fucking great. I used to
live on Dr. Giggles. The doctor is out. Dot dot dot of his mind. And I remember I
said to my mom, I was a little kid. I said mom, you know, they also could have made
the doctor is in dot dot dot saying that's better and she said that's really
good because yeah I fucking know mom that's when you knew you were gonna be
right at it. Dr. Giggle I mean what were they doing to me as a kid in in the 80s I
mean they got they that guy played the retarded guy L .A. Law Larry Drake yeah
and then they got him there's the bad guy and dark man and Dr. Giggle it was
spinning me in all kinds of directions as a kid I couldn't handle it well actress
play different types of roles, Joe. Is it wrong that I said retired it? It's not great and you're
saying it again now. Let's move past it. Mentally handicapped is generally preferred. This guy
stole a gun from a civil war museum right to a convenience store to rob it. You know you can't,
he's got pocket hair combs on the wall behind him. You can't find those that a convenience store anymore.
Got these days. Used to be going to a convenience store, you pick up a pocket hair comb.
We talked about this this sequence earlier. This drives me crazy. It's guy gets into the car with this wonderful pizza feast
They get a call
Why does he do that
Save it for after you make the bust. You have a celebration with some pizza. It is insane put it in the back seat
Well, you know how pizza tastes terrible when it's cold. No way. It's even better
That's the only thing in this movie that strains believability for me was that they threw
the pizza out the car window.
This guy's teeth, just a black magic marker job.
I believe his teeth really look like that.
Okay.
That's my...
We were also trying to figure out earlier what drug he's on.
It's a drug I haven't done.
I felt messy to me and the teeth also indicate that, but was meth around in 1999.
I think it's always been a road, okay, to try a different name.
You know, I briefly worried today I took my probiotics in the morning and I worried
that I had taken a molly from a previous trip to Las Vegas and I worried that this podcast
was going to be real crazy.
I love that you're flying around wheeling nilly with molly in your bag.
Well I put it in a pill thing and you can't tell the difference but that's a problem because
you could just take it by accident.
So if I start making out with you, you'll know, you're a bad man.
The guy auditioned, the guy that auditioned for the shop clerk role, went and said, now
listen, you know, Hispanic actor, this will be a respectful, not racist stereotypical
role, right?
Yeah, of course, yeah.
No, no, go ahead.
Go ahead.
No, you're good.
It'll bring a lot of pride to your family.
There he is. First sighting in the maniac cup. Thank God you got here. Never
mind if there's fog on the floor. I, uh, oh, why does nobody notice the fog on
the floor? It drives me crazy. It could be coming out of the freezer, a particularly
overactive freezer section. Goodness is its own reward. Not today. Yeah. I love how
there's a full shootout and the guys still very focused on the lottery
ticket. Yeah. There's also a deformed zombie standing in front of him. Yeah. It's
not that dark in the store. Yeah. The fog is on the floor. There's also a red light
coming up from the bottom of everything.
Can't make up the guy's face at all.
This guy, I mean, just takes his life
and it was on hands right here.
Now my question I had throughout is,
does the maniac comp just sense that crimes
are going on or how does he keep showing up
as crimes are happening?
You know, they never explain it.
It's like a Superman kind of thing.
Right. He just knows.
They love a harness jump in these movies they might maybe they explain it in many at cop three which I've never seen
I have an either I think it's called badge of silence or yeah that's what maybe not see it yeah but I do like the first two the third one I don't know
Badger, look at that, that's not a winning ticket today, is it, Pat?
No, everybody lost.
I won $1 ,000 on a Missouri lottery ticket when I was in college.
What'd you do with the money?
I put it in the bank, it's a terrible story.
I had no money at the time.
It's a shit story.
I know it's Christ.
You'd love me to go on some Ferris -Bueller -style adventure with it,
but I put it in the bank.
That's why I'm a home owner today.
Home owner?
Let's cut off the bloody marriage.
Yeah, and that's why I that's why I still rent and my most important build a pay every month is what blu -ray am I buying
Bruce Campbell
Real handsome man in his prime, you know, we need a can we say that? Yeah, gorgeous
Michael learner also a very sexy man, right? This character is a heavy set man with a pipe at a shitty attitude get Michael
learner yeah Michael learners actually in the office like he he sensed that it
was coming he's like the maniac cup right he senses when they need a fat guy
with a pipe and a bad attitude he's right there sounds like you need Michael
learner baby nominated for an Oscar two years later for Barton Fink which is a
honestly kind of a horror movie itself by the colon brothers great tremendous in
that film he's great and I believe learner could have played I believe good
been a learner could swap roles. I would have bought them an either role in that film.
You wouldn't have wanted that much learner. I'll tell you that. I like a peppering of
learner. You don't want a full two hours of learning. I learned that the hard way. Folks,
these are the jokes. A young Darryl Hannah type. I was positive this was the woman from
flash Gordon the movie, and it's not her. They look almost identical. It's crazy.
Bruce Campbell, one of my favorites. He's coming off Evil Dead, Evil Dead 2, and then like what?
He did like crime away. I think this is pre -eviled dead 2 if I'm not mistaken. Evil
Dead 2 is like 90. This is like 89, isn't it? I'm pretty sure Evil Dead 2 is 87, and this is 90.
I don't want to make you into an asshole in front of all these people, but I think you're just wrong
I guarantee we could ask anyone at this horror festival and they'll tell us anybody to was released. Does anybody know you can yell it out
No, I think it's
Yeah, you like those bangs
You like that? I like this chair. All right, you take her or you take checker boards here. I love that little interaction
They have there where he's like look we both know we saw a zombie
But god damn it the pension
Well nobody ever believes it now let's say one person comes to me and says hey, I saw a maniac cop. I'd be like
Oh, somebody's been hitting the sauce pretty hard.
Three people come to me and say they saw a maniac cop.
Did you see that stunt?
I did.
That was outrageous.
That was a real stunt.
Yeah.
I just found two stories under a van.
By the way, he's also actually dead.
Everyone who did a stunt on this movie died,
which put, you know, cast a certain realism to the part.
It was lusted, insisted on it.
Here he is.
in the same cost to me were in the goonies. Yeah. I love the cheapest Fedora you got. I pictured
this guy as a street cop that wears a Fedora. He plays this like it's, you know, Godfather 4.
He takes it very serious. He plays everything. Yeah, I love it. He sings opera in the goonies. Yeah.
Yeah. You know my lawyer, my ex -weyer was chunk. Yeah, he's a big Hollywood lawyer.
Yeah, that's true. People are laughing. That's true though. Yeah, the actor who played
chunk is a big Hollywood attorney. Yeah. Real thin now. I didn't like that. I wanted
him to be fat. Yeah. That's the future two poster up there. Look at that. It was 1990.
All right. We get it nerd. Well, Jesus Christ. Fucking Almanacca movies over here. I used
Speaking of nerds, I would have my dad quiz me from the Leonard Moulton's video guide.
It was the only time he would speak to me, so we had to get to the portal.
I'd be like, Papa, just a couple more questions from the Moulton guide, and he'd throw his bottle
of bourbon at me and go, I'll give you two and then it's bedtime.
Right.
Take a swim with my mother.
First question, why are you such a pussy?
question two how are you my son I'm a man so how are you my son this isn't
true folks he's an okay guy this little interaction here reminds me of the
departed I think the departed took a lot from maniac come to Scorsese I heard
had this in the screening room every morning before he started shooting when I
of a maniac zombie cop, it's corruption.
There's a maniac cop inside of us all.
There's my scores, sayzy impression.
Actually, it's all off the cuff.
That's the first time I ever did it.
It's good.
As ridiculous as maniac cop too is, even they wouldn't end it
with a rat crawling on a window sill as the departed ends.
I remember, I mean, I fucking loved the departed,
but everyone in the theater was like, are you serious?
With that rat shot?
Yeah, that rat shot's bad.
I called Marty as a smarty.
Marty, what are you doing?
Many I come to wouldn't dare try to convince us that Mark Wahlberg worked his way up the bladder and any occupation.
No, no, no. My favorite Mark Wahlberg wrote, wrote robotics expert in transformers for
or how about, I mean, we're gonna do robotics for a long time. How about scientist in the happening?
The only less believable scientist is Denise Richards in that James Bond and college professor
in the gambler. Yeah, oh, I like the gambler, but yeah, I stayed in for about half of it
that I bailed out. Those scenes where he's like teaching the class, you can see him straining
to remember the dialogue. We love you, though, Mark. I'm sure you're listening. I love this
lady. I mean, love with the psychiatrist. I do too. I like when he tells his story about
a psychiatrist for a year and then she left him so that's why he hates
psychiatrists. It's good enough for me. That's the backstory they give you for
this guy. Look, this guy's old school. He doesn't have time for the mumbo
jumbo. You know what I mean? Sure. You go to work, you go to sleep, that's it. That's
that's how life goes. I don't put them. This is a strange outfit. I always can't
to say. It doesn't match, Bruce. It doesn't match. Now, I'm a black actor
and I want to make sure this isn't going to be a stereotypical black role that I'm playing in Maniacop too.
No, as we told the Hispanic guy, totally respectable role.
I love how he tells the story about how he...
All he has to say was the guy was cold.
The Maniacop touches him in his hands or cold.
Yeah.
And he tells this horrific story of being faced down on the muck and war with bodies on top of them
to prove that he knows how cold flesh feels.
Right.
typical executive note too yeah you're just like he's blind so he couldn't see
him but why is he blind yeah let's have him tell a story doesn't that give it
more stakes yeah here's my impression of the notes for the new angry birds movie
but why are the birds angry nobody gives a shit this shocked me the first time I
saw it the Campbell goes down this quick yeah I couldn't believe it it's like
Psycho you kill your star right off the bat. I couldn't believe it. He gets all the way through the first one and then it's they ice him right away and this one. Oh
Yeah, daddy like just kidding everybody. I actually do like it and I'm not kidding. I don't mind corp's nudity because I know the actress who played the corpse was a lot
so I can just imagine that she was sleeping.
There's a movie playing at this festival
about three teens who have sex with a corpse.
Robert Davie chooses the Fedora with Levi's.
So sometimes Joe will just ignore a point that I made.
I didn't hear you said because I was so distracted by that outfit.
It is a wild outfit.
He's all Marbrow man on the bottom, all synatra on the top.
I don't know what the fuck's going on there.
No belt.
We're coming off a scene where Bruce Campbell is wearing old Navy khakis white new balances a black trench coat and gloves
Who's doing the wardrobe and whoever's doing the wardrobe forgot to give this corpse a shirt folks?
But there is a movie playing here. It's a Spanish movie
I think we're gonna see it this afternoon
Yeah, and it's three teenagers who sneak into a morgue to have sex with the corpse. I don't know why I watch this movie
I know I signed up just because it sounds horrific to me, but yeah, I do want to see it
Because there's got to be a twist, right? I mean, I assume that she comes back to life or something
Do you ever see that movie teeth where the girl is teeth in her vagina? Yeah, it's dicks. I sure did
Called my friend the the day I read the synopsis of that movie when I heard it was coming out of called my friend
I said if they were making a movie called teeth and it was your dream movie what would the plot be?
That's all I asked him, and he goes,
did a girl head teeth in her vagina that bit guys dicks off.
And I said, well, it's your lucky day.
I'm in the car outside your house.
Let's go.
He didn't believe me.
He thought I was making it up.
I was like, no, it's a real movie.
I like to imagine like the guy who directed this movie
we're going to see, which is called,
I think the corpse of Ken, what's it called?
The corpse of Anna Fritz.
Anna Fritz.
Imagine, like, you call your mom, and you go,
mom I'm gonna make a movie I got a budget I got actors it's all happening honey
that's great what's the movie about and you have to say it's about three
teenagers who fuck a corpse right that does your mom just give up on you at
that point she says at that point she goes well at least it's not like the one
you made about the girl with a teeth in her pussy it's not the same director
I know Pat it's a bit for Christ's well learner we just missed him he was back
with the pipe. I love the way to the world on this guy's shoulders. Oh, Christ, give me my pipe.
Just constantly smoking and he can't handle it. Yeah. What the hell's happening?
Here we go. Now, let's just listen to this speech, Rookway.
just a ridiculous overshare to a woman he's just met I admit I'm not the easiest
guy to live with I didn't ask or the best dresser and I wear ridiculous hats I
admit sometimes I pay her 501 jeans with an elegant trench coat and a
Fadora. I'm still wearing a class ring. Hey, there's a horse looking thing on my tie suspenders.
That's why he's got no belt on. He's got suspenders. You ever want a pair of suspenders
in your life? Uh, once. When I saw, I did a stage production of the little rascals kidding.
No, yeah, I went a wedding or something for a tuxedo. They did suspenders instead of the
vest or something. Yeah. Right here, folks, a little movie trivia. This is this is angel
Charles Salazar. He is a comedian who I knew fairly well in New York from doing shows.
He also played Chi Chi in Scarface.
Fingerless line Scarface. Chi Chi. Get the Yale. That's Chi Chi.
He had a bit in his act where he had stripped down to a teal thong on stage.
I'm sorry, I missed that.
Once he was on stage and I found several multi -colored fluorescent thongs in the green room.
And I said to my friend, these are the bits he decided not to do tonight.
These are the jokes that didn't make the cut.
Yeah, but he's a great guy, very nice guy.
Now he was also in the movie Punchline.
He's the guy with the big boom box in Punchline.
Go ahead, what?
What I really liked about this, and I really haven't seen it in other movies, is that it's a standard setup
where they portray this guy as a complete, yuppie asshole.
He's rich. He's terrible and you're expecting him to die and then they killed the good nice cop
Well because the maniac cop is trying to create
Term oil in the department of the police department city hall for what they did to him
So this movie steps it up and he goes out of his way to kill the good guy and let the asshole live
Yeah, so it makes even less sense that to them than the first move, right?
And this guy just saw a man get killed and I'm gonna hook and all he cares about is the ticket.
Yeah, you know what's ticket obsession in this film I related to him to be honest with you.
Excuse me, traditional horror movie character who's always a black guy that can't see.
Can you give me the clues that I'm looking for right now?
Is he wearing, like, horrifically painful 80s contacts, or are those his actual laws, you think?
I don't know. I mean, the makeup in this movie is very good. So I can't tell, like, who actually had a disability of some kind or moving.
This movie, remade today, would be so timely, like, in the first one when that woman is just scared, because she gets pulled over.
Like, you could make some really prescient political shit out of this movie today.
Well, you you already did when you said as it would be called regular cops. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I I remember them
This is like in Jeepers Quieppers creepers when that like island lady comes in to the police station like I heard it on the radio
I always love I got psychic powers. It's like this is convenient. Yeah
Come back here and let me give you some jambalaya to warm you up.
If you, she just is like, hey, did you see anything last night and he's like, hey, how about
a five -minute monologue about my experience in the war?
And she just said, I had to cover myself, I had to use corpse blankets, yeah, with the
monologues about.
She's like, why is everybody telling me they're personal shit today?
Well, she's a psychiatrist, she's used to.
The guy from goonies just opened up about his wife leaving him. Yeah, look. I'll admit I'm not the easiest guy to live with
That's not Dana Carvey and that's not Brett Ratner. No matter what everybody thinks
He's got looks like Martin Short there. Yeah
Every I love oh everyone in the movie knows that the cop is six foot three
Six foot three all scarred up as the detail of the face
Not blue skin.
Yeah.
Did he have any zombie -like qualities?
No, I just, I scarred up exactly six foot three
as all I remember.
Was there fog on the ground?
I couldn't say.
Probably, you know, I don't know, I didn't look down.
What are you wearing, Robert Davey?
He clearly bases the whole outfit on the suspenders
matching the tie, and then he lets it fly from there.
Yeah.
Look at that.
Pieces got man
It's a serious good acne scars on Davey. Or what do you think? I would assume so unless he was hit with some kind of fragment bomb
Right, that's what boomer is face
Yeah, it's probably acne scars my dad has
Subscarring like that I always feel for those guys, you know
I had a horrific acne and I can't believe my face looks as beautiful as it does now
I can't either you hear that silence for everybody everybody in the theater is nodding behind us. Yes, yes, yes, that's correct
I didn't know you had acne and I thought that this morning. I saw your face
I said I can't believe how beautiful this kid is what you rolled over you look me in the eye, right? I had
I just have to take acutane. Yeah, I had to take that for a while too at one point about eight years ago my career had
I had to fall into a point that I was so stressed that I had an adult break out of severe acne, and I had to take acutane.
Well, that shit fucks you up, man.
Every pill had a picture of a pregnant woman with an X through it, which makes you feel real good when you're a 16 -year -old going through all these changes.
And then now they've discovered that people who are on acutane for long periods of time have severe mental issues and try to kill people.
Well, there's lawsuits all the way out. Yes, damn was yelling at people. Yeah, maybe it's the actual thing. It might have been the accident.
I killed two people this morning. I like that amidst all the zombie cast she took time to crimp her hair up.
Yeah, I mean, that's like a two hour hair job. Feed the fish. Make sure they're good.
Before I blow town, I got to feed these fish one last time.
Look, I've got a facial and a man he petty in about 10 minutes. Can we wrap this up?
Pat, I'll tell you what, I'm putting the order in, I'm going for another screwdriver.
Are you on two or three?
This is going to be my third.
Oh my god.
The warning?
What are you on?
This is my second.
Well, I'm on my second, but I'm going to go for the third.
You know what, I'll take a third too.
Let's go crazy.
The nice waiter here had to take the order slip out of my hand because I couldn't get it into the slot on the table here.
He's like, I got it, buddy, just for Christ's sake.
Sometimes you drink too much.
You can't get it into the slot.
Folks, this is possibly my favorite character
in movie history, this cab driver.
Now, I'm an Italian actor.
Is this going to be a respectable role?
Yeah, not stereotypical, though.
Put on this hot -frized Andy Caphat and get into this cab.
Care way too much, about a 425 fare.
And then he has a weird thing about how cops always cause trouble and don't tip well in his car
Yeah, that's a good stereotype. You know how Italian take cops
Oh
Like is that a thing that cops don't tip well. No, all right. I don't think I don't know maybe
It's kind of writer's room. I know a cop. He says they never tip. Yeah, we got to put that in the movie
I don't think this movie had a writer's room
there's always a bunch of room you know that that's right I own this cab which
apparently is 15 years or so outdated look at this Dick Tracy cab he's driving
around you ever play the Roger Rabbit video game with Benny the cam no no
pad it's really fun who in Christ name would have picked that game I had all the
other great Nintendo game. Every game I had was like an off -shoot, whatever was in the clearance,
but my favorite game was Tuban about going in an inner tube down a river drinking beer.
Somebody should tell this cab driver that the Mamie at cop drives a newer car than he does.
Doesn't matter he's dead.
I really had really good action. I felt. Yeah, it's great. Very realistic. I'm very excited for
the sequence and when he raised the police station. I really liked that part. You know, when I'm
Curious to know remember how there's the one guy that hasn't seen this. Yeah, I think he's lost right now because we talked over at the whole time. Did you guys shut up?
Or can you follow it? You get what's going on, right?
He said yeah
They say the key to a good movie as you can turn the sound off and follow the plot
Fantastic car chase.
Again, all very real, yeah.
This is all happening.
They shot this.
You know, as of 2012, Nicholas Wynding -Rethan was going to remake Maniac Cup.
I guess it fell through, but you think that might still happen?
I read that.
No, no, yesterday they announced it's moving forward.
literally yesterday yeah I I mean obviously I love drive I know you hate
drive I can't even imagine it's a horrendous film it's hate it so much one of
my favorite many years I loved to have an idea for a movie let's have Ryan
Gosling silent and take all the likability out of Albert Brooks I hate the
film I hate it did you like only God forgives what the hell is only God forgives
It's drive -in Thailand with Ryan Gosling, same director, same everything.
Never saw it. It's good. I never saw the place beyond the pines either. Love place beyond the pines.
This is great. This whole thing. Now, I just happen to be there.
This is a great, this is a great little detail right here. Yeah, there's a function.
That was in a store, though, right? The chain saw. I wasn't just on the street.
Okay, no, yeah, I was in the store. I love this now handcuffs her to a car. Let's the cargo down the hill. She's fucked. That's just
Now here's where I don't get he catches the chainsaw. Why can't it cut him?
Why can't it cut him? Yeah, I don't know. I guess he's
Invincible in someone I think it could cut him and not hurt him, but I would still be gonna cut his hand. Yeah
Am I wrong?
Again, this is real they got a lady hanging out of a car going down a street fairly fast
We can't really speak a lot during these sequences because it's, it's just loud heavy
action. But we're still here.
She's in the car.
Now, for those of you not watching, she's just crashed into a pile of boxes.
That always upset me because she pulls off getting back in the car and not dying and
and then they just have her crash.
I feel like she should get the victory of landing safely.
And not just immediately crashing, wouldn't you say?
I would, but what are you gonna do?
I was six years old when this movie came.
Has anyone seen Maniacop three badge of silence?
By round of applause.
I'm seeing literally nobody.
All right.
Well, now I don't feel bad.
I thought they were gonna be like,
you, you're a fucking travesty.
You never seen the entire trilogy.
Yeah, I feel okay about uh -oh here comes drinking number three and can
Lustig doesn't he run a DVD company now like a specialty DVD which one blue underground. Okay, that's awesome. Thank you
This is the end of the line
Our bill has come no that somebody must have told them look give them the bill. They're done drinking
Let's get back on track here, last night we saw Silver Bullet here and when the bill came
I had to wake Joe up, always good, nothing against the film, it was, it was, it was tired,
it was worth it.
Midnight screening, I understand.
I liked Silver Bullet, I had never seen it.
I enjoyed it much more seeing it on the old film stock and everything that, you know, the
first time I saw it was on like Netflix, yeah.
I thought Busey was fantastic and I liked yeah like oh here we go
Busey I guess like he had been nominated for an Oscar two years prior
I don't think he just put on a ton of weight and then wound up being in silver bullet when I first saw this film I couldn't believe
That this guy wasn't Mick Foley from WWF it looks like Mick Foley it so much that I literally thought it was him at first
But now you pointed out to me that it's the guy from analyze this yes
She is blue my mind. Yeah, because he looks nothing like this is Charles Napier. I love Charles Napier
Right favorite Charles Napier line is in a cable guy do a song for us. Yeah, sure. I love when he says it
That's true strange that you know any any news show would have a good hair and makeup team that couldn't take care of that
Shiner on her for bring the bangs that the other ladies got bangs covering her entire face take a tip from her I like that the
news reporter is like I don't see a say there's a zombie on the loose what would he have to say about
this commission nobody bats and I nobody this guy's my favorite character in the whole movie
it was a really interesting development because it becomes a whole different movie at this point
really yeah and I dug it and he's like almost has a crush on the maniac come yeah to the point
that part. You want to come back to my house and hang out. Yeah. And then they do. I like that.
This guy, whatever his name is. He's a tremendous actor. Yes. This character.
Great. It's always nice to give a shout out to whatever his name is and reward him for his work.
I'm sorry. I don't know the name of the supporting cast of analyze this. I didn't play a movie quiz
with my uncle as a child. Like you did my dad. I like to analyze this. We all know he was actually
You're a different game with my uncle if you want to
get into some real dark shit.
Why would you?
Analyze this is great.
Analyze that.
It's just as bad as it gets.
And analyze the other, the unmade third.
Did I ever tell you my idea for the third?
Please do.
Analyze me.
Okay.
And it's De Niro's to Analyze Billy Crystal.
I like that.
It's great.
They'll never make it, but I like it.
Just.
Do you get uncomfortable when there's nudity in a theater or no?
I saw the movie Welcome to New York, which was what's his face that made Bad Lieutenant
able for our, able for our, one of his later films.
I saw it at a screening that able for our hosted and the graphic, the sex was so graphic
that I literally was, I felt like I was watching porn in a theater.
It would make me very uncomfortable.
It makes my upper lip sweat, I get very uncomfortable.
It reminds me of like my parents walking in while a sex scene was going on, it's very
uncomfortable.
Yes.
What made it worse was during every sex scene, my friend Brian would reach over, grab the
back of my head and force, try to force my head down like he was trying to get me to blow
him.
Okay.
And then I'd pull back and he'd go, all right, relax.
Max kept doing that every sex yeah which didn't make it any better.
That's some 80s underpants right there.
That's 80s everything.
Yeah.
That's 80s body.
That was a real 80s body back then.
That's how the bodies were.
80s hair.
You ever just cover your body in glitter Joe?
I'm covered in it right now.
Okay.
Look at this guy.
just act like you're having fun he's doing all he can to get on screen as an
extra I mean for like for this guy on the right this old guy can you imagine
how happy he is he got into being an extra in the strip club see make a hundred
dollars to do this all day? I'll say I love this girl. I want a barrier. Isn't she beautiful folks?
Yeah, when does that happen? He was doing it. We talked over.
That movie welcomed in New York. Do they play Taylor Swift's Welcome to New York over any of the
sex scenes? No, and in fact it came out years before that song came out. It's a great song.
No, it's not. Oh, it's a great disagree. I have a question for you. You know I'm dating
Taylor Swin. I have a question for you. What? If you could be a maniac, something. Sure.
What would it be? And what would your catchphrase be? Well, it's hard to find one that hasn't
been a movie, like even the dentist was a movie with Corbin Burnson.
That's okay.
Um, I guess I would want to be, do you have one ready to go?
Yeah, I've been thinking about this for the last couple of days.
Okay, that's weird, but share with us.
Mine is a maniac boxing judge.
Okay, go on, and then I would cut people in half and I'd go split decision.
Okay, all right, that's pretty good.
Do you have any other quips or it's always going to be a split decision?
What else do they say? What else do boxing judges say? Knockout, total knockout.
I've never seen a boxing match. They say I'm Rocky Balboa. I don't know anything about boxing.
I can't wait to see Creed. I'm very excited. Yeah, but it's going to have to be pretty good to
beat Rocky Balboa because I thought they ended the franchise perfectly. I cried my eyes out during
and raki about ball.
Yeah, I have a little bit of experience,
so I really held a place close to my heart.
Tears of excitement, tears of sadness,
Adrian's dead, oh my God, I love that movie.
This, I mean, these horror movies are what,
when I lived in New York for 10 years,
these movies were what made me never want to move to New York,
because everybody lived in one of these like motel things yeah and it just
looked like diseases were growing in there and everything and then when they
call for help they're like I don't want any trouble yeah do you ever see the
fly the you know the gold bloom one yeah we've discussed it at length it
terrified me to move to New York I was like you got to live in a warehouse yeah
for me, it was the Muppets take Manhattan. I was like, Jesus Christ, if these Muppets
are living like this, how am I going to do? They got singing rats, preparing meals.
What's up with that new Muppet show, by the way? We all got jokes and hate it. What are
they doing? I don't know. It's like, uh, Kermit's like, hey, bitch, get in here. It's terrible.
you know who runs the show the guy who does Big Bang thing the guys that did
anger management the Charlie scene sheen sitcom okay that's who they got to
run them up its TV show they're making like gay jokes like I mean like that
are disparaging to gay people yeah like Fauzi's a bear but he's also like a bear
that kind of thing yeah it's upsetting it's not a good not a good show I don't know
see meet the feebles Peter Jackson's yeah to set up set me it actually made
me vomit I don't like when kids things get turned dirty like I read the book
wicked and yeah the witches having sex and it and stuff I don't bother's me two
harness throws on that one I think I would love to be thrown by a harness to see
I think it would be a lot of fun I'd like it
So the mini -acop has just rescued what apparently is a serial killer
Right imagine so that girl's like hey, yeah, that was strange
One guy breaks in tries to rape me a maniac cop comes in
saves him and and runs out with and prevents the rape yeah
Look at these people dancing up in the window up there.
I wonder if they were, uh, knew they were in the shot or what?
I like that this guy appreciates a tight around the buns, pair of pants, sure.
That's where he tells him he's not gay, but just come back to my house.
You know, I gave it some thought and I think I'd be a maniac tailor.
Okay.
Uh, what would your thing be?
I don't know. I have to give that some thought.
I know they've never made a movie about a maniac tailor. That's why I'm choosing it.
I would if I was a maniac tailor. A lot of in -same material and you cut the guys
dick off. Yeah, exactly. In -same. We got to take this jacket in.
Yeah, yeah. I don't know. You cut the guys side off. I don't fucking know.
look it's a work in progress he's not at all there's no part of him that's
like what is wrong with your face yeah they're just hanging out so he killed all
of these women correct I guess and it to me looks like a lazy serial killer what's
that five six chicks yeah it's better get on it if you want to make a name for
So yeah, by the way I live in New York 10 years had an upstanding job never in
Department this nice. Oh, no, look at this fucking place. Exposed brick. He's got
four rooms. I lived in a railroad apartment which meant that if my roommate wanted
to go to the bathroom he had to walk through my room. He had to open one door, come
through my room, go out the other door and go to the bathroom, then walk back
through three times a night. I had that in college. And my place was robbed and
they took the door off the hinges to get in. Right. And I called my landlord
who was named Mr. Stool. And he goes, I said, Hey, my front door is off the
hinges. I don't have a door anymore. And he goes, Did I take your door? Why
you calling me? Did I take your door? Wow. So you're not going to fix it. He
didn't fix it. I had to leave the apartment. That's really incredible. That was
in Williamsburg, which is now Disneyland.
Yeah.
They cleaned it up, baby.
But back in those days, I lived on the corner
of Stabbington Street and Shootamup.
It was terrible.
There was a, I thought it was a maximum security prison.
Deserve more than it got.
There was a, like a prison next to my building.
It was a horrible, horrible place.
Love that.
Querydella's spoken for the first time.
I'd wear that shirt.
I'd wear that shirt yeah you'd wear it now you'd wear it now this guy so good as a
serial killer I really mean it I mean I I really enjoy we're back in Davies
office now what what is he writing there he's filling out paperwork he doesn't
see he's a guy who'd be above paperwork now no copies that's below his
that's that's part of the deal I shot some son of a bitch in a grocery store
robbery and they got me doing paperwork now I got a push pencils the only
paperwork I want to do is the trash I wrap around that piece of shit's body you
know that they always take stuff like that sure sure sure now he's wearing a
denim shirt and her forehead's cleared up oh no it's it's taken on it she still
got a well on it but this is again good makeup in this film that looks like a
progressive yeah a progress brews you know he never sticks it to this lady
does he it's actual sorry to put it so sticks it to it it's amazing that you
you have relationships with women it's 9 a .m. I've had three screwdrivers already
I'm sorry if I'm not tacked for he never sticks it to this bro
It's called making love Joe you might try it sometime. I
Don't think dovey would put it that way now he
Especially now with that x -wife look I he knows he's a difficult man to live
Well I had this
Knife, fashioned out of my night stick, it cost a few bucks but it was worth it.
Who do you put in the Davy role you're remaking Mania comp to?
I already don't know who Davy is.
Robert Davy.
Oh Robert Davy.
Jesus Christ.
Who do I put in that role?
I'm going to go with Paul Giamatti.
Okay.
All right.
I think it could work.
I mean I'd like to man anything.
I don't know that it could work but I'd watch it.
You know what?
I'll put Paul G. Maddie in this guy's role.
Yeah, that makes more sense.
In the serial killer role.
I'm going to put Mickey Rourke in the Davey role.
See, I think you want Rourke in the maniac cop role.
Because he's got a huge face.
Yeah, he's got a huge loaded plastic surgery.
Rourke is the maniac cop.
Okay.
I'm going to put...
He goes into makeup and they're like, uh, we're all good.
You're good to go.
Yeah, let me just put my kid away.
You freak.
All right, then I'm going to put, you know, there's no Italians in Hollywood anymore.
I don't know who, what Italian actors are out there that could play the Davi role.
There is no tough guys in Hollywood anymore.
Like the toughest we got is like Chris Pratt, who's not tough.
No, you need a man's man. You know what I you know what I'm gonna go out I'm gonna do a different way here Rarissa Tome
In the Davy role. Let's switch up the genders. All right, sure
I'd buy hers a no nonsense plain clothes cap
Maybe some high -waisted jeans showing some of the front pus. Oh my god. I thought that she has one but
As opposed to the rear plus well, you know that that like do you know how that mom bodies work?
The mom, oh wait, I didn't mean front put.
What do they used to call that when like the mom would have like the little belly bump
and they'd call it the, the bussy, do you not know what I'm talking about?
No.
That was a common thing when I was a kid.
That was a phrase.
The mom jeans.
Yeah, but the mom jeans were high waisted so it would show like if you had a little bit
of a gut and then kids would call it like the bussy, like the belly pussy.
Okay.
Sorry.
Is this too much?
I mean, I'm rolling with it.
I was kind of mad.
You don't see Rob.
The maniac cop is dick right here.
I really thought we were going to see some maniac cop dick.
Absolutely.
He must have had it in his contract.
Well, there he's wearing...
Oh, those guys.
Those guys wearing jeans.
Robert Tsar, we found out last night from our friend Ken just passed away, right?
Okay, very sad, rest in peace, sir.
Oh, yeah, that's rough.
They cut his face all up, that's gross.
But if I'm not mistaken, this entire sequence
beat for beat is in Maniacop 1 as well.
Is it in Maniacop 1?
I don't remember it for some reason.
Except there's a 20 minute panning shot
through the prison that I guess they just used to kill time.
I like this push in on the Maniacop.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
day. Look, that lady looks like Marisa Tome. Yeah, I love Marisa Tome. I love her. And it
be a wrestler reunion, which is exciting. That's as exciting. Well, then maybe we make
Marisa Tome the stripper role again. Sure. Anything. We need somebody in this cop role who's
playing Davie in the remake. All right, let me, let me look. Robert Lozier. Lozier is older
than Robert. I know. They have a similar quality. They do. All right. How about Mark
Walberg? There we go. Yes. That's good. That's good. Yes. Very good. We got it. Hey, we
got to get this maniac cop. I put an reflect in the world too. I'm tired of this maniac cop
doing stuff in my city. We got to get him. That's a decent attempt, right? It's this. All
it is. Wait, what was that? Oh, the old is good. Sure. The
old would be great. The old is also having some weird face issues. He could
maybe play it over the cup. The old is like, you're just like, why on earth
is Ray Leota getting like a facelift? It's just tragic to me. Yeah, I don't
know. He's got like an eye lift like a, you know, it's just sad. Everybody got
facelifts. It was no big deal. Okay. That's a Nicholson bleeding into a
right. It's far back as I can remember I wanted to look like an old woman.
Leo does a difficult impression. I can do the laugh. I won't do it into the
mic because it'll blow your ears out but I can kind of do it. A good impression of his
life. I agree. I've been trying to get a Sam Rockwell down. I can't get it.
You don't see many apartments with that brick arch and
them. I kind of like it. It's an awesome apartment. Yeah. It makes me mad that he has this
apartment. I mean, it's windowless. But now, I think this serial killer wants to bang
the maniac cut. I have no doubt about it. And I think he kills the women. Or as I put
it, stick it to him. I think he couldn't, he never found love. And he's killing the women
and because he can't face his homosexuality,
is how I took this movement.
Yes.
Are the girls doing table dances?
I remember you had a table dance pad
or a lap dance of any kind?
I have.
I went to a strip club once in New York
called Mixed Emotions, which is the best name
for a strip club ever.
Uh -huh.
And what happened in Mixed Emotions that fateful night?
I had mixed emotions about being there.
And my friend got a hand job, I believe.
He got a hand job, yeah.
Wow.
All right.
This chick's making a thousand bucks a week, she just said, is a stripper.
I think, what are strippers make now?
A thousand bucks a week.
I'm trying to do the conversion math here.
$1 ,000 a week in 1990. What would that be now? About $85 ,000 a week. I think so. I mean,
it was doing all right. Why is she living in that shithole? She's like, I make a thousand
bucks a week. Yeah. But I like to stick to my roots.
You think you could live in an apartment where the landlord wouldn't ignore your
right. There he is. Just shoving
strippers off the stage trying to
catch this guy. We got him. They
just got the they just got them
serial killer for those of you at
home.
Have you ever seen a jail where they let you keep your jacket on and everything?
I don't take the ring nothing.
Well, why do they take it so you don't kill yourself or others?
Yeah, they kind of take all your shit from you.
You ever been to jail?
No.
Have you?
Not jail when I was about ten, some buddies and I walked a quick trip at like three in the morning to get candy.
And this cop picked us up and brought us to the police station and called each of our mothers and
Every cop that came in was like did they steal the candy and they was like nah
Like why would you bring them to the police station? That was a maniac cop
And then my mom was like pat you're in jail at three in the morning. What were you doing?
I'm like I went to buy some candy
I'm like how you tried to make it sound like you sort of knew what jail was like and the story started with when I was ten
well I mean I'm not saying we were put in the in the big house but we were at a
police station at three in the morning watching actual criminals it was
horrifying. I got busted stealing cassette tapes from a department store in
Pennsylvania that was called ports of the world. Okay when I was 14 but they didn't
call the cops they just find us through the store and told our parents and I got
I got a good beat in that night, yeah.
Yeah, they also they just called my mom and they were like, yeah, your son's in the police station no further information
At that point like I had never missed a day of school. That's the kind of get that I want
Oh
Now what's the other move they do this now where they're in the shooting range and then the maniac cop kills them all
What's the other movie where they kill everybody in the shooting range?
I've never seen one. I thought I maybe the heat with Melissa McCarthy. No, no, I don't believe so right just kill
Oh God, with a 50 cent?
Yeah, I would have said with De Niro Pacino.
No, I consider that a 50 cent vehicle.
I don't know, I've never seen a bunch of people get killed in the shooting range, which is why I like it when it happens.
And this one, sorry guy that's never seen this, we just ruined what's about to happen.
I imagine 50 cent is the toughest vitamin water executive.
There's probably no vitamin water executives tougher than 50.
here we go machete right that is machete that's pretty cool no dialogue and
there on the right is the landlord from it's always sunny in Philadelphia show I
used to ride for do we see him again yeah you see him there's Clarence Williams
a third this guy never doesn't play a guy that seems to be coked out of his head
Yeah, just a hundred yard stare so this guy was the lead on the mod squad
Which was a hugely successful show right and now like 10 short years later
He's got three lines of maniac cup to I mean you see that happened a lot of TV stars. Yeah, it's just sad
You know, whatever happened to those girls from too close for comfort
Don't know I follow one of the one Twitter. She follows me back. Okay. Yeah brag much
He's got a very similar quality and not just because he's black Joe.
You mean they both look crazy and it makes me uncomfortable the whole time?
Yeah, and they talk about that kind of like sexy whisper.
I like a sexy whisper.
Do not use as a urinal.
Yeah.
I got to get that sign from my house.
I had a big poker game the other night with like Florence Williams is holding his
dick right now. And he actually says I'm going to hold my breath and hold my dick.
Yeah. And it poker again the other night with like 10 guys in my house and the end of
the night I realized the floor was covered in pee. And I put forth like a clue style investigation.
Like trying to like casually ask people like who pee's on the floor of a man's home.
Well, you did it. And then I knew it must have been one of my close friends in the living room.
No, in the bathroom, but just like such a miss of the toilet that it was like
They'd never gone to the bathroom before and in that case you got to sit down my friend. I know it's not
I'll take a seat. I'm not above it
Here we go
If you peed on the my bathroom floor come forward I
agree
I agree
Wipe it up. Who doesn't wipe it up?
Absolutely. You got to wipe it up. Look occasionally I have what's called a forked
stream where it'll shoot out in two directions. You got to clean that.
Usually caused by sex. Always caused by sex. We're jerking it. All right, Joe.
Jerking it, working it. There he is. Great shot. That's a really tremendous shot. Yeah.
Now this is the part where he starts bustin' through all the glass, I really like this part a lot.
Upgrades the gun, smart move.
Maniac cop 2 on his way to shoot up the city of New York Police Department, it seems.
That is where he is now, correct?
Now the cool part about this sequence is he starts walking through windows.
The maniac comp throughout this movie does seem to have very vague goals until now.
Like he just kind of shows up places and is like, I guess I'll do this now.
Why wasn't this his first order of business?
He had to his work his way to the top, all right, fun.
That one broke before he walked through it.
Yeah, that's the one you pointed out before, right?
A couple of these windows break before he hits it.
But it is a cool visual, like a guy that can just walk through walls.
Very good.
Oh yeah. That's the best one.
That's the mother of all harness throws.
Yeah.
I'm still thinking about what kind of other maniac occupation I would have.
You know, yeah, maniac cobbler, maniac cobbler, yeah, like you repair shoes, but you're
so many. No, you're a cobbler. You mean, you make shoes. You've got a pair of shoes.
Cobblers, in this, in this market, you think cobblers don't also repair shoes? They have to
make money. But it's not like you said, you're a pair of shoes. You repair shoes. Oh, repair shoes.
Okay. Jesus Christ. Yeah. What would you, the catchphrase be? I got nothing. No, it's
It's clean out.
Oh, I think it was that split decision thing,
and I can't, I got nothing to say.
You peaked too early.
Come on, man.
I'd see this woman as a poor man's Rachel Wise.
Rachel Wise hasn't been in a movie in 10 years.
She's in the lobster with Colin Farrell,
which is about to come out.
Looks tremendous, right?
That's a poor, poor man's racial wise.
Sure.
They're going back to sincing
Listen, I just want to have a rational talk with this guy
I don't know how many of you are on the field.
Let's talk about anything.
There he is.
Remember it.
Oh, yeah.
You're like ten episodes.
He's the guy that the DeVito won't ever pay.
Yeah.
I really like that.
the serial killer is so crazy that when he's talking to the media cop even the
maniac cop is like uh yeah you're a little much for me yeah we're gonna
recruit an army you you go ahead first to recruit the army and I'll catch up to
you okay Michael learn or pissed off again yeah what the hell is this Betty grab
I have my pipe.
Lustig never really went on to have that big success.
Like, this is a very well made action movie.
Yeah.
Why didn't he never get other work?
And he considers this his masterpiece, I run.
well it's certainly what he's known for I mean I'd give Uncle Sam a ride around
the block sure I've never seen it can you see Uncle Sam now have you seen Jack
Frost Jack Frost Jack Frost well wait which one the Michael Keaton one or the
horror one the horror one he which by the way when I worked at blockbuster many
many people mixed those up and showed their kids the horror one.
You know what I thought you were going to say?
I thought when I said the Michael Keaton, one of the horror one,
you were going to go, what's the difference?
Yeah, well they're both.
Jack Frost with Michael Keaton is one of the worst movies ever made.
It's what sent him into retirement for like 15 years.
And the horror one, he assaults a woman with a carrot.
How happy are you that Keaton's back?
He's the best.
very happy about that because now finally we might get that jack Frost sequel off the ground.
I have an idea for Keaton. I'm pitching this out loud right now to everybody.
Mr. Mom's sequel. Mr. Graham Mom. It's good. It could work. Yeah, no, I'm not saying it couldn't.
I mean, if I mean it writes itself, that old man, I mean the stunts, again, incredible.
Absolutely incredible stunts.
They use zero models, this is all, this is like smoking the bandit level, stunt work,
All right, or blues brothers.
I got to tell you, Michael Lerner versus the maniac comp is not a fair fight.
For those of you at home, Robert Davy just told Michael Lerner he was the only one that
could stop the maniac comp.
Which Michael Lerner, if he could eat a sandwich without panting, I'd be shocked.
When he pulled that gun just now, they had to take us a break for about a week and let
him rest up to continue the scene. By the way, we had a giveaway before the movie and
I want to apologize to the young woman who got the poltergeist remake. Terrible. Just
terrible. Sam Rockwell, my favorite actor. We talked about it on the show. It was just
a tragedy. It's terrible. I don't know if that's even considered a problem.
Well, I'm pressured ready. It's more of a punishment. I'll tell my Sam Rockwell pressure ready. Oh, yeah, we get a poltergaste
That's good. This house is crazy. It's good
One guy back there or lady gets it somebody's cackling. Yeah
I tell you between my wall bergen your rockwell we could
Really not do anything with these impressions
The only other impression I can do is Tom waits in an interview.
Let's hear it.
Well, I like the film maniac cop because I've always related to justice.
That's sort of a thing.
That's good.
It's a decent impression.
Yeah, yeah.
I do a bunch, but they have to be like just spontaneous. I can't do them forced.
Well, then they're not really impressions. Are they? No, not at all.
Sounds more like flying by the CD or S. Here I do a Gandalfini. You ready? Yeah.
What are we going to do by this many? I can't.
Come out of what we're gonna do with many I can't it's terrible, right?
Don't stand by the my claim that the soprano is one of the worst tells you to try
Stay Jay. Yeah, you hate everything that's good and love everything that's bad. It's not true
It's not true at all. All right. You have no other examples. Then don't say towerized. I'll hit you with this fucking microphone
Oh, yeah, Joe was like pat you got to watch tower heist. I
I sat and watched this thing. He's like, huh?
It's a funny movie.
All right, fine.
Tower height.
I didn't say it was great.
I said it was enjoyable.
You liked Norbyt.
I thought you'd enjoy it.
Yeah, you own Norbyt.
I tolerated Norbyt.
I own Norbyt because it's a masterpiece.
It's horrifically racist, Norbyt.
Eddie Murphy is that.
It is terribly racist.
Eddie Murphy is the Asian guy.
How that got past.
I have no idea how he got that in.
But any Murphy as the husband and wife is masterful.
Yeah, that's got some laughs.
We're gonna do it with America.
That also sounds sort of like a, like a, uh, like a, uh, like an Andy Garcia.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, what are you doing?
AJ, come on, uh,
I keep having visions of this woman in season four.
Show stinks.
Well, you've seen three scattered episodes from different seasons.
I don't give a shit.
All right.
I know bad when I see it.
It is just widely considered pretty much the best television show I ever made.
But go ahead and have your opinion.
You gonna tell me it was better than true detective season one?
Yeah, I am.
You fucking asshole they also managed to sustain the sopranos for more than eight episodes before falling into a cauldron of shit
Look at this guy Richard Greco made it out whatever happened at Greco
He had that if looks could kill which was supposed to be his James Bond and then we never heard from him again
Yeah, that was like how they got to play Nick on family ties was in my team and
other than that was the end of the line Greek go was in night at the Roxbury
As Richard Greek as Greek never a good sign. That's like how screech was in made as screech
Yeah, and the joke was Vince one going. Did you just fucking let screech in the club and not us right never a good position to be in if you're screech
Or Billy Zayn and Zoolander or whatever. I love Billy Zayn, though sure
Billy Zane used to be in all those soft core like porn movies red shoe
diaries yeah and this was like the typical like Billy Zane description in the
TV guide for it would be like a reluctant handyman falls into the
wilds of a lonely housewife that was like Billy Zane's whole career then he got
Titanic yeah insane insane that he got that part you find Billy Zane a little
little hammy in Titanic. Little over the top. Yeah, he's a little hammy, but in a good way when he's like a machino way. Drop kicking babies into the ocean and everything that he does.
He's like machino hammy, so I like it. All right.
Michael Lerner is now trying to defuse this situation by telling the maniac cop that
his conviction which was wrongful to begin with will be reversed. Hopefully that will
stop the killing, probably as you still have Clarence Williams III, who's just got a
hard dick to kill something and the other guy that looks like McFully.
Still a lot of Clarence Williams III?
I believe so.
I mean, I'd love to just go to that guy's house on a Saturday night and explore the mountains
of cocaine that are being stored.
Allegedly.
You know, I'm just saying he looks like a guy with parties.
This guy in a towel.
Yeah.
Tell perfectly staying on.
Tell you if I'm in prison I don't walk the grounds in a towel.
This is, this is an awesome sequence here.
They light maniac up on fire and he still takes everybody down while he's burning.
Again, real stunts. No CGI fire. That guy is on fire right now.
Very frank and stint -esque.
I don't know how to do this shit, they have a safe
word like in case he actually gets burned just seems terrifying to me well
it's there's a technique I think it's called like cold fire or something but
they put a gel they put a gel on you that burns and apparently the fire is
cooler than normal fire okay something like that but I'm sure there's a safe
word yeah and then they have like eight guys with extinguishers ready to put
out, you know.
Serial colors burn up through the wall.
They fall to their deaths.
I'm going to go out and live here and say that just because you're on fire and you fell
into a bus, it wouldn't explode like that.
No, I agree.
What do you think?
I agree.
Here we are in our final scene.
Now surely no one could have been surprised that that hand coming out of the coffin at the
end of this.
what? Stop ruining it for the kid that's never seen it. He would have had no way of
suspecting the maniacop would return. I guarantee he knows that there's maniacop
free badge of silence. I know I'm kidding. Badge of silence. What does that even mean?
What does that mean? It's the worst title I've ever heard. Worst of silence. Worst
So actually quantum of solace is probably the worst like big title I've ever heard of my life. I still know what it even means. Daniel Craig doesn't know what it means.
Quantum of solace. That's a good name for an action movie.
They are giving Matt. What's his name? Matt Cornell. Matt Cornell. Maybe Matt
Cordell. Cordell. Hearing Matt Cordell proper burial at the end of the movie
here, he's been absorbed of all falsely accused wrongdoing. I love how they come to
pay their respect. Like, you know, he was a good guy after all that maniac comp.
Despite the women he murdered in the first film and the shop owner and yeah newspaper clerk and you know the cops that he murdered in this film the traffic cop that he hung from a book.
We should go to his funeral seem like a cool guy.
Yeah, literally Michael Lerner is just like the lesson is Michael Lerner being like I was asking for it. I'm sorry.
Yeah, it's a terrible. Look, I've made mistakes terrible message
Why did the picture suddenly get incredibly clear looks really good. Yeah
This is the 25th anniversary by the way of maniac come to happy 25th babe sure
There's that badge of silence
Half melted from the fire
Should have done that Davi
So this guy needs his badge back.
I also found, well, you're going to see it here in a second,
but he has a very non -threatening hand bust out.
He just kind of casually grabs his badge as you'll see.
And do you think these two are off to stup?
I hope they do it in the graveyard.
On, you ever make out in a graveyard?
I think I was fingered once in a graveyard by a corpse.
I did I once made out with a young lady in a graveyard and she was wearing
patchouli and every time I smell it to this day I get a get an erection. I get a
corpse. That's a much better name for a maniac cop. Jack Lashert. No let's go
with Mike Cordell. That's a good name of it MTV VJ. Yeah it's back Cordell.
Oh, bring the hottest of indie jabs.
You guys like that one, that was the gin blossoms.
I love the gin blossom, they're underrated band.
Now this guy's come back for the dead twice.
Do we want to cover the coffin with anything?
Nah, that'll be fine.
Yeah, should we put some dirt in there?
Nah, just leave it an open grave.
He's fine, he's dead.
Michael learned her apologize to him.
That's the end of it.
How was your day at work, honey?
Oh boy, I tell you I thought there was a good bust out in grab
All right, I was wrong ladies and gentlemen folks hold on
Let's all just take in the song in the closing credits. Please listen to this hip -hop
Explanation of the plot of maniac cop too
As Ken pointed out last night, you weren't a movie in the 80s unless they recap the plot
at the end with a rap song.
And then Will Smith brought it back with Men in Black and Wild Wild West.
I
Okay, that's a terrible set of one fire should one of those you'll show up in your jacuzzi that doesn't happen in any of the movies
No, as far as I know correct
That's like some maniacop fanfiction where the rappers are like what if he was in our jacuzzi?
He'll show up in your jacuzzi to do what yeah, then I was like, oh who'd they get run DMC or whatever at the end of the movie
It's like just two guys names did this rap so like Matt Cordell
Back or hell rap by Matt Cordell
Ladies and gentlemen, Maniacop Joe, let's hear it.
Thank you so much for coming, everybody.
Thank you for coming.
This has been We'll See You In Hell, a production
of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
If you want to learn about any other Fangoria Podcasts,
whatever, go to Fangoria .com.
You can email a good friend here, Ken, at Fangoria .com.
Thanks for coming out, everybody.
You were really a lot of fun.
Okay, one, two, three, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight