Welcome to We'll see you in hell it's a new year a happy new year I hope but it's
the same old show you know and love I'm Joe Derosa and I'm Patrick Walsh 2021 it's a time when I
thought we'd have flying cars and Doc Brown's and things like that but no it's actually just it's
like the other sci -fi movies where the world is at an end in 2021 yeah it's you want it to be
back to the future one but instead we're getting back to the future two here in the fifth reality
you know like it's it kind of sucks uh how was your Christmas you had to ask me that off
the air let's let's revisit on air now you know it was uh blow average uh it was you don't say
you know I had a nice day I opened uh presents with my lovely wife we watched a couple pictures
and hung out but you know they're it's not the same obviously did you we had well presents um yeah I did
I got um awaited blanket for my crippling anxiety uh -huh I got the new uh Prince Deluxe vinyl set
for uh the sign of the Times album which I'm very excited to dig into it's got like 500
unreleased tracks on it I made this joke on Twitter that was like when you're really
because I did it with his 1999 album too but when you get deep into those Prince B sides
one will be like called Jesus Christ you are my savior right and the next one's called like
licking the shit out of your pussy he is all over the place but it's always either about his dad
fucking or god and uh man even the B sides like the guy was an absolute genius so I'm very excited
to get into his uh sign of the Times which is an amazing album on its own so I can only imagine what
the stuff he left off was like I'm a fan of Prince I you know it's pretty much just me he's kind
of this obscure guy but I really like yeah you were into him yeah but nobody knows knows knew about him
right exactly first yeah yeah I feel like that's like I'm like that with green day
well that's true punk I got some milestone gifts this year for my folks uh okay my mom made me
well this is very lovely she made me an album of that document of the first three years of my life
it was very sweet nice month to month pictures me as a baby with the family really sweet lots of
captions and things very touching uh so that was a big one and then my dad gave then they lived
together I don't mean to separate the gifts but you could tell who was giving which my dad gave me tools
which I was excited about so that's clearly I've hit a point in my age right uh and I did do the
Tim Taylor when I opened them up I went yes did you see by the way the in the last season of last
man standing Tim he's playing Tim Taylor and yeah I did you know I never talked about this on here
I really try not and I hope you realize when I talk about my TV experiences it's not like oh god
what could have been it's just like you know yeah I'm over it for the most part I just I sometimes
you can't believe what goes on they were adamant adamant on the cool kids about us having
as a guest star on the cool kids like the eighth lead of last man standing uh who is like a 30 year old
guy and they were like well he can come in and maybe his dad is like Martin Moll or something so we're
like so where does last man standing take place and they told us wherever the fuck it takes place
like all right well that's not here so and they're like yeah but he travels across the country to go to
this old folks home to see and we're like who cares about this guy oh they wanted it to be a
crossover yeah we're not Tim Allen comes comes to visit but like the one of the like the daughter's
boyfriend comes in and they're like well he's a breakout character on that show I was like the show
does slightly better than this one what are we what are we trying to get here but uh that was going
to be a big get like they advertise this guy coming and and I thought I mean they make you say no to
these things 10 times so if you're ever watching something and you're like how the fuck did this happen
it probably just means people got tired of saying no and finally went yeah fine yeah anyway the other
gift I got that was a but yeah what Joe's talking about sorry is Tim Allen uh Tim the tool man tailor
guest star and they did like a back the future thing where he was talking to the last man standing
version of Tim Allen yeah and I'm such a sucker for any sort of nostalgia thing yeah with a
shell like home improvement that I didn't watch it wasn't into I got excited still that he was
doing the part like I'm not gonna watch it but I'm a real sucker for anything where they bring
somebody back anyway not a sucker for that uh my my parents also gave me a whiskey decanter set
monogrammed with my name on it okay and it's a moment like that where you think maybe it's time to
take a look in the mirror look look at the gifts I'm getting here for my back they're like we know you
like the booze bottle whiskey wrapped up under the I mean it was just I was like I look I was excited
about it but I was like yeah well this is kind of like your parents giving you like a coke mirror or
sure but like a decanter is like the glass antique if you pour the whiskey in it and then you
get a nice yeah so basically I'll trick anybody into comes into my apartment into thinking the the
cheap whiskey I drink is like fancy right right got my family name on it on the bottle oh what is
this uh Evan Williams Evan Williams I um in every 50s uh show movie I watched a lot of film noir
lately what you did not have an office without a decanter yeah yeah 12 bottles and uh and a bunch of
glasses I mean these people are drinking constantly and I love it I met uh when we were gonna do can I
kick it uh very briefly at true which was the hip -hop comedy show me and Al Jackson and tone bell
and mark age used to do uh we briefly had a deal with true TV and we were gonna do a show and didn't
happen but um our production company was Vindabona which is the he's the guy that
invented America's funniest home videos I don't got to tell me who fucking Vindabona is yeah so we were
at his production company working and then one day Becky uh our producer said do you want to go
meet Vin and we're like yeah and we went down to his office and it was awesome he's like it was that
office it was a you step back in time he was like this old guy in a suit full drink cart over the
corner I think he even had like the fucking bull horns hanging behind his desk like I was like man
this is and my favorite part was the decanter and everything were empty and I was like here's a man
that he's pouring it out he's there for show uh secretary comes in he grows her no no don't don't
disparage the man Jesus sorry sorry if you're listening Vindabona to our patreon podcast
we we know you didn't grow up anyone um but it was an interesting Christmas uh pinkstone
our friend friend of the show very sweet him and his wife Jess sent me uh there was a
I opened my presence in my mom and dad so there's one more under the tree for you and I opened it
and it was a box from Jim and his wife I was like this is so sweet what is this and I opened it
and and it was it was like a gift box of like a bunch of random stuff that there was a DVD for the movie
about time in there because Jim was like I think you'd like this movie uh at the time the the
romantic comedy Richard Curtis yes because he was like I know you like love actually this is like
this is a romcom sci -fi thing you can watch with your folks over Christmas about time is good did you
watch it I haven't watched yet no yeah it's a good movie uh there was a seven inch in there
there you know just so cool little things but he but he put a note in that was like I know I know you
didn't have a lot of surprises this Christmas man and I just wanted to send you something to
catch you off guard it was really sweet all that between that and the my dad gave me a socket wrench
that was my granddad's that he gave to my dad and my dad gave to me and yeah that and then the photo
album it was a sentimental Christmas this year that's very nice I uh my dad you know they asked
on the Q &A for a Walsh family Christmas story that this is one I kind of don't bring up because I
just feel bad about it but he in his basement has this huge assortment of like boxes that when my
parents divorced he got half she got half or something like that but um you know it's boxes of old
papers old like perfect attendance certificates of you have mine on my sisters and pictures and so
forth for every major holiday for the last I want to say five years at least meaning Christmas and
then my birthday or a combination of both I get some sort of box um or album of pictures of me
that I don't like looking at I do not like looking back at my childhood or thinking about it anyway
so I never look at them uh one year it was his old videos of us converted to DVD which I immediately
filed on a shelf and we'll we'll never watch I imagine that they are dark portraits of my family life
but I'll we'll see and or in the case of this year it is just simply a bunch of my old schoolwork
so it's like Christmas I'm getting no gifts you know basically and I'm like okay here's something for
my dad what's it going to be it's the usual card where he signs it like love Kevin um the one
year I put it on Instagram but he he's it's said to a great friend friend was crossed out and wrote
son and then he put love Kevin and on the front was a lighthouse because I love lighthouse is so much
but this this year was just my old papers like I'm looking through it and I'm like oh okay like
here's a spelling test from third grade or something I and there's a there's a sweetness to yours
where it's like they put together this album of like your first three years or whatever but
if you're getting it every year and it's just like he's trying to free space in his basement
there's a real business to it you know yeah I hear you I get and I don't have the balls to just say to
him like dad I'd rather die than relive growing up so I don't think you should say that to him
if you had the balls I don't think that's a good thing to say I think you just let him
yes I have let it go uh by the way quick quick plug Christmas plug uh not for myself but I received
this book in the mail from Emily Simpson uh one of the Helian sent it uh it's called coffin blossoms
yes book John right yes yeah book you can buy night right now it's a collection of horror
short stories um but John Wolfe who's a Helian wrote a story in here called heby jibis
yes I am the show I haven't read the story though yeah so anyway I finally got the book in the
mail but uh I look forward to reading it John and uh go get the book if you if you want to support
um yes and thank you Emily as always I sent Emily a nice little Christmas gift I said well I
I'll I'll just tell you because I got one for myself as well as a little Christmas gift for me but
I if I got the uh the new Friday the 13th box for Emily and myself the shout factory you asshole
Jesus Christ you really outdid my gift big time this is like a curvy enthusiasm
Jesus Christ I centered the re the reanimator arrow uh special edition my gift yeah it is
but next to a hundred and seventy dollar box set not that great uh well I you know I usually
just send a DVD she was she's she's a big help especially during the pandemic you know
damn it son of a bitch all right boy this song put that up somehow
I got it for myself too and I'm debating like do I open this or do I save it until it's worth
a thousand dollars in a year it's it's on it it's if if you're a prime member you can get it
it goes on sale sometimes for like 105 bucks or something or 110 bucks
and I've been tempted to grab it a couple times because it's a very nice set
but I already own every one of those movies except for Jason goes to hell which I have no
interest in ever watching ever again um but I don't know and I own the first I own all of them
up through Manhattan on Blu -ray already and I'm just like god damn it but like these are like 4K
transfers and all that and I'm like fuck well yeah they're supposed to be you know a great picture
and then tons and tons of special features but um you know as you always say that's right at the
13th series seems like the kind of movies you'd want to see grainy yeah yeah I'm just you know
again this is another thing I'm a fucking sucker for when they start talking about transfers and all
this like well I guess I should have that what you know yeah um and these box sets you know so many
of them we both own quite a few at this point they're so intriguing because the box art is so great
and yeah it seems like when you get it in the mail and you open it up it feels like for a minute
like you're opening like a toy chest or something and then you realize no it's just a box that has movies
in it but the pictures of those boxes online I'm just it gets me man it's still a thrill for me and
it's a good deal I mean it's it's 10 movies or whatever and all this extra stuff so uh I'm excited
about I've only seen the first Friday the 13th that's the only one you ever saw the only one I've
seen maybe maybe I saw two at some point but I haven't gone beyond that so aside from the classic you
know aspect of it that's one of the worst ones I think I think you really two was superior yeah
three is a lot of fun four is great six is my favorite oh all right I'm open in the box then I'm
gonna do it uh I would I you know it's like you you want to set see don't you already have a
Friday the 13th set though that you opened yeah I had an open Friday the 13th set the old one which
was like kind of a a much thinner black box with Jason's face on it and when that went out of print
I sold that guy for four hundred bucks opened and all I had watched I think was one and two so
that's why I'm thinking this one being shout factory and a limited edition it might but it
could go the way of the fly set the fly set I bought for 70 bucks and now it's 20 bucks so like
I guess it just depends on how well it sells fucking Amazon dude I mean they if anybody that works
in Amazon sales is listening to this take the god damn back to the future trilogy off of the deals
of the day it's enough they've had the same deals the day for three months months it's been on
there it's like take it off already yeah and I feel like and I paid $75 for that fucking thing when
it first came out maybe even more and now it's like $13 or something it's like a real kick in the
ass man well they have the new for even the 4k versions are like uh still like 40 50 bucks but
Amazon I'm doing my best to just veer off it I try not to go on it I've stopped using the delivery
apps I'm trying to order from restaurants themselves it's just I find as I rant about this stuff and
get angry about this stuff and how the basically the fabric of society is collapsing around us I can't
still do that and be you know dropping all this money on Amazon and over postmates and so forth it's
not fair so I do my best to to always support the other people I haven't been good about that in the
past because Amazon always had such better deals I mean it used to be you'd be an amoeba and you'd be
like okay I can get this for 30 bucks I really want it you look on Amazon and it's 12 it's it's really
hard to give Amazon the money at that point I mean sorry to give it me but the money at well amoeba
also too in in many ways an incredibly fairly price store and in many ways incredibly unfairly
priced I always thought amoeba had great deals on vinyl and insane deals on CDs and the worst
deals imaginable on any movie you go up into that movie floor and you're not even go up there and
you know I'm much I love I love Blu -ray and DVDs but I mean I get up there and I'm like man this is
outrageous yeah you're like this used Blu -ray of lethal weapon three is 2899 like what the fuck are
you guys pricing this shit based on yeah I'm I'm excited I've been I was talked of Vince I mean we
we I really want to get back to me but looking at the new space I have a feeling I'm going to go
once go and it's pretty good trying to convince myself go a second time and then never go again it
just like the soul is gone I think it's still going to be a kickass record store to go I hope so
I know days getting lost into me I mean you know anytime I needed a little distraction or pick me
up in LA when I live there I'd go to amoeba get lost in there for an hour lightly stoned at amoeba
I could be in there four hours yeah and just leave with amazing finds I mean great stuff yeah I
miss it I went in there drunk a couple times with no intention of anything you you leave with
$230 a record you're like right that shit yeah yeah the um the the box sets I I have because you
know you you know Joe and I always joke about how we got this beautiful Igmar Bergman box set containing
like 50 of the greatest movies ever made and just we just both know we'll never watch it same with the
Werner Herzog but I've been digging into both lately and I've been thrilled I mean that the Bergman
movies I've seen have been so good we Allen I knew I knew rip the man off but I didn't know quite to
the extent he stole his cinematographers then knife guest the movies look like Woody Allen movies yeah
but um I watched Fannie and Alexander on Christmas you know which is considered one of the best ever
and I mean mine blowing so and I'm watching the five -hour cuts I watched a five -hour Fannie and
Alexander five -hour scenes from a marriage that's wild and I got the new mini box set from Criterion
which is beautiful too and I love how even though it's not great you know like I got a big wall
collection like yeah I also put on Instagram it covers a wall and generally when a box comes out like
the Simpson season six was in the shape of Homer's head and I was like well god damn it because then now
it doesn't fit and then season seven they got so many complaints they went back to the old box
models and now you have this weird head in the mix yeah I never buy any weird shaped box I don't
care right it's like even as cool as like you know like the hell razor one where it's the box or
or like the phantasm it comes inside a silver I'm like yeah yeah well I don't do it when it's an
extra like they had a big Lebowski where you can get big Lebowski for five dollars or the big Lebowski
in a plastic bowling ball for a 110 you know like I'm not doing that but Criterion now is clearly
trying to spice up their packaging and they you know they had the giant kind of storybook Godzilla set
which looks great I have that still haven't watched it the Fellini set is similar I have an
open open mind but the Fellini set is very similar it's kind of it's almost like a vinyl album shape
and I've seen very few Fellini so I'm excited to do it yeah I would I would like to get that Fellini
set too the Bergman set the Criterion set it's the best deal I've ever gotten ever on a blu -ray set
it's every Bergman movie it's 35 discs yeah I think I made $90 for it or something like yeah I mean
even at its more price it's it's $4 a blu -ray of a master you know like it's incredible and a giant
book and the set looks great and makes you look smart you know oh yeah it does I got it right above
my cast it casts of vetties and right below my Herzog and Hitchcock yeah and I got him
her now set on top of that too I really look like a real fucking intellectual and people come over here
little that they they know I'm the only one I'm cracking up there is the masters of the universe
yeah with the the belt that you can clip to your own belt to act out the scenes
I um I love the box sets I love the Criterion I always will I feel like I feel very happy that they
have survived all this stuff that their their streaming service has taken off so well I love seeing
when I go on Twitter now there's like big pockets of really interesting film conversation and I feel
like between Scorsese and his film preservation work which overlaps with Criterion he's done some
great stuff with them but uh and what they do like they I feel secure that film history will be kept
alive I love what they do I really do I have a a good scary stuff for people to go by if you have
the chance I if you're a comic book fan I recommend buying this digitally the hard copies are
are out of print and rather expensive unless you can find a good deal great but I didn't know this
existed uh it's called Frank Miller's Robocop and basically Frank Miller the great comic book writer
who who wrote uh uh the Dark Knight Returns is his big one uh one of his big ones um but Frank Miller
obviously you know Sin City and whatever um he was hired to write the sequel to Robocop the the
screenplay um they he wrote he wrote scripts for two and three uh they got sort of hatchet job and
reworked and what made it to the screen didn't really represent what his story was even though it had
some elements of it here and there um and Robocop two and three obviously pale in comparison to part
one particularly three is an abomination two is passable but Helen Will Potter and I were just talking
on letterbox he told me that two was worth watching I've only seen one two is worth watching in the way
that like a death which sequel is worth watching where it's just outrageous and fun but none of them
get anywhere near the the the the Verhoeven original but this comic book Frank Miller's Robocop and
then there's another one called Frank Miller's Robocop with a subtitle I'm blanking on it um
anyway it's the comic book version of his screenplays for two and three and I read two uh and I got to
tell you man it's a it's a shame it really is a shame this didn't make it to the screen because it it's
such a sensible sequel it's got the same vibe and energy of that first movie it's an extension of the
first movie it does everything right it it takes everything in the direction it should have gone in
in that second movie that that it didn't and it's really if you're a Robocop fan worth reading uh the
art is is pretty glorious in it and it's you know the the the violent it's uber violent like like the
Verhoeven movie um it sounds awesome is this a reissue I just read them uh digitally because the the
hard copies were like you know they it was like three volumes and they were like 65 dollars each
right throughout a print I was like yeah I'm just I got it I have a I have comicsology which is a great
comic book app um that you can get and and you pick a monthly subscription fee and you get discounted
prices on downloads if you want to purchase but then they also have a free they have a library section
you can borrow from okay you know it's like unlimited borrowing from certain titles and these were
under the borrow titles which was great um but if you like comic books and you like Robocop it's
a no -brainer I I highly recommend it it's a great read I will check that out I'm a fan of the original
Robocop but uh I got to watch two according to well patoar I got to read this book according to
joderos um comic book it's not really commenting it's not reading who I think that'd be quite a
discussion with some nerds online Joe bring it on you name all right let's let's go over to the
movie corner it's about that time um I saw actually here's what I did on Christmas day to be honest
with you I woke up and watched a movie I've always wanted to see called Merry Christmas Mr. Lawrence
you squeezed in something besides the five hour
that was Christmas Eve oh okay yeah Joe I have nothing nothing
I mean I don't know how much more clear I can be and I don't think any of our listeners have
anything either we're all hanging on by a thread I mean I know you are a man about town but we're
on lockdown you're eating onions you spot dimes I don't know what the hell's going on over here
uh is your sandwich plays done by the way yeah we're just closed for New Year's the New Year's week
and uh oh so you don't have like an end date no we're do we're going to pop up you know
few probably a few months we've been about a month now we'll probably do it for a little while
longer and then see if it's something we can move to its own thing who knows I love it uh so yeah
Merry Christmas Mr. Lawrence and it was I was actually laughing by the end of this movie it's
it's not funny at all but I was laughing because of just how little Christmas is in this movie
and how much sepuku the Japanese art of killing yourself by slicing your own stomach open so
it is not a Christmas movie people um but it was very interesting I like to quite a bit
it's David Bowie the best I've ever seen him although I have somehow never seen the man who
felt earth I own it but I've never seen it I couldn't want to see a movie less than that film I just
don't I mean David Bowie and Rip torn I want to see what's going on there in space you're
fucked in the head oh am I uh so yeah David Bowie's in this thing it was made in like 1983 so we're
talking around the um you know modern love era David Bowie and he he looks completely like a Nazi
like he always kind of did but in this one um it's nuts I mean his hair is super blonde he's like
he just he's you know him and Iggy Pop both kind of danced in that like are we enjoying Nazism kind
of way that was always a little weird anyway David Bowie this is a World War II movie uh he's a
British major who ends up at this Japanese prison camp and the camp leader Japanese man clearly has
some sort of weird sexual obsession with David Bowie that's the plot of the movie I'm not making it up
but uh I think you could conceivably watch it and miss that if you were like real obtuse and like
you just never thought about things like that but it's very much there the got David Bowie has I
keep I just like saying Bowie has this weird psychosexual hold on the the major at the camp and only
David Bowie you could totally understand you'd be like yes I see how this is happening but um
right it's a whole it's a movie about war and how war is bad that's why I never like war movies because
the moral is always war is bad and I know that war is bad you know what I mean yeah I that's why I
never care I'm just like all right got it but this one this is the kind of war movie I do like um where
it focuses on the people a small group of people how they are affected there's no combat in it um
but it's getting worse by the second it's it's good it's it's uh they're this little like weird
like I said kind of psychosexual mind struggled between these men is really interesting
and in the end you know the anti -war message is very well done the title kind of takes on this
cool meaning when you think back on it and uh the score is kind of the most talked about aspect of
the movie it wasn't done by David Bowie but um the score is really its most famous aspect it you know
wasn't won all kinds of awards it still talks about all the time and then recently on the uh the
Netflix show song exploder I watched the losing my religion episode which is great if you like
REM or that song and I don't know how you couldn't but the uh Peter Buck talks about how the rift
from losing my religion is essentially taken from the score of Mary Chris's Mr. Lawrence the ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding and you'll hear it uh I thought that was kind of cool so all in all not a perfect
movie it reminded me a lot of unbroken that Angelina Jolie directed which was also not a perfect movie
but weirdly that was another movie about a Japanese prisoner camp leader who had a weird psych you
know sexual attraction to somebody so I don't know if this happened a lot or if they're both
referring to the same one article about it or what but it's interesting I I liked it okay it's not
a Christmas movie all right well we were talking about it already so I'll talk about a rewatch I did
of Friday the 13th part six okay uh my favorite of the franchise hands down if you've never seen it
which a hard press to believe a lot of the fans of this show haven't seen it yet but it is called
Friday the 13th part six Jason lives because at the end of Friday the Friday the 13th part four
Jason is still just a human being uh that's just out there in the woods killing people and the end
of four it's called the final chapter it's supposed to be that he's finally dead and they've killed
him five is the mental institution one where there's like another Jason impersonator or something like
that and then in six it's when Jason becomes supernatural it's very meta it's very funny at times
it does a lot of winking to camera probably the most famous line uh that does that in the movie
is when the grave digger uh or the graveyard attendee or whatever the hell that guy's called uh
finds Jason's grave exhumed and he says uh who the hell would want to dig up Jason Voorhees some
people got a real sick idea of entertainment and uh so it's that kind of film but that said
a lot of fun uh a cool storyline and two of the best Friday the 13th kills ever one of which is
executed on uh Arnold Horsheck okay welcome back codder fame uh it's on his real name I can't
remember is Ron Polito whatever's no he was Epstein Ron Polilla I think that I don't remember
John Polito was in Big Lebowski either way uh it's a full ranch Doritos a cool ranch Doritos okay
hornitos uh it's a it's a fun movie it's a really really fun movie and it really up to to me
epitomizes the the that late eighties fun horror supernatural slasher thing that was going on a
lot back then absolutely worth checking out I'm gonna do the whole run maybe I'll do another uh
special uh maybe we should do a special going through all the Friday the 13th we'll discuss
but um you know it's a huge investment that's the thing like when when you got to rewatch all
these movies it's an investment of like 20 hours so um I'm telling the listeners I know you know
Joe another investment you made financially on Emily's present versus my I guess we should have
compared I don't know I mean that that it couldn't be more of a fucking side fell plot I mean it's
it's it's it's good if they never did it I don't remember them doing it but yeah it's like it's the
tips thing from Kirby enthusiast yeah they did they did some gift stuff you know on on
side fell they always had gift chip ins and stuff I'm I'm rewatching Seinfeld again because it just
gives me comfort and I love watching shows that I've seen a million times right but arguably the greatest
monologue in the entire show and I forgot about it is when they do the episode where they take the old
people out they're doing like the old people assistance thing uh -huh I mean the the goiter episode
one yeah the goiter one yeah yeah that that scene with Jason Alexander in the diner with the old man
who's like I don't think about dying and he starts just screaming at him how could you not think
about it could happen in a second what do you got no brains yeah what are you stupid yeah it's arguably
the best monologue ever on the show you know it's the best and still you know even though I own the
the DVDs and everything there's I still love to just sit down and watch it with the commercials at night
I've been doing it now for 20 plus years but like I have noticed more and more lately they're not showing
those like the one you're mentioning I haven't seen in years and reruns and I think this at some point
just started focusing a on just the classic episodes and be the later episodes now granted I
prefer the later episodes I'm fine with that but I almost never see certain episodes of that show like
ever in reruns I don't know why that is I guess they probably learned through research that some are
more watched than others or something but it sucks I like when they used to just show like they showed
the Simpsons I'd go oh sweet this is season four episode six and then the next one would be seven and
they just showed no notice with syndication these days there's no rhyme or reason to any of it
they're mixing season five with season one you're like what the fuck is going on here man yeah I was
watching I feel like I witnessed the change because I was watching King of Queens live every night I
had never seen it and I was on season four and I was checking with the Wikipedia making sure I didn't
miss any episodes and I hadn't and I was loving it and then just one night they randomly showed some
Thanksgiving episode out of season and I was like oh fuck and then from then on it was just a
grab bag and I never was able to complete the show I'm a complete it all right what do you got
another round is my next one Joe I think you'd like this movie a lot it is about they're gonna
they're gonna remake it definitely probably like Todd Phillips something for an American version but
it is a Mads Michelson movie who was an actor who if you don't know the name you love him you've
seen him at a bunch of stuff he was in the Hannibal series which is one of my next watches Rogue one
he was in yeah he just replaced John Depp in the fantastic Beast and how to fuck is that definitely
happening because it was rumored and no that's happening he was denying it I love how they just
looked like no that's not true yeah so another round is is a foreign movie it's Danish as his
mads himself it is directed by Thomas Vinterberg who directed another amazing movie with an amazing
Mads Michelson performance called the Hunt if you've never seen that it's always streaming I think it
might be on Netflix but a great foreign movie about a man who was mistaken for a pedal file and what would
a episode of we'll see you in hell be without a mention of that word another round which I somehow
have still not discussed in my rambling is a movie about four high school teachers who read this
theory this guy had that the body is born 0 .06 or something percent low on alcohol so you're always
unhappy until you get to that 0 .06 or whatever it's like some actual quote some guy made some study
so these guys that's the loose like jump off point of the plot is these guys are like we should try
this this this experiment where we're always constantly a low level of drunk and from there you know
the four guys all have very different experiences at first they're like oh my god this is amazing
they're being more outspoken in their life you know they're having more fun with their partners
etc but then as you might expect it leads to alcoholism for some you know it leads to their lives
falling apart so there's some dark comedy it's a drama to me I wish it leaned a little more into the
comedy or a little more into the drama as is it just kind of plays like a series of events a very
entertaining series of events but yeah I could have gone for both more comedy and more drama from it
but this Thomas Vinterberg is part of that kind of dogma you know the Lars von Trier thing where they
don't seem to like plot they don't seem to like things like that and and find whatever but the movie
is a lot of fun to watch I think if they nail an American remake this is the kind of movie that they
should be remaking you know finding a foreign movie like this with a can't miss comedic premise and
doing it with four really funny actors I hope they're planning it now maybe I should ask maybe I
look into doing it but it's a really good movie it's a movie about drinking which is always
interesting to me it reminded me a lot of John Cassavetti's stuff and Mads is great and it also has
like the best ending of any movie this year so I recommend another round all right I watched a 1974
film called Behind the Door which is basically an exorcist rip off it's something I know that behind
the green door is one of the most famous pornos were these was that was one a spoof of the other no
they're unrelated okay sorry behind the door I think originally was titled who are you
it's one of those confusing 70s films where it's made in Italy and but stars all English people
English speaking people yeah and then for some reason their voices are dubbed over again like it you
know one of those things um you know why do they do that I don't know I can't figure it out
I just heard Dustin Hoffman on stern and he said he kicked himself that he didn't work with
Ingmar Bergman or no Felini I'm sorry but and he just said to Felini he was like I won't do it unless
you promise not to do that weird dubbing shit with me I want my voice to be coming out of my mouth
and Felini goes no I only do the dubs yeah it's odd it's odd it's crazy um there's not much to say
about this movie it's an exorcist rip off it's low budget I enjoyed it thoroughly though you can get
it on Amazon for like ten bucks if you want to see it uh it's kind of hard to find otherwise um it
didn't do well critically Roger Ebert gave it one out of four stars when it was released and called
it scary trash uh which is a great description um but three hundred fifty thousand dollar budget made
fifteen million dollars at the box office not bad for its time um uh you know it's got some fun
visual the the basic plot is the the mother of a household gets possessed by a demon yeah that's
that's your basic ins and outs now obviously there's more to the plot than that but I don't need to
get into it just watch it uh if you're interested in some scary trash that will remind you of the
exorcist but I mean they just ripped off the exorcist that's all they did but that said it is kind
of freaky and uh the visual effects kind of scary and uh it's got a real creepiness to it so I
enjoyed it very much it's a movie that I think should be remade as I was watching and I was like
you could remake this now and make it really awesome uh and there would be no comparison to the
exorcist now so uh who knows if that'll ever happen but uh it's uh it's it's it's it's a cool film
it's a cool it's a cool little weird seventies horror Italian film yeah the Italians used to rip off
stuff constantly and the um the other big one that I just watched was piranha Joe Dante's early movie
which sucked everyone talks about how great it is I mean Joe Dante is an awesome director but piranha is
not good and they were gonna sue them that because it was such a jaws rip off which it is it completely is
but Spielberg saw and loved piranha and wouldn't let them sue and then that started the friendship between
Spielberg and Dante I just learned that but anyway um what's interesting is is it makes perfect
sense that Dante was picked to direct when you know piranha it makes perfect sense that Dante
was picked to direct gremlins because gremlins initially was a hard r it was really great and violent
and you know when you see piranha and you're like oh of course this is the guy for that job
like he was at a direct people getting ripped apart by a pack of you know fanged monsters right
and knows how to make tiny things that you feel like you could flick out of your way scary which is
hard to do yeah um I would like to end with a movie that I hope you put on your Christmas yearly list
I had never seen it it is now going to be on my every year Christmas list I have always heard it was
awesome but could never find it and now I think more and more it's becoming available because uh
Edgar Wright and some pretty big filmmakers lately have talked about how much they love it
it really is great it's a Canadian movie called the silent partner it is Elliott Gould kind of
as he's sliding out of his 70s peak uh he is awesome in it Elliott Gould is is I've been watching for
whatever reason a lot of his movies just because I've been watching a lot of 70s movies but you know he
is always kind of gives the same performance and it's good but it's always kind of the same sarcastic
dry guy his vibe in this movie is something completely different I think he thought it's a low
budget Canadian movie I'm really going to make this guy a character and it's awesome he it's the
best I've ever seen Elliott Gould um it's the best I've seen Christopher Plummer if I'm being honest
just because I've never seen him be like this he is the villain in it he is he's like hot uh I've never
seen this side of Christopher Plummer but he's this like a he's hates women so there's like scenes of
him mashing his barefoot to a woman's face and like you know he's like really fucked up but it's
also a very funny movie it's a heist movie John Candy plays a small supporting role uh before
his career got started serious role or comedic role he's sort of a you know comic relief around
the office the fact guy at the office whatever okay but um it was cool to see him at age 25 or whatever
you know um and it was written by the great Curtis Hanson RIP who did all kinds of great movies LA
Confidential hand that rocks the cradle um etc etc so I couldn't have loved this movie more the
Christmas vibe is very strong in it and it's just a really fun surprisingly kind of like nasty heist
movie with like a really dark fun sense of humor and John Candy what more do you want? I'll try to
check it out uh I'm my final one is a Leslie Nielsen movie called The Silent Fartner which is a spoof of
that film pretty pretty niche audience you're going for there with a spoof of a movie no one has
seen now for my final movie this is kind of on topic with today and it's a movie that
uh is very very funny and brilliantly done I've been meeting to talk about it for a while
and also addresses some of these um gender themes in a really creative way and in a very interesting
way you know that a lot of these movies we've been talking about lately just do swappily including
today's film um but it's called greener grass it's it's it's an absurdist comedy it's insane I've been
wanting to watch that actually it's incredibly dark it's incredibly strange and it's about
basically the competition of suburban mothers in suburbia and it's
fucking out there and awesome it's awesome it's just awesome awesome movie it's shot brilliantly almost like
almost like Edward Cesar hands like with that Burton style of like fluorescence suburbia
where everything is you know every woman's got bright red lipstick on and a pocket
address and and and and everybody is so affected and talked so strange and acts so
eccentricly the movie starts with the two main characters one of them complementing the other one
on her new baby and then she's like great do you want him and she's like really and she's like yeah
take him take my baby that's how it starts okay it just goes from there it ends on an incredibly dark
note um it's just an awesome awesome well done movie um I'm gonna give it up on Hulu yeah it is uh
I want to make sure I give credit to I'm terrible with names but the two women that made this
their names are Jocelyn Debeuer Debeuer Debeuer and Dawn Luby
Lubb I don't know sorry they're I don't know their name out of city anyway Jocelyn D E B O E R and
Dawn L U E B B E uh they uh wrote it and they directed it and they star in it and uh it went a
bunch of uh awards on the indie circuit and stuff and it's just a great movie man the kid uh Julian
Hillard plays this one of the sons in it and he's fucking incredible in this thing this kid deserved
an Oscar for this Jillian Julian Hillard is the also in a color out of space in the haunting of Hill House
a bunch alright I'm pumped I'm gonna check it out it's one of those where I'm always like about to hit
play and then I watch something else that I've already seen it's worth it's worth seeing it's really
great really great which brings us to our film for today which is not really great wonder woman
1984 two and a half hours slog through the DC universe usually something that I at least
marginally look forward to uh I enjoy the first Wonder Woman uh when I started to see trailers
for this one and started to hear about the production and hear about the story lines and what not
I started to get a little hesitant or concerned because I was like this sounds like
sequels stigma stuff man like they're jamming way too much shit into this sequel they're making it way too
big the fact that it's Wonder Woman 1984 sounds like some kind of kitschy unnecessary hook um
and all of those things were true uh in watching this thing it's uh it's it's a it's a two and a half hour
mess yeah I mean the the plot as it were is uh I mean it's just exhausting to even try to recollect
what it even happened but I texted you when I started it and I said the opening sequence to this
thing is absurd has nothing to do with the film that nothing to do with the themes of the film nothing
to do with anything about the movie no it starts with a seven or ten minute sequence of Wonder Woman
as an eight -year -old girl like in some weird competition it's playing quits from Harry Potter it looked
exactly like quits and like none of it makes sense they're they're running through some crazy optical
obstacle course it doesn't make sense why any of it is situated the way it is like it's not and by that
what I mean is is like as they go through each obstacle it's like why would you jump on that thing
to slide to the it just doesn't make any fucking sense it's just like crazy visuals that that make
no sense like it's just there to to try to wow you and it just goes on and on and on and like this
eight -year -old girl is beating every other grown woman that she's competing with and it's just stupid
and dumb and it takes forever and it's a lot like that second pirate to the Caribbean opening sequence
where he's trapped on like the cannibal island and you're like what the fuck with this man like get
to the fucking movie we're supposed to be watching right and I text you and I said this opening
sequence is absurd and you said just strap in and then your next text was what if I told you that
the power of wishing played a major role in this film and I was like there's no whatever he means
by that that's funny but like there's no way he means what I think he means and I was wrong the plot
of this movie is they find a wish stone they meaning a Gaggedo wonder woman and Kristen Wigg who
be eventually becomes Cheetah and it's something from the comics but but in the comics it's actually
something kind of cool and interesting and in this movie they took that cool and interesting thing
which was basically a stone that had the power to bring your to make your dreams a reality
which is much cooler than what they did in this movie which is a stone that you make a wish to
and it just makes the wish real so now you're you're you're supposed to be all in
mm -hmm with a character by the way that they impossibly pulled off in the first one just like they
impossibly pulled off Thor in the original in the Marvel Thor movie where you're like how are they
going to do this and it's not just cheesy and corny whatever they managed to land the plane
no pun intended wonder woman with with that with the story of this Amazonian woman that where where
there was so much of the look they introduced this character into Batman vs Superman they managed
in the same way that Marvel did with the Avengers leading up to that first Avengers movie they managed
to ground this superhero world in some sort of a reality where they they they they were convincing
and conveying Superman being an alien to you and that's why he had powers they were convincing and
conveying that Bruce Wayne had a lot of money and practical knowledge of things and that's why he
was able to do what he was able to do is Batman when wonder woman came into that mix you start going
well how are they going to pull this off just like when Thor came into the mix and the Marvel thing
after they established so much grounded whatever in science with Tony Stark and whatever
but they managed to pull it off they managed to pull it off and in this one it opens with this concept
of we we found a fucking genie stone and you're like guys we are way off the fucking map now like
this is nuts yeah and it just goes from there uh where to begin where to begin well I think first I'd
like to say just if you look at this in the in the in the in the cultural discussion when wonder woman
came out that was another movie you were not allowed to say you didn't like I didn't like the first
one but it seems like a masterpiece compared to this um now I think then well black Panther then you
couldn't say anything about black Panther but what happened then is that now because the shift has
rightly focused to black people diverse people minorities um the knives were just out it was kind of
insane to just see like hey Gal Gadot sucks this at least sucks out because the last time it was one
of those like where you just felt like I need to just say I like this because women are getting
there their big shot whatever uh you know tell it was presented to us so I think we're done with
a society we're putting we're caring less about women already I think that lasted about two years
but I don't mean me I don't mean yeah I mean the culture at large I think America was like hey let's
support women and then immediately we were like no we have much bigger problems and now we're just back
to like yeah this movie fucking sucks it was fun to see the truth come out about this movie I think too
that the what happened was is is you get you get a little slack at the beginning where it's like guys
everybody's trying their best and we're trying to give uh people whatever their persuasion or gender
whatever it is who haven't had the fair a fair shot a fair shot here so yeah that was not the time
you know it's kind of like when somebody dies it's like hey how about on the day they died not
bringing up the bad thing they did you know what I mean it's like give it some breathing room
and I think now enough time has transpired that with stuff like this it's like okay well now we're
gonna look at the quality of what's going on here and I really do think that Wonder Woman the first
one was was a quality film I really do I'm not just saying that and I also understand why you didn't
like it because it's not your type of movie I get it you know you're not into that kind of thing you're
not gonna like it I'm a big rooter for DC so you know I'm a fan boy I wanted to see them do well
and they did and I thought that the the reaction to that film was very justified with this
it's well it's getting it's getting pretty slammed I mean the the the the the rating yeah
Rotten Tomatoes keeps dropping and dropping and dropping but this to me now felt like
and every interview I read post -watching reinforces this opinion this movie to me felt like people
trying to show you something and failing tremendously at it Patty Jenkins I just read an interview
with her where she talked about like you know Warner Brothers didn't want me to have two opening
sequences on this movie and I insisted and I got it and I was right and it's like no you weren't right
the first fucking thing I said when I was watching this not even knowing that that conversation took place
was why the fuck is this opening thing on this that makes no sense and has nothing to do with anything
and a two and a half hour movie no love yeah so in two and a half hours they managed to not just
over stuff the movie they also managed to not act adequately execute any one storyline nothing
it goes nowhere in two and a half hours it is it is a broken fucking record from start to finish
and the tiniest things the tiniest details that needed just a little bit of attention or vastly overlooked
I saw an article the other day online said the 10 plot holes in Wonder Woman it was like number one
why is why are they pretending like cameras didn't exist in the 80s everybody carried around like a
portable polaroid you know what I mean people had cameras she's in the mall beating up all those bad
guys and everything and she tells she turns to the little girl and goes like keep this a secret you'd
ever saw me it's like they're fucking video cameras recording you right now that you that she
you know what's it called she she for Christy she breaks them yeah but then the article pointed out
yeah but those cameras record footage they would have footage of her like you can't just run around in
this outfit with a golden lasso right and have nobody like it's like the most minimal reporting on it
or you know or sightings of one it's ridiculous so that's one thing they did this thing with it
to where she goes back to her normal life and I mean she's not even put on a pair of fucking glasses
right to you know what I mean it's like you you're spotable yes no it's like it's a movie of
plot holes it's like it's like why you're mentioning this stuff I'm like yeah true true but I'm also
thinking like let's just but the the whole story at large is plot hole like there you could probably
point to a million of these things that just don't add up but it felt like people didn't care
about this four hundred million dollar giant thing which is always crazy to me but it felt like
they didn't care to land it they did the two villain thing which can work in a Batman returns
it can work in a dark night even though they almost lost control of that movie I would argue I
think they landed the plane for sure but they they try to do maybe a little too much but the two villain
thing is a lot it's a lot to handle and this movie isn't up to the task I mean you look at Batman
returns you have two great actors playing two great villains this movie has Kristen Wigg who I love
and I never understand her in like a big budget thing she does very small character based comedy
and she is I would say one of the best in the world at it so to bring that to this just doesn't work
she's doing her awkward comedy at first the villain side of her is never scary at all at one point
she's walking down a street and 20 men in a row say she's hot to her until she kills one and then
that's supposed to be her moment of going too far she's killing a guy who sexually assaults her like
were we rooting for it's very confusing and look I'm sorry I'm not doing I'm not saying this because
I'm I would never judge an actor by their looks I'm not here to do that I have no interest in doing
that but if you're going to make a plot point in a movie about a nerdy woman becoming hot where
you're going to have literally like you just said every man that passes her in the movie because
this is what happens she makes a wish to be great or whatever and she suddenly is like an attractive
woman and like and that's and that's a plot point and every man she passes is like oh my god you're the
hottest woman I've ever seen and you're like guys she's a pretty lady it's Kristen Wigg for Christ's
we're not talking about fucking uh what's her name uh uh margo roby it's like this is absurd
I'm talking about margo martin dale I I do find Kristen Wigg very attractive I think she's attractive
but I mean come on dude it's like no I I thought that that was uh I I took it as she had some sort of
spice power over them or something maybe that's what the movie was just inventing things left
and right so I was like oh okay I guess now she she's got like poison ivy I think had that too
maybe that's what it is but man I texted you and I meant this I go this is like what to me like
watching a movie where martin short is walking around and women are falling to their knees I'm like
he's not that with a bad -looking guy but I mean for Christ's guys that would have to be the plot of
the movie is why that's happening it would have to be like a mark what like martin short had you know
ate a pie that made him irresistible or something um but I mean but so so maybe you're right maybe it's
because she's you know I'm not gonna nitpick over it she's a very attractive woman but I'm just like
guys can this is just come on guys like stop my issue with it really is that that is a character
that has just failed again and again the like nerdy scientist type who becomes that like they did it
with Jamie Foxx and the in the worst of all of the superhero movies amazing spider -man 2
and it's basically the same character so like everybody hates that movie everybody hated that
character why are you doing it again also I think they are actually doing it again bringing Jamie Foxx
back to play that character he's back in the third spider -man movie I give up you know like that
that was the worst character I've ever seen in one of these things so I hated that yeah and he
mean it's it's it's also to go into Pascal now because I'm gonna wait let me I want to say a
couple more wig things to say all right great actor uh she plays the nerdy thing very well she even
plays the sinister part very well yeah the part that she then why she shouldn't have been cast in this
fucking thing is because every time she's gonna do a crazy action stunt it's blatantly obvious that
they create a CGI body of her right to do the thing it's like guys like she put somebody in the tick
to check off all the boxes that's all I'm saying you know and listen I wouldn't be going as hard
as on this as I am if it wasn't for this latest thing with Gal Gadot and Patty Jenkins where she's
now playing Cleopatra and she's getting shit for whitewashing right okay and neither of them are
copied to what the fuck they're really doing which is she wants to play Cleopatra and it's that
plan and simple now she's making excuses that they tried to find an actor of the ethnicity to play or
and they couldn't find her and this now such bullshit yeah you know and and everybody's so fucking proud
of themselves with this movie and the statement they made and what they did and this and that and it's
like you know what if you guys didn't fucking tree stump so hard and virtue signal so hard around this
movie I wouldn't even make some of these fucking criticisms but you're going to put it out there like
you've created this piece of work that we all need to admire I'm sorry I'm much more prone now to
call bullshit on half of it I don't you know I don't know what you're doing with this I took nothing
from that I mean that the those aspects I a million percent took from Black Panther I I got what
was inspiring about it absolutely this I didn't even find it to be empowering to women in any way
I don't know what what was it say would be the scene that made it feel that way it wasn't you have
a woman who so desperately needs a man that she brings his soul back to possess another man's body
without any regard for the other man and let's be honest rapes that man let's be honest yeah
and what if what if Gal Gadot had chlamydia this man wakes up he's like how did I get chlamydia what the
fuck yeah yeah it was crazy um another question I saw floated a lot online and I have to bring up
because I agreed with it as well why did she need to bring him back in a host body it's a wishing
stone wish him back in his own body that you love so much she didn't it's it's stupid it made no
sense patty Jenkins dumb fucking motive to humanize the villains these villains aren't like
what do you like fine it is interesting to show the christian wig is sort of a downtrodden human being
and that she wants to be powerful and it corrupts her that is interesting
to have in Pedro Pascal who in the comic books is like a Lex Luthor type
turning to like a mushy I love my son father by the end of this thing it's like what the
and by the way I'm sorry I'm gonna say it and I'll get shit for it you're gonna have a Hispanic
guy is the dad and then just an Asian kid is the son maybe it just make one comment about about
the mom or something help me understand this you're you're fine to say it though that we both
said it when we watched it over here and Walter Shaw who is one of my favorite film critics at film
freak central an Asian man himself brought up this why why is his son Asian you know I don't think
that's a bad thing to bring up at all and I'm I'm sure at some point they were like let's just not
comment on it that'll be cool but like throw me a bone help me in a movie where nothing makes sense
he can have a Hispanic son or he can have an Asian wife or it's something
yeah it's it's it's man this this movie sucked Chris Pine who did you know was decent enough in
the movie you know he's just doing the charismatic hero guy thing but like he's hitting the sauce
or something man he looks worn choked I that's something I might not have said but boy does he
he looks and I know in the movie I mean he's like 800 years old or something but I mean he doesn't
have to look at folks he I met him he his father played a love interest of Vicky Lawrence on the
finale of cool kids and he came to the taping he was there the whole time he asked for no special
treatment he could not have been a nicer human being and his dad was great too but um yeah he
he looked he looked pretty rugged especially for like the star of one of these things Gal Gadot is
beautiful gorgeous he is not an actress and for some reason I did not notice that in the first
movie and I really noticed it here I mean she she can't pull off basic stuff well she can't even
drop the Israeli accent right right oh no it's the the full accent yes she you know and then
and that's the thing it's like you know that's what bothered me so much about that Cleopatra thing
the woman they make everyone in her home planet do Gal Gadot's accent yeah I don't think she's
trying to do an English accent I think they're like okay she's not she's such a bad actor they had to
make everybody else in the Amazonian world right right there's rarely accent yes so but here's the
thing that's what pissed me off so much about the but not to say wonder woman can't be Israeli she can
be I don't give a shit all right my point is is not well I promise you we're gonna get a Cleopatra
with this is a really accent that's gonna be a little odd uh that's not my point my my my point is
not that Wonder Woman champion Israeli my point is is that is not a choice on behalf of the actor right
you got people getting mad that uh that uh uh you know the characters in soul spoke in a certain
affectation or whatever you know so my point is she's just not a good enough actor to not do the
voice but the bigger issue I have is she the thing that pissed me off so much about that Cleopatra
comment is hey lady nobody knew who the fuck you were when you got to play Wonder Woman yeah and it
made you and you can't now pass the buck you can't now do that for somebody else because you're so
up your own ass with your imagined video and all your bullshit that you you've got to now take that
role too and and and somehow justify whitewashing it's I really really lost a lot of respect for
her and patty Jenkins when I read that stuff about Cleopatra and I really think that this movie sucks because
of their hubris and why the fuck is patty Jenkins directing blockbuster action movie the only other
movie she made was monster go make another drama go make a gritty character drama you're great at
that why are you why are you why is she being assigned to something like this and and they do this all
the time they assign these people that make these indies to these big blockbuster thing and they suck
go find the next spielberg go find the next who's the lady that directed on uh uh zero dark 30
Catherine Bigelow yeah get get get a Catherine Bigelow on this or something you know what I mean
well that's the reason they pluck up they get these indie filmmakers like I always talk about the
guy who did cop car which I loved and then his next movie was Spider -Man and you're like oh so there's
a career we'll just never see we'll never see what his career would have been um patty Jenkins is the same
way monsters this crazy dark really interesting beautifully acted and directed movie and then her
next project 10 years later is Wonder Woman like it doesn't make sense I have heard that Marvel
likes to control every aspect of production and I get it with budgets like this so they're not doing
the Tim Burton thing of saying here's the money have fun they're micromanaging every single aspect of it
and for that you can't bring in a big filmmaker you have to bring in somebody who will sort of just
take it I think the issue is that now when you go on to part two patty Jenkins is not going to
do it anymore that's the only reason I liked Wonder Woman 2 at all and I really didn't much
is that it didn't feel like it was part of the big machine of all these movies that are identical
to each other until the end then it did but I'm not saying any choice they made was good or that
it worked I'm just saying I like that it didn't feel like every single one of these movies be they DC
or Marvel but when I heard Wonder Woman 84 I was like at least we're going to have some 80s bangers
on the soundtrack there wasn't one there was nothing about 1984 that was explored that added
to the plot it was just a hook of get it because the Wonder Woman TV show took place in the 80s
literally all it was so then they could have that fun little button at the end with
uh for Christ sakes the lady that played Wonder Woman I've never seen the show I don't you know
Linda Carter Linda Carter and it's like it's like but nothing about the 80s played a role in this
there was no like oh the Cold War is part of this or nuclear weapons are are talked about well
no that's not true nuclear war is was a thing that they really shoehorned in at the very end of
this fucking thing read Walter Charles review again if you want to see a really interesting take on
the Middle East stuff that is kind of awkwardly shoehorned into the middle of this movie and he
he really pissed him off in a way that I'm probably not smart enough to get while watching it but um
yeah especially with her being Israeli I think a lot of people had major issues with the politics of
this movie which didn't even enter my field of vision really you know and then just put just every
little thing they did I was just like why are you making this worse than the comic Cheetah is like
Wonder Woman's main adversary why are you reducing her to a 10 minute fucking sequence at the end
of the film where by the way they've got Kristen wig and what looks like Halloween adventure makeup
they just painted lines on her face yeah it's like it's like there's no makeup job no effort went into it
to make her look cool or anything like that they had the feeling like you would think it was rushed
out but it has actually been sitting on a shelf for a year I think there's a reason for that I think
they knew it was a mess I think they probably went back into tons of reshoots I think they re -edited the
thing 800 times um then then you know uh you know I already complained about the changes they made to
the wishing stone the invisible jet thing guys you're calling it Wonder Woman 84 go for the fucking
gusto and make it kitschy and fun and have her have the invisible jet don't do this bullshit thing
where Wonder Woman can suddenly make things turn invisible if she tries really hard what the fuck was
that and another great plot point that that article pointed out was they're flying through fireworks
and she goes oh yeah it's the 4th of July like so first of all just the laziest writing on earth oh
yeah it's the 4th of July they go take notice in the scene before that there are people in fur coats
yeah I mean this thing is a fucking disaster man that that's really like when I was just going to
like give a brief synopsis the plot when this started it's like it like made my brain hurt to just
even have to think about like to even summarize this movie it requires a lot of talk it requires
like a kid at Easter being like and then I did and then I did this and then I did that's what it
feels like a kid rattling off what they might like to see and then you actually see it and you're like
boy this sucks the the 80s vibe to me I feel like they had no fun with it the guy I asked Joe is this
president supposed to be Reagan I haven't gotten that question answered online I don't think it is
look or talk like Reagan so I guess he's just a generic president um Pedro Pascal I
I don't for something about the guy doesn't work for me I don't know what it is but the
this character they'll they'll spend big chunks of time with Pedro Pascal big chunks of time with
wig uh Wonder Woman is off screen for a lot of the movie she's also not in her outfit for a lot of the
movie just Wonder Woman and the thing for like 12 minutes or something yeah that's you want a half hour
movie the focus of this thing is Pedro Pascal and his child is his child and like we're really
supposed to care about that but he's also supposed to be a trump figure so you can't really care about him
some I don't know what it is about Pedro Pascal but he does he didn't have the chemistry or something
that a villain this role like this calls for I definitely preferred week to him in this but um
yeah it ends and you feel completely empty and and alone in the world which is uh where we're at you
know it's it's just the the ending of this when she is talking it just that monologue about world
peace or whatever the what was she talking about at the end what was the end Joe I don't I don't
even help me out he tried for five minutes to make sense of it and then we were like fucking hey
Pedro Pascal becomes the dream stone they never quite understand explain how or why that's possible
then he's also has the ability to take whatever he wants from you in exchange for a wish yes they
never explain that part of it or what sense that makes it's absurdly written that every time he wants
to grant a wish he has to hold your hand and you and he says to the person you wish for that and
yes I do I wish for that it's fucking ridiculous and then at the end I don't even get it he's like on
TV and because he's technically touching people because it's a signal going out to them he's able to
grant wishes over the television yes but then she comes in and talks to the people to reject their wishes
as if you could have any understanding of what the fuck was going on if you're watching
Trump on a press conference on TV and suddenly you just go out loud your living room I'd like some
gold and then you have gold and then a woman in a red white and blue underwear suit comes on and tells
you to renounce it's nuts it's nuts it really is and it's so over complicated it could have just been
we there's this thing called the dream stone it's called the dream stone the comics there's a thing
called the dream stone it has the power to make your dreams a new reality if it falls into the wrong
hands we're in trouble and it's based in the mythology of the Greek gods and all that stuff which
would tie into the overall thing with Justice League movie and Steppenwolf and all that bullshit
it was such a simple thing to do and instead they just you know it's this stupid Hollywood bigger
is better horse shit and it's never worked it's never worked you know look I enjoyed Batman Returns
for the first time in my life this Christmas it will never be more to me though than just a fun
goofy Christmas movie to watch I'm never going to watch it and go what a great comic book movie this was
it's too much it's too much the formula that works works Batman and the Joker Superman and Lex
Luther one person versus the other guy the guy's got a diabolical plot the superhero needs to stop it
and then when you get to the team up movie it's a world threat and they somehow save the world that's
all you got to fucking do that's it and they make these things so convoluted and stupid and complicated
and I just don't even understand man and the notes from these executives half the time as you know pet
and as I know they're telling you to dumb shit down yeah this is going to go over people's heads
too complicated dumb this down dumb this down dumb this down how I had to put a previously on on every
episode of a multi cam sitcom yeah so exactly so how a movie of this budget in this caliber
becomes this complicated and confusing and it's not a movie by Steven Spielberg or George Lucas
or or or even like Jody Foster or somebody who is incredibly established in the directing field
you know what I mean who has done yeah it's fucking patty Jenkins who directed one movie and then
10 years later got to direct this superhero movie by who know even knows why I don't know
you know what I mean you'd think hey she hasn't done anything in 10 years maybe we fucking find
somebody newer who's working but you know whatever I'm not trying to shit on her but my point is it's
like this this entire thing wreaked of hubris to me it wreaked of gal Gadot's arrogance which she
leaks out more and more and more over the internet each each every few months and it to me made patty
Jenkins look fucking dumb when I started reading her commentary on the movie and it was like you know
like I said oh I insisted it be like this it's like well you you were wrong and you know what you
don't have much of a director's eye if you didn't look at that shot of Gal Gadot flying through
the air and go that looks ridiculous right it looked ridiculous at times like it was like what yeah
doing here like oh it was god it was bad it was really bad it was really bad there there's no
other way to put it and in classic Hollywood fashion they fast tracked Wonder Woman 3 with Jenkins and
Gadot and and that's where they basically everyone on the internet for for the last week everyone
has said how much they hate this film and hate the choices that were made and hate every aspect of it
and they respond by fast tracking another one with the exact same team so there you go
that that's where we are at in in film basically that's what's going on right now
so it's sad I think you know in terms of the HBO Max thing I do sometimes wonder be like you
were saying Joe because since all these movies are bad how often it is a case of them just not
wanting to release them theatrically anyway and kind of using the pandemic to get this shitty stuff out
but then again people go see this stuff no matter what and regardless of quality so I don't think anyone
cares both the audience and the executives I think the audience says we'll scoop up whatever
shit you feed us and the executives say they'll scoop up whatever shit we feed them and that is
where we're at and that's how you wind up with Wonder Woman 2 84 you hogged down for WWE 4 and this
is one movie critic that will not be waiting for Godot you do that now or you have that sitting for a
while I just saw it right now and I got excited it's good sort of a jean shallot kind of
I like it yeah thank you folks that's the show thanks for tuning in thank you for a great year we
appreciate your support so much we really do we appreciate everything you contribute to us
with your with your meaning your energy and whatever whether you're on the patreon you're not on
the patreon whatever we love you guys thank you for sticking with us thank you thank you thank you
agreed there would not be a show without you guys we would just not be doing it without this
patreon and and we we have been blown away by how much you guys keep on listening loving supporting the
show and it's not bullshit yeah thank you to Emily for all your help some thank you share their
gratitude a little more nicely than others but I think Emily does a great job I'll be at a one
blu -ray job not just some blu -ray sect job yes happy new year just let's all hope that it is better
than 2020 thank you all for everything we will see you next time and we will see you in hell