I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the sound of your screams
becomes a thing on my dreams,
you know what I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Johnston, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson
Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson, Henry Johnson
What did you really do in a theater? I mean, you're not going to rip the screen, or they're ripping the seats? I don't understand what you could do. Just throwing shit everywhere against the walls, like stuff like that, you know? Yeah. Um, anyway, so this is from our favorite website movie web, uh, and it came out in April, so that it is kind of old news, but, but still, uh, a Minecraft movie will promote chicken jockey chaos will promote
chicken jockey chaos in new block party screenings. So I'm going to just read a bit from the article here. Um, a Minecraft movie fans are getting the rare opportunity to go against the rules, although it has already been a trend worldwide since the film was released. Warner Brothers is making it official encouraging it for their block party edition screenings for people to go crazy and whatever and outburst and blah, blah, blah during the chicken jockey scene. What's the other one allow that?
Well, I'm reading it. According to the Hollywood reporter, the historical entertainment studio wants to go over to revisit their love of the film on May 2nd. So this has already happened. This time you can sing along and even recite the lines. Minecraft movies heading into its set for Christ's get to the fucking point. Here's the quote from the studio. Warner Brothers pictures and legendary pictures invite fans back to the theater to experience a Minecraft movie together the whole new way. You know the moments, you know the lines. You love the songs. Now it's time to get loose, laugh out loud.
And belt out those lyrics. Whatever. Here's my point. Okay, the block party edition allows fans to be messy without causing trouble for the movie theaters as some did before when the film was first released.
I don't know. I guess, you know, I don't know if without causing trouble means they're going to arrange the theater in a way where it's covered in plastic.
Or if they're saying go crazy within boundaries and that's what they mean by not causing trouble, but my whole thing is this why the fuck is the studio embracing. I mean, this is where we're at anything that gets a reaction.
Anything that gets people up and out of their seat, it doesn't matter the value of it at its core. It doesn't matter the decency of it. All that matters is it gets eyeballs on it. Yeah.
So why is Warner Brothers embracing this thing that has caused problems? It's like saying it's like saying, you know, there have been fist fights. You know, this movie came out and every time the boxing scene comes on, fist fights started breaking out.
Well, now Warner Brothers is going to tell you go and embrace that part without getting in too much trouble and just, you know, try to keep it in bounds or or we'll create a safe space where you can have safe fist fights. Why are you embracing it at all?
It's disgusting behavior. It's poison the hood. You know, there was there was gang violence at theaters. It's like we're doing where your colors to a special screening of a voice in the hood. It's insane.
It's really gross to me, man. It's really, really gross that there's any condoning from a studio of this thing. And it's really sad to me.
It's encouraging kids to vandalize a public space. It's very odd and like I, we're no prudes here. I don't think this is like age. That's, that seems really nuts to me.
Yeah, that's crazy.
But here's the thing. Even if they're not encouraging the vandalism of a public space, it's embracing behavior that led to vandalism.
And even if you're putting that behavior in a safe, undistructible space, it doesn't matter. You're still embracing that behavior.
Whenever there should be coming on going, guys, we love that you love the movie. Stop being assholes.
Yeah. That's not cool.
Right. You know what I mean?
You and McGregor when there was when there was racial backlash with with Star Wars casting, he didn't come out and make a statement of, you know,
that that's, that's no good. But we're going to create a safe space for you to explore your racial hatred at a special screening of Obi-Wan. No, he came out and he goes, this breaks my heart.
I don't want this to be a part of this. This is supposed to be a beautiful thing.
I just, it's so sad to me, man, that this is where we're at. Like it's the anything that is exploitable, anything that is, again, that makes enough noise, that gets attention.
That is the value of it. And it does not matter if there is any value beyond that. It's very sad to me.
I'm with you. And now the sequel, you know, they're definitely going to say, well, we need to have two scenes where the kids can run around.
And what this is leading to also is people going, we need to make more movies where people have to stand up and run around.
That's how dumb and short-sighted they are. Oh, this is causing a phenomenon. I think that's why Minecraft was a hit.
Because kids were like, what? So we need to come up with more interactive movies, which nobody wants. Nobody wants.
I was told by a friend the weekend after sinners that an executive was like, maybe we should make more original stories.
Yeah, you mentioned that. I mean, they're, they're children.
Children, I had a, I had a pitch at HBO today and they asked such intelligent, fantastic questions about my project. And I was like, guys, can I tell you what a pleasure this was and how rare this is.
There's a reason that HBO makes great shit.
What we're going to some places, they're so bad at everything. Like the questions they ask, you're like, oh, you don't get this at all.
So you're not going to buy it. So I'll leave. What were some of the, like, bring us behind, bring us into the boardroom at HBO. Like what, what kind of stuff are they asking? I'm curious.
I've written my first hour long.
And it's a, it's a spec, which means I, I'm not pitching the idea in hopes that you pay me to write it. I wrote it because I've never written an hour long drama.
And nobody would just trust me to do it without proof. So I wrote it.
Mr. Judd Apital produced it. We send it there. They read the script and then they come in. I talked to them about my plans for the season if they want to pick it up.
But they had so many probing questions. It's a family drama comedy. And there's so many characters. And they would be like, I noticed the relationship between this, you know, this brother and this sister.
I mean, I can't even read it. So it's not going to help. But they just, they knew the right questions to ask in series. Do you see this relationship becoming problematic? Do you see it becoming sexual?
Do you see, you know, like, the questions usually that these places ask are like, so, I mean, how do we get more eyes on it?
Like, how do we, you know, like they're about the business and they're never about the story, whereas HBO was like, let's talk about these characters. And that's obviously always going to lead to a better show.
Why would she well with it? I hope it goes forward.
Thanks, Joe. I would like nothing more, but we will see. It's a very difficult time.
I have a friend who is dating or friends with, I'm not sure, something with David Chase's daughter, the creator of the sopranos. And he said he went out to dinner with David Chase the other night.
And he spent the entire night complaining that he can't get anything made. And that made me feel really good because he made it. And I know your opinion. But he made it.
I mean, he should be able to get something made. Yeah. And most people's estimation. He made the greatest and most commercially successful television show in cable history.
And he's like, I go out and pitch and nobody's buying. I get eight knows. So when I get a no, it's, you know, it was actually a shock for me. I used to just kind of sell stuff. And I'd be like, I'm on fire. But you definitely feel it now.
And it's a huge hesitance to buy anything. And it doesn't really matter who you have attached. I've heard of projects with Robert De Niro attached that got passed on.
Merrill Street attached that got passed on. And when you get passed on, that means eight different places are like, we've weighed the pros and cons. And no, we're not moving forward with us.
So it's a rough time. I prefer to be somewhat optimistic about both the country and the film industry and say these things going cycles. There's always low points and high points. And it'll get better.
But generally, most people seem to think on both fronts that we're pretty irreparably fucked. So we'll see.
That's a, that's a shame. And there's a great clip of, I guess it's when, who's the guy that directed the law city of Z and Margo at the wedding or whatever that and half the way thing was called.
Those are two different directors. Okay. And so Margo at the wedding is in a cold kidman movie directed by Noah Bombak.
That's, that's not who it is. I'm talking about, Rachel getting married with Anne Hathaway was directed by Jonathan Demi. No, I'm talking about James Gray. James Gray did the yards and we own the night and any movies. Yeah. And Armageddon time was the half the way he did. And at Astro, it's boring. Boring as fuck.
But yeah, there's a clip of him. There are some festival and it's, it's for Armageddon time because Anne Hathaway sitting next to him. But you know, they're like, what do you think the state of filmmaking is? And he's like, we're in a lot of trouble.
We're in a lot of trouble. And he starts talking about franchises. Yeah. And he goes franchise used to mean McDonald's Burger King. They're talking about it with movies. What the hell is going on?
Like they all really say content. When I hear somebody say content, I'm like, well, we're not going to get along. What's what does that mean? I've never heard that. I mean, I know what the word, it means everything. Film.
A TV show, something on your phone. It's all content, which to me is just like, let's lump everything together into some big amorphous blob of shit. Just treat art like it's.
Content, I mean, content means like something to fill time. Right. And the places that make these giant creative decisions all refer to films, television, everything as content. And it's very irritating.
When I hear the worst one I ever heard, yeah, I had a friend who worked at true TV when true TV was still a thing. Yeah. And it was right before the collapse. Everyone that collapsed happened where true TV and comedy central just fired everybody. It was like these blood bath firings. Yeah.
It was right before that happened. And she said, I had a game show I wanted to pitch. And she said, I like the idea, but I don't think you should bring it to us because I don't think it'll go anywhere. And I said, well, why true TV seems like the perfect place. And she said, because one of the directives we were given this week was we want TV shows that people can watch without the sound on.
Without the sound is insane. I mean, I'm there's two two friends that pitched a Netflix recently, the one I told you about where he got notes in clearly written by AI clearly because he typed in.
You know, like the questions and he saw exactly what the notes were. It was just the first response from AI. The other one I've heard that Netflix tells everybody if you're going to make a show with them is that whenever possible.
A scene should start by your characters saying where they are and what they are doing.
They're like, you know, people come in and out they go to the bathroom. They're on their phone and you know, oftentimes they look up 15 minutes into the show and they have no idea where they are and what's going on. So just always remind them instead of saying, why don't we make more compelling entertainment so that people can't look away.
You know, but you think a lot of its phones to you know, the phones have destroyed us.
And I mean, but there's the thing that there there was a benefit to it. There was a logic to it. You know, when when Seinfeld did comedians and cars and somebody said, would you ever do a sitcom again and he goes, why would I he goes, I have a show that you can watch in your pocket.
He's again, you can watch my show anywhere at any time. Why would I want to make something where you're forced to watch it in one specific place. And that made sense.
And there is sense to that, but it doesn't where it loses the thread is when it becomes that is the only way to think. Yeah.
Yeah. There's room for Marvel, but when Marvel becomes the only thing. It's, it's just so disheartening man. Jesus Christ. Remember, remember back when, remember, when more, I mean, when Marvel was so big and so the only focus of anything that people had to apologize publicly for criticizing Marvel. I do.
And now everybody's like, it's kind of gross. Like how big it's gotten. It's like, oh, oh, did it finally get too big for you? Yeah. Now it's too big for you. It's so nuts, man.
It's bad. You know that they're focused on the wrong things. When today they announced that Max is going back to HBO Max.
And then they put up somebody had on on Instagram was really funny. A line of like 10 blocks of all the different app design. Like you know, like when you're looking at Apple TV or whatever when you click on that app and it opens up.
They went through them since the inception of Max and it was like max HBO HBO Mac they all one was purple. Then the next was dark purple. The next was light purple. And it's just their focus testing. Zazlaw is like, why aren't we doing well? Why aren't people watching our shows?
And someone decides that the fix for that is that we need to change the name of the network again. Max HBO, but whatever you're doing it all that matters is do you have good shit on your platform?
Most of these platforms do not. I can I still don't understand what possessed them. I remember when you texted me and said, H.B. HBO Max is changing its name to just Max.
They're getting rid of the part that anybody cares about. Sit him back. It was called you. You spent 30 years. 30 years establishing a brand that says quality.
It's actually talking about this with Judd this morning and he was like, you know what it is. I think that they think when because now that they're going for a broader audience than HBO used to, they think that the HBO indicates to America.
Snobby, high brow and then very funny. Judd goes, juice, which maybe lap. But I think there's some truth to that. I think like the middle of the country who is now so against anything elitist sees HBO as that, which is kind of crazy for the network that puts out righteous gemstones or whatever.
But yeah, it's a it's a it's a time. It's a time. They're all focused on the exact wrong shit.
And you at home that can't see us pat his sharpening a knife as he is saying all this and it's disturbing and he's sharpening it on a leather strap, which is just more disturbing than if it was just one of those stones.
Now I agree. Sparks are coming off of it as well. Going on the ground. It's a wild time. I got a I got a buddy at Hulu, who's like we do. Well, the one in comedy they're doing four, four comedies a year. So one every three months, which means pilot, which means doesn't make it to air. So maybe one or two comedies a year at a Lulu.
And then my buddy there was like the but but but but Pat there. They're hilarious. I don't understand how you can only they are hilarious. And it is Hulu. We ain't coming up. I know, but they do have a couple good standup specials on there. I like I said I've said on here numerous times. I like the new gaff again. And I like the new Roy Wood Jr. on there.
But Hulu is yeah, he was just like we are all about IP and that's all you here now.
Everywhere it's not like one of the streamers says IP. He was like will only do IP. So I said, so somebody comes in who you really respect and they have an amazing pitch.
You don't buy it and he goes not unless there's IP right now. That's our M O meaning you got to have a book or an article or something meaning the person bringing in the pitch has to buy that.
So it's like you have to buy the rights to something in order to do that. It's like guys, this is supposed to be about a young fresh faced kid walking in telling you a story and you going, I'd love to see that on the screen.
Make him one of those giant novelty checks. And it's just it's not that anymore. No, no. It's become ever more a corporation by the passing day.
David Spade and Theo Vaughn are shooting a movie right now. Yeah, they're right. Yeah. But dude, I think they're doing it.
Indy like excellent, which is excellent. But did you ever I might have actually said this on here. Did you actually did you ever see the day where David Spade couldn't get a fucking dumb comedy made.
Well, I mean, maybe he could maybe he could and said, I'm not playing this game. We can do better, you know, because they both have podcasts that are making them a lot more money than being actors ever did is my guess.
So they're probably like, well, let's find a real, you know, DIY way to do this. I respect it. There is also a chance that everybody passed on a two who knows I hope that that's how they made it. And it's not a thing of.
I guess we got to do it ourselves if we're going to do it. You know, I don't know. But I got a movie. I'm really excited about a big comedy that's about to go out super wide.
And we were talking about who to play the lead and these conversations are what really breaks your fucking heart. There's a real juicy fat comedic role for a loudmouth actor over 55 basically.
And we had this big list of like every great older actor in Hollywood, you know, Bill Murray and we're going down to the list of the people.
But I'm talking to like a top producer who's on the movie and we're going through who means something and who doesn't at all the streamers.
So there's people like sometimes Netflix will be like, we'll make anything with. I'll just pick somebody at random will forte. But then you go to Hulu and they're like, we would never make something with will for today.
So they have different people sometimes. There's somebody like Tom Hanks who means something no matter what. But then there are people who don't mean anything anywhere and you would not believe some of these actors like he just went down the line.
It's like because I go GM out of you like because there's some screaming in it and who screams better than GM out of he's like he doesn't get the movie made not at all.
It's like, okay.
Who are the other ones? Brian Krantsten. He's like obviously fantastic. He doesn't get the movie made.
What? Kurt Russell. Kurt Russell maybe. But I think they might say like we can't just put his face on a poster.
Like so it's like with that actor you'd need to really cast up the other parts stuff like that. Like he's not going to be enough. And that list was everybody in Hollywood basically you know like there's very few people that mean something to everyone.
It's sad. Whatty Harrelson. He was like he's marginal. He means something here and here. He doesn't mean anything here and here.
This is the point they wanted to mean everything everywhere. They can't they can never make enough money. It's they have to make all the money.
It's disgusting. It is disgusting. Yeah. And look well. They're trying to target everybody like you know Marvel does that to great success.
Super hero movies do that to great success. Everything can't be that. I mean the promise of streaming was that it was going to be more niche.
And we could all find our special thing that we want to watch and watch what we like and it's just not that it's exactly what you're saying. It's we need every eye on this. And that's never going to happen.
I was talking to somebody about. And this really is the truth. I was talking about somebody about my special getting passed on by Netflix and Hulu. But particularly Netflix.
And I forget what comic it was. It might have been boss. I don't remember. But they were like just put it on there. Guys. Just put it on the thing. There's a million. What is it hurting you to just put it on the thing? Yeah.
You're saying you don't want it to the point you think it's going to detract. Yeah. From the bottomless pool of content you have on this thing like just put it on the thing. I don't understand. And this is the point. It's what we're talking about.
They can't just put it on the thing. Why? Because everything on the thing. Even if it's acquired must make us money at all times. And if it does not, it needs to go. It's it's wild.
It's man. It is it is truly truly wild. But it put more importantly. It's unsustainable. This is by the way, dude. I'm not a Trump fan. And I don't quite understand the tariffs thing. Some of the censorship stuff that's getting talked about is very frightening to me. Yeah.
This thing where he's like, I'm going to tariff. I'm going to put a hundred percent tax on movies made overseas. And it's like and everybody's going, he's coming after the movie industry. It's like, guys, I'm supposed to feel sorry for mission impossible.
Nine because it's going to get tax because they shoot it overseas and then it makes a sh- 38 billion dollars or whatever it's going to make worldwide. It's like, I'm sorry guys. I just don't have a lot of sympathy there.
If you're talking about it's going to make it harder for independent and smaller filmmakers to get their films made.
Or it's going to be harder for people who make foreign films to get an American audience. Then that's a different story. I want to listen to that.
But the bulk of my understanding of this is, and I might be a hundred percent wrong. Please, if I'm wrong, I'm wrong. I'm not sitting here saying I'm right.
My understanding is, it's going to tax these movies that are getting away with bloody fucking murder, making money hand over fist. Yeah. And I'm sorry. I just, I don't feel that sorry for them. I don't, you know, I don't know. But, but I might be wrong. Maybe I'm in for a pretty getting correctly.
No, I mean, you and I were talking about these tariffs a little bit this week. And I just kind of sent the article and then we tried to figure it out for a minute and kind of got lost. But in reading comments and reading a few articles about it, nobody seems clear on it.
People in the government don't seem clear on it. A lot of this is just stuff he says. And people don't know if it's going to actually happen or not even. But the tariffs currently are seemingly on a collision course to destroy America.
And I don't know enough about it. But I can't imagine people are like, just you wait. You know, maybe it is. Hey, maybe it is 40 chess and by the end of the year, the economy's booming, but doesn't seem like it. It just seems dumb.
We should see. Here's. Yeah. I'm sorry. No, no, no, go.
No, I have a scary stuff. But this is a positive amidst all we're talking about is we're saying there's the death of all independent art and all that stuff.
I went to here in Austin. I went to a store. I want to shout out Austin books and come. Yeah, Austin books and comics. Yeah.
It is a massive comic book store, which that is not easy to find these days. Comic book stores in general are not as prevalent as they used to be as all bookstores are not.
And comic book stores in particular because iPads and iPhones and whatever made reading comic books. A lot more convenient because you could download it and and keep it digitally and save space and whatever.
But there are people out there that still want the tangible thing. I am one of them.
I'm not an avid comic book reader, but I do enjoy reading them.
So first of all, just off the bat, the store existing and existing at the breath that does exist. It's a gigantic store.
It was amazing. It was it I walked into this place. An amazing staff.
There were probably six people theoretically working there at the time. Three of them at different times offered out of their way to help me.
Like just being courteous like the staff was amazing. The staff was the only thing I missed here was the key ingredient. What is the story around.
Austin comics and books. Okay. So not a place I can attend.
So the staff was so helpful and thorough and wonderful and they knowledgeable. They were all fans of comics. So I was like, do you have this? And if they didn't have it, they were like, well, you know, if you don't like that, if we don't have that, you might like this.
And let me tell you about it and whatever and come to this part of the store, whatever.
They had new issues of things. They had back issues of things. They had classic vintage, like, you know, super collectible old issues of things.
They had an amazing graphic novel section. They had comic book art for your wall. It was a fucking amazing store.
So if you're ever in Austin, go to Austin books and comics.
But the scary stuff that came out of this. And although I was not super excited about the new product.
I'm excited about the idea of this. EC comics, who put out tells from the crypt in the 50s, the vault of horror, shock, suspense stories, crime suspense stories, weird science, weird fantasy.
And then later when the comic code came out and those comics got banned, they created Mad Magazine.
William Gaines is the sort of, you know, there were a few guys over there. William Gaines is the sort of poster child, Jerry Garcia.
Yeah, you know, kind of main guy out of it, whatever. Anyway, EC comics is printing new comics again. Now they've been reprinting the stuff from the 50s for years.
They're bringing degrees of acceptance. Some of the reprints have been a little maligned because of the color, new colorization and stuff.
Some have been praised because of the recreation of the classic colorization or the black and white versions of the reprints or whatever.
But they started printing new stuff. They have two new titles, maybe even three at this point, but one is called epitaphs from the Abyss, which is a horror comic.
And there's a science fiction one called Cruel Universe. They are anthology comics, just like the old ones. Now of course the art style looks different and all that stuff.
But the fact of the matter is, One Press, which, you know, as far as I know, is not a massive, well, they're distributed by Simon and Schuster.
But One Press, it's a graphic novel and comic book publisher out of Portland, Oregon, best known for publishing Scott Pilgrim and Rick and Morty.
But it seems to me that One was, you know, a sort of indie player that published some bigger things that went mainstream and now have kind of come into their own.
But they have helped revive EC Comics as a label. The Gaines family is licensing the titles, which is really cool.
And they're doing new reprints of the old stuff too. So I actually grabbed, which I thought was very cool for 20 bucks, an issue or a book.
They have the soft cover collections of the old titles. And I got crime suspense stories. And it's like six or eight issues of the first eight, whatever in the initial run.
Reprinted in one book, 20 bucks, soft cover, nice big book, great art reprinting, easy to hold, read. It's an enjoyable read. It's nice and big. Like, it was just really, really cool to see.
And it was something I didn't know that I would ever see again, which was EC putting out new stuff.
And the fact that the Gaines family is involved is very cool to me. And it seems like everybody's heart is in the right place. So, hey, man, there's hope amidst all this shit we talk about. It's easy to kind of get caught up in the idea that all of it is this just industrial processing of art.
But there is hope there is hope and there are ways to get stuff that that isn't that that isn't the manufactured, whatever you call it. And that that makes me quite happy to see.
Yeah.
Great. Could this mean more creep show.
Creep show is not EC party me creep show.
Okay, so creep show was was never a comic.
Creep show was just the movie and then they made the comic book of the movie and then later years and years, meaning like 2010 or 12 or something.
I think they then started to put out a comic book called creep show because of the new series.
But creep show.
Stephen King and Romero couldn't get the rights to tell some the crypt.
And they said that that's what they wanted to do. They went away to make they went away for a weekend to come up with an idea for something.
And they said we want to do tells in the crypt. They couldn't get the rights to it. So then they did creep show.
Creep show was a hit.
Yeah, creep show two came out then George Romero.
Amidst that said I want to make a TV series called creep show.
They couldn't get the creep show name for the TV series. So he called it tells them the dark side.
Then they wanted to make creep show three.
But for whatever reason they couldn't.
So he made tells from the dark side the movie with all the guys that made the creep show movies.
And he was like, this is basically creep show three, which is why everybody always says tells the dark side is the unofficial.
Yeah, creep show three.
So it's a weird string of events.
And then right around that time just after tells the dark side of the movie came out.
Tell some the crypt got licensed to HBO.
And the show came out and it got this big revival and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
All right, let us talk then about today's movie and now I remember it because I've said it 50 times you got to you got to repeat these things till they land in your brain
Henry Johnson directed by David Mammott last year this was a play here in Santa Monica I believe Venice Venice yeah
I really wanted to go and didn't make it I know it was pretty sold out it was a very small theater and LaBuff still is a big star
but yeah, basically the movie very much feels like a film to play even more so than say Glen Gary Glen Ross
and more so than a lot of Mammott's movies do
Super low budget you get the feeling it's probably under a milley but then again everything's five times what you think it is
I was like I think they shot this and they could have shot this in three days I think
Oh easily yeah, it's like three scenes
Yeah, I mean, it's basically
three long long conversations the first is
Well, Joe walk us through the plot basically I will
But before I do I will say what this movie I'm a big fan of Mammott and I'm a big fan of his films and his plays but
This movie is very very reminiscent of O'Leana
And
I'm very good for it. O'Leana, but I see what you're saying. Yeah, very very very very reminiscent of O'Leana and American Buffalo in the sense of you're dealing with a few characters
You're dealing with a specific situation
They are gonna talk a lot about that situation
There will be some reveals that keep things interesting and you're probably not gonna see more than three different settings
This is about a man who's a lawyer named Henry Johnson
The opening of the film
Takes this is seen between he and his boss
Or you know senior partner at the company whatever Chris Bauer plays him
The actor the place Henry Johnson I'm blanking on his name, but he's actually married to Zosia Mammott
Oh, is he yeah, just a little bit of NEPO action. Yeah, so
And the first guy is from the wire. I loved him on the wire. He's a character actor. You definitely recognize
He's awesome. Yeah, he's great
So they're having a conversation about
Henry had a friend who was imprisoned and he was imprisoned because
A woman he was dating was pregnant
the man
Urged the woman to get an abortion
She refused she wanted to have the baby so he forced an abortion onto her by
during intercourse
Like essentially
Slipping a poison into her vagina. They killed the baby. He was caught and he went to jail
He's now getting out of jail and Henry Johnson has talked to his
Superior at his law firm about giving this guy some kind of job
He is being heavily questioned as to why he would have any allegiance to this man
and as that
questioning goes on
His his allegiance to his company is starting starts to become or his firm becomes under question and then it is revealed that
Henry Johnson raised money to pay for this guy's legal defense and
Then it's revealed that that money was stolen and imbezzled out of his law firm
And you realize that his boss has him there
So he can stall him as they are changing the locks to the company because he's about to be arrested
It's a nice little twist at the end of the conversation. Yeah
And the lesson
In that moment or in that conversation the takeaway rather of that conversation is
A man asked you to do something for him or a man treated you well and the only reason he treated you well
When he was in a bad position was because he knew eventually it would allow you to do a favor for him
He puts you in his good graces with his charm and his charm and you and accepting his charm has led you to a place where you will actually try to do something
To to assist this man
And that is basically the theme of the movie manipulation. Yeah people will
Offer you something whether it's a secret whether it is their decency
Whether it is a favor whether it is assistance, but it is all emotive for them to then
Abuse and and exploit you
So cut to second scene he's in jail. He meets his cellmate played by shy LaBuff and shy LaBuff expounds on this concept that I'm
Clumsily describing in great detail and and beautifully beautifully poetic
The word that this is word to me where the script really shined this middle section where shy LaBuff is giving these
Saliliquiz about this concept we're talking about
He is he's off the charts as
Far as is acting go. I mean he's just so on point. It's insane and
The language is beautiful. It's beautifully written
and
It is revealed that
Excuse me Henry Johnson's
counselor is
Is a female and she's potentially in love with him and she tells him that
She has access to a gun and shy LaBuff is explaining to him the only reason she told you that is to
Again, it's it's I'm not going to be able to regurgitate the the dialogue, but the point is is she told you that for a reason
Right
And shy LaBuff says we can get something out of her again
Exploiting this concept of somebody gives you a secret why because you because they want a secret in return
She gave you a secret now
You know, whatever the deal is struck
And they devise a plan to basically request this woman to bring him the gun
And once he has the gun he's an inmate with a gun and where is it going to go from there and then it jumps again
To the final scene
Which is there sirens outside their walled in at the library you you realize shy LaBuff's character is dead
He's locked in with a prison guard
Uh
You know they're the that's swat and whoever else is going to be storming the room probably to kill him
Yeah, he's got the gun their plan worked
And we get the last of our saloakwis, but this time it's it's from the prison guard to
Henry Johnson and these are three scenes where this guy
Is manipulated by the other person he's talking to in one way or another
For better or for worse
Because he doesn't understand how the game is played which is another part of
Or so another something they they get into and describe in detail on the movie about the way the game is played
A loser should never run with the winners
Because they will never see you as that something along those lines. Yeah look
Even as I explain it
I realize this does not sound very riveting
Um
I as Pat said it feels very much like a play
But the reason I compare it to Oliana and American Buffalo is because that's how those
plays initial plays that later became films worked as well
It was two characters talking about a concept and that concept continually was explored and unfolded
To affect those characters as the story progressed
Um, it's it feels very real
Uh, it feels very
Uh honest
Uh
There's no flash
It's 85 minutes long
I enjoyed it very much. I you know, I know but I say that with knowing it is not for everybody
This is not for everybody. I'm a massive mammoth fan. I was I was excited to see David mammoth's dialogue on screen again
I was excited to see people really acting the shit out of it. That was very cool for me
Yeah, it's not fun mammoth
Um, it's not like playful mammoth
It's a serious drama
I can't say it felt real to me though as you said because because of the dialogue
Um, my issue with mammoth and it's less of an issue in Glen Gary because it always has such an eclectic cast
That uh, brings such interesting characterizations to all these roles that that's a play that always gets the best actors and and and really you know
Great personalities and larger than life actors always want to play those parts
This all four of these actors talking in roughly the same way
Got to me, you know, and I know that's mammoth everybody kind of talks like mammoth and a mammoth thing but
It's it was a little too dense here, you know
They're talking so much about legal jargon and
um
In particular the last
30 minutes of this with the older black security guard played by Evan Johnnick it who was great um
Yeah, oh the performances across the board are are fantastic, but
It at some point you feel like you're watching
Uh, actors monologue class, you know um
And that kind of took me out of it when everybody is talking in these in these florists
um
flowery
Dialogue ways, you know, yeah, that's Shakespeare. Yeah, that's
That's a lot of our great writers, you know, it's it's even it's like sorkin to some degree everybody kind of sounds like Aaron sorkin
It bothers me sometimes it doesn't other times uh usually it's just
Did you get a bunch of great actors involved so that all their personalities make the dialogue feel different when spoken and in this one
That didn't come across from me except
LaBuff
Shyla buff is so much better than everybody else his segment is so much better than everybody else
I love Chris Bauer from the wire. I love
Um, I don't know this guy dominant Kaufman. Oh no dominant Kaufman is the older black guy. I do apologize
Um Evan Johnnick it is oh, yeah, that's that's her husband the guy. Yeah, okay
So I was incorrect there and then Chris Bauer is the guy from the wire so for me
Shyla buff
Gives this movie the the paddles that you do at the at the hospital, you know paddles on the chest he jolts this movie to life
He's riveting. He's excellent
And then when he leaves the energy goes out of the film to me the first sequel
I mean the the guy playing Henry Johnson is kind of a nothing he basically just reacts throughout the movie
I
I just I think he doesn't have as much to do as everybody does, but I think he's very good. I
I oh yeah, he's not bad. He just didn't have as much to do. That's what I'm saying
But I mean, but I would also say though, but like it's it's that's again
It's kind of like we're talking about with Paul Rudd in um friendship
It's what we talked about way back with the Nero and the Irishman or peshy in the Irishman
It's so hard to be the guy that sits and reacts. Yeah, yeah, yeah, and not not create a hole on screen and this kid manages to do it
Which was impressive to me?
Yeah, the performances are not the issue
and I can't
I definitely didn't like it as much as you. I definitely was not riveted by it
But to me that was the whole issue. I understand that this is four different
Are three different, you know short films almost
Combined each one with a new kind of commanding actor taking over the space
To manipulate to pressure to get what they want out of this kind of cipher of a human being
I
Got it. However
Shia LaBouffe's us a movie star
these other guys are character actors and
When you have a movie star pop into a movie like this
All of a sudden for 30 minutes. You're like, oh, I'm watching an a level piece of entertainment here with a big star
And then the rest I got to say it it fizzled out for me. I was so not interested
In the last half hour of this movie and it was no fault of that actor who was excellent
But
God, he just kept rambling on and I'm like, what are you talking about? There's a police siege going on and you're doing this like monologue under a spotlight
I'm not particularly interested in it
um and as you were saying the dialogue in the LaBouffe sequence is stronger
It's almost like he knew he's got to get this star
So that segment. I don't know. It's just like suddenly you can't not look at the screen
and
Then once he leaves for for me. I found it hard to look at the screen part of the problem was I was watching it on my laptop
Which is always a guarantee that I won't like a movie
But it's the only way to watch it right now unless you want to go to Brynmar, Pennsylvania
So we should say and I did say it on on the solo corner
But if you want to watch this movie
There's only one way to do it unless you live in Brynmar and that is Henry Johnson movie dot com
You can do a seven-day rental for $10 which I think is pretty reasonable
And my guess is that this will sell to a streamer in a few months
But this might be the kind of thing where mammoth self funded it and is trying to just make his money back through a website
Like kind of how Louis K does his stand-up specials now. He said
He said in an interview
He was like like all things I do in my life. I have to be drug
Kicking and screaming
Yeah, and he was like, you know, so during covid somebody approached him and said, you know
Friend of his and said, do you have anything in a drawer? Yeah, that hasn't been made or maybe it was during the strike
I don't remember and he's like, what are you kidding me? I got
Fucking cabinets full of shit and he titty pulled this out and he gave it to tour
And then that led to them putting it on in the Venice playhouse whatever it was called
Which child above and he said during that run, Shiloboff said to him
We're gonna shoot this we're making this a movie and he was like, okay, let's do it
And he had very very glowing things to say about Shiloboff
Um
Yeah, I mean, I I hope this kid turns it around man. I really do
um
Because he's just incredibly talented. I was telling Joe how much I have always wished that he played the miles teller role in
Whiplash. I think he would have been so much better than miles teller in that part
um
But right now he is in a place where if he's gonna work it is gonna be with somebody controversial
Uh, it is gonna be with somebody who doesn't mind risking their reputation
um, my guess is Timothy Shalamay didn't like
Him posting those private emails, you know, like it's the kind of thing where you're not supposed to associate with this guy
He's got pretty serious allegations against him, but if he just
Sticks with it does the work this is a town that will redeem you he could be the next Robert Downey Jr. We don't know
Um
From what I've heard Joe I want to do Megalopolis with you on this show, but apparently
He lost so much money that he's not releasing it. Oh, yeah, he's gonna take it like on tour
So I don't know when we're gonna actually see this thing
But he's child above is supposed to be horrible in that movie like way way way way way over the top
I watched some scenes with him. I thought it was it looked fun and interesting to me, but I don't know yeah
Well, I think almost everybody in that movie goes over the top, but um
Yeah, he gets little parts and things nowadays and I really really hope
He keeps it together, you know, I hope that this all this work he's doing is legit and that we can
See him again because like for example this show I'm talking about with apatel
The there's a part that he's so perfect for and it's got to be a guy who's just
so
depressed and angry and frustrated with life that he's about to blow and
And to me that is zero actors in that age range working today
Nobody nobody gives off that feeling of like this guy's a loose cannon anymore and that used to be all of our actors
Where guys you felt like you might not leave them alone with your sister, you know
um
LaBuff's exciting in a way that most movie stars these days are not
So I do hope he gets it together because he's electric and this this movie to me is
is
The best possible proof of that you watch it you go. I recognize everybody here's great and the dialogues
Cracklin and the stories okay kind of interesting stories not always mammoth strong suit
Um, but then LaBuff comes in and you're like I'm watching an excellent movie right now like he has that power to uplift what he's in the interesting thing
is
uh
The thing at the beginning about his friend that
Terminated the woman's abortion against or the baby against the woman's will yeah, that's not the story
Right you think this is going to be like this
Weird challenging thing about abortion
Where the man wanted to abort and the woman didn't
Yeah, and then the man is saying it's my choice
It's usually the other way around it's a man's going it should be my choice to to to keep the baby to
It's and it's like this weird inverse thing and you're like
Oh, this is going to be wild like I guess like this is going to be and that's not it. It's just it's just an interesting
Conversation, you know, it's an interesting piece
It's an interesting
Element of that conversation so um I would say this I would say I don't disagree with a lot of what you're saying
I don't agree with all of it, but um I'd like to see it again
So the
Absence of LeBuff when he leaves the film is not as apparent because I you know or or is not so deflating
Yeah, uh because I know that that's going to happen
And I think that will allow me to absorb the final sequence a little bit more and maybe even reframe it to to have even greater meaning than it does
Because I was admittedly distracted a bit throughout that last sequence because I was like
Fuck where is he man like what happened to him is he dead and I kept you know whatever I was asking all those questions
So I think um I think I want to see it again
uh
and and and and and and see if it reframes the experience for me, but in the meantime
Uh my hog is up. I I liked it. It's not it's not raging
But but I enjoyed this film and it certainly was better than the last you know mammoth's last movie might have been Phil specter
Last when he directed was 16 years ago Phil specter. Yeah, which was
Such a letdown and yeah confusing
Confusing like it almost non-movie. I didn't even understand what the fuck it was supposed to be
So it was nice to see him back in his traditional form again and uh and I did enjoy this
Yeah, I mean to me this is pretty average. I would say my hog is not quite up
But my hog is very up for shy of love buff and since I do have OCD
I didn't really finish my thing earlier. I was just saying that like we all agreed you can't cast shy of love
And this thing which leaves you with a sea of pretty boys who can't convey that something is going on inside of them turmoil inside of them
a lot of times
The only way to convey that there's turmoil inside of an actor is if he's going through turmoil
And I don't think we allow people like that on sets anymore, which is great for safety for everybody and and has to happen
It's a it's a good thing
I'm just saying it's a boring thing for the cinema that an actor like
Like LaBuff who can't get it together who has done
appalling things
You know, it sucks. It's like we used to kind of turn a blind eye and like he's a bad boy
You know, and a lot of actors would be a Sean Penn was the the OG bad boy
You know, and he tied Madonna up and was like putting cigarettes out on her and all this shit
Cut to today. He's still acting and he's still you know, he's still in movies and he won an Oscar after all that
So this is a town that will redeem you and for me. This is just a a LaBuff love fest. I wish you the best
Though I may not approve of what you have done. I believe people deserve a second shot
Um
Check her out all right our next episode or I don't know what order we're putting these up in but it'll be Joe
Better a moanie already have already have already happened then it's in the past
What we can air that we can show we can post them whatever order we want. It's uh it already happened
In case that's a two-parter. I don't want to sit yeah
We talked about all this off the air but you know patches
Well the two-parter thing. I mean, I don't see that happening
Well, if it does though now there's this awkward thing where
This is
Don't let it freak you out. I hope this isn't like war of the worlds where you all lose your mind and think you're in the future because I said that
So this this this episode is either the last episode of May or the first episode of June
We're not sure yet. You're gonna be May
We don't know yet
Anyway, folks we appreciate you. We love you. I'll see you
Well, I'm not even gonna plug because I don't know when it's coming out because I follow the damn rules
Pat it was good talking to you man. Uh, this was fun tonight
You as well Joe and it was great talking to Joe Ramone when we did that yesterday
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell