Welcome to We'll See You in Hell. Pat Walsh, Joe DeRosa, talking about movies, doing the
reviews, doing the disguise.
Hello, we're talking this week about Ghostbusters Afterlife, directed by Jason
Reitman, the son of Ivan Reitman. He struggled with picking up the reins from
such a impactful franchise, but eventually he knew it was his destiny.
Did you read all those interviews with him?
No.
Stupid.
I mean, especially right now, as everyone's so upset about nepotism and all
this stuff, it's like, shut the fuck up.
Well, you're changing your tune a little bit.
You were saying they were being too hard on him about that about a week ago.
They were, they were, and then also I came around because I actually read some
of his interviews and he, it was really annoying.
It's like, you know, another reason you might've turned to Ghostbusters, Jason,
is that your last nine movies have flopped.
Let's, let's just say that, you know, I mean, you know, and like up in the air,
which was good.
And thank you for smoking young adult.
No, he had, he had good movies.
Don't get me wrong.
And honestly, I didn't think all of his other movies were bad.
They just lost a ton of money.
And then he had to go, Hey dad, can I do Ghostbusters?
Like he, he wraps it in this whole, like, you know, the, the stars align kind of
thing, people come up with any narrative.
I've done it myself.
Anything you can do to get the pain off of yourself.
You come up with some shitty narrative.
Um, I will get to it.
We'll get to it.
I have a lot to say about the film.
I actually, I posted my, um, letterbox review of, of Ghostbusters and I was
chiding people for not liking Ghostbusters who also liked Bill and Ted face the
music and the amount of complaining and bitching I saw about this movie being
too, too much of a fan service thing and to giving the fans too much, whatever.
I'm like, guys, you like Bill and Ted.
It was the exact same problem with that movie.
However, that movie sucked balls and this movie is fun, you know, but in the
comments, people were like, Oh wait, I, you know, can't wait to hear what Joe
says about this one, you know, there's a, there's a, there's a heat about your
opinion, Joe, people want to know.
Because they think I'm going to hate it or they think I'm going to love it.
And they want to hate me for loving it.
Cause I find the ladder usually is the truth.
You know, anything they like when you, when you chime in on something that is
either universally loved or universally hated, I think is generally when they
like the Joe coming into, you know, which way I'm going to go if it's hated,
I'm going to love it.
You love it.
I'm going to hate it.
And you got, it's good to hear that self -awareness that wasn't always present.
You know where I stand.
Yeah.
So, uh, Ghostbusters it is.
I didn't mention last time and I'd like to, that I still do, you know, a 40 to
60 minute, uh, solo movie corner each week or each month, excuse me.
Um, this month went a little deeper than I probably should have.
Cause then all of a sudden, when I started having to do, uh, movie corners
on the main show, I was like, Oh shit, I talked about everything else, but I've
been liking doing it.
And also, I just want to say that I read all of your comments.
Sometimes I'm reading them at an odd time or I'm reading them in bed or I'm not
in a position to respond, but they're always read just so, you know, and I try
to respond when I can, there's been very few, but there's been a couple, like
kind of payment issues and charging issues, stuff like that reach out to us.
Um, Joe, me or Emily will get to it and we will always help you out if, if it
seems like we're ignoring you, it is never, we're trying to take your money.
That is just not something we have any interest in doing and pissing people off.
And we know that you guys are giving us your heart and money to hear us and
support us and we love you for it.
So if we miss something, just please trust that we'll make it right when we
see it and that for me, logging into Patreon is actually an incredibly
complicated process that requires me remembering several passwords, logging
into a separate email address, usually texting Joe to find out what those
passwords are, you have to verify yourself.
So sometimes it's just a hassle and I don't look rambling way of saying,
we always read your stuff.
We read your Instagram comments or messages, et cetera.
If we don't respond, just know what we saw.
Thank you.
I always say your comments are like my nipples.
They're always red.
That's good.
Thank you.
You got foam under your nose or is that like some kind of Coke line?
Whoa.
Yeah.
You getting busy over there?
It's a, uh, it's a little piece of a Kleenex.
When you, I hadn't shaved in ages.
I had the beard forever.
And then, uh, it leaves you with kind of a jagged stubble in spots.
And I think when I blow my nose, I get little pieces stuck in it, which
is always an attractive look when you have a part of a Kleenex
hanging from your upper lip.
It's just like, so I need to avoid this guy is what everyone says as I approach.
Yeah.
Hey babe, what are you thinking about going to that new Italian place
for dinner tonight?
What are you saying?
That's very funny.
That's a funny visual.
Um, well, you know, while we're on the subject of, uh, Reboots and
remakes and sequels or the only movies that are made.
Yeah.
Matrix revolutions.
What's it called?
Resurrections.
Yes.
Okay.
So I found that I was never a huge matrix fan.
I liked the first one.
I saw the second one in the theater.
I remember thinking it was cool and then never watching it ever again.
Resurrections.
I tried a few times and I was like, I don't give a shit.
Yeah.
They, they disappeared in their ass.
They forgot to make them entertaining.
You know, my friend Brian was telling me the other day, I said, I don't
understand how is Neo still alive and how is this, how does he not know
the matrix or whatever?
And Brian explained to me, he goes, oh, well he goes, they, they told you in
the first movies that he's like the sixth Neo or whatever.
And every time they reboot the matrix, there's a new Neo.
And I was like, oh, okay.
So clearly this is literally a reboot.
Yeah.
That, that is due to a reboot.
Right.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Right.
So I was like, okay, that's interesting.
And then I was like, well, that's fucked up that Morpheus is now being played
by a younger, better looking, hotter actor, because they felt Laurence
Fishburne wasn't, you know, wasn't, I mean, that's crazy.
The whole reason I thought Laurence Fishburne wasn't in this was because
he dies in the matrix video game.
They kill Morpheus and I was like, okay, well, Morpheus is dead.
That's not why, that's why he's not in it.
And this is like, clearly like they want them, but they can't have them.
So they got to make some like parallel Morpheus.
It's like, no, they just, they just don't, they just don't have
Laurence Fishburne in it.
You think they made the call and just told them like, Hey, you
haven't been hitting the gym.
I mean, they would have had to.
He said he never got a call.
And Fishburne seems like a pretty happy go lucky sort of straightforward guy.
I mean, he doesn't seem bitter or anything like that.
Like, you know, I talked about home sweet home alone on the solo movie
corner and I watched that on, I watched it on Disney plus bad.
It was a bad move.
I didn't want to comment on it because we're friends with Pete
Holmes is in it and he's our friend.
Well, Pete's barely in it.
I felt comfortable with that, but I actually got a good laugh out of him.
I texted him and I took a picture of the screen and I was like, Pete,
I'm 10 minutes in here.
And I think you guys might've fucked up with his title.
I mean, everybody's talking about going on a Tokyo vacation.
Like, so I'm, I mean, I feel like we're heading on a fun Tokyo trip.
Why don't you call it Tokyo trip?
And I just, I, I was pretending that I didn't know why they call it home alone
because he hadn't been left home alone yet.
It was a good bit, went on for a long time.
But, um, regardless that my issues with it, I discussed at length, but
basically the burglars are in the right.
The kid's an asshole who at an open house steals a very valuable doll from them.
Oh, for Christ's sakes.
They're trying to get the doll back.
One of them is a woman of a thin, sweet, pretty woman.
So every time she's hitting the head with a paint can, you're like, Jesus Christ.
I noticed, okay.
Yeah.
And I noticed too, in the trailer, like she's always yelled, she's the peshy.
She's always yelling at the guy, right?
Like, what are you a pussy?
You know, or however they say it in that movie, but yeah.
I mean, they do a scene where she's pushing him over a wall.
She's pushing him.
He weighs two 40 and she weighs a hundred pounds.
There's no real explanation given.
And then he farts in her face, you know, it's like, it was, it was pretty dire.
They gave John Hughes a story credit because they changed so little, but the
things they changed made it so much worse.
Every change was so much worse.
Who's the man?
Who's the male crook, Rob Delaney, who's very funny.
Okay.
I was thinking Rob Riggle.
It's Delaney and the female crook.
I didn't recognize her.
She's Ellie Kemper from, um, well, she got infamous last year, so she played, um,
is that Kimmy Schmidt?
Kimmy Schmidt.
Yeah, it is.
I didn't realize it was her.
It was her, which is a funny show.
Kimmy Schmidt.
But, um, she got in trouble last year for being involved in something when she was
18, which wound up being like, it was a beauty pageant, but it was sponsored by
the clue Clucks clan and it took place in St.
Louis where I'm from.
So this was like the ball and she was like, I did not know this was affiliated
with the client and I believe her, but I think her career survived that, that
awkward time, um, anyway, home sweet home alone is bad for sure, but the, the
reboot aspect of it, it's like, you know, they, they really just sat down and said,
like, what could we do to make this a less funny, enjoyable movie?
The changes they made were not about diversity or progress, although it's a
more diverse cast, of course.
Um, the changes were just about like making the burglars more two -dimensional.
No, it's, I'll tell you what it is.
It's not even that.
Why would they do that?
It's not even that it's, it's, it's, they had to make the burglars friendly
burglars with a decent motive.
So, because it's too traumatizing to see a child in danger that that's exactly
what it is.
Everybody has to be likable.
Every single person has to be justified and likable.
It's stupid.
What makes the original awesome is they're bad guys.
Yeah.
Joe Pesci threatens to bite his fingers off.
Yes.
So when he gets the best of them and is like hitting them in the
head with bricks and all this shit, it's awesome.
Like, and it's hilarious.
Yeah.
And you're rooting for him, but you're kind of rooting against this kid who
is pretty much in the wrong.
And for the kid, the kid to be British is also weird.
And they do, you know, they have him come out in his mom's dress.
They have him Google porn, you know, there's some modern touches
that also feel Google porn.
They feel kind of uncomfortable in a home alone movie.
Joe, I said the exact same thing, you know, like basically every change
they made from John Hughes, the script was the wrong one.
It's like, he was just a guy and he apparently wrote that script on
flight basically, but he just instinctively knew what everybody
could handle, what everybody would enjoy.
He made movies that everyone on all sides still love to this day.
And then, you know, two guys with all the time and money in the world
sit down and try to duplicate it.
And you come off with something that just misses every possible mark.
Some people got it.
Some people don't.
Johnny Hughes, you had it.
You had a kid.
He did.
But yeah, it's a bad film.
Home sweet home alone.
What else are they?
Oh, you know what I was just reading about was Nicholas cage being cast as Dracula.
And I'm like, love it.
And that Nicholas Holt who's a funny kid act or not.
He's not a kid anymore.
He's probably 30, but he's playing Renfield.
Yeah.
And I'm like, look, I love everything about this package.
What I just read as I was logging into the zoom was that aquafina has just been
added to the cast and then literally as I'm reading the deadline article, the
guy who wrote it was like, wouldn't even venture a guess as to what aquafina
would be playing in this, you know, it like doesn't make any sense.
What would it be?
But, um, just because she is so modern, I'm not even talking about her being
Asian, you know, who's also gotten in trouble for talking black, you know,
just sort of a, you know, multi -layered, uh, issue that, that, that's to me is
the interesting aspect of this is when these things start reaching points where
it's like, okay, now you're accusing the Asian woman of being racist and then
that gets into a different areas.
But it's a lot, it's a lot to take in.
It's interesting.
I'm just saying she does talk, uh, you know, she talks hip hop.
That's her thing.
It's kind of the whole, so it's like, where does she factor into Dracula?
You know, like they'll start putting it's a comedy.
First of all.
Oh, is it?
I thought it was just a straightforward drag.
No, no, it's a comedy.
It's a con.
That's why Nicholas cage.
They have got him playing Dracula.
Okay.
All right.
No, it's a comedy.
Um, it'll probably, you know, then I'm, then forget everything.
I just said, probably great in it.
She's fine.
I just, yeah, she's fine.
It's just, it's this larger issue of like, you start hearing about a movie
being good and then there's some element added into it where you're like, what?
And then over time it becomes way more stuff you just don't get or understand.
It's like, there's never been a movie that with each new announcement,
you're more excited about it.
You know what I mean?
It's just, it's just what they're, the approach to everything now is don't
offend anybody in any way.
Hollywood appeal to everybody.
So that you get 100 % of the audience and you just can't, it doesn't work.
It just doesn't work.
And nobody's saying, I hate that you're trying to appeal to a lot of people.
It doesn't work.
That's all.
So you got to narrow your beam a little bit here, you know, no art ever worked.
I mean, I, I'm really hard pressed to call the Renfield comedy art, but you
know, my, my point is, is that no, no piece of art or maybe it is, I don't know,
but no piece of art ever worked because you tried to make it appeal to everybody.
You know, McDonald's is for everybody.
Not, not a movie.
It's just the way it is.
But, um, you know, and they want everything to be the wizard of Oz.
They want everything to be like, it appeals to all ages.
It's timeless.
It's this, it's like, guys, that's lightning in a bottle, man.
Like you can't recreate it.
Well, I bring up, I bring up the show I did not because I, I'm, I need therapy
over it, but because that's what I have experience with the notes that I would
get on the cool kids, which was a show about four really funny old people was.
Where are the young people?
You know, like they always wanted to either meet their kids or they wanted
there to be a really young, hot lady who worked at the old folks home or something.
And I would always just say like, nobody under the age of 50 ever appeared on
old girls, you know, once in a blue moon, you have the girl scout pop in or
something, but I was just like, that's not what people want from this.
We, th their whole thing was like, wouldn't it be funny if some hot young
woman was showing them how to use iPhones?
Oh, no, no, no, you know, like, are we making fucking coffee commercials here?
You know, like just the most generic shit.
And that is the goal now.
So like a movie like home alone, which still released today would still be PG.
It was PG then, and it's PG now, but somehow that becomes something that
needs to be watered down and softened.
Joe, there's a moment in this.
I didn't mention, okay.
You know, that, you know, the original well, well, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay.
There's a, they're watching a movie.
It's in space.
And it's this guy who goes, I'm going to give you till the count of 10 to get
your ugly yellow, no good keister off my planet before I pump your
guts full of space bullets.
Oh my God.
Then they, you, you cut to two guys sitting on, you cut to two guys
sitting on the couch, Joe.
And I bet if I gave you three guesses, you'd get it, but I'm just going to
He goes, boy, this is why they should never do these reboots.
They're always worse.
Just like, and you've seen that.
I've seen that joke 50 times and it's always they're right.
It's always there.
They're just admitting that they're not trying and it's not as good.
And it's like, no, you think this is like arch and funny because we're
supposed to think you're the cool, funny movie and that home alone is the dumb
movie, but we all hate you and you don't get to make that joke.
I mean, where's the outrage about this?
Phil peep.
I saw people online screaming because they pulled a goddamn Nestle
crunch bar out of Egon's coat pocket.
Well, as much as people love home alone, I think they write off kids movies and
maybe people haven't even watched home sweet home alone.
I watched it cause I was like, I try to give myself some Christmas spirit and
you wind up stomping around the house angry after you watch it.
Oh boy.
Well, it's not, and honestly, it's not the fault of a cause as you know,
we do have a friend in the movie.
It's not the fault of anybody in the cast.
The cast is actually quite charming.
It's just a, it's a script issue, you know, and you know, I can't tell you
Joe how sad it is to watch each trap be aided by heavy CGI, every single
trap you have, I would bet no stunt.
People did shit in this movie.
You see Rob Delaney like get hit by a bowling ball and then Rob Delaney
in slow motion looking like he's made of pixels flying through the air.
It's like, again, you're missing.
What made that movie special was the blunt trauma that these guys were
going through and that it was done like a cartoon.
I don't know.
I'm madder about that movie than I even realized I was.
I'm shocked you sat through it.
I was like, I can't, I can't do this.
No, I did it.
I did it.
Look, you know what?
Let, let that be my first movie corn.
We're so I'm surprised bitch.
We're in the movie corner.
Go Joe.
Two surprise movie corners this week.
Yeah.
I got to pull my, hold on.
I closed my thing by accident.
My notes.
Uh, Oh, for fuck's sake, give me a break.
God.
Uh, I only have two because it sounds well, I can do, we are going to do repo man or
no, if not, I'll do it here.
Yeah.
Do it here.
Deep cover.
We'll do though, because you know why?
Because it's fish burn at his best and let's give fish burn some love since
these pricks didn't put it in the new.
Some tells me with the way they're dropping this new matrix on HBO max, a
movie like that, that fish burns probably going to be counting his blessings
that he was not in it.
Let's be real.
I just saw an ad for there.
They announced somebody's doing something.
It was some big thing and it's just going to Hulu.
Yeah, it's happening a lot.
I mean, it's not necessarily an indicator of quality, but I will say
nothing that's premiered on HBO max has been good.
Some of the things that it premiered on Netflix have been good.
Yeah.
I mean, it's getting to the point where it's like Scorsese and DiCaprio
reunite for direct to Hulu.
You're like, what?
Yeah, exactly.
Or it's like, yeah, Terrence Malick's new one on Peacock premium.
And it's just like, I give up.
All right.
Repo man.
I had never seen it.
Uh, I'd heard of it my whole life.
I'd never seen it.
I never quite understood what it was.
I knew it was sort of a sci -fi thing.
I knew it was sort of a punk rock thing.
And I knew that it started Emilio Estevez.
I was one of those movie boxes.
I saw at the store all the time as a kid and just never, never went any further
than looking at the front of it.
Um, but I finally watched it because I got it with the criterion deal.
Uh, I texted you and Matt McCarthy and said, is this worth the purchase?
You both said undoubtedly.
Yeah.
I said, all right, got it.
It does not disappoint.
This is a hell of a hell of a movie.
Uh, it's, it's a wild ride.
It's first of all, it's Estevez.
It's my favorite Estevez.
Oh, for sure.
I haven't, I forgot that he used to play characters like this, but it's
Estevez where like laughs like maniacally when he almost gets killed.
Yeah.
But it's, it's very young guns.
He's like that in young guns too.
Yeah.
It's around the time of, of a breakfast club, but he played kind of the square
jock in that, but I think, I think that was more in tune with his personality of
the time was kind of the punk rock kid for the first like 30 minutes of this
thing, or anybody that says anything to him, he's just like, fuck off, you know?
Um, and then, uh, old what's his name is in it in his first leading role ever.
Um, not his first role ever, but his first leading role.
Um, you know, the skeletal skinny old man that's always smoking.
Yeah.
Twin peaks, that guy.
Christine, Harry Dean, Stan, Harry Dean, Stan.
He's a, yeah, he's great.
He's awesome in that movie.
Yes.
Yeah.
One of his best performances.
And that's saying a lot because he was in a hundred movies.
Yeah.
Anyway, it's just about repo men and there's a government agency tracking a car
that has some sort of alien life form or something in it, and they're trying to
reap the repo men are trying to repossess the car because there's a huge price on
it reward and Estevez gets tied up in between the two, uh, he gets roped into
the government, uh, cat and mouse game and also his own interests on
behalf of the repo men.
And, uh, it's a romp.
It's a romp.
It's crazy.
It's a crazy movie.
It's a lot of fun.
It's super indie.
It's the epitome of what indie cinema is when it's great.
I forget the director's name.
He made a movie right after this that apparently bombed so badly.
He was like blackballed from Hollywood.
Yeah.
Alex Cox.
And now he just does super independent stuff.
He did a string of movies that where the budget was a hundred thousand dollars for
each movie.
One of those, I believe was called repo chick that he shot completely on green
screen, which has, if you watch the trailer looks terrible, but it has good
reviews, so I am curious, but I never saw it, never saw it.
Insists it's not related to repo man.
Okay.
It's like, all right.
Anyway, he also, I mean, he did one other masterpiece or at least really good
movie, which is Sid and Nancy, but, uh, yes, Gary Oldman.
But beyond that, yeah, he did not have a lot of luck in Hollywood to be sure.
He does great commentaries.
If you ever see him do a commentary, listen to it because he does a great job.
His third movie is also on criterion.
And that's the one that like bombed like, yeah.
Legendary, I think I don't forget what it's called.
It's like going to Western, but he puts helicopters in it and stuff and, you
know, real art house type stuff.
But, uh, but anyway, I, I really liked this film and, uh, I think anybody that
enjoys like those early eighties punk rock sort of post, it reminded me like,
if like, like, I mean, street trash, I wouldn't say is a good movie.
I really like street trash, but, but it's like getting that same ilk.
It's like a lot of punk music and it's, everything's sort of post -apocalyptic,
but they never really explain it.
Yeah.
There's a science.
To me, it feels of the same world as return of the living dead.
Yes.
Like even though they're different genres, you feel like that could be two
different weekends, uh, or amongst the same group of people almost.
I agree.
And when I was watching repo man, I started thinking, how the hell is
mad max not in the criterion collection?
Sure.
It seemed like it just, it should be right.
I agree.
I mean, they, I bet they tried to get fury road.
I mean, most, most publications consider fury road, the best
movie of the last 20 years.
So anyway, uh, my next is called the piano teacher.
I've been going back through the movies of Michael Hanneke, who is one of the
more disturbing, provoking, unsettling directors of all time.
He is probably best known for funny games and it's American remake with
Naomi Watts, which are basically seen for seeing the same movie, but, um,
and also cache, which is just one of the great thrillers.
If you've never seen it, it's got one of the, the all time best shocks.
It's got a shock that I would put up with the exorcist three, uh,
nurse scissors shock.
It's a similar kind of like, holy shit.
Definitely one of the three most, most effective kind of jump
scares of all time for me.
Uh, but he's a master of making really fucked up shit and doing it in very
real and uncomfortable ways.
So I rewatched the piano teacher, which many consider his finest.
It's an amazing movie.
Uh, the letterboxed headline is perversion at its wicked best exclamation point.
But, uh, yeah, it's a lady.
She lives with her mother.
It's Isabelle who pair who you'd recognize great actress lives with her
mother.
She's very sexually repressed and over the course of the movie and very slow,
long takes, you see the way that she deals with her sexual repression,
which is often cutting herself.
One point she cuts her vagina.
She is getting sort of increasingly, uh, desperate and depraved.
I read about this movie on a Buzzfeed.
They had the 10 greatest vagina cutting movies was the list.
They only had three that the rest were just ads for a blue chip, another
blue chew ad I'll throw out.
But, um, yeah, it's, so I thought you were actually going to say, I'm sure
it's all one of those Buzzfeed lists.
Like the top 10 films we'll never watch twice or something.
It's always on those lists, but it is the, the most, you know, outside of shame,
which I think is another kind of masterpiece about a very tricky topic
like this, well, that was sex addiction.
Uh, if you never saw a shame, I highly recommend, but it feels real.
It feels like these guys have lived through this.
It feels almost like you're watching a documentary.
It feels very intimate and uncomfortable.
And I bet a lot of people judging by the reviews of this thing would
not be able to handle the movie.
At some point, a young man enters her life.
He really wants to fuck her.
And she's just like, no, I need you to do this, this, and this.
She has very bizarre ways of being turned on and of what she'll
do and what she won't do.
And so it's a definitely an adult film.
It's not pornographic, but there's scenes that kind of come close to it.
I don't know, man.
I think Hannah Kay has made more great films than almost anybody.
He doesn't quite get the props he deserves.
I would recommend almost everything he's ever done.
Right.
And that's a criterion too.
So next 50 % off sale.
Not that, now that that's one you'd want to own maybe, but check it out.
It's on, I think it's on the criterion channel too.
Sorry, you're fine.
You're fine.
I I'll stay on the criterion kick for a moment here.
I rewatched all that jazz because I bought it on criterion on the sale.
Uh, I had texted you and said, I don't know, man.
I, you know, I remember liking it, but do I need to buy it?
You said, I think it's a must own.
I bought it.
Um, I don't know.
Now I don't like it that much.
I kind of like it, but it's interesting.
I don't know.
I get it mixed up.
I get it mixed up with the Fosse veered in miniseries and I can't remember
what, what, which happened, which thing happened and which, I love all that
jazz to, to be honest, it's not my, my, my favorite part of the movie is
definitely not the 20 minute Ben Verene musical number, uh, that part kind
of leaves me cold, but the rest of it, I love, I really do love, um, I like it.
I mean, I find myself these days every morning swallowing pills and saying
it's showtime in the mirror, so I can relate, but, uh, it's interesting.
It's interesting.
It's so close to Bob Fosse's life.
I mean, it's so, and I guess at that time, not a lot had been done like that.
I guess Fellini maybe had done some stuff like that, but like, you know, a
movie where it was like, this is autobiographical, but it's not, but it
is, you know, the blurred lines of reality and fiction and all that.
And you know, him having his actual girlfriend play his girlfriend in the
movie and all that stuff.
And then when you re it's almost like the story of all that jazz is a little
more interesting than the movie itself.
Like knowing that all of this really happened to Fosse and then like
knowing on top of it, he made his real life girlfriend audition to play herself.
Yeah.
And how wild and fucked up and crazy that is like, there's just a lot to it.
There's a lot to it.
It's interesting.
Um, I'm gonna watch it again.
I feel like I'm supposed to own it.
I'm just not sure why.
And, uh, it seems like the Fosse -Verdon, you know, the real version you
prefer to all that jazz, which I'm sure they would be blown away and honored by.
But, um, yeah, for, for most people, that's how they first encountered
the story was the movie.
So it just seems like you prefer the real deal.
I might, I might, I really love the movie the first time around.
I believe you use the word masterpiece.
I yet.
Well, I mean, maybe I just wasn't in the right state of mind for it this time.
I love seeing, I love the Lang character as the, she's the angel of death or
whatever.
I mean, that's really cool.
And it's, it's, it's a, it's edgy, man.
It's a very edgy movie.
I mean, that part where he's the strippers are like teasing him and then
he goes on stage and it pans down.
He has like that big wet jizz spot on his pants.
Yeah.
Uh, I like it a lot more than Lenny, which is a very similar movie by Bob
Fosse with Dustin Hoffman as Lenny Bruce, but I like all that jazz a lot more.
Well, that's what I mean.
That jazz has the dad from Alf in it.
Yeah, he's right.
It is better.
Um, yeah, he, I mean, that's the thing is like, like the movie.
That's what I mean when I say the, oh, it's almost like the story of all that
jazz is, is, is more interesting.
Right.
Cause then you watch, cause Lenny is the movie he was cutting in real life in
the, in it's the, it's the movie he's supposed to be cutting in the
movie of all that jazz.
Yes.
And then you see Lenny and Lenny is sort of like a Bob Fosse story too.
So there's just, it's a lot of tangled webs and it's very interesting.
It's surreal.
You know, the fact that it ends with him dying all that jazz and, and it's
almost like he's per that's a whole other level that he's like predicting
his own death, right?
Uh, you know, it's pretty wild stuff.
That is, it is.
I'm a big fan.
And I think there's some good interviews with him on that criteria.
And maybe with Fosse or with Scheider, I think with both.
Okay.
Uh, you know, like Criterion always has like 50 minute Dick Cavett
interviews with people that, you know, Dick Cavett, I guess the show must
have been nine hours long because there's endless footage of Dick Cavett
talking to everybody on earth.
Dick Cavett had like seven shows.
Like he just kept, he kept getting them.
And so like, finally, I think he was on at one point PBS with no audience.
Like he was just one of those guys.
They just kept being like, have another talk show.
Right.
And, uh, into a mirror at the end.
Uh, I rewatched Phantom Thread, Paul Thomas Anderson's Phantom Thread.
And it has happened, you know, for me, uh, Boogie Nights and Magnolia
were the masterpieces, the ones I fell in love with from the jump, um, and
the others I had to kind of find on a second viewing, like, you know, punch
drawn glove, I probably loved the most, but then they all definitely want to
step up on a second viewing and Phantom Thread is no exception.
I found it, everyone, basically everyone told me it was funny.
And then when I watched it the first time, I was like, it wasn't funny at all.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Uh, and it let me down this time.
I was cackling throughout and I just got something very different out of it.
The movie to me now, uh, much like how Mulholland drive on a second viewing
clicked for me and I got it and I wanted to talk about it like at every party.
And I'm sure I was very annoying, but it just, it, it clicked in, it clicked
in for me in a way that like, I wanted to write an essay about Phantom Thread
basically, but the movie, and I'm sure I'm seeing it this way because this is
the life that I live is about a creative person and how difficult it is to be a
creative person and be in a relationship and make both things work and allow
time for both.
That's what the movie is completely about clearly to me now.
And I think the Daniel Day -Lewis character is so funny because it's Paul
Thomas Anderson making fun of himself and making fun of how stupid and
pathetic it sounds when, like when I'm talking to my wife about how I need time
alone to write something, write my little stories, and then she goes into
work and tells somebody he has HIV, you know, right?
Like, I think that Paul Thomas Anderson knows how ridiculous that request
sounds to a normal working person and makes fun of himself throughout all of
Phantom Thread and makes fun of creative people in general in a way that it's
super funny and knowing, and I'm a little ashamed that I missed that angle on it
the first time I watched it.
So I really loved it.
Uh, I think Daniel Day -Lewis is so funny in it and so good.
The other two women in it, Vicki Kreps, um, and the other lady, I'm sorry.
They, he goes with unknowns in this one.
But they're incredible.
Uh, the cinematography of course is incredible.
I just really dug the movie.
It's one like, I'm glad I own because I think it's something I'm going to be
watching every few months for a while.
It's how there will be blood hit me.
It was like first time I get it, but I'm missing something second time.
Okay.
This is awesome.
And then each new time it's like, you find all new shit and there's very few
directors, I think making movies on his level at this point.
It makes me excited to see licorice pizza again, because that one, again, I
was like, good, but you know, whatever.
But I think his need time to grow on you.
All right.
Did I take cocaine?
No, I don't know.
My final halfway through that rant.
I just love that movie.
I got, I got so much out of it.
Your final one, Joe, the night books on a Netflix starring.
Why can't I never remember anybody's goddamn name?
We're getting old.
The lady that played the superhero.
I can't remember the superhero's name, Jessica justice or whatever the Marvel
Oh, not Jessica.
Just, I think it was just something Jones, Jessica Jones, that lady,
January Jones.
No, it was, um, the girl from Breaking Bad, right?
The girl from the B and apartment 23, Kristen Ritter, Kristen Ritter.
Yes.
Not no relation to John.
No, uh, Kristen Ritter stars in this movie.
This is a great little movie.
I really enjoyed this.
I watched it closer to Halloween, but, uh, what's it called again?
Night books, night books.
I'll put it on my list.
Sam Raimi produced it.
It's got a Sam Raimi feel to it, but it's a kid's movie.
It's a kid's horror movie.
And it's about a kid who loves to write scary stories, who, um, is very upset
about something that's occurred between him and his best friend where he feels
very dejected and he runs away from home at the beginning of the movie and he
lives in an apartment and in his apartment building unbeknownst to him lives
a witch and he gets sort of coaxed into her apartment and then he's trapped
there and he can't leave and in there, he meets another girl that's also
been trapped there for, for, you know, they don't specify the time and the
witch played by Kristen Ritter says, you have to tell me a scary story every night.
So that's the kid's charge.
It's very cool the way they do it.
Like when he tells the story, they do that, like paper, like the thing they
did in the new candy man, like the paper thing, almost like marionette stuff.
That's how they show the stories.
But then there's this whole adventure of him and the little girl and the
young girl inside the house where it's like a Hansel and Gretel kind of thing.
And they have to figure out how to escape and how to defeat the
witch and blah, blah, blah.
And it's just a really, really fun kids horror movie.
It's, you know, it's, it's just awesome.
It's great.
If I'd seen this when I was a kid, I would have gone batshit.
Like if I saw this when I was 10, it would have changed my life.
But even as a 44 year old man, I really enjoyed it.
It has that Sam Raimi touch to it.
Um, it's a lot of fun.
I recommend it.
I will watch, put it on my list.
Yeah.
And now we come to Ghostbusters afterlife, which is the, I guess you
would say the third in the franchise, because I don't know that they're
counting Paul Fieg's Ghostbusters.
Uh, I, but I also don't know that they're calling this Ghostbusters three.
It might just be the launch of its own thing.
Joe, do you know?
They're saying that it is the Jason Reitman said that one and two are
Canon and this is the third movie.
Okay.
I mean, I do also think it's starting things fresh again, which we'll get into,
but right, but I do think it is.
It's a true sequel to Ghostbusters too.
It is supposed to be the third Ghostbusters movie.
Okay.
Yeah.
And you know, let's just start by saying that this movie really, to my surprise,
has been critically reviled.
I mean, I, and, and at least Twitter really reviled.
Um, but like on my, the people I follow on letterbox, which generally is either
friends or critics, I respect, um, you're talking one star out of five, two stars
out of five, like just everybody hated it.
And I can't wrap my head around it.
Um, I saw it in IMAX.
I thought it looked great.
I was concerned that Jason Reitman might not be the most visual director, the
special effects director.
He's never done anything like that before, but I thought he pulled it off really well.
The ghosts were a nice mix of old school.
Uh, you know, what do you call that lot?
What do you call live action, special effects in camera practical?
Yeah, sorry.
Practical effects.
Um, it was a nice mix of the practical and the CGI.
I thought, I thought that the, like, you know, big swings, like the mini stay
scenes were really fun and funny and looked cool and that he actually did a
good job with the visuals, with the special effects and certainly with the
cast.
And I think it's really one of the most charming cast assembled in a long time.
The kids, the adults, uh, Paul Rudd and Carrie Kuhn are both extremely
charming and sweet and they're great.
They're great.
Really, really good together and separately.
And the kids, uh, mechanic grace, I think is, you know, steals the whole movie.
She's so good.
She's awesome.
Not only good, but also suggests Egon, you know, in a, in a really cool way and
not an obvious way.
Like she, she's not doing an impression, but she does a really great job of kind
of just, you'd, but you totally buy her as, as 100 % podcast is really funny.
Yeah.
So then I also saw that like, uh, you know, people like, oh yeah, you'd all
like a movie where the, you know, a character's name podcast who gives a shit.
The kid is very charming and funny.
Is it corny that his name is podcast?
I don't know when he explained it.
I thought it was funny.
He was like, cause I have a podcast, you know, I'll give, I'll give my
biggest praise and my biggest criticism.
My biggest praise is, and this is a criticism against the criticisms I'm
hearing, everybody's going, huh, they really laid off the comedy in this one.
It's like, no, they didn't.
This is how comedy is supposed to be written.
Comedy is supposed to be character driven and funny because the
character is funny.
If you watch Seinfeld, I just listened to Fred, um, Fred Stahler's book,
my Seinfeld year, he talks about in the book, he goes, he goes, the prowess
of these performers that they're making this stuff, this funny when there
are no jokes on the page.
Correct.
Yeah.
And that's what comedy is.
It's like, there's nothing funny about, for instance, Ralph crammed in
screaming in his wife's face and then her saying, Oh, shut up.
But when you understand those characters and those characters are brought to
life by those actors, it's hilarious.
And that's what comedy is supposed to be.
That's what it used to be.
There's different types of comedy in a sketch.
You need gags.
You need things that are quippy and whatever.
People are so goddamn used to these cobbled together movies of a series of
sketches with gags and shit that character, these characters would never
do in real life.
It's just shit for a laugh.
Like, Oh, I know what we'll do.
We'll have a whole scene where everybody drinks X lax by accident and they all
have to shit that's got nothing to do with the characters.
It's just a dumb, stupid, jokey device.
So, or improv that go on for five minutes and do nothing to add to the story.
And so for that became the norm for a long time as well.
So I thought that'd be funny, but it also like, oftentimes you're going not
only off story, but off character as well and saying things that character
wouldn't say or do right.
So I thought this movie was very funny and in the right way.
My biggest criticism to it is I felt that unfortunately the ghost, the
old school Ghostbusters, it felt very tacked on.
It felt rushed and it didn't feel organic with the rest of the movie.
And I believe the reason for that again is COVID it's you can tell that Ernie
Hudson, Dan Aykroyd and Bill Murray, when they show up or shot on green screen.
Oh yeah.
They're not in the same room.
And it takes away so much from the special specialness of the moment.
It's just like, Oh, so this was just kind of hacked together somewhere.
So I think it's all COVID related.
You know, the end of the movie and also, and so, so, and then, but let's
get to the big criticism, the big problem that everybody has with it.
That it's just hitting the beats of the original movie.
Does it do that in the third act?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
However, I can tap out to the fact that we now have a new genre of movie, which
is we're going to reestablish the plot points of the first film so we can set
up sequels that go in a new direction.
Yeah.
The model here was force awakens for sure.
Yeah, I think they were like, basically let's just do the same thing and do it
in such a way that we can introduce this to a new generation while also paying
tribute to the old, and maybe we can make all kinds of movies and money off of it.
It just seems like that, that was the goal.
And to that end, they completely nailed it.
You know, was the, was the, um, the force awakens too much fan service.
Did people say that at the time?
I don't recall at the time.
No, everybody loved it.
Because it was, it was, it was one of the first times that that had happened.
Right.
And now it's happened a lot since then, but I, the people who generally
like fan service are fans.
That's, they like to go and cheer for things at the movies.
I mean, people are simple.
I'm sorry.
Well, but here's the thing too.
If fan service is done and delivered in a good package and great.
Right.
That's all.
If it works, it works.
If it doesn't work, it doesn't work in this movie.
It worked for me for the most part.
Um, for sure.
And like, what brand are you tarnishing really?
Like, you know, like I like, I like Ghostbusters.
I even like Ghostbusters too.
I've seen them both a lot of times.
It's just kind of like, do we re do we really care at this point?
Like, you know, that we're tar tar and they were even more
angry about the lady Ghostbusters.
It's like, let it go guys.
Like, you know, like those movies still exist, you know, is it a little sad
to see these guys come out and stand in front of a green screen and trade a
few pretty lazy quips among each other.
It's a little sad.
Um, but they were also kind of funny.
It was cute to see Bill Murray and Sigourney Weaver in the, in
the credits scene there.
So I think what this was, was you said force awakens and I agree.
Yeah.
Um, Winston says, I'm going to, when he, when he sees the car again, at the end,
he says, I'm going to fix you up and whatever.
I promise.
The last shot of the movie is the Ecto one driving across the bridge in
back into New York city, the camera focuses in on the car, the sirens are
going and for the first time, the original Ray Parker Jr.
Ghostbusters starts playing to me.
That is blatantly obvious that, and then you've got a post credit scene where
Winston goes back to the firehouse and reboots up the containment unit and
all that stuff.
So it's very obvious to me that what the second movie is going to be is
Winston leading the new Ghostbusters.
They're clearly giving, doing like a, um, they're, they're, they're doing a,
uh, giving a just due to the Ernie Hudson character because everybody always,
that was like a running joke was like the black Ghostbuster, the, you know,
he doesn't get to do anything and like, he's always a second afterthought or
whatever, but you think they're going to have just Ernie Hudson in the
sequel and not Morgan Akroyd.
They absolutely, I think they'll all three will be in it, but I think
it's going to be Winston in the field.
Winston's going to be like the Han Solo where he's like in the
field with the young people.
Right.
And then Murray and Akroyd are going to be like the princess Leia.
Maybe they're not out busting ghosts, but they're back at the
firehouse mapping shit out.
You know what I mean?
Right.
That's what I think.
I don't think I'd be excited to see that.
You know?
Yeah.
I don't think they put Sigourney in it just to be like, look, there she is.
I think they were like, no, no, no.
Like these characters are coming back.
Like Annie Potts shows up for a few minutes.
I don't think that was the end of Annie Potts's storyline.
Right.
So, um, and what about the ghost of Harold Ramis?
Will he be returning?
I don't think so, but I got, I got what I needed out of that.
And it went right up against making me cringe and it never did.
And I was like, they pulled it off, like, don't revisit that.
That whole five minutes where the Ghostbusters walked out.
And then when Ramis's ghost appeared, I was like, you could feel the whole
audience on the verge of just laughing, but also cheering.
It was a weird time in the, in the movie because it certainly doesn't work.
But then I did hear people sniffling around me with the ghost Egon, you
know, like it got to some people, but it was a huge swing, a huge swing.
Yeah.
And, uh, for me, the whole movie was charming enough that it pulled it off,
but I got to give most of the credit to everybody in this movie who was
not the original Ghostbusters.
They're the great work.
I agree, but I thought the grand slams were McKenna Grace and Paul Rudd.
Yeah.
Uh, I hope that Paul Rudd is, I obviously McKenna Grace will be
back because she's the heir to the.
I like Finn Wolfhard too.
I was saying he looks just like, uh, Julian Casablanca, but, uh,
he's funny.
I guess he's from stranger things, right?
Yeah.
He was good, but it was funny.
I was talking to my buddy about it.
I was like, he was almost an afterthought in this.
Like he was like the focus was not on him.
He was just kind of the dumb older brother, but I like, yeah, the star was
definitely the other two in a great way.
McKenna Grace and the podcast kid podcast kid had me laughing
so many times.
I gotta be honest.
I, I laughed more.
I wouldn't even consider it afterwards saying like, Oh, it was super funny.
But when I think back, I laughed more at it than probably any other
movie I saw this year, it was very funny.
My other gripe, uh, is that the end of the movie.
And again, this could have been due to COVID or whatever.
I felt like the end show, the set piece of the end was just nowhere near as
grand as it was in the original Ghostbusters, like them fighting
Gozer on a farm and sort of easily defeating her and her not calling out
other, like the state puff marshmallow man or any other minions, you know, it
just seemed like a lot easier for them to do this time, but it was, I had to
tell Joe also that goes, or was being played by Olivia wild.
I heard that's not true.
It is true.
She was in the credits.
Oh, okay.
I saw an article that said it wasn't true.
No, she's in those credits and she would know right man.
Yeah.
Can't believe anything you read anymore.
Nothing.
Thank news.
Um, uh, so I'm excited to see where it goes next.
I really am.
And, uh, I am too.
Well, you're describing with like Murray and Acroyd fat and sitting in, in chairs
and barking orders at the young Ghostbusters.
It sounds like a treat.
You know, I think that's, I honestly, I think that's what they'll do.
I loved seeing Acroyd again.
Yeah.
You know, I just, you know, he nails his one, you know, he gets a showcase
scene where he, he's the first Ghostbuster you see on screen.
And he are, you know, in the, in the present day.
And he does basically a monologue into the phone.
He's great.
And that seemed really, really good.
They all, they all came to play.
Um, it's just, yeah, the ending doesn't really leave you pumping your fist
quite the way you want, but I think in terms of launching a new franchise with
characters you like did a hell of a job.
I'm very relieved too, that the three of them were on.
Fallon and Murray was very vocally complimentary and
enthusiastic about the movie.
And I was like, Oh good.
That is a guy that will not play ball.
Right.
If he's not feeling it.
So I was like, okay, that's a great sign, man.
Like he was, he, you know, he was, and he was really funny and like,
and they were all great.
It was just great seeing them.
And I was like, this is, this is cool, man.
I hope, you know, I hope they do something again.
I hope it's successful.
And I think it's doing pretty well financially.
And the audience score is like 95 % on Rotten Tomatoes.
So we're seeing more and more of this where critics score is like 50 and
then the audience score is 95.
So right.
Or vice versa.
Um, but, uh, I'm curious to see where it goes and like, who knows, dude,
maybe they bring, you know, all those years, they were like, you know, Eddie
Murphy was supposed to be in it.
Like maybe Murphy's in it.
You know, like would be a dream.
I wanted more Annie Potts.
I mean, she came in that she got probably the biggest applause of the night.
Yeah.
That was great seeing her.
She looks like she's an aged hand.
All the designing women.
They really, they kept their kept their designs going.
I mean, Jean Smart looks fantastic.
Jeannie Smart.
I was, I was, I was one to meet Jean Smart.
I feel like she'd be like your favorite aunt.
Yeah, for sure.
Like, well, she's famous now.
She'd big time you.
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, folks, two hogs up.
Pretty much for sure.
Ghostbusters for Ghostbusters after life.
I think the people who didn't like it are really just kind of being
Scrooge's for no reason.
I mean, it's a, it's kind of, it feels a lot like the movies we used to
love going to the movies to see.
And maybe it's a little bit of a ripoff of them.
Fine.
It works.
It, you know, it's kind of like super eight, that movie, you know, like I saw
super eight, I was like, you didn't, didn't love it, but I love kind of having
that childhood feeling again, of going to a big franchise movie like this.
They actually care about the people.
And it worked.
It really enjoyed super eight.
I would have liked to have seen those kids back in a, you know, just like
we all said with the damn goonies, how the hell did they not make a goonie
sequel, what the fuck were they talking about it for 40 years?
I mean, my God, it's not like it was trying to get Pacino and
De Niro in the same movie.
Hey guys, it took us forever.
These are children for Christ's sakes.
How were they not like eight goonies movies?
Well, they could have easily done, you know, half the adults bring them back.
These guys are not people you have to pay a lot of money to, to get Martha
Plimpton and, you know, Sean Aston to come by the set and then you have the
parents and then the new goonies.
You know, I refuse.
I refuse to watch skinny chunk.
Jeff Cohen is in tremendous shape.
Now, uh, he's still having, well, you couldn't have the character of Chuck.
No, when I met him, when I first met Jeff Cohen, I was, you know, they were
like, yeah, that kid that played Chuck, he's a lawyer, my managers at the time.
They're like, we're going to introduce him.
I'm picturing in my head, a candy type.
Yeah.
You don't even, I'm picturing like this big guy coming into a suit, like
throwing them back, like a big person.
Right.
I'm talking to this kid for 30 minutes before I realized that he's
Jeff Cohen.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
Yeah.
So, you know, I, I need a, I need a heavier chunk.
Uh, and I don't know if you get, yeah.
Who would be the sloth would be 78 now, Jason Momoa.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
Look, we fixed his head.
Now he's gorgeous.
Now it'd be the other one.
Who's who's the one with even less charm than Jason Momoa, the bald one, Dave
Bautista, that's who would be chung.
No sloth, not Chuck sloth.
Sorry.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's it for us folks.
Uh, we were talking our next one.
I bet we're going to do the new matrix and I bet we're going to do video
drone and we're probably distance.
Yeah.
We can deep cover.
We're going to get to the new Guillermo del Toro.
I'm sure.
Well, don't forget to, these are our December 1st episodes.
We got to get some Christmas this next round.
We should probably have one or two Christmas through.
We always do a Christmas one.
We'll, we'll figure one out.
Yeah.
So, um, we'll be back at you folks mid month, but thanks for listening.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.