Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to, we'll see you in hell your favorite horror movie sci -fi and fantasy podcasts where
we review, discuss and commentate on films and television shows of the stated genres.
was we're here. It is late. It is about 11 p .m. our time on a Saturday night. And I think
it's time we just get this damn show on the road pass. We start with a bit of tension
in the air as Joe and I actually recorded this podcast hours ago. Then after we were done
with it. Joe played it back to realize the sound was hopelessly garbled and you could
not understand what was being said. Wasted an hour of my life, frankly.
And now we're re -recording it after we went to a, well, I mean, we drank all through the
first recording. Then we went to a lengthy dinner, drank all through that. Now we're back
at 6 p .m. about how tired I was just bone tired right now I've eaten a large meal I've had
three to four strong drinks and I really don't want to be doing it but maybe we'll find
something beautiful from this pain that we're going through I was mulled by a dog earlier
tonight outside of Joe's apartment very bizarre dog just ran out of nowhere and started biting
my arm do you ever think it's maybe it's something about you of course I thought that I mean
I mean, it was so strange.
Not only was I not provoking it,
I had my back to it and was like looking at my phone,
sitting on the curb.
And this dog went out of its way to just run at me
and bite me.
And that's not the first time.
I had a poker game I went to where the dog tore through my pants
and blood was pouring out the cuff of my pants.
Like, in all fairness.
I'm provoked.
In all fairness, you are wearing the Alpo jacket.
You got when they sponsored you in the Indy.
Yeah, and the Indianapolis 700.
And it's not just, you know, the Alpo logo on the pocket.
It's a jacket made of Alpo dog food.
Yeah, a mistake, probably, but here we are.
We went to a, so we recorded, we're talking
about the Halloween franchise this week,
because it was just previously Halloween.
and you know the franchise is about to start back up again and you know it just
seemed like a good thing to do was Pat's suggestion and I agreed with it I
had just seen how the original on the big screen on Halloween night which was
fun so that's what we're talking about this week and we as Pat said already
recorded the episode earlier and the goddamn thing didn't come this happened on
emotional hangs recently too we recorded a whole episode and then we went and
listen to it. And it sounded like, like almost like if you were lost on an island and you
had a walkie talkie and you were desperately trying to communicate. Right. And on like
in between channels, you heard somebody being like, come in, come in, you know, like one
of those things. Yeah. That's what it sounded like. It sounded bad. So we had to ditch it. It
friend David and we went to dinner with him.
That's Hollywood's David Crumholz phone.
Yes.
Ever heard of the judge?
He's in it.
What was he in the judge?
I saw it.
He's the lawyer at the beginning when Robert Denny Jr.
Oh yeah.
If you didn't see the judge, that film is basically, if Iron Man was a lawyer, yeah.
That's basically the movie.
There's a small town in the south.
Yeah.
They're like, let's just pretend this is an Iron Man movie,
except you never see him dress up as Iron Man.
This is just kind of Tony Stark, me and Tony Stark.
And I believe Robert DuVal pisses his pants in it, correct?
In the actual film, was this behind the scenes, folks?
No, in the film, I'm pretty sure at some point,
Robert DuVal pisses pants, because I remember being like,
DuVal doesn't need to be playing the characters
pissing his pants.
It made me very sad.
Why does he, he's because he's old and senile
and these budding heads with downy and bloat.
Seenile is not a term we use anymore.
Why not?
It's just not a term anymore.
It's not like...
It's not like baddie?
No, yeah, you say it's that dizzy old damn.
Yeah, no, it's not like a medical term.
It's dementia, Alzheimer's.
Dementia sounds goonier to me than Seenile.
Seenile, it's not, I don't think it was ever deemed derogatory.
It was just a term where they were like,
like it's not an accurate medical term.
I think.
Now Pat, far be it for me to doubt anything I'm saying right now
after the night we've had.
Yeah.
Because I'll tell you,
I'm also four, five strong drinks in.
Yeah.
We've had a little bit of the wacky
don't have to tell them.
To back heat.
Don't have to tell them.
It's legal here, it's fine.
I know.
I have a card.
And I have chosen to have another whiskey while we record this.
I'm sitting this round out so I don't fall asleep.
Yeah.
But are you upset that I told him about the wacky tobacco?
No, not at all.
Okay, good.
Folks, before we get too far into this, I think we should probably pause briefly to get on with the show.
oh and in doing so on w -i -t -h -t -h -e -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o
It was fun. It was kind of like noises off, but you know, my George, my favorite George Lucas movie is red tails.
Never saw reds. Did you direct red tails?
Now he just produced it, but like that was the one where he's like, I'm done. Yeah, like it was, you know, it was a shame because there's a good story about
the black fighter pilots in World War II, but like he couldn't, he had a hard time getting funding and I don't think anybody saw it.
Did you ever see noises off?
yeah I did when I was in college it's a well it's a great play of course I play I was in at one
point which now which role did you play in it I played the John Ritter role okay now did you do
that fall down the stairs like he does in the movie yes but I I think the movie is really really
funny especially to be directed by Peter Bogdanovich who is not a man known for his sense of humor I like
that movie. But wait, you did that fall down the steps. I fell down the stairs. How did you do that?
I didn't, I probably probably didn't look as good as John Ritter, but I just fell down a fly
of stairs. You didn't hurt yourself. That's a very hard thing. You can't hurt yourself when you're
sick. That's a very hard thing to do. Yeah. Well, I'm a skilled actor. Well, why do you bring up
noises off? Because the radio land murders had a similar vibe, a lot of doors slamming and etc.
And I think that they're both kind of good fun Oscar has a similar vibe which is a very underrated movie as well
Stallone's Oscar soap dish. I would throw into this category wrong. They're farce Fraziery Fraziery
I'll tell you what I throw John candy's delirious into this into this mix. You ever see once upon a crime
You know
When I was a kid
There's not a movie. I wanted to see more. I never got around to it
It's not great now looking back. I'm thankful because I also felt that way about nothing but trouble
And then I finally saw that I was like, oh god, what have I would like?
Well nothing but trouble has sort of a traffic accident feel where you're kind of like
To me, it's better than Delirious or
Once upon a crime because it's just such a train wreck. It's more interesting to watch see I like Delirious
You don't like Delirious. I don't know. Why not?
Yeah, just like real bottom of the barrel candy shit.
I mean, I, well, see, to me, Canadian bacon is when you're getting,
that's fucking sucks.
Down low, but Michael Moore did Canadian bacon.
Yeah.
I like the lyrics.
I like the guy from happiness, like,
falling apart from the radioactive exposure.
Yeah, like that too.
Uh, it's funny watching John Candy be like the sort of like 007 character
where I like he's like that
watch who's Eric chrome
Then you know at least she'll laugh all right. I mean, I like I like Muriel Hemingway
Terrible Jerry were Bach no interest. You don't like Jerry or Bach never did he does he that by the way
This is my chair squeaking it's a most squeaky chair Jerry or Bach does
Confirm folks when I'm
Unconfirmed
What
What am I saying?
Are you okay over there?
Yeah.
You're all right.
Jerry Hormach does.
What are my favorite movie gags ever?
Come on.
In Delirious.
All right.
One of your favorite movie gags ever is in Delirious.
I'm not saying his version is my favorite.
I'm saying it's a gag that I always am a sucker for when they do it.
And I've talked about it before in this podcast.
It's when he's on the,
He's talking John candy out of the room
Because John candy's all nervous about the script and Jerry or backs like the producer of the show
And he's going it will be fine. We love you. You're our favorite and John can he's like
Okay, as long as you tell me to be fine. He's like it'll be great. It'll be great
John he's thank you. Thank you. All right. That makes me feel better. Thank you
And then Jerry or Bach shuts the door and he turns around and he goes schmuck
I always like that gag, that gag makes me laugh every time.
Would it work for any word but smuck?
I think schmuck is the best word for it, you know.
Schmuck.
So, what's your favorite movie gag?
Like what's one of those, you know, the old classic?
Yeah, like you've seen it a million times.
Like the judge gets up, he's got no pants on.
You know, he's one of those things.
I do always enjoy a, uh, when, when they'll knock a service person out and then the next
scene be wearing their clothes.
Most famous example, of course, is the naked gun and Rico Palazzo.
I just named my production company and Rico Palazzo.
You were terribly.
But I just like that.
You karate chop someone.
They fall to the ground unconscious.
And you wear their clothes and they fit better on you than they did on them.
Well, the double the double gag is when the clothes fit terribly.
Right. That's always really great.
I've seen a lot of variations. Austin Powers did some I think.
Yeah. I like that.
Delirious, he was a soap opera writer who starts to fantasize that he's in the show.
Well, he's in love with. He's in love with Mario Hemingway who's auditioning for this part.
the network. Oh, no, no, I'm sorry. He's not. He's in love with the lady from, yeah,
she's like a soap opera actress. And she's Susan Loci. Yeah, I think he's in, like,
in love with, I think it's Susan Loci, right? He's in love with her, but she's, I'll think
it's Susan Loci. It's not. It's definitely not Susan Loci. You fully agreed with me. No,
it's Susan Sarandon, I believe plays the part in the film. Anyway, he's in love with
her, she like strings him along, she suck her own cues.
I think it's who it is.
It's psychotic that you know the actor's name.
I'm gonna look.
If I'm right, I'm gonna be very excited.
I mean, that's, that's real.
Do you know the cues or something?
Go on, go on.
Anyway, he's in love with her.
She's the star of the show.
She strings him along.
She knows that she can manipulate him
because he's in love with her
and she gets him to write the show basically around her
into her liking.
Gotcha.
and then he gets into an accident, she screws him over,
there's supposed to go away for the weekend
and he's furious and he's driving
and speeding up to this cabin alone without her
because she's left him to hang once again
and he gets into a car accident
and then he ends up in his own soap opera
that he hates because of the way everybody's making him write.
Gotcha.
And then he starts to write it from the inside
And it's actually a very cool idea. It's just it's not the actress was Emma Sam's
That's right Emma Sam's and then also you know who else is it is sledgehammer David rash. Yeah
From a very very funny and burn after reading. I love burn after reading. I do tell so much. I do tell so much
I was walking around my house today going. I had a drinking problem
Uh, fuck you, Walsh.
You're Mormon compared to you.
Everybody has a drinking problem.
That's, uh, that's a very funny scene.
Yeah.
His name's not Walsh in the movie.
I just said it because I couldn't think of his name.
I don't know what his name is.
You want to do a Pat's movie corner?
I, I will say yes, but I haven't seen anything.
I, nothing.
I've been extremely busy.
Hence, hence my extreme tiredness.
I watched, I'm still enjoying the new season of curb. I think it's funny folks. I think
it's taken a meaner turn, but these are meaner times. Other than that, I'm up till six
on a strange of things. I'm finding it okay, but it's losing me. Every time I started I
fall asleep. I've heard seven is a real low point. And that's the one I got coming up next.
A lot of people hated seven. Seven's the one where she's like training. I ain't saying that. I don't know.
I liked Stranger Things quite a bit. I finished it. I won't spoil anything, but I will say it is
certainly the Empire Strikes Back of the series. So far, at least, it's definitely more of an
emotional story. And I did like how the characters were sort of going off on
their own emotional journeys. I really liked it. I thought it was great. And I
really came to care immensely about the characters. Like I fell in love with
Sean Astin's character. I like him. Bob the brain. I really fell in love with the
Steve character. The kids I already loved and then you just love them even more. I
really like Max the new character. She's great. I like the guy that plays her
brother. I just, you know, I really enjoyed the show. I got really into the characters.
All right. And I wept uncontrollably at the finale.
Okay. Because I was so touched by it all. I was just a depiction of innocence that I had,
if I could be honest, I have lost complete touch with at this point in my life. Was this a
It's not a cry, a wet cry, an embarrassing cry.
No, it wasn't a snot cry, it was a,
it was a real dad cry, like the kids
to see the tears, but they're coming down
and you know they're there.
But now why here alone would you need to hide it?
Well, have you ever blubbered on your couch alone?
It's not a great feeling.
I've done it.
But why not?
It should be a great feeling you're letting out a lot of sadness. I don't know if you are aware of that
But I am not in touch with my emotions nor am I but I'm saying if you're sitting on the couch and they start to flow
Why not just be like oh good? I can I let them go as much as I felt comfortable with
But I feel that all people can see everything I'm doing at all times and they're judging it
Well, Jesus can well, yeah, and he's a son of a bitch as well
Whoa, folks, I'm kidding for you religious people. I'm joking. Oh your mother fuckers. Um, I have some Pat's movie corner stuff
Before before I forget folks, I'd like to tell you a dinner tonight. Joe who was a little high
David orders a
Prime rib. What is it pork chop?
And he goes, I'd like it, he goes, he goes, should I get the pork chop or the steak?
And they go, I like the steak.
He goes, all right, I'll get the steak, but I'll get it medium rare.
And then Joe says, I'll have the pork chop.
And then he looks up, his craze is looking at his face.
And he goes, not medium rare.
And the waiter looked horrified.
And neither the waiter or me or David so much a smile and Joe like buried his face in the menu ashamed and embarrassed
I was out for the rest of the meal. I didn't really speak again, but it was a huge swing and a huge miss
Yeah, it made sense in my head in my head. It was a great bit. Yeah, it was a closing of the episode freeze frame Joe
right uh and it just was not that when it came out no you know not medium rare very bad joke
uh I also led the meal tonight my appetizer was a slice of blueberry cheesecake folks I don't
know how I buried the lead on this one Joe as an appetizer ordered a piece of cheesecake before that's
before the meal. I don't know. All right, take us, take us through. No, hold on, hold on. All right.
And Walsh is giving me shit. He goes, he goes, you know, I thought we were going to share the
Gator bites because it's fucking restaurant has a thing called Gator. On the way there, Joe said,
I'm going to get those Gator bites. They're delicious. And it is actually alligator meat that is
battered and fried and then they give you some sort of a Russian mixed with ranch dressing to dip in it heavy on the
Chives whatever it is it's Chive heavy so I decided to last minute you know I'm gonna get this cheesecake first
I'm you know we're a little stone. I like a little sweet tooth action
Then then after pets give me shit it goes he goes who gets a cheesecake is an appetizer
I say who gets a gator bites as an appetizer never see them to menu my wife folks gator bites
have been ordered by me and Joe there before.
They're delicious.
Joe said he wanted them tonight
and they're on the list of appetizers.
Yeah, not only that, but the special appetizers.
Yeah, but they tossed that cheesecake out at us
and I was like, I gotta get this.
It was a stressful thing.
We got in there.
Look, let's be honest.
I didn't want to smoke weed.
Yeah.
My friends pressured me into it.
I said, I don't want to smoke weeds.
We're gonna get this restaurant.
I'm gonna get all weird.
they said shut the fuck up yeah be a grown up they slap me in the face a couple
times I hit Joe with a phone book at one point at one point grab my dick and
yell this declares ownership the way like Kevin Spacey did that guy in the
bar uh -huh and uh he's right that what he said he grabbed the guy's dick in a bar
and he goes this dictates ownership wow I guess it's not funny sorry but then the guy
I said he had PSTD or PTSD for six months because of it.
It's like, buddy, he shouldn't have done that.
But are you comparing this to watching your friends face
get blown off in a fucking fox hole?
Yeah.
I mean, we can't minimize it, but like...
I don't want to admit, I'm not...
The amount of time someone on the subway like grabbed my dick
and I was like, eh, you're not traumatized.
I'm not minimizing anything.
Kevin's basically shouldn't have done it.
It's wrong that he did it.
But to say I had literally PTSD. Yeah, which is what soldiers who are an awful war combat hat
It's like come on buddy. Like Sue unless he twisted the dick unless his fingers cupped a balls into a taint
Situations. I don't know. I don't know
Probing grab Andy dick now on the dick grabbing Andy Dicks
been
and widely known sexual offender for decades.
The anti -dick story. Keep working.
I keep talking about is that he,
when the time he was on Stern, he had a black eye.
Yeah. And Stern's like, why do you have a black eye?
And he's like, I, I grabbed Wesley Snipes
his dick at a bathroom and he punched me in the face.
Yeah, that's crazy.
And they were just like, all laughing.
They were like, you're an idiot.
What, why'd you do that?
He's like, I don't know, it was, I'll be funny.
So he made a move on a writer on my show, you're the male writer on my show a few years back and he was like,
sorry man, I'm married and I'm not interested. Thank you. And he goes,
are you really not serious about your comedy career? Oh boy.
Literally. Oh boy. Oh Andy, it's going to take you to the top. Oh Andy, don't be a dick.
Spacey. I mean, they stopped that fucking thing on a dime. Yeah. Like how they were like,
We're gonna stop production on this show in three years and everyone calls them out and they're like
All right, well, I guess we'll stop production now. Well, you don't get credit now
And by the way Kevin Spacey, I don't approve of what you did at all
I don't condone it, but thank you for being a pervert so I don't ever have to fucking hear about how I need to watch house of lies
Ever again cards cards. What's the other one? Oh, that's the Cheatle one house lies is one of the worst shows until the house of cards
first few years the house of cars are very entertaining I don't give a shit I'm tired of people telling me I have to watch it
It's riveting and all this shit. It's kind of riveting. It's god. It's gone. I'm glad. It's gone
I tell you the only house of cards now is this gentleman's career
Sounds like he wasn't playing with a full dick
I don't remember how it came up.
I do.
I finally remember it and I remember why it was food.
Okay.
It was in the movie Grandma with Lily Tomlin.
Bad movie.
Where they go to Sam Elliott's house and for some reason the scene is him going through
You want some corn. Yeah, and he feeds them corn on the cob and some dried tomatoes. Yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah, anyway
I'm the wind whistling through his mustache
So
Where were we why how did we get off on the Kevin Spacey?
We were oh, you were talking about the PTSD and the grabbing of the dick. No, no, but before
Oh, you grabbed my dick. I said, Oh, you made me smoke weed. That's what it was. Right. Yeah, you forced me to do it
Not true at all. I we're like, come on man
Once and you're like, okay, and then we go to this restaurant and from the jump everything in the restaurant was everything
I was afraid would happen
We had to stand at the host station for way too long forever
whatever. Being ignored by multiple waitstaff, they wouldn't see us. Terrible service
throughout. Damans in Glendale. It's such a fun place. They really whiffed it tonight.
It was a bunch shop. Then I go to the bathroom. I'm standing there and there's like a line
of people and the guy in front of me turns and goes, hey, I think the men's room's open.
They go, okay, aren't you in line? He goes, no, none of us are waiting for the bathroom.
So then it's it's weird. There's like a line of people just hanging around outside the bed
I didn't understand that then you go back to the table the waiter's taking forever. Then my god damn
Rare not medium rare joke bombs. It was it was a rough night. I just checked out at that point. Yeah
Uh
I got nothing else for pets movie corner. I
Haven't watched in perfect strangers. We don't need to talk about it again
What's the what's the best app I need to watch?
It's either season five or season six premiere where Larry lies to his girlfriend, Jennifer,
that he's an amazing roller skater because he wants to be impressed for the fundraiser
that the airline is holding where it's a skate -a -thon and that's how he tries to impress
me.
And he's never skated, but he makes up a story where he says, you know, when I was in high
school, they used to call me wheels.
And then the whole episode is it like a dramatic monologue? I hope no
Not at all and then the girlfriends leave and Bucky goes
Cuz and you need to teach me how to skate and he's like, okay, let's put the skates on
They do and then Bucky goes what next and then Larry goes. I don't know. I've never had a pair of skates on my life
Uh -huh
And then the whole episode is Larry's plan that if they just wear the skates everywhere they go
So they'll be able to learn how to skate to impress Jennifer for the fundraiser, okay.
And then of course he wins the fundraiser and she goes, you raised the most money out
of everybody.
Later you did it and then he goes, Jennifer, it was never a competition and it was, it's
your typical perfect stranger's episode, I'll watch.
Your typical perfect stranger things episode.
What is the worst thing Larry Appleton has done on perfect strangers?
like meanest or like the dumbest, the meanest, the one where he goes to the seminar that teaches
him to be assertive and then his girlfriend cancels plans and he's like, I'll tell you this
right now, don't you don't do this ever again or you're out of here, Missy. And she leaves and then
back he's like, you were just really rude to your girlfriend. And he's like, no, don't you get it,
people like it when you talk to them that way, especially women. That's the one where he kind of goes
off the deep. Okay. But it's like funny because it all comes blows up in his face. It's not
like he just gets it's not like he just gets away with being an ass or something. Right.
I have something for Joe's scary stuff. And for once did you get it right? Well, I think I might
have known you did because we recorded this episode already. John Carpenter's anthology on vinyl.
It's a collection of John Carpenter's most famed movie themes, Halloween,
other ones, big troubles, little China. And it's very cool. They even like dark star and
shit. They have like all these themes and I think they're re -recorded with his band, which is like his
son. I've always found the title dark star troubling. It sounds like a porno. It sounds like a
Um, but it's great. I got on a vinyl is like 18 bucks and you listen to these themes. It's great writing music great Halloween music
Check it out
Uh, I got a video game uh, during the sale of the dead on the ps4 network. If you remember they offered
Uh, uh, extremely discounted prices on video games all month
Uh, that were horror themed
I got a game called the Order 1866.
It came out about three years ago, it was released to very lukewarm reviews, which
is why I never bought it.
It went on for the sale of the dead last week.
They were selling this thing for, I think it was $4 .99 and I was like, well, I'm going to
buy that because I always wanted to play it and you can't beat $4 .99.
I got to tell you folks, one of the most striking, visually striking games I've ever played
to my life. It's one of the coolest story lines. It's the steampunk thing where you're
a knight in this sacred order, and then you find out that the order is the Knights of
the Round Table, which is descended down from King Arthur, and you're there because there
are lichens in the city, and you have to hunt down the lichens, and it's cinematic and beautiful
and so well acted. Voice and facial capture is truly just remarkable. And then you go
to these action sequences where you're like doing like Gears of Worship, like ducking
behind multiple, you know, boxes and walls and whatever to take cover and having like
shootouts with guys that are going to turn into werewolves sporadically. It's fucking awesome.
is awesome I don't understand why this game didn't get better reviews uh order it
yeah and I think when it's not on sale it's still only like 20 bucks which why is it called
1866 that makes me think like I'm gonna watch something about the old west takes place in the year 1866
but not the old west no it takes place in London excuse me sorry uh I only like the old west
I like well red dead redemption two is coming out and that's gonna be pretty insane
Is that a zombie one?
No, it'll probably be like a zombie bonus thing,
but that's an old West game, and that's gonna be awesome.
But I like, you know, sort of 1800s,
that's not Victorian, right?
What is that?
What era do you call that?
That's not Renaissance?
What is that?
Or is that Renaissance?
No, it's definitely.
Renaissance are like the 1500s.
Or 1866.
Whatever.
I like 1800s in England.
I always think that looks very cool. It looks like it's coming. It's just getting out of, you know, sort of a Christmas carol
Sure, and that's a story in England. It is Victorian. I said I can't remember if I said that anyway
It's a great game. Go get Renaissance
Well, and then I said another one too, but I can't remember what the other one was that I said
Then I called 1866. It's called order 1886. Oh 1886. This chair is really noisy. Sorry guys
1886. Alright I'll get it. I thought it was 1866. I mean sue me Pat you know
what do you want? Well you're recommending something. It's not that hard to
find you type in PlayStation the Order and that's why I was typing in 1866 and I
got no results. Well I don't know why you would do that. Because that's all I
remembered from the name of the game. That's like sort of the sub -look. Let's get
to the movie. You made the error. Folks, the movies we're discussing today are the Halloween
franchise. One, two, three, four, Halloween five, Halloween six, H2O, Resurrection, Rob
Um, and then, you know, the on the horizon, the dynamic bride, uh, new version of Halloween
with Jamie Lee Curtis, which is about, uh, Michael Myers returning back to kill and
telling everybody how great of a murderer he was at one point.
Yes.
Uh, but now he's lost it all and nobody respects him right and he's pitching, I think, which
is weird.
Yeah.
Still wearing the mask.
All right.
I'm glad you got what I was doing with it.
I did.
it took a second. For me there's one classic movie out of the entire franchise and that's Halloween
one. To me there's one above average movie out of the entire franchise and it's Halloween one.
Beyond that, my favorite is probably three because it's the most interesting. It veers off the
beaten path. I like two, four and five. I almost forgot that I've seen H2O is really fun.
resurrection is terrible. Zombie won. I liked, even though it was repellent and I hated watching
it. I kind of liked how scuzzy it was. And I hated that he killed that janitor. The janitor
who was nice to, it made me depressed. And then Halloween 2 is worse than that. It's not a
great franchise. Frankly. I think you're being harsh. I think you're being way
harsh. All right. Now I'll tell you something about your precious Halloween one.
Please do. It's a good movie. But I saw it on the big screen the other night and
I'll tell you, there's a lot of flaws in the movie. Go through them. There's a lot
of flaws in the movie. First of all, Laurie Strode's best friend, whatever that
character's name is, gets a lot of center stage time. And just she's just a
terrible actor and the whole movie she's just being like,
you just need to get some dick in your pussy, Laurie.
That's like her whole character and she's not a good actor
and she gets so much stage time and it's crazy.
You didn't like that she was a modern woman
with a sexual appetite all around her.
I don't care for it, act like a little lady.
All right?
She's talking about I wanna go have a career.
Yeah, here's your career.
Cook me some eggs.
Sure, sure.
No, I just didn't she's just a bad actor like it's not good. So that bug me
There's also stuff in the movie that's shot extremely well, and then there's stuff that's not shot that well
It's like it's like you know the scene where she's trying to get out of the one the Jamie Lee Curtis trying to get out of a door
And there's like a rake stopping the door from over. It's like come on like
You know, so there is a lot of that sort of old school
Shooting and editing in it where it's just like well if we just cut back and forth between the bad guy and the good guy
That'll be suspenseful and it's like not really I think Halloween is very
Suspense I'm not saying it's not in places. I'm just saying that it's not this perfect gem of a film
And you frankly don't know how heavy that rate was it's it's got its flaws. Yeah, it's got its flaws
And this is all I'll say it all among us doesn't this is all I'll say about those flaws
I think it is
Arguable that one or two is the better of the movies. It's that that's all I get why people like one more
I get why people like two more
I like two more because it's sort of like the the the slicker version of one
it just kind of hits the ground running and and
You know, it's there was more at stake. So the acting overall is just better. I believe
You know, one feels like a very indie low budget 70s film, which is great. It's not bad. I'm just saying I can get why people like one versus the other.
All right.
Three I like quite a bit, you know.
It's for everything you said.
It shouldn't have been a Halloween movie, but it's very cool.
Should have been because that was Carpenter's original vision was every movie was going to have a different Halloween story
Okay, so the first one was a serial killer the second one was going to be something completely different like
There was going to be an anthology series and in the studio the first one was so successful. They're like you have to do a sequel, right?
So I like Halloween three. I mean, it's Batchit our friend Ken Hanley formerly of Fangoria
He thinks three is the best one. I
Can't agree with that
that over the first two, but I understand why three would appeal to somebody, and I like
it. It's just a little, it's a little too nonsensical. There's a lot of real logic
holds in it, but it's fun to watch. I like four quite a bit. It was a return to form.
It was a return to the Michael Meyer story. Five to me is just a worse version of four, and
And five is where the full on directive video business started.
So did it really not go to the edge of the release following for did limited I believe
and then five I think went directive I think.
But why if these movies were such hits I thought well because back then it was like you
know there was two levels of successful there was there was theater successful and then there
was also you're talking about a time when movies in the theater you get Jurassic Park and
like that in the theaters. You know what I mean? They're making gazillions of dollars and it's,
you know, it's not like now where these low -budget things can go into the theater.
Right. But yeah, five was just sort of a worse version of four. Six is dog shit.
Yeah. Six is where they try to say that Michael Myers, you know, the cause of his violent nature,
is some old like, I think American Indian curse
or something like that.
Has that ever been a good idea?
Has it ever been a good idea to just go,
that is like on the Stephen King wheel of reasons
for things happening like?
I love Stephen King, I like his stories,
but some of his stories, you're reading them,
you're like, he just spun his wheel
where he's like, what's causing this?
A giant spider, okay, you know what I mean?
Like, that, we get to burn his tool
was voodoo. We get a burst of voodoo, uh, Michael Meyer's six voodoo, uh, were, were ancient
magic curse. Freddie is dead the final nightmare, ancient evil, ancient curse. Jason goes to
hell, ancient evil, ancient, it's never good. And John Carpenter said about the first film.
He's like, look, here's the thing. He's a mysterious evil. He kills the sister. Why? We don't know.
It doesn't matter. You just know that that's what he did. Right. And that makes you question what his nature is and then you have an interesting story. That's
Any time you know they have what the Matrix movies once they started explaining everything people were like, dude, fuck off, man
I don't look I even like the Star Wars prequels as you all know I get shit for constantly
But they did it with those two where they're like every wonder where Darth Vader came from everybody's like, not really
You know, so
So six really sucks ass, H2O though, great jump back. Kevin Williamson and his prime coming
right off of the Dawson's Creek and the faculty fame.
Just to watch it every week Dawson's Creek.
I'm never like the faculty.
I'm never not a fan of Michelle Williams or Jared Lido.
No, that's not Jared Lido.
What's that kid's name?
Pacey.
James Vanderby.
No, no, no, no, in James Van der Biggs, don't listen to Joshua Jackson. No, I know an H2O
Josh Hartnett Josh Hartnett. Yes, don't like him. I love him. Why don't you like him?
He's just a very sleepy actor
Isn't that incident to be trying you mean as opposed to the
Electric performance you're giving right now not an actor. I mean granted I portrayed Ben Frywater in
Episode nine of season one of Showtime's Rody's directed by Cameron Crowe. What's there season two?
no. No false of mine. And I read the reviews. They said despite
Walsh's turn in the episode nine. Yeah, where it didn't get renewed. I was
very good on it. Now what was your character? Ben Frywater, I was the manager of the
band Fanta Graham. Okay. Who are real bad? Great band. Love them. And I come in and
they're unhappy with the way the stage is set up for a charity event. And I scream
in a woman's face about how it's not up to code okay it was great and then I'm right
there with fanogram all right oh I get Ben fry water and no I guess I would have missed
the any cutoff now did you study the real life brand fry water for a few weeks he was not
a real person so Cameron really gave me the space to create okay and I I mean believe me I took
that space what would a man in this position do that sort of thing exactly I got you
Now, I did live for about 18 months as a music talent manager.
Right.
Unbeknownst to the musicians themselves.
So, for 18 months, I would kind of shadow a lot of big music executives all on preparation
of this role where I made, you know, $900 for about four hours of work.
I also heard that you would sleep in a hammock in the studio just to stay in the in the sort of zone of the whole thing
I always do that. Yes. Yeah. I
Carry a hammock around you know wash. I often say we're not paid to act anymore. No, and we paid to wait
Yeah, is what I say and when a director gives you that yeah, yes
Unwrap it. Yeah, exactly. I couldn't say it better myself and I for me
acting as playing
thing. You know, and I'll get right out there in the sandbox with my tools, my tools being
my craft, my talent, my experiences that I bring to each role. And I got to tell you
when somebody else steps into that sandbox with me, hand me a shovel and a pale body because
because I'm ready to play.
And that's how I see acting.
And you might get a little dirty.
I think you're not doing it right
if you don't, right?
Yeah, I would just like to say right now,
and many people I admire, I've heard say this since.
Yeah, but I'm still gonna say this.
If you're ever somebody that's under the words,
I get to go to work and play.
Yeah, fuck you.
Can you believe we get paid for this?
I just, I play all day, that's my job.
I just play yeah shut the fuck up. Yeah
Not because you're not playing fine. You're playing you're just only an idiot shut your idiot fucking mouth
Idiot. Yeah
What are you rank of Mike Myers with a Michael Myers with a Freddie and a Jace?
Freddie's always going to be my number one kind of pin heads always going to be my number
two my side piece if you will so you need them to talk I like I like a talker
sure I like I like a talker in the bedroom yeah you know I mean right I mean you know
You know, you bring Michael Myers up there.
He lays there like a dead fish.
However, try to do a little finger in the butt action
with Freddie Krueger.
You're gonna wind up bleeding out.
The man's got sharp knives for fingers.
You will get a little bleed out,
but you're also gonna get a nice pun to go along with it.
What's that?
Huh?
You know, he'll be like,
talk about a rectal exam.
Oh sure.
Yeah, one of those things.
Rectum, I damn near killed him. That's what it should be. Yeah, something like that. Yeah
From one asshole to another. There you go. That's it. That's it. That's perfect. I got some ults for it
This is why you do what you do. You're good at it. That's right from one asshole to another
That's very good. Oh, thank you. That's very good. And I'm very tired. I want to say again
He was flowing out.
Pithead's gonna be my second in command, though.
Always.
Now Joe, let me ask you, why did you tell Jeremy Piven
to do what he did on the set of on drums and beyond?
I wanted to bring him down.
Okay.
I wanted to bring him down and I didn't believe in him.
I didn't believe in his work.
Yeah.
And I knew that he was probably just dumb enough
to do something insane.
He did.
I have talks, I'm pretty sure on this podcast about people
I know who were sexually harassed by Jerry Piven about him and warning you if you hook up with him
He'll only do it in the butt and all this kind of stuff. I've heard. Well, that was Grenier actually
But folks by the way, I didn't allegedly I didn't tell Jeremy Piven to do anything. It's a joke
It's a joke. I feel like we need to state that right now. Wait, you didn't tell him as you asked. I don't know Jerry Piven
I've never spoken to Jerry
I did meet him once. He was smoking a cigar and drinking cognac and he didn't really talk to me
Yeah, and he didn't do anything inappropriate that one time that I met him
But all right, at least while I was there, so that's pretty good, you know, but
Yeah, it's you know, it's you know see see you later pivvon
I guess yeah, see you later spacey
See I'm gonna go
Freddie see I don't like Freddie though
Why I don't like Freddie why not I don't like looking at him
I think he's corny.
He wasn't corny.
He was fucking scary and awesome,
which is why I got mad when everybody hated the remix so much.
I was like, look, at least they made Freddy scary again,
like, it's not like Goddamn one -liners and shit.
So did New Nightmare, though.
New Nightmare is great.
I think two is good.
He's scary and two.
And three is where it starts to, three's good,
but three is where it really is teetering.
Right.
They're pushing it in three and then four five and six are where you know, I I'll watch the movies
But that's where it really goes off into like pun zone sure into the pun zone, but I'm
Who do you like better than Frank? I mean if look if you're gonna talk about the coolest one
It pinhead is the coolest. He says the coolest shit. He's the scariest
You know, he's like I'm gonna take you just hell and rip your skin off with these hooks
Sure, and he says really great stuff, you know, we have such sites to show you. Sure
You're suffering will be legendary even in hell, you know, like those are really scary things to say to somebody
And you know, I would say them my mom sometimes I'd sneak into a room at night and I'd wake her up
And I would just whisper that in her ear to see how she'd react
My favorite is probably the lady in the water from the film lady in the world. Yeah, that's probably my favorite
Bryce Dallas Howard. Yes. I'll tell you she's not half as scary as her father on set.
No, why is that? I don't know. I'm just making a joke that you like yells on. I don't fucking know.
Ron Howard. Could you imagine a nicer seaming guy to wear a word? It seems like there'd be never a
problem with it. You're excited about Ron Howard's solo. Yeah, of course. Star Wars.
I just thought Christopher Lloyd was a weird choice. As Han Solo? As a young Han Solo.
I mean, I don't get that at all, but I hope he does a good job.
Jupiter!
Yeah.
I need you to fix the engine on the Millennium Falcon.
I'm young.
At the end of every line.
I swear I'm not a day over 18.
Halloween resurrection.
What's around this out?
Go on we already did a whole episode about this one it fucking sucks ass
It is the low point of the series. It is worse than even though there was rob zombie movies and I hate the rob zombie
Halloween's but at least
They have a plot that makes sense and
They're not
Cash grabs in the sense that they're just putting celebrity cameos in the whole thing right
Halloween resurrection is a fucking dog show it betrays h2o
it's terrible and you know and we've talked about this as well I'm very excited for the McBride one
okay I'm excited for Jimmy Lee Curtis's return I'm excited to see what they do with it as a
sequel to the first movie to see if Lori's is his sister still or not and I'm excited that Carpenter's
coming back to score and I believe produce you know so I think it's gonna be pretty fucking good man
Is it a Halloween release?
I would imagine.
But I mean, here's the thing.
Carpenter has essentially ran screaming
from this franchise for years.
For years and years and years.
I saw a documentary once about the franchise
where it was like up, it was on a regular network
so there was commercials.
And after one of the breaks, they go up next,
find out how John Carpenter is still involved
with the franchise.
And I was so excited because I thought
they were gonna say he was coming back.
And then it goes to a carbonary is like yeah, I'm still involved every time they use my song. I get a check
Keep paying me. I don't care. Keep making them. You know like I was like oh this guy is like so over it
It's crazy. So the fact that he's back and said this was an idea. I couldn't resist. I mean, that's that's intriguing obviously so I had to see him
Folks, that's our show and that is the Halloween franchise
Guys, you got anything to plug, Pat?
I got my show living biblically.
We shot promos this week.
They'll probably start airing at some point soon.
It's getting close.
I think it's gonna be January.
We don't have an air day yet.
Keep it in your thoughts.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
It's all I got, folks.
These days, I'm only posting to my Twitter
from my Instagram, but it's Joderos Accomedy on Instagram.
Come follow me and I will be in Texas.
three cities, Austin Dallas and Houston, Austin on the 15th, Dallas on the 17th, and Houston
on the 18th and 19th, check out joe de rosa info dot com for venue and ticket details.
And that's our show.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.
That was a hitgun podcast.