I'll see you in hell.
Hi, they folks.
Welcome to.
We'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear reviews of your new program.
Your favorite films, and then sometimes films that really stink like today's film.
My name is Joe DeRosa, and my name is Patrick Walsh, way to keep the listeners in suspense
Joe on how we feel about the film.
I don't think anybody is in suspense about black Christmas 2020, but you know, there's
plenty to say.
I saw black Christmas in 2019, and I think I believe at the time I thought we're going to do it for
the show, and I've been harboring resentment all this time that I went to the theater to
see it.
So I'm glad we're finally getting it done.
But enough time at past that I had to go back and fast forward through it to even remember
what it was about.
So I actually had to watch this movie twice.
This is a lot to say about this film, but we'll get to it later as we always do.
For now, let's just catch up like man.
Yeah, I'm quarantining currently.
I started, we're recording this today on Monday, December 14th, you're hearing this probably
on Monday, December 15th, or Tuesday, December 15th, because people usually listen right
away when these things drop, it seems.
But anyway, as of today, Monday, December 14th, not when you're listening when we're recording,
I am three days into a quarantine so I can safely go see my mother and father at Christmas
time.
That's nice.
I get a test from my doctor on Thursday just to be extra safe.
That's literally the only place I'm going until I get a negative result back on the test
and also to pretty much for two weeks.
I'm going to go home on like Christmas Eve.
So I'm shaving, you know, I'm inside for at least the 10 days that they're now recommending.
Funny how these numbers just change.
So that's what I'm doing.
And I got to tell you, when you have a little bit of a light at the end of that quarantine
tunnel, it's pretty sweet when it's not just the indefinite God knows when this is over,
but like I'm doing this, then I get to see my folks for Christmas, fight with them for three days,
come home, it gives you a little something to look forward to.
And it turns the ramping up into that, it's, you sit on your ass and you order everything.
Yeah, that's it.
It's kind of fun.
Yeah, I definitely had like a post -made month that was just the least healthy I've ever been
on my life.
And that was the month I had kind of decided that we were all going to die.
You're right.
Yeah.
So now I've moved out of that.
I did have my first ever COVID test, which was negative.
I just sort of felt like why not get one?
Sure.
And I really do think I had it in early March, a brief mild case.
Maybe I've got antibodies, maybe I don't, but I went and got the test.
It was easy.
It was quick.
There's a way out.
We got the vaccine in the mix, you know, there's, there's good things on the horizon.
Yeah, my doctor told me they're receiving it next week.
Okay.
And then who does it go to?
They said it goes, you know, immediately it'll go to the staff, but, but they're receiving
it like to begin, apparently to begin the like patient, you can get a fucking vaccine through
them, I guess.
So just another case of nurses getting the best of everything and the special treatment.
And for what?
Tell me if you think this is strange.
My doctor doesn't have a nurse, but what I'll catch him doing is slipping out of the office,
returning with a wig, lipstick and a nurse skirt on, putting on a high pitch voice.
Yeah.
I know we're supposed to be accepting of the, I'm not judging.
It is a little odd when he does that though.
Your doctor's office is directed by Brian De Palma.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Yeah.
Dr. De Palma.
I had not been to the doctor in forever.
I actually, I was talking to a buddy of mine and I was like, hey, so we had this doctor named
Dr.
Well, not gonna say his name, but I go, who do you go to that's in our network?
You know, and he, he tells me I've been going to this guy forever and I went to him and
I think I've talked about him on the podcast.
He'll talk to me for three hours and I'm not kidding.
And we're not talking about my health at all.
What he, but he, but he is still for some reason holding your balls while he's doing.
Yeah.
Exactly.
But I'd go in and then I would lead.
He used to say this to me also.
He'd be like, boy, if you just dropped 10, 20 pounds, you would be so handsome.
So handsome.
And that voice and it's like a, it's a compliment, but it's also not at all a compliment.
But so I go in there and every time I would leave, I would owe $45 at the valet parking because
I had been in there forever or the underground parking in LA.
And I on the drive home, I'd go, he didn't check my balls, he didn't check my breathing,
he didn't look into my ears, like, what was I doing?
I actually find a link himself through most of this.
Right.
All he did was when he asked about my extended family history and I told him, you know, my
grandpa had a heart attack at 60.
My dad has huge heart issues.
My mom's side of the family has weird cholesterol issues, even though they're all healthy.
So he goes, look, you're pretty good cholesterol wise.
Everything seems on point.
But I'm going to put you on this small statin, a 10 milligram statin, small dose you can have.
And it just sort of keeps your cholesterol in check because you got this history.
So cut to, I get a letter from him and he's like, I'm quitting.
I think he probably had COVID.
He was way too old to be a doctor, but he's like, I'm quitting.
I'm done good luck finding somebody else basically.
He recommended some guy who was not even in network for me.
So I go, all right, and I text my buddy and I go, hey, what are we going to do now that our
doctor ended?
I mean, who else am I going to talk to for three hours about nothing?
He goes, well, you have your regular doctor still, right?
And I go, what do you mean?
He goes, well, that guy's a heart specialist.
I didn't even know.
That's like how uninformed and stupid I can be.
So I've been going to this guy for five years.
As soon as you walk in the door, he thinks I've got a heart problem.
He does the test, realize there's nothing wrong.
So anyway, because he wasn't there, I couldn't renew my prescription for this cholesterol
medication.
So I just let it go.
I was like, well, it was preventative anyway.
So who cares?
I go to a new doctor.
I get my tests, everything's aces, but then he's like, you know your cholesterol is insanely
high.
And I'm like, how, what, like, what are you talking about?
And when I explained that I came off the statins, he's like, yeah, that caused your
cholesterol to go through the roof.
That's very dangerous.
And I'm like, so I'm just supposed to be on these things for the rest of my life.
And he goes, that's what you're supposed to do with statins, yeah, but I didn't even really
need it.
And he's like, yeah, it's just a, it's a problem now.
Now you're kind of locked into having to figure something out.
So that all sucks.
I think probably me getting very into large Italian sandwiches, which I crick -credit Joe for
a little bit, but I saw his sandwiches on whatever, you know, the ones he's making at
the stand, Comedy Store in New York.
And I was like, it's closed sandwiches.
Yeah.
Right.
So I started eating a lot of sandwiches, but not enough to cause this insane spike.
So now I'm concerned about my health.
I'm probably going to have to avoid good food, you know, eggs, bacon.
I don't eat that stuff anyway though.
We'll see.
Right.
I sure cholesterol, by the way.
I mean, you eat fried chicken by the bucket.
It's higher than it should be, but it's not, my doctor was like, it's not so high that
we need to be alarmed.
He's like, you know, okay.
And I said, do you need me to change what should I do to change my diet?
He goes, yeah, you don't even really need to change that much.
It's not that bad.
It's just, it's just higher than it should be.
That's what he said.
Now who knows?
It's so, it's so reliant on who you go to.
And some of these guys are so fucking checked out, you know, like some people, some doctors
never update their information.
So like things completely change regarding diseases and they never even know that these things
have happened.
It's a scary world.
I've had, you know, slightly high cholesterol, and I do mean slightly, like, you know, when
I've disgusted with people, they're like, oh, that's not that high.
But I have had slightly high cholesterol for a few years now.
And the first doctor to the diagnosis was a doctorate that I went to when I lived in LA, who
would sit there and read me the riot act about this high cholesterol and how it needed
to be changed and how this was terrible and all this stuff.
And you know, and I'd sit there listening to him staring at his face that had been pulled
back so much by plastic surgery at this point.
You know what I mean?
And you just want to be like, go fuck yourself, dude.
Yeah.
Like get the fuck out of my face.
I never forget seriously.
And then my current doctor now in New York is like, yeah, I'm not worried about it.
And he's like, just, you know, keep it high on it.
I was like, all right.
Great.
Yeah.
You never know.
I mean, I have yet to, in my adult life, I have yet to have a doctor's appointment last longer
than five minutes, aside from these three hour things, which were not doctor's appointments.
And that concerns me.
I want to be like, could you please grab my balls, please, and let me know that they're okay.
Yeah.
That is weird that they're not lasting more than five minutes.
I don't understand that, but this was supposed to be a full physical.
And I asked the guy to check my butt.
I said my dad had prostate issues.
He goes, not enough.
You're too young.
I'm going to be 40 a week.
It's 45 is when that test starts now.
All right.
But with a father with a, with a case, I mean, you think he would do it to indulge you, you
know.
But I, you know, it aroused me.
Right.
It's a weird thing to indulge, but now granted, when he walked in, I was completely nude, bent
over the table.
Right.
We, we hadn't discussed that that was going to be part of the, yeah, point of thought.
Didn't help that you're, you're opening line with, see anything you like, doc.
That doesn't help.
Um, I got a new character.
Yeah.
I want to debut, new comedy character.
I want to debut here on the show.
Oh, good.
But it's called wizard from the Bronx.
Okay.
All right.
Ready for this.
Here we go.
I guess.
Oh, I need you breaking my crystal balls.
Oh, man, that's all I got.
It was just just for the pun.
There's no other real.
I was watching a movie about Merlin last night, but I'm going to talk about on the movie
corner.
Yeah.
Was it Merlin, the old miniseries?
Oh, God, no.
That would have been a treat.
Wasn't it dead?
It's in Merlin.
No, it was Sam Neal.
Oh, okay.
Wasn't Ted Danson in it?
I don't know.
Okay.
Uh, you were sure quick to jump on me with the Ted Danson.
And why are you grilling me about the Merlin miniseries right now?
I don't know.
What do I know?
Go ahead.
Uh, I was watching a Merlin movie.
Every last night, uh, because I'm at that point where I mean, you'll get real upset with
me with things I watch in this COVID, uh, amidst this COVID business.
I like to go on to Amazon Prime and just toss a wide net and I find shit on there.
I'm just like, I'm just going to put this on and see what this is like.
I texted you that night.
I put on a movie called Elf Man, uh, that starred We Man as a Santa's helper elf.
Yeah.
So you don't have any that like, I should check these movies off the list.
I should watch the sopranos.
I should what you're just like, I'll watch absolute shit.
Sometimes it's a, let me watch a movie.
I want to watch because I think it'll be quality, uh, and sometimes I'm right about that.
And sometimes I'm very wrong.
And then sometimes I, I do the same thing with something that looks bad.
The Elf Man thing was just, I just wanted to see how We Man was as an actor and at children's
movie.
Uh, I got it.
It wasn't an adult like I pictured it as like a bad Santa, but with elves.
No, no, this was for kids and his job was, his opening gag was, he goes, I can't believe
this.
I've been waiting all these years to get a gig on the sleigh and they assigned me as number
one poop or scooper.
And he holds a net out under the reindeer's butt and the reindeer farts.
And he does like a, like one of those like WC fields takes, like, you know, and, uh, and
then the scene after that was him sitting on the top of the toy pile on the sleigh, staring
off into the stars going, I just feel that I'm meant for something more, having like a reflective
moment.
That's as far as I got in that.
I turned it off.
Um, but, uh, I'm not, I, I realized something, I'm not a fan of We Man unless he's getting
like knocked off of a bridge or something like that.
I've seen in the past couple of months, I saw Johnny Knoxville, uh, do some political video
or something, but he looked like a million bucks.
A man who was, he looked incredible for, and it didn't look like it was surgery at all.
Well, then that's changed something because for a few years there, he looked like the
preacher and poltergeist.
Yeah.
He clearly changed something.
Then I saw a picture yesterday on Twitter of Steve O and Bam and Steve O looked fantastic.
And I know he quit drinking in drugs, but he, I mean, he really looked great and he looked
damn looked like his dad, like he looked awful.
He wasn't that fat yet, but he looked like a hobo.
His, he was missing teeth.
So like, I mean, I think basically they went one of two ways.
And then who knows if we'll ever get this jackass for, but that's the dream.
My concern with these guys all are looking good and with families, they're not going to
want to go to the extents they used to go to.
I think they will, I think they will, but I, my, my, what I actually think would be very
cool is that they treat, and I think they even said they would, they tossed the idea around
and then they dismissed it, but I actually, before I heard that, I thought it'd be very
cool if they treated jackass for the way you would treat any modern day sequel reboot
to a franchise and do just that, where it was them passing the torch to a new, a new round
of jackass guys, like they recruit, but there's got to be seven other people out there that
are the fucking nuts and hilarious that they could, they could assemble.
You get a few women in there, right?
Yeah.
I just feel like a big part of the appeal is that you grew up with these people.
It'd be real hard to find some, some cast that you love that much, but who knows?
We'll see.
Well, not if they're there doing stunts too side by side, and then slowly it gets handed
off to the new guys because I want this crazy shit to keep going and we're going to need
some new guys to take it over.
Sure.
Maybe with them.
Maybe it's you and me.
Maybe it is.
Yeah.
All right.
I mean, I wouldn't do, I'd say about 97 % of the things they do.
Oh, I wouldn't do.
I mean, I sit there thinking how miserable it would be to be on the crew and just be always
living in fear of somebody like shaving the back of your hair off while you're sitting around
doing nothing.
I mean, look, that's the least of your worries.
They're not pissing on each other.
Yeah.
They're throwing snakes at each other.
I mean, it's really fucking wild, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, it seems like the, well, it feels like what it was like going to school when you're
bullied all the time.
I mean, it gives me like bad feelings, but they're at least good people, so yeah, I'm a fan
of them.
Did you ever see an out the outtake?
I think it's from the second movie with Luke Wilson.
Yeah.
I've seen every piece of footage, he's like removing, yeah, where he's like, you're going to
die.
And they're laughing and he's like, it's not funny, man, I'm serious.
Why don't you just kind of die?
I'm, I'm amazed it didn't happen to be honest.
And it did.
It just not, you know, I'm not making fun of the fact that Ryan Dunn died, but one of them
did die.
He didn't die doing the jackass.
No, not doing it.
No, and that's not what Luke Wilson meant either, but I mean, I think I guess you'll eventually
die of old age to the group.
No, no, it wasn't a woody Allen bit.
No, no, we're all going to die, but I do think that, you know, it's, there was a certain
at that period in time with that, with that crew, I think there was a, there was a lifestyle
they were living, yeah, and encompassed all of their, completely their lives as a whole,
not just when they were on set.
I'm pretty sure they were going pretty fucking wild all the time, you know?
I mean, I, I'm sure they're not doing this now, but I had a meeting at their company pretty
early on in my career.
And I believe it was, I'd have to look to my emails, but I think it was for the gig writing
bad grandpa, which they eventually decided to just do themselves, but I went in there
and just, it was like a 10 a .m. Wednesday meeting, and they were like throwing it, they threw
giant balls at their female secretary, like bouncing them off the back of her head.
They were all running up and down the halls, you know, like they, everything is nerf, you
know, arrows and everything, it was, it was fun, but I imagine that's not the office culture
there anymore.
Yeah, it's probably slowed down a bit.
Not really slowed down a bit.
Why did you tell shy LeBuff to do what he did?
We haven't had one in a while, amazingly, but this week we had, we had new updates on
depth and LeBuff.
Well, I'm going to do my news cycle about depth.
Yeah, but LeBuff, you know, I just got tired of seeing him around and I thought this might
be a quick, yeah, yeah, LeBuff, I mean, look, I'm torn
with the LeBuff news.
If you don't know, his ex -girlfriend, who I think is named FKA Twigs, yeah, I'm a fan
of her music.
I mean, the name is ridiculous.
I like her music a lot.
Yeah.
So she said that he was abusive to her, and that I think also that he gave her an STD, knowingly,
yeah.
Then Sia came out and said he conned me into a relationship when he was dating somebody,
and he conned me because he said he was single.
The Sia thing I find suspect, so you see as a little Sia's a little off the rails herself,
but that's not something that should be part of the news.
Yeah.
Sia felt like, what do you, what are you jumping in on here?
Right.
The other one sounded, well, not only sound illegitimate, but then Sia LeBuff admitted
to it.
Now, this is where I'm torn, was what he did terrible, absolutely.
Yeah.
But this is also a guy, that we know from the movie Honeyboy, that grew up in an extremely
fucked up relationship, was abused himself as a kid in his own ways.
And he came out and he goes, yeah, I'm really messed up, and I've abused a lot of people
around me, and I'm really working on it and whatever.
And I wonder now, do you say, okay, but you got to pay your patents, but thank you for
saying that.
And God bless.
We hope you get better.
Or do you say, bye bye, you're done forever, you know what I mean?
Because I think it should be the former, quite frankly, I think it should be like, okay,
you don't just get to skate, you know, but it also doesn't mean you never come back.
You're trying to be a better human being, and you've gone through your, you know, your
child star.
These people are fucked up, like it's, it's a terrible way to raise a child.
They're fucked up.
I mean, yes, it's like if somebody kills somebody, if somebody assaults somebody, whatever
they do, they, they did it, you know, like everybody's got their shit to deal with.
It's unfortunate.
You can certainly be sympathetic towards them if they have a traumatic upbringing as he
definitely did.
I think in his case, he had been, he had been, you know, mostly, mostly on the public
drunkenness side and less in the abusing women's side.
But he had been kind of let go by Hollywood, you're too much of an issue.
He had too big a mouth, too big an ego, too big a drinking and drug problem.
Then they started letting him back, like when I saw him on that fast times video where he
appeared to be losing his mind, I was like, okay, so these are big stars who are willing
to share the screen with him.
They are letting him back in.
He also got great press from that.
Everybody was like, shout out to the show.
He was amazing, you know, so I think that Hollywood was very willing to let him back.
And then I think this is kind of like, all right, we, we tried, man, I know this stuff
probably happened before that.
I don't know the timeline, but there's only so many strikes and I think he's probably at
his limit.
And it's a shame.
I think he's a wonderful actor.
I've always just liked his vibe and it's hard for me to like like a pretty boy actor,
but I think he's great.
I imagine he's not done.
You know, part of that thing, like I said, for some reason, this was not in a lot of the
reporting on the F .K .A Twigs thing.
She said he was researching a role where he played a serial killer and he would drive around
with her in the passenger seat shooting straight dogs.
That's big, you know, like that's somebody who needs a lot of help and probably shouldn't
be on a set with actors and actresses.
Sure.
Yeah.
No, like that, that I get.
Now by the way, shooting dogs, you know, a lot of people love animals more than people
and vice versa.
I'm not saying shooting dogs is worse than a sexual assault or throwing a woman against a car.
I'm saying it's all bad.
Yeah.
And that's like, you know, stuff that he needs to be off the grid for a while and I think he
will be.
Well, Pat is clearly saying shooting dogs is not worse than abusing a woman, but abusing
a woman is less offensive than shooting a dog.
We get it.
We get what you're saying.
I'm saying it's all, it paints a picture of a man who's not stable is what I'm saying,
you know.
Hold your horses.
This guy's not.
Yeah.
No, yeah.
He's a troubled guy.
Now, the Johnny Depp one, if we, this was the new psycho that I wanted to do, yeah.
Amber herd is just announced that she's going to be in Zack Snyder's Justice League.
Okay.
She's excited and she can't wait for everybody to see what Zach has done with the Justice
League.
Look, I can't wait.
I'm excited to see it.
But I got to tell you, I know, I got to tell you, and we might have a very different
opinion on this.
This really pisses me off, man, in this current climate that we live in and this enlightened
culture that we're all striving to become, where gender is not, is not a, a, a signifier
anymore or a qualifier in any way, right?
That's what we're trying to do.
We're trying to get away with that concept that gender qualifies you in a certain way for
something.
I think, hey, man, Amber herds got to take her lumps too right now.
They're in a very heated, very nasty court battle.
And you've got equal people on equal sides saying that one abuse the other about the other.
It's nuts.
Now, I don't know who hit who.
If anybody hit anybody, if they're both crazy, if they both did it, I don't know.
But if we're going to live in this world where we're supposed to believe people, sorry,
that also means believing Johnny Depp, especially when there are other people coming on saying, no,
she abused him physically.
And it really bothers me that he's the one that has to step down from everything.
And she just gets to coast along here and nobody's going to say anything aside from, you know,
internet trolls.
I think that's, I think that's really hypocritical, man, and really gross.
However, I think that Depp's has been, he's hit it well, but from what I've read, and
we're all just reading whatever's put on line, so who knows, but this was, you know, full
court documents and the judge talked at length about the judge really through the book of Johnny
Depp.
Like, he talked for hours about what a piece of shit Johnny Depp was after reviewing all
this stuff.
So I think, you know, the reason he's unhyrable and the Hollywood Reporter article, if you
didn't read it as this huge expose, like why he's, it called him radioactive as the Imagine
Dragons might sing, but do they sing radioactive?
I wouldn't know.
They suck.
God, they fucking suck.
I put them up there with like snow patrol, like, you know what I mean, there's, there's a
gaggle.
I'll definitely take a snow patrol over Imagine Dragons.
Never heard any hands open.
Why don't you download hands open?
You won't listen.
But it's a great.
It creeds in that category.
The national is in that category for me.
It's just a list of bands where I'm like, I don't give a rat's ass.
If you want to put a group of bands you don't care about, fine, but creed in the national
have nothing in common, I know that the national is a better band than creed.
That I'm aware of, but I'll cut just either when I hear them, my, my insides go all
just, I get that.
That's all.
I stop listening to the national and, you know, bands are music I really love, like Elliot
Smith and stuff, just because I'm like, Pat, this is not helping your depression, listening
to people who are deeply depressed.
It's Elliot Smith.
I never met a girl like you before that Elliot Smith.
No.
Who's that?
That's Edwin Collins.
Okay.
And that's a great song.
I like that song.
I have a metagirl like you before.
It's on my, my main song playlist, like I love that song.
Elliot Smith killed himself by stabbing himself in the heart a thousand times, but he's one
of the best songwriters ever.
His music is just, it's sound, it's the soundtrack to killing yourself basically.
Yeah.
When I lived actually in royal tenimbums, Luke Wilson tries to kill himself to Elliot Smith.
When I lived in Silver Lake, that mural was right near me.
Yeah.
The Elliot Smith mural and they recently built a burrito place over it.
Okay.
Well, that was the one thing that made everybody go, you know, Silver Lake's just like Brooklyn.
There's a painting over there.
You go.
Okay.
Is there any like fun places to go though?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, but there's the painting that we hit, the Elliot Smith to you.
Okay.
You stand by that, drink a 40 in the street.
No.
I love Elliot Smith.
He did all the music for Goodwill Haunting and et cetera, but I love XO is one of my favorite
albums.
I can't say enough.
I just stopped listening to him because it was bumming me out.
But what were we talking about, John?
Johnny Depp being radioactive.
Yes.
And that led us to Imagine Dragons, which for some reason led to this.
So a parent, now he, they're like Johnny Depp, he, the things he requires on a movie set
in addition to his outrageous salary usually was totaling $3 million for the things that
he would ask, meaning like a writer, nothing wrong with that.
That's, he's got, look, if he's got that kind of sway, he's got that kind of sway.
So then he'd show up every day, four hours late to set, always high, always drunk, everyone
in his life, including friends are like, yeah, he's the guy who like, you're wiping
cocaine and sweat off his face at a restaurant because he passed out in there.
I think he was just a complete fuck up.
I think that he's unhirable in a much more extreme way than La Booth in terms of his personal
issues and with drinking and everything else.
I read this Rolling Stone interview with him a few years back where the amount of drugs
and alcohol he did over the course of an interview was deeply disturbing.
And I mean, look, that I get, but when is Hollywood, you know, I'm saying how reliable
is this narrator of him saying she beat me?
It's like, okay, that's a fair point, but also to the guy clearly never heard
peep until this whole thing that this guy had been a problem on set, not once, not
ever. And you do hear that about other people.
We've all heard the Russell Crowe stories and all these other things.
Sure.
And Hollywood has never given a shit about a drunk or a drug addict.
They're all fucking drunks and drug addicts.
As long as you show up and you do your job, they don't care.
I mean, Gandalfini would cancel full shooting days for the sopranos and pay the 150 grand
that they lost because he was too hungover.
It's like, this is par for the court.
So the Hollywood reporter can fucking relax on acting like, oh, God, you know, clutching
their pearls over, I'm not doing coke and drinking in Hollywood.
That said, I understand you make a very good point about he might be a very unreliable
narrator.
If he's that shit face, all that's right.
And I think he hit a, he hit a point where, you know, like, well, you see him in
Ed Wood or something, that's not somebody who's fucked up on set.
I think he may have had issues.
He may have partied too much back in the day, but I think at some point it was bleeding
into his work life to the extent that he, he was unhierable.
And I think that's just been getting worse throughout the years.
So that's what I think happened.
But I mean, when he's bringing out, when on a rider to say, well, he was never
mean to me when we were sweethearts 25 years ago, I mean, that's, that's drug
addiction and alcohol.
I mean, you can completely change over time for that's, that's a fair point.
But also Paul Bettany came out and supported him.
Doug Stanhope, who, you know, I know if you're talking about, you know, Doug, Doug likes
to drink himself, but like Doug, you know, it was one of the people that came out and
said, look, I hang out with this guy.
None of this is true.
What she's saying is not true.
He didn't say he doesn't drink nobody came out and said he doesn't do coke.
It doesn't drink what they said was he didn't beat Amber heard.
In fact, he was physical with him.
That's what they said.
It was rough, too, that they read that text he sent to Paul Bettany.
If you read that, which was like this floppy vagina pile like it was like real,
real rough and him describing how he was going to kill her and like, yeah, that's
not good.
That's bad.
And you know, if the judge is reading that in the courtroom, I'm sure even Johnny Depp was
like, yeah, I'm probably not going to be acting for a bit, you know, but yeah, yeah, it's
a ugly stuff.
It's look, it's a disgusting business.
Yeah, it takes, and I'll say this about anybody in it.
It takes a certain personality type to get to that level.
We've discussed it many times on the show.
It's a sick fucking world.
It's sick.
It's a sick fucking industry.
It is.
And you know, no matter how many people get to, you know, that's certain level of success,
were anywhere even near it and think that they're still normal human beings.
They're sick.
They're wrong.
You're not.
You're just not.
So that's it.
Anyway, let's go to the movie corner.
We're past there.
Oh yeah.
We're at the 30 -minute mark.
Joe, I was just enjoying talking to an old friend.
Who?
Who's here?
Oh.
Uh, Ted Danson was not in the Merlin picture.
It was Martin Short.
I knew there was somebody who played like an organ.
I was like, do I want to watch this?
Ed Danson.
Very similar.
You know, in a weird way here, in a weird way, Ted Danson is the much more handsome version
of Martin Short.
In terms of their face and their hair, okay, I guess they have nothing in common.
Nothing.
I tried to convince myself for a minute, and then I couldn't do it.
Yeah.
Okay.
So movie corner.
Yeah.
Folks, by the way, this is, if the audio just changed, it's because we are now recording the
second half of this podcast for the third fucking time in a row due to technical issues.
Uh, I, I met my wits and, um, let's just, I don't understand what's going on with this
episode.
Why?
What's happening?
Uh, it's day two, hour six, maybe, to put together a one hour podcast.
We've never had any issues in five years, really, but they're all hitting now.
They're really hitting.
Um, but anyway, I got my cat in my lap, so I'm very calm about it.
I got my, that's why you need a cat.
That's what you, we're talking about getting a cat.
Get a cat.
I got to wait till I get my to COVID test is negative.
So I can leave the apartment again, and then I got to go see my mom and dad for Christmas.
And then when I get back, I'm getting a cat.
Okay.
Uh, I, I got to do something over here.
I'm, I'm going, I'm going crazy.
Uh, I feel like just get really fucked up tonight.
Maybe I'll just do that.
You should.
But I bought alcohol when I went out, I'm going to open it.
Prater Joe's.
No.
First of all, I've seen it without a, like, some trader of Jose's tequila.
I think they banned trader, Jose's.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I was making it.
Well, they, they banned the name trader, okay, Jose's, a trader mows.
I thought I was in bad taste, you know, right, or mouse was what they call the, now I'm
kidding.
I'm kidding.
They're a lot of cheese.
But that, no, that's not far off from what it was.
It was like trailer mings or something.
It was really was.
Yeah, it was, yeah.
Uh, anyway.
Look, they've brought people affordable food for a long time.
I'm sure they mean well, I love trader, Jose, I had no problem with trader, Jose.
I thought it was a good, nice way of saying like, right.
Being diverse.
I thought it was actually very sweet.
Um, mows they just meant because it was a dictator.
No, I know, I know.
Yeah, yeah, trader eight offs. That's only in the sausage section. All right. Let's do a
Two two and two movie corner not not because just because it's technical issues
And I'm afraid this is gonna shit out on us again
By the way guys when it shits out we lose the entire thing. We were almost
God, I don't want to talk about it. Yeah, it's like when you when you write 30 pages and then you didn't save
I mean we lost up the whole the whole recording and we were by the way we were flowing. Yeah, we were yeah
Heavy flowing now we come back in it's awkward. It's we're sputtering. We're anchored defeated. I got a tryumphant about this
Fucking Merlin movie again for the third fucking time. I'm tired of talking about it. I mean imagine me hearing about it
Guys listen, I'm really gonna bullet point it for you
I'm not mailing it in. I can't talk about this again. I can't do the same jokes a
third time in a row
Wait, you're a stand -up comedian. You can't do the same jokes a third time in a row
None of these Merlin jokes were that funny the first time they were just a quirky little things to say as I talked about the movie
I didn't I wasn't like to stave off death I
Watched him. I watched a movie called Merlin in his magical workshop
Why?
Because when I can't sleep at night. I peruse the children's fantasy section on prime video
Make that an edit point and send directly to the FBI. There you go. There you go insert that joke that we've now done
Three times. No, I just put a fresh spin on that joke. You know I did
No, no, the first time we recorded the other day you said put put it at a point right there. I didn't say the FBI
Bet that was new you didn't yeah, by the way
You're telling the story more concisely more confidently. They're not as many as in it. You've polished it
Okay, I started this thing up thinking it was gonna be like a sword in the stone kind of cartoon type of Disney animated feature
I
Started not only is it live action. It stars top -billing Ernest Borg -9
Who's never been good in anything except the movie Marty? That's the only thing Ernest Borg -9 was ever good in and I offered
From here to eternity when which he was very I forgot about that, but I never saw that movie believe it or not
I'm embarrassed to say that because it's not huge not your fan. You know, it's not in my synatra blue race set
From here to eternity. Yeah, it's the the detective isn't it, which is my favorite synatra movie that I've seen and also kind of hard to come by
In in singular form
But no no from here to it's got like Manchurian candidate for the detective
Those other comedy detective movies he did called like you know like Frankie jugs or whatever the fuck they were called I can't remember
Well, I would have loved it if it was Frankie jugs
It's an otter with a pair of ladies tits, and then I think it's got like man with the gold normal on it or something
I mean they're good movies, but it's just some it's some surprise that's not on anyway
The plot of this Merlin movie not a lot of fun. It's geared towards I'd say seven to nine -year -olds
It centers around Merlin we're having a magic shop in the middle of North Hollywood not in a funny way
Not in like the way you'd see in like a Wayne's world kind of gag or you know, he just has it there for some reason. I don't know why
But they don't they don't go like north of Hollywood and south of the valley village
No, it's not like they're they're treating California like a mess like the game of thrones land or something
Could you say no and they don't even they don't even go far enough to say like long before industry
This was once a magical. They don't even do that right, right? It's just I
Guess you're just I guess Merlin just has a taste for the glitter and glitz of journal anyway
The plot of the movie is is that a couple a married couple who are on the rocks keep in mind this is for seven -year -olds
are having more problems than ever
From the emotionally abusive husband because the wife found out she's barren and
The husband is disgusted by this and he won't raise a child that isn't his
There you go. It's the plot of the kids movie
He also for some reason is a critic of that none of these people are played by Ernest Borgnein by the way
He's got a quick flash cameo as a grandfather at the beginning of this thing
He's the Peter Falk tell him the story. Yeah, yeah, which is was a line. I said in the last three recordings
Thank you for picking it up this time. I couldn't stomach saying it again
Uh
The plot so anyway the plot of this thing is this asshole husband who's mad at his barren wife
um is also
Get this a
Critic for I think the LA Times
Who can shut down a store with one column? I love that was like a thing they'd do in the 80s like there was a twilight zone with Elliott
Where he but it's one of my favorite 80s twilight zones where he plays a food critic and literally
It's like he keeps a graveyard of matchbooks on his desk for all the restaurants
He just shuts down with a column like I guess at one point critics had this kind of power
I think they thought they did
Um
He threatens to shut down Merlin's shop why because he doesn't believe it's really a magic place
In that guys like you Merlin scam people all the time his heart's actually kind of in the right place
I guess there's a lot of magic scam and going on at that point in North Hollywood
But uh anyway Merlin gives the guy a book of spells the guy goes home
He tries the spells out he realizes magic is real
Of course he says I'm gonna make millions from this
Uh, and
I fell asleep at this point
It was in the same choice. I'm embarrassed. I chose it. I watched it
After watching the I can't remember if I already talked about this the elfman we man's movie that I put on like
I'm just making bad choices these days. Yeah
So anyway, that's that's my first in the movie corner this week with the christmas. I'm choosing that shit movies
I decided because my choices are going to be too bad shit things that I watched
Because the movie we're discussing is bad shit
Not just I hope I pray to god that I never have to hear about that movie again
From you Jim. I'm Michael back and finish it tonight just to see what happened. Okay. Well, I mean let me know
Uh, I watched tenant
Christopher Nolan's tenant an equally popular and important film to Joe's Burbank Merlin
He watched
Uh, Burbank Merlin. That's a good title for sure
Uh, I am gonna tell you the only thing I want to do less than watch tenant is listen to you explain it for a second time today
Hey
Set by only a second. I've heard yours repeated talk
Uh
So tenant I'm not gonna try to explain it doesn't make any sense and
Uh, I have heard people say that if you watch it again and again it starts to make more sense
But I do think there's some pretty huge
um
lapses in logic and cohesive story telling here part of that is fun
It's uh, it's Christopher Nolan getting weirder and weirder and weirder and more and more kind of up his own ass as his career goes
Which is interesting to a point, but I hope he
He
You know, I don't want him to keep making superhero movies, but I just hope he he stops just making things that only kind of really interest him
Because they're just getting too
up his ass. That's all I can say. This is so far up Christopher Nolan's ass and yet
I enjoyed being up there. I
Had no idea what it was about
Uh, the dialogue made no sense moment to moment and as I was telling Joe earlier
The lead character played by Denzel Washington son John David Washington who was good in the movie doing his best with the dialogue
um
His character's name is the protagonist
He refers to himself as a protagonist everyone else refers to him as a protagonist
But they never explain like why he's called that or what agency he's from or that he's a secret operative under the code name
None of that if they did I missed it and I think that like well just just to point out you could have missed it because you are the one person
I know that watched the vacation
Uh, Ed Helm's sequel and didn't understand that it was a continuation of the original films even though Chevy chase showed up as Clark
Rizwold did I also enough time has passed
While I'm popping over here. I got to get a drink my mouth so dry
um
But enough time has passed that I don't feel like I'm spoiling it, but I saw Tully
And did not understand what took place at the end of Tully. It's a it's a twist
It's everyone that season everyone that sees it talks about the twist and I'm like wait a minute
I completely missed the twist in Tully. What did you see it and you like the twist go oh my god. What's Tully?
Diablo Cody it was a pretty good little movie actually
Uh
Just tell me the twist. I don't give a shit
No, I won't because people might check that out. It's not it's not excited to just hear it. All right, so I missed it anyway. Tenet
um
Yeah, at a certain point me and my wife both looked at each other and we're like all right
I give up trying to understand what it's about. I'm just gonna enjoy myself
That's what you got to do at least for the first viewing and then decide if you want to go back and figure out the world and the minutia
It's up to you. I probably won't do that
However, if you look at it like a mission impossible or a James Bond
I think this is the best action movie in quite a while you got 10
giant huge big budget beautifully shot beautifully staged action sequences
Uh, they don't keep you waiting long between them. Although the dialogue between them is painful. I grant you
But you got ten of the brand out going way over the top as this Russian bad guy
He is awesome in the movie. He's a better villain than you usually even get in a bond
uh, I
Really surprisingly dug tenet
I would watch three more of these if they made him but they won't because it was a huge failure
But I don't understand all the hate for it. I think if you if you want an action movie
Uh, if you want to take it as a no -brainer just a visual fest
You're gonna have a blast if you want to take it as a brainier than usual action movie and try to figure it out
Like a jigsaw puzzle like a nerd
You'll have a lot of fun too
All right
My second insane choice and while you talk jaw I'm gonna get a beer you hear you hear my lips smacking
Yeah, I can hear him smacking. It's troubling all right
Go get a beer. I gotta get this cat off me
Go get a beer bitch
My second choice insane uh choice for the movie corner this week and I did watch these by the way. This isn't a gag
A little picture called my five wives starring Rodney Dangerfield
Uh
You don't need to be a rocket scientist to figure out what this film is about
It's Rodney Danger Reels. You know, it's a comedy and it's called my five wives
So, you know, it's about how he has five wives
How does he get the five wives? I'll tell you how he's a land developer that lives in Los Angeles who's very rich
Who goes out to Utah to acquire a ski lodge that he's gonna turn into a you know ski resort
Now there's not a lot of fun like hit skiing in this
It's not one of those it doesn't turn into like hot dog the movie or one of those 80s type of roms
He just goes to Utah to get because that's where the ski place is um
And uh with the acquisition of the land that he buys to create the or operate the ski lodge
He also inherits the dead man's wives
You know, we're not we're not pushing the envelope too hard here with this they they not not a lot of time and think tank on this one creatively
But hey, it's danger field it works
I mean it works if you like that kind of thing
I mean, this is a brainless film people if you need to put something on to forget the stresses of the pandemic
the state of
Everything that you could think of or look at in the news and whatever that makes you depressed
This is a great one to put on. This is a real volume of a movie. You're not going to think it's so absurd
You're not going to get any stress or anxiety from it
Anyway, he inherits the three wives that he of course has to marry two more hence your title
And it's basically two hours of jokes about how he can't fuck his wives enough even though they need him to bang him all the time and
Now Joe does he ever come down the stairs covered in lipstick kisses
like and and is if he does is he in
Heart polka dotted underpants boxers the cover of the movie is his face with lipstick kisses all over it
I don't know if that actually happens in the film. I don't think it does
But it's chock full of danger field one -liners some of them terrible some of them kind of funny some of them pretty good
I will say this I enjoyed this more than we meet while he sparks
Um, I would take this movie in a in a box set
Like if you gave me a danger field box set that started with Caddy Shack and ended with this
I would I wouldn't be mad at it. I'd take this over ladybugs
I'll tell you that
Well, I have a real soft spot for ladybugs. That was maybe the first Rodney I ever saw because it came out when I was like a kid
I had already seen at that point
Back to school at least back to school and and
Ladybugs to me was such a letdown because it was suddenly like this like family movie
Yeah, had like two good danger field lines in it. This is like definitely okay
Jackay. Yeah, but but like wasted. She's not jackay in it like
You get jackay you want like ooh Mary and all that stuff like and how fun to play that energy off of danger field
But that is good to do it
Um, you know why racism
probably
Uh
Dice is in this movie as a mobster. That's kind of fun to watch
Jerry stiller shows up at the end as the boss of the family
the top mob guy
Uh, John penets in it
John biners in it, you know some fun cameos not even cameos. They're all in supporting roles
You know, like I said, it's a brainless film. Yeah, but I found that enjoyable. You know, I'm not gonna tell you to go watch it, but
My five wives what more do you want? I'm there. All right
Uh, my second picture is twins
uh from 1988 Ivan rightman
And you know, it's following ghost busters
You know legal eagles the guy could do when a legal eagles didn't do that well
But the guy could do no wrong. He'd do these huge high concept comedies
Right after this he did kindergarten cop
I rewatched
kindergarten cop recently and I felt exactly the same way as I do about twins
I was amazed at what a great comedic actor
Arnold was he's right right from the jump. I couldn't believe it. I think he I would
Twins is the movie that makes me say he's a great actor like he's playing so against type and it's so believable
I was like he is a really good actor in this guy. Yeah, and that was kind of the first time
He was doing the comedy really so I was very impressed by his performance
But it also in both cases
The movie suck and you gotta kind of blame rightman, you know
I think that it was it was a big part of the 80s
But also something that rightman thought you needed to do now
Let's not just sit and enjoy
This amazing relationship you got two of the biggest comedy stars in the world
DeVito Schwartzenegger
And you put them together. They wind up having beautiful comic chemistry together in this outlandish premise
And they immediately abandoned the premise and bring in mobsters
And DeVito has stolen a car that belongs to a mob guy and then he's he's coming after them and it's like
The second you start getting like swept away. I'll say it by twins
You're like I love watching these two interact and they're so charming and so funny together and Arnold is so sweet and DeVito such an asshole and I love that and it's really working and
This set like right as you're settling down into that it's into this boring -ass
Plot you got Schwartzenegger driving on two wheels as one of the big set pieces. Yeah, it's fucking stupid
And the plot also takes DeVito into such dark places that the character becomes very unlikable at times
And yeah, it's a it's a bummer
It's fun when he's the lovable scumbag
And then he becomes so selfish at times. You're like god. He's just a terrible guy
You know
But like I
I agree that movie should have just been crocodile Dundee. It should have been Danny DeVito taking his
Long -loss it should have been perfect strangers like take the guy around this is like he's a fish out of water
You get him married by the end of the movie. Yeah, everybody lives together, you know, but like three men and a little baby style
Like put the put them in the weird situation. We don't need a we don't need a mob
And by the way a serious mob
They brought in a heist they brought in a heist and three men and a baby if I if memory serves. Oh, they did
Yeah, remember that but anyway, but like a serious mob sub plot in twins not a funny one
Not funny in the like my five wives very funny sub mob plot
Now it's like and I remember seeing the trailer for twins and as soon as you see those two
Walking wearing matching suits with like whole matching Hawaiian shirts and they both throw their jackets over the same shoulder
The audience was like howling and like yes
When can I say twins? Yeah, yeah, the trailer does not even mention the fact that the last half of the movie is this miserable slog through
The mob underworld
So you just think the lesson would be oh right we could also save money and just explore these characters
So that sucks and kindergarten cops the same way Arnold is so delightful with the kids
But then it goes into like a real top movie. Yeah, like he's blowing people away while holding a child
haha
All right folks
While we're on the subject of batshit films our Christmas movie for this year
Is black Christmas
Yeah, I would just like to say first and then you can go into the plot but I saw this movie last year in the theater
Right before Christmas up in Burbank right where uh
Joe's Merlin tail was set
and
I
despised the smooth with every fiber my being I told Joe like you're not gonna believe how much you hate the movie blood block
Because I thought we were gonna do it on the show we never did it
So now that Joe decides he's ready to do it. Oh, I never said I was right you said you suggested again
I said okay, I'll watch it
But I realized I was gonna have to watch it again. So I've now seen this movie twice forgot say
Uh
Look folks you're gonna watch a black Christmas movie watch Friday after next, okay
I had that on the other night
Laughing my balls off by the way Friday after next yeah
Mike absent one points us to their land lady while you're always coming up here with that wolf pussy
Oh my god
Wild line to that flick you got Terry cruise like molesting ice making forcing them to hug him because he just got a jail
It's a fun movie okay
Anyway, uh, you know what's you know what's a good uh black Christmas movie as well this Christmas
I feel it's been very it's been very under scene and uh, I enjoyed it. What about jingle jangle Delroy Lindo Idris Elba loretta divine
Hollywood sweetheart chris brown what you want of your favorite chill
jingle jangle was that what was the tagline for jingle jangle jangle jangle was uh, it's all about the
music, marimen and and melanin for me and I thought it was gonna be when you told me that
I thought it was gonna be like a movie about a black family at Christmas
Mm -hmm, you know
Like and that was some play on like, you know, like the like a waiting to exhale kind of like we've got soul
You know what I mean like that kind of thing right and it's not it's a fantasy movie that just that has an all black
Why you yeah, that's that's what's so gross about it. It's like yeah, that's got that's like a like a how Stella got her groove back flare kind of
You know what I mean like right anyway
um
All right, so uh black crit now here's the thing for people not only is it hard to make a remake of a classic
uh
But it's real hard to make a remake of a classic that's already been remade once
Uh, let's see our commentary on the original black Christmas, which we did one of our very earliest episodes
But it is damn near impossible
To do a remake of a remake of a remake that's gonna have nothing to do with any of it
But that preceded this movie
Scratching my head I thought maybe
Blumhouse because they have this deal with universal now to make all the universal movies the horror movies rather
that
The original black Christmas was universal
And maybe they just had the title and the property so they said let's just do it but put a new crazy spin on it
That is not the case
um
I don't know why this is called black Christmas
The audience it is aimed towards which is tweens
With a nice soft PG -13 rating
Uh does not have any clue what the movie black Christmas is
Uh the people that go to see blumhouse pictures in general outside of the Jordan peel movies
I would say are people for the most part that don't even know the movie black Christmas
Uh, I am confused by this film
Imaging poots I will I'm in I think she's great. I heard it had a supernatural twist at the end
I was like okay, I'm listening this sounds batshit
I actually was excited to watch this. I was like this is gonna be batshit crazy
And it's not gonna make a lot of sense, but it's gonna be fun
And boy was I wrong
Dear god almighty
What a paint by numbers piece of propaganda this thing is
yeah, it um
It wears its issues so
So much on its sleeve that there's nothing left
They're just saying words like buzz words throughout the movie
Um, there's no real feeling behind any of it
they
All speak in exactly the same way which is
You know sort of Diablo Cody -esque actually very heightened everybody is talking in twitter terms and etc
uh
Right away the first line of the movie girl walks in says hey, have you seen my diva cup
Then she hands a tour and she shoved it by the way. It's like um, it's like a
Good for the environment tampon
And it's called a diva cup because it's a metal cup that I believe and you can all feel free to please make fun of me
And I know that I should know what a diva cup is
Should work for a plant parenthood, but uh
Yeah, it's a metal cup that you like insert within yourself to catch the
Flow right, but why is it called a diva cup that I don't know because the lady who invented it was a saucy diva
I don't know. I don't Elton John's considered a diva VH1 showed us that on their diva special
That's true. Oh, he can't use the diva cup
Uh, not for that purpose. No
But maybe as a nettie pot or something like that
Okay, yeah, I didn't know what the fuck she was even talking about when that happened
I was so it's like curtain up like movie begins have you seen my diva cup here she shoves it into herself
Walks out into the end of the day and you're like
All right, man like the entire thing is so
Just it's joyless. There's no there's nothing real about any of the people who are in it
Imogen poots does her best. I do think she's a really good actress
She is and you know, they had a couple good scenes written like the one where she
Kind of spins and and makes the Christmas song about the guy who raped her. It's a good moment
I don't know how she had those lyrics handy. I guess it was kind of an eight mile moment
You know, I think no, no, I think that was pre planned because she doesn't want to do it
Because he's gonna be there and then they say no, that's all the more reason for you to do
Okay, I think like that. I think that was the their talent show piece was about frat boys or rapists fair enough
that wasn't quite clear, but
Or I'm dumb one of the other, but I mean again
Didn't understand what the vacation Ed Helm movie was
Basically I
Hated every second of this movie, you know, and there's like there's carry L was in the mix as the
Dean and it's kind of nice to see him from Princess bride also doing some yet again some kind of accent
I'm like, yeah, he's supposed to be Southern right English like I can't tell what he's doing right
So and his first line at you know every character is introduced like in the most them way so he's like
Uh, you know, they want me to take all the white males off the curriculum, but I told them like I love you know white
Everyone's talking at all times about the patriarchy and white males ridiculous
Well, he and he says in his in his speech to the class. Yeah
You know, and I know some of you won't appreciate it particularly those trying to have my tenure revoked, right?
Like oh for god's sakes
it's like
I think there is
A brilliant wonderful scary exciting horror movie to be made about the patriarchy and about the things this movie
Everything this movie is about absolutely
And not only do I think that there's a good movie to be made
I hope one is coming. I'm sure one is coming and there have been some already
but
My issue with this movie is that it's like you've got classic source material
You've got very juicy subject matter that everybody in the world is talking about right now
And you gave us this it's it's it's a bummer. I think that Jason Blum
Is too blame
Uh, it's his studio to Blum to Blum and look man. Let me let me let's call facts facts here
Blumhouse does not put out a good product
They get lucky once in a while
With the Jordan Peele movies right that do very well very well received critically
I love get out you know is brilliant and I think this movie could have been a get -out style film
But it just had no nuance and no thought behind it
Now maybe it did at one point. I don't know
but
I think it's Jason Blum's fault
I think in some cases he lets artists do whatever they want
Right and he strikes gold. I think he does that with Jordan Peele
I think that's why us was 45 minutes too long and you know what I mean like he's yeah
To me an example of a studio not getting involved enough and not making some changes
Uh, and then I think with other things
He's got his fingerprints all over because these messages are so heavy handed in these movies in in this and invisible man
In uh fantasy island. I believe I was I just read the synopsis of that one
I mean it was so poorly reviewed and it looks so boring
But I remember reading in that there was there was some of these elements and whatever
And it's here's the thing man if you're gonna have a message you need to make that message interesting
And the way you in my opinion the way you make it interesting is by not beating your audience over the head with it
Let them think let them draw a few conclusions challenge them
Right in an interesting way don't take excerpts from a pamphlet that you would get it like a doctor's office
Uh or at a college campus seminar and and and and turn it into dialogue and think that that passes for getting a message across
It doesn't it's it's it's preachy and nobody receives it well
If you read the reviews of this movie not only is it poorly reviewed you've got feminist critics saying this movie is is poorly executed
so um
So the point is is that
I don't think this landed with any audience no even the most intended of of the of demographics that they were going after
Yeah, obviously I saw it was mostly teenage girls and then you know disgruntled guys in their 40s
And uh, which is always a dangerous combination
But everybody hated it, you know, everyone was laughing throughout the girls. You know, you could just tell no one was into it and
There must it does feel like something was gutted from it, you know
Maybe there's a slightly better version somewhere, but the ending is so and competently shot and edited together that you feel like something must have gotten
Chopped out of the movie or something like it just it it it feels that to me
Bad it feels and the movie's only you know an hour 25 minutes or something which is usually a sign that
There was some tinkering and something went wrong. I think yeah, I think it doesn't work
I think he is on a mission and I bait look
I'm basing a lot of this too on like the fact that he got that
Award if the Israeli film festival and went up and was like I'm gonna trash
Trump up here. No look. I think Trump's a fucking idiot too
But but pick your audience a little bit man. You're going don't don't accept the award from the Israeli film festival
If the only reason you're going in there to get it is to piss off everybody at the Israeli film festival
You know what I mean like
What do you think is going to happen in this situation? It just seems like grandstanding to me
It seems like a dumb battle to fight. It seems completely ineffective. It's a publicity run
You know and if your grievances are a little more specific than mine
Well, I'm just saying though, but but but I'm using I'm citing these incidents to reference why these movies that he makes are not good
Yes, it's it's these are publicity
Studs virtue signaling is as I believe the latest tournament. Yeah, and that's what it is. It's just like
You know instead of actually challenging people on these
Subjects which are the most challenging facing us right now
We're going to just kind of say that it's very much like the stand -up comedian who says
uh
You know, so I gave this girl AIDS and then everybody goes ugh and he's like oh what I can't say aids
Yeah, it's that meathead shit. No, you're not funny. It's not funny. Yeah, it's that meathead shit
It's yeah, and then the other end of that is the Hannah Gatsby thing like I'm so deep up here and all that stuff
You know what I mean? It's it's all of it. It's like
There are there are two when you preach the the cause too hard you come off as dumb as the meathead
That you're railing against you know, I mean it's like right you get a clue read the room
So um, I don't know. Yeah, I mean and these these frat guys in this movie
I I despise and always have despised frat guys. It's a it's a it's a real uh
What do you call it?
Pre -you know prejudice of my genuine prejudice like if somebody says they were in a frat. I'm like oh fuck this guy
I just can't help it. It's in my bones
But I found the portrait of the frat guys in this movie to be
Over the top like beyond something like the skulls that came out when I was 15
You know, it's like every frat guy that comes up's got like the Nazi hair and it's like you know like hey
I was just wondering if maybe I could date rape you tomorrow. I mean date you tomorrow. It's like come on
It's awesome. I'm not saying give him credit. I'm saying find a more
Slime interesting way to portray these characters also put a couple decent guys in then counterbalance it with something
Yeah, yeah, you have to counterbalance it or it doesn't make any sense. It's like okay
The one decent guy in the movie that manages to not offend any of them
Is also the one guy that is brought into this
Mal cult against his own will and hypnotized by them
Which then undercuts your entire premise because by the way the premise of the movie is
They're doing a super they're doing a supernatural ceremony on this campus that will into and indoctrinate all these men into this
Secret male cult that will write the world of all the wrongs women are doing and keep men in control
The good guy who image in poots has a crush on
It gets inducted into this at the end but against his own will and then like sort of snaps out of it
And it's like well if that's the case
Well then
Aren't all these other guys also in that same boat haven't they also been
abducted and and and hypnotized against their own will which means then they're not bad guys
But they never explain any of that they never
Explain why one guy will do it willingly and another guy won't
I guess that's supposed to be some kind of metaphor for
This is how it gets into your bones and into your head and you don't even know what's happening. I guess
Um, maybe yeah, it's just it's just a paper thin
The movie plays like it was written by an angry
Uh, well, you know what I got a better analogy and I said this when we recorded before
This is your parents
Entertainment that's what this is
No kid likes to get preached at
No kid likes everything to be dry
No kid wants to learn the lesson kids want to have fun
Kids want something rebellious
And the problem is is all of these people who are now in their 30s and 40s
Some of them in their 50s who are obsessed with their children and worship their children and want to protect their children at all costs
Are creating all of the entertainment
And they think they're making things that kids like and they're repeatedly falling on their face
You see this over and over and over and over again and they try to pass the buck and say
Oh, this got bad reviews because the trolls and then no no no no
It got bad reviews because it got bad reviews
It's not a good movie now the trolls don't help their dicks they suck
But you're making bad movies
This is like when they would call the school assembly and the none would get up and tell us all about drugs and how drugs work
And as a 13 -year -old kid I'm sitting there rolling my eyes like what the fuck does this lady know she's never even had sex
You know like
It's it's crazy and they think that they're making things that kids want to see and they're not and that's why this stuff isn't being well received
That's why bombing that's why you see these franchises launch and then close, you know within within a month later
You know well we had plans to do this this this and this now we're not doing it now
Stop
Stop this is not what people want to say. He nobody wants to see it
I completely agree, you know and
I who's take I would have liked to see on this would be actually Diablo Cody
I know she is a polarizing figure, but I really love young adult. I did love tolly. I like Diablo Cody. I like her
Yeah, I love the second half of Juno and I recently rewatched
Jennifer's body after being told by many people that it was underrated and misunderstood and blah blah
And while that's not a perfect movie like yet
You know she's dealing with
Issues in that movie in a much more subtle much more interesting way that kind of lets the viewer have the fun
of
Finding the parallels to like Megan Fox and
in real life and her character and
and
You know all the different issues that movie brings up about
People's appearance and what it means and so on and so forth also to let me point out too because you said I was going a little deep on
Blum. Yes
You actually mentioned this to me before I'm but I'm gonna
I'm just I'm only saying that to give you credit for where I learned it from. Let's not forget to mention
This is the man that said there were no women directors out there
Yeah, well they said why have none of your movies been been directed by women and he said to be honest
There aren't that many women directors out there and there are none that are interested in horror
So that's pretty fucked up I would say
So I don't know that he did the appropriate search here for like the the best candidates because
And I hate to shit on the people and I hope they make better things in the future
They've made better things in the past. That's why I'm blaming him. I don't think this was the creators. I think this was
Yet again, this guy stepping in look. Let's call spade spades
This is a white guy who's got a shitload of money telling people what's wrong with white men and what we need to do for women
This is the core of the problem in this discussion. This is everything bad about this discussion
I don't want to hear from Jason Blum about why white men are evil as he buys a 9 .8 million dollar brownstone in Brooklyn
And contributes to the
to the
gentrification problems out in that burrow. I don't want to hear it. I don't want to hear it dude make another fucking insidious
Show me a few monsters and that's it
You know, and if you're gonna do it step aside and let people do it the way you let them do it then let let peel
If you're gonna give peel that kind of because it's it's so obvious that peel had so much more leeway
Because he was peel even before get out. You know what I mean? Like Jordan was very established
It is so painfully obvious that they let Jordan do his thing
and because he and Keegan were incredibly sought after
right
Or key excuse me
We're incredibly sought after after that show ended and it was clear that Jordan got a lot of rope to do his own thing
And it shows in the product. It's it's blatantly obvious in whiplash
That that movie was not and then the stuff that really has Blumhouse really written all over it
It's all stuff like this. It's like come on and give me a break
hog down
Way down and also they stole the best scare out of exercise three
They just replicated it completely down to the way the killer is dressed in the scene
The way the shot is done everything. It's just completely stolen. They stole the the lady coming out with the scissors
Moment from exercise right
And put it
Joe's got the anger today that I had when I walked out of that theater one year ago
And unfortunately I couldn't talk to a single person about it because no one saw this movie
But now that it's hitting HBO HBO Max everybody's quarantined. I feel like people will be checking it out
And I imagine sorely disappointed hog is down as well
Folks, my name is the Patrick Walsh on Instagram and Twitter
I recently recorded a
Pat's pre -Christmas solo movie corner
Where I go through all of the kind of for your consideration type movies that are being dropped on all the streaming services right now
all about big Oscar contenders
um
And then before December is up as a little bonus gift
I'm going to do the long promised
Oliver Stone every movie he ever
Wrote or directed. I'm not counting his documentary work. I'm not gonna watch that shit
I'm just doing the narrative to watch his showtime series about America. No, but
Yeah, so that'll be you know definitely an hour plus kind of episode a deep dive into the filmography of Oliver Stone
And that will be dropping at some point between now and the first of the year
Thank you for bearing with us. We've had some audio issues
But I think this one win -piece together will be great and
We've also got the Q &A up so enjoy that as well
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram and Twitter happy holidays to all
Check out the Joey Roaches sandwich shop pop up in New York City at the stand currently
Uh in Union Square
Uh, we'll be closed Christmas week and we'll be back in the new year
So come visit us then and delivery will be on and pop in at that point too when's it a Friday 12 to 4 p .m
On top of that
Sal volcano and I have taste buds the new food debate podcast on the no -press network
Which you can find on youtube check us out over there along with the other new show hey babe featuring Sal and Christopher
No, that's our show folks. We love you. Good night
Merry Christmas, everybody. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell