Background Music
Mm -hmm, mm -hmm.
Tabling a discussion.
Wait, that means putting it away, right?
I was trying to do a play on the coffee.
Anyway, we're here coffee talk about the coffee table.
How about that?
I love it.
That's great.
But first, something even more disturbing.
The, yeah, we're gonna go through this Apple music list.
I also would like to mention that I didn't eat for five days.
All I had for five days was water.
I'm just sort of reset my downsides.
Oh, yeah, that sounds healthy.
Well, if you look online, there are numerous benefits to it.
Sort of re -grows yourselves and et cetera, et cetera.
But I feel so good today because I got to start eating again at noon
and you obviously have to start very slow.
But like, you have a pickle and it tastes like the best thing
you've ever had in your life.
That's kind of one of the benefits of it.
It makes you re -appreciate everything.
You're like, oh my god, this pickle.
And I lost 11 pounds.
Which is good.
Yeah, I feel, I like it.
I like doing it.
Great.
Also, I'm going to sequence the Stone Age tomorrow
in Santa Barbara and I'm excited about that.
I don't know why.
I just wanted to give you a little personal info
before we jump into something.
Any turn around on the new album yet?
I'm telling you, I think it's really excellent.
I've kind of let it go from my,
I don't listen to it, you know, I moved on.
I listen to their old albums more.
Fair enough.
I just watched a concert of theirs on a flight
one from this new tour or recent tour.
And it was excellent.
There was one of the great live bands I would say for sure.
And the only good rock band currently, you know,
I like Arctic monkeys and a few others,
but like not many and not as much as them.
They've become one of my favorites, Queen's.
And, you know, the, the new Fuman shoe,
so excited comes out in June.
Both songs they released are excellent.
Very much about those singles.
I didn't know they're out there.
They're not like single singles.
They're just, if you go to the album,
there's two songs you can listen to now.
Okay, they're both great.
All right, Apple's top 100 best albums.
This is of all time of all time all genres.
Yes, there we go.
Nothing before like 1972, by the way, it's on the list.
Yeah, I mean, it seems like it was done by children.
And then you look at the, I all I saw was Nile Rogers
who they always asked to vote on these things.
I love not Rogers.
I'm not sure why he's always the go to.
But I don't know who the voters were,
but we need to talk to all of them very soon.
Number 100.
Also, let's not let this devolve into look, look,
tell your Swift or what you know, we don't need that.
But we're kicking things off with an album.
I've never even heard of Robin.
It was 100 Robin body talk.
I do own this album, probably the gayest album, my own.
And the big single from it was dancing on my own,
which is one of the great pop songs of the last 10, 20 years.
Whatever.
Beyond that, the album has another good song or two
and some catchy shit on it.
It should be nowhere near a list of the greatest of all time,
which is going to be the case for a lot of these, I think.
Isn't this the lady that got in trouble for something?
Didn't she cast something inappropriately or something?
Cast something in a person?
Didn't she producing something and she like, oh,
see it, never mind, okay.
All right, Robin.
Didn't cast a real autistic person or so?
I don't know.
Something like that.
Yeah, Robin, okay, second, hotel California by the Eagles at number 99.
The Eagles, in my opinion, have never written a good song.
Let alone hotel California, but there it is.
I agree.
I don't like the Eagles.
And I think Jeffrey Lebowski put the ultimate nail
in the coffin of them when he said he fucking hates the Eagles.
I think a whole generation was like,
I also hate the Eagles.
But I can't say the album doesn't belong there.
It's like one of the biggest set up albums of all time.
Everybody's parents own it, whatever.
But yeah, I don't like the Eagles either.
Astro World by Travis Scott.
Travis Scott, Travis Scott stinks.
In the way, this album came out in 2018.
I love how many albums I think it was more recent than that.
I mean, Travis Scott, what are you talking about?
Right below them at 97, the Rage Against the Machine debut.
Rage Against the Machine, never for me.
I never understood like driving around listening to them.
It's just not something fun for me to listen to.
Are you a fan, Joe?
Yes.
And this next run of four, three albums are the first three on the list
where I was like, okay, I get it.
Rage Against the Machine, Self -titled, makes sense.
Lord, pure heroin makes sense.
Usher confessions makes sense.
These were monumental records.
They were breakthrough records in their genres.
They were massive phenomenon records.
Like these, I was like, okay, these three make sense.
These, if you're talking, Rage blew the lid off
of the merging of rap and rock.
Like that, you know, that's them.
Yeah, they belong on there.
They're not my favorite, but they belong on there.
Lord was the first like of that, you know,
there would be no Billy Eilish without Lord in my opinion.
And I think Billy Eilish is great, but my point is is,
oh, you'll see her on the list too.
Blue the lid off of that.
And then Usher, as far as like modern day R &B,
Michael Jackson style musicians, yes, there you go.
Those three made sense.
Yeah, that's his best album.
We hit the next stop with Burial.
Who the hell is Burial?
Burial is an electronic music outfit.
They are definitely the most Indian obscure artist
on this list.
I have that album.
I don't listen to it.
I know it's beloved by the pitchforks of the world,
but can't see why it's here.
Same with Salange, a seat at the table.
Like the Beyonce and her family make up
like 10 % of the list.
Salange, I do not understand.
She is Beyonce's younger sister.
I don't think we would know who she was if she wasn't.
And to put her on this list is absurd.
I don't know any of the songs.
I don't know any of her music.
Yeah.
I do know the next person, Tyler, the creator,
not for me.
I respect what Tyler has established,
but I do not think he, I don't,
well, I don't know.
I'm iffy about whether or not he should be
on a greatest of all times list.
I'm not iffy, he should not be on the list.
He is nowhere near that good.
They've chosen the album Flower Boy.
Second or 91, listen without prejudice volume one
by George Michael.
I think I have almost all,
well, I have the ones that are good.
That album, I don't even think it's George Michael's best.
He's not, he wasn't an album artist.
He was a singles artist.
Sometimes it's like they want to honor people who are dead
and it's like, but that's not what this is.
There's no, in my opinion,
there's no good George Michael album.
There's great George Michael songs.
That's how I feel about Tyler,
where I'm like, there's cool stuff.
It's just like, I don't have an album.
No, maybe I'm wrong.
AC, DC back in black without question.
Yes, way too low on the list, I would say.
It's too low.
I mean, I would, I would put highway to hell on
before I put on back in black.
I prefer it.
I just mean, you know, back in black is the staple,
but I also prefer highway to hell.
Gaga, the fame monster.
Absolutely.
Gaga, just an iconic.
Well, I never heard that album.
I consider her a singles artist,
but maybe the albums are great too, I don't know.
Nina Simone, absolutely.
Put a spell on you.
87 blue lines, massive attack, very influential.
I like that album.
It reminds me, though, of like,
sitting in a lounge, you know, like a hookal lounge
or something.
But, you know, for sure, a great,
like an album to me should be like an experience.
Doesn't have to be a concept album,
but it should work as a cohesive whole.
I think if you're on the top 100 list,
there should not be bad songs on it.
And I do not think they have done a good job of that.
My life, I married Jay Blige.
Sure, she's a legend and aren't be legend.
I think she's excellent.
And I also think this is insulting
at how low on this list she is,
considering the R &B singers,
they have a much higher than her.
Mary J. Blige, to me, is our generation's
Diana Ross or Aretha Franklin
or, and for her to be only at 86
with what, in my opinion, as her masterpiece album
is insulting to her.
With Casey Musgraves, an okay country artist
at 85 beating Mary J. Blige,
Golden Hour, an album I'm not familiar with,
but, you know, that album wasn't on top 100 lists
of the year when it came out.
Doggy style by Snoop Dogg, of course.
Absolutely.
Patty Smith, I'm not mad at.
Patty Smith, I dislike, but that album
is always on these lists, horses, you know,
people love it, it's very influential.
50, I'm a big 50 fan.
Get Richard Dye trying is not one of the top 100 albums
of all time, not even close.
I mean, it's a crazy, crazy thing, it's ridiculous.
I'm a huge fan of 50 set.
That is not a top 100.
I'm sorry, it's just not.
I have sat in a sauna with 50 set.
That's how big a fan of him I am in Las Vegas, Nevada.
No, I'm not a huge fan.
I love what he's doing with P Diddy,
and I love that he's already made a documentary
about what a scumbag he is.
It's hilarious.
After the gold rush by Neil Young,
that yeah, it's, you know, the man has made numerous classic
near perfect albums.
If that's your thing, he's not for everybody.
But in the classic rock genre,
that's a legendary album, for sure.
If you like Neil Young, that's your problem, not mine.
Eminem, Mark Sharma, there's OP, sure.
It's a, you can't deny the landmark.
Yeah, sure, nature of that record.
It's a great record.
Lana, come on, guys, I like Lana Del Rey a lot.
I would not say Norman fucking Rockwell is her best.
And again, I wouldn't put her on any sort of top 100 albums list,
but I do like her a lot.
So many like her too.
I like her too.
I like 50.
It's like guys, this is 100 of all time.
I know, I know.
It's like Elton John Goodby -Yellowbrook Road.
You know, I love should be higher.
It's his best.
The best of one of the best guys ever.
Madonna like a prayer?
What?
No.
Madonna, yes, like a prayer?
Yeah, not her best.
Yeah, no.
Like a prayer is not the one that should be here.
It should be like a, I think, like a virgin.
I like her early ship as a, as did the old man and reservoir dogs.
Now, here's money, well, this is, this is where it starts to get real pro.
Bad money at 76.
Now, this, did this album come out this year or last year?
Just guys, bad money.
Come on, guys, it's silly.
Top it.
2000, my thinking is, are they maybe going to do some like a warred show
and they want all these big people to be there or something?
That's the only explanation I really have for how bad money is on a top 100 list.
Apple Music is a lifestyle.
Apple is a lifestyle brand.
The iPhone is a lifestyle product.
Apple Music is a lifestyle service.
They are clearly aware that if they do not put things on here,
that speak to their most important customer ship,
the young 20s and late teens and even tweens,
they're going to have a problem with customers sticking with them
or backlash, you know, so they're, I mean, come on, guys, for Christ's sakes.
They're also so far in the distance to Spotify that maybe they're trying to boost their numbers.
75 Missy Elliott super dupe fly.
Yeah, it is groundbreaking.
I have the album.
I love it.
I do not think it's Missy Elliott's best album.
I think under construction is probably her best,
but I'm a huge fan of Missy Elliott.
She's a genius.
The downward spiral by nine -inch nails, of course.
I don't like it, but I get it.
I exclaimed when well placed on the list.
I just recently learned that this is pronounced
Asia by Steely Dan, not aha as I have been calling it for years.
I am and I'm going to say this.
Now I'm going to go beyond disturbed and say disgusted with myself.
But I was always told I got these friends who were obsessed with the Dan as they call it.
And they convinced me to go with them to see Steely Dan only because Elvis Costello was opening.
And I wound up leaving during Steely Dan is how much I hated them.
And I think what I finally realized is that I hate how much I hate how they look.
They are the ugliest, you know, the main guy.
And they told me they were like, Pat, that was probably when I was about 30 or some.
They were like, in a few years time, you will get older and you will start to understand the Dan.
And I was like, fuck off.
I hate them. I don't even like their catchy songs.
And sure enough in the past couple months, I have started really falling for Steely Dan.
I like them.
That's one of the best produced albums of all time.
If you want to see a hilarious behind the music, Toobie has a great making of Asia,
sorry, Asia,
thing making of the album where they just like, they torture Michael McDonald who's doing backup vocals.
He would like, we would do thousands of takes of the backup vocals, but you hear it, you know,
like the, I think the albums are immaculately produced.
And even though I would not tell it to anyone other than right now in this podcast,
I get Steely Dan's inclusion.
I did.
Sissa Joe.
I think you heard me.
Sissa.
I think Steely Dan sucks.
That's fair.
Sissa, I don't know or Sieza, I think it says, I think it's Siza.
I don't know.
Siza, I'm not familiar with.
It's Siza for music.
I've heard her name a million time where I've seen it a million times.
I've never quite known how to say it before.
SOS, there's another album that came out in 2022.
I don't know the album.
I can't speak to it.
it. I like it. It has no business being here. I like it. I own it. But no. Now this next
run is pretty. Now we're getting somewhere. Now we're getting the next, yeah, the next
several actually. So 71 trans Europe expressed by craft work, not my favorite craft work album,
but another band I've gotten super into lately. I saw them in 3D at the bowl, which was sick
and beyond influential, like in terms of electronic music. There'd be no Kite without it.
And on and on and it's major hip hop influence. It's huge. It's a very important record. Straight
out of Compton, NWA, then which is the rap version of Master of Puppets by Metallica, which is
right in front of it. Uh, that's that's perfect placement of two great, great albums that really
represent their genre in a beautiful way, uh, followed by an album that is sort of that for the rock
world. 68 is this it by the strokes, one of my all time favorite albums and gone to my head,
I might prefer a room on fire to it. And then I love is this it. I've listened to it probably more
than any album. And then the album of that equivalence to the trip hoppy fusion hip hop world,
Portis heads dummy. Absolutely. And then the version of that to the English, uh,
Hunk slash Indy Rock, whatever of the early 80s, the Smiths, the Queen is dead like that. They're
they're they're they're now they're on the right track. Now they start hitting it. Then they'll
lose it again shortly. But, uh, Queen is dead is the best Smith's album. I love the Smiths. Um,
people call him a singles band, but no, I disagree.
Uh, 65 day lost soul three feet high in rising, a masterpiece with our question. And I,
reason, I was recently talking to Joe about how I prefer, um, wait, what is the album, Joe?
Day lost soul is dead. Day lost soul is dead, particularly the back half of the album, I think,
is insanely good. Love day lost soul. Happy to have them, uh, around still making music on Spotify,
putting out vinyls, bodywism by Erica Badu. I completely respect Erica Badu. I saw her open for,
I want to say Saint Vincent and she was a lot of fun. I just don't like her music and I never have,
but, you know, some some things are a matter of taste. I think that album deserves to be there.
Um, right in front of it, Jimmy Hendrix, are you experienced your brainer right in front of that?
Tupac all eyes on me. No brainer right in front of that. Sade loved the lux. Again, no brainer.
To me, Sade is kind of the predecessor to Erica Badu. Uh, Sade, what a voice. What a voice.
Then you got velvet underground in Nico, which if you're going to get, I don't really like the
velvet underground. I think Lou Reed tries to be Bob Dylan and it's, when it hits, it's cool and
when it doesn't, it's boring, but that is an amazing record and that is the record that should be here.
Well, I love them. I'm surprised it's so low on the list. Uh, I think you could put almost any other
albums on here for sure. And then I said earlier, I like the Arctic monkeys and this is not anywhere near
their best album, AM. It's probably got their biggest hits on it, but it's not their best. And
that's when the list starts to really not make sense when you see the velvet underground and the
Arctic monkeys after them. Like what are you talking about? Um, Oasis. Yeah. Sure. It was, it was a
monumental record. The angel of Lauren. In fact, the angel of voodoo, when you told me the number one,
which I don't not agree with on this list, we'll get to it. But when you told me the number one,
I thought to myself, the angel of voodoo is a better version of that album. Like, yeah. Um,
that's a really good album, man. That's a really, really good album right in front of it. The cure
disintegration. The cure. I fucking love the cure. Talk about a great live band and uh, disintegration
is probably their best. Sure. Anti is probably Rihanna's best at number 55, but that's only because her
other albums contain a lot of filler. And that one is just 10 really good pop songs.
Maybe they felt they had to include Rihanna. And that is her best at 55 year out of your mind, you know,
where I'm not in sync with these people as I prefer Rihanna to Beyoncé. They gave Beyoncé a lot
of spots in this list. Um, I love Supreme by John Coltrane. Another thing that I have grown to
appreciate with with with ages jazz. And I never thought I would. But sitting around the house on a
Sunday, you know, uh, whatever you're doing straightening straightening books or whatever you're
doing with your Sunday morning, like I love jazz. I'm into it lately. And John Coltrane is one of
the best. But since saying that that's the first that's probably the oldest album on this list,
aside from Charles Davis that will come up on later. Yeah. There isn't there isn't one
uh, Billy holiday record on here. There isn't one. Ella Fitzgerald record on here. I mean,
it's like they they decided clearly this they were stopping at a certain year. Yeah. Yeah. I mean
for Christ six guys, you know, like, I don't know. I those those records haven't, you know, Robert Johnson.
It's important stuff. It's like, yeah, you know, anyway, go ahead. I'm sorry. Well, they're,
yeah, they're clearly not going to create. They're not trying to create like, what do you call that?
The what do you call that when you're trying to create the
what's the word, Joe? Compendium? Yeah. Lexicon. Is that it? No, Compendium. I don't know. I think like
I wrote like Rolling Stone when they do their top 500, they're trying to give you like the template.
Like these are the, if you want to, if you're a student of rock and roll or whatever,
these are the albums you must own or whatever, that's clearly not what this list is about.
Rolling Stones at 53 per exile on Main Street. You know, I love that album often considered their best.
I prefer sticky fingers, but uh, can't argue with the stones. I know you're not a fan, Joe. I fucking hate
the Rolling Stones. I think they have no business anywhere. I love them and exile probably has the
least singles of any other albums, and uh, it's a double album just full of great rock. It's a great
album. Speaking of great rock, appetite for destruction by G and R. Absolutely. Prince sounded the
times. Absolutely. Masterpiece. Yes. Keep my favorite Prince album either. I like that one a lot.
It's fantastic, but not my. Kate Bush. I'm not a big fan of Kate Bush's music, but I think she's
incredibly important. So I'm happy to see her on the list. She is only on this list because of
Stranger Things, which really goes to show you how stupid this list is. Like they would never have
put her on here without that song being on Stranger Things. And by the way, she's probably only on
Stranger Things because big boy from Outcast, his favorite artist is Kate Bush, and he's been very
vocal about that. And I have a feeling that that's what turned somebody on to Kate Bush. Yeah,
I like Kate Bush, and I like that album, but I mean, her albums always have a few songs where you're
checking your watch. You're like, we're talking about unicorns in a meadow here. What's going on?
Yeah. The Joshua Tree by U2 at 49 goes to show you how far U2 star has fallen. Sometimes when a band
keeps making music, you just like, it's what we talk about with Nirvana, a big part of their legend
is that they made three albums and he died. And I think it's why they're so highly regarded.
One of the reasons you know, I love Nirvana, but the Joshua Tree by U2, when I was growing up,
was always in the top 10 of all time. And to see them falling is like, I think it's just they've
made a lot of shitty music in the last 20 years. I love the Joshua Tree. I don't listen to it ever
now, but I used to listen to that every night to fall asleep. And then when I got more depressed,
I replaced it with back sea change so that I could cry myself to sleep every night.
Beastie boys, Paul's boutique, absolutely. No, that needs to be higher.
Higher? No, I think that's right where it needs to be.
That I think it could have been lower to be honest with you. All right.
That's just my take. Drake, take care. I mean, look, Drake is without question a monumental.
Well, yeah, I can't, I can't deny Drake. I don't think Drake deserves to be this high.
He doesn't, but not a public. That's insane. That's insane. I don't think Drake would agree.
Take care is his best album by a considerable margin. He's also a guy who puts out a lot of
shit lately. But I think take care is a really, really good album and got me through some tough times.
Exodus by Bob Marley. Yeah, fine. Bjork, sure, yes. All right. People like Bjork, I can't imagine sitting
and listening to her. I saw her in concert once and I don't get her. Homeogenic is the
44 interventions by Stevie Wonder. Yeah. Stevie Wonder made five of the best albums of all time
in a row. And interventions is unquestionably one of them. Not a bad song on it.
Remain in light by talking heads. I know you're not a fan, Joe, but I would have put this higher.
I'm a fan. I don't think this is the one though. I think a fear of music or the first one should have
been on here before this one. Don't you agree? Yes. I mean, Remain in light has once in a lifetime,
which is there, you know, far and away, their biggest hit. But I like all their albums. I wouldn't say
that's my favorite, but generally it's considered their best. Control Janet Jackson. It should have
been rhythm nation. It shouldn't be control. It should be rhythm nation. Speaking of which, by the way,
Michael Jackson's, I don't know. No, he is. I'm sorry. Okay. Sorry. Yeah, it should be rhythm
nation, but absolutely outcast. Same thing. Aquaman. I know. Aquaman has a great record over,
over. Oh, for Christ's sakes. What's the third one? Speaker box. Love blah. No. The one before that
with Miss Jackson and oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. No, that's a that's a masterpiece. What is it? I'm called
white. Why aren't we doing stanchonia? Stanchonia. Um, I love Aquaman. I love all of our cast albums,
but I would agree. I think that was the better album. It's got that like put them on the map, for sure.
Um, I never loved to man the way I love you. Aretha Franklin's best album. I mean, of course,
yeah, she needs a spot on here, for sure. No, no, no, no. You a Naz guy, Joe? Yeah. Who is it?
Who the hell is it? Are you a Naz guy? Do or die? Are you just like Elmatic? I only have listened to
Elmatic. Well, Naz is, I love Naz. I'm always excited to see his name on something. He's got a new
album coming out, fully produced by DJ Premier. I'm very excited for that. Um, you know, DJ Premier is my
favorite producer. Naz is amazing. Naz also though has 37 records. So it's like, you know, it's kind of
hard to keep up with him. Like he's kind of like motorhead where there's like a new album every year.
You know, like Jesus Christ, but Elmatic of course is the one. Um, Carol King tapestry. I know
the importance of this record and I, I think it's good that it's here. Yeah, well, you know, a classic
of folk rock. I listened to it very recently. Actually, I bought it for a dollar and I was like,
yeah, these are beautiful songs. I think Carol King has, her songs have been recorded by people with
better voices. Her voice doesn't do a lot of for me, but she's a great songwriter. Same with James
Taylor, honestly, who used to be her boyfriend. I'm like, I don't, I'll never listen to James
Taylor. Right. He's this boring as they come. Uh, enter the wood sang. I would put it higher than
37, but of course, yes, that's a, that's one of the great hip -hop albums ever made. Beyoncé, of course,
she's the queen. She's got to be on here, not for me, but she's got to be on there. Yeah.
The clash London calling can't deny that would have put that one higher. I don't think out of 19
songs. There's a bump cut on that album. It's one of the great punk, punk records. We're,
there's a, we're about to have a shake up after this next one. Public Enemy takes Nation
to Millions Thones back. Absolutely. Yes. Just unquestionably important and amazing record.
I'm glad it's on here. Arguably should be a little higher in my opinion, but I'm glad to see it
as high up as it is. And I prefer the follow -up by the way. The pop. Oh, fear of a black planet. Yeah,
I actually would make, would have made fear of a black planet. But I think that's the most important
of the, of the records and, and the best. But it's great to see this one on here.
The fact that fucking kid A is on this list, it makes me want to spit. It's a shit record.
It's got two good songs on it. If you're not high, it is unfucking listenable.
How this is here over robot kids or whatever the fuck the one.
Oh, but kids. The fuck is the one before this? It sounds like a crap fork out.
Okay, computer. I'm hoping it's higher on this list. I don't know. But if it's not,
then that sucks. Okay, computer and the bends are radio heads best albums. They are perfect.
And it's this whole thing that when kid A came out, they felt like they had to, like,
everyone was talking about how they changed the game. They, can you believe they made muse an
electronic album as if such a thing had never existed. I love kid A, you know, probably just because
of my age, when it came out, you know, I was in college, when everybody was like, dude, you're kid A.
But okay, computer and the bends are infinitely better albums with infinitely better songs.
You are right. Ready to die in a TORIUS BIG. One of my favorite albums of all time, of course.
Yeah, that's a landmark landmark hip -hop album. I think all eyes on me deserves to be higher.
And I only say that because in front of ready to die. I only say that because of the feud.
But I think all eyes on me is the better record in my opinion, but whatever.
I prefer Biggie to Tupac and I prefer ready to die to that album, yes.
I'm the opposite. That's what makes this country great, which is different.
A Lannis Moore set Jagged Little Pill at number 31.
I remember my sister listening to this cassette tape before my mom threw it out the car window
when she heard go down on you in a theater. And I don't like a Lannis Moore set at all outside
of you ought to know. Obviously, she had massive, massive hits. The half of the album that aren't
hits are really shitty fucking songs. So I would not put it at 31, but okay.
Billy Eilish, her first album. I've only heard the singles on Billy, but I think she's created a
whole new kind of pop world. She's massive. Okay. But 30? Yeah, I think it's too high on the list.
But like, let her grow up. I hope she'll hopefully make better albums like that.
Come on. Yeah. Tribe Called Quest, Low End Theory. Not my favorite of the records, but it should be
here. I love that album, but what's your favorite, Joe? Midnight Marauders, probably, or the first one
to instinct. Probably Midnight Marauders. I think those albums production -wise, it's very clear.
This is sandwiched by people's instinctive travels and Midnight Marauders. And those are much
bigger records. There's a lot of interludes and it's more of an experience. It's very clear when they
did Low End Theory. They're like, let's just do one where we go in and hit them with like 12 tracks
and get out. And it's a great record. Yeah, I love that album. It's to me when I imagine putting
a needle on the turntable, I imagine going into that first song on Low End Theory. Back in the day,
when I was a teen, it's got that feel to it. 28, Dark Side of the Moon by Pink Floyd. Honestly,
I've never seen it out of the top five or 10 in my life. This, I get it. I mean,
lack should be in the top 10. Both of those. Yeah. Their records don't leave the billboard chart.
It's like crazy. Choosing Zeppelin 2, of course, I love Zeppelin, but choosing 2, I don't understand
that, but okay, they deserve a spot, for sure. Kanye, my beautiful dark twist and fantasy. I think it's
too high on the list. I think he deserves to be here. By the way, let me say this. I would have
put college dropout above beautiful dark twisted runaway is his best song by such a considerable margin
that I think people overwrite the album a little bit, but it's good. It's great. And let me say this,
he's not good as a man. I'm just happy that we're back to a place. And this is something I used to
criticize, but it went so far in the other direction. I'm happy to see us back here. I'm happy to see
us back in a place where you can put a record like this on a list. And everybody understands that
you're talking about the quality of the record and not whatever the personal life of the guy.
For sure. For sure. I was really surprised by that. Like, I don't think any list of the best
movies made in the next 100 years will include Woody Allen. You know, so I was very surprised to see
that. The mind of blue by Miles Davis. Again, I had a real jazz period recently because I was using
it to write a particular project. And Miles Davis is as good as you've heard. I mean, kind of blue
is not my favorite of his, but that would be sketches of Spain, but I love Miles Davis and sure.
David Bowie, crazy that he's appearing for the first time on this list. My favorite is not
Rise and Fall. Ziggy Stardust. My favorite. I'd actually probably put five albums above it.
But yes, he is one of the greatest artists of all time. And that's a perfect. Yeah.
This is where things get a little insane.
Daft Punk Discovery. It's a great record. It's an awesome record. I wouldn't even argue if you
said it is one of the best records ever made. Fucking 23. Guys, what are we talking about right now?
I know. What do I tell you like? You know, if I had opened the list and discovery by Daft Punk
was at a hundred, I would have been like, that's where it belongs. This list is going to be great.
23 is weird. And I love Daft Punk. Springsteen -born to run. Yeah. I can't stand Springsteen, but sure.
I mean, I get it be here. I get it. But I prefer the river to born to run. But he's made also five
perfect albums in my opinion. Revolver by the Beatles. I fucking love. It's
not bad. It's up there. It's definitely top three Beatles albums for me. I know Joe, they're not for you.
But yeah, 21 is weird. Revolver is another one that's usually top five. I know Rolling Stone had it
at number four, I think. Revolver is the only Beatles out of my like. It's I own it. It's the one that I
like. It's a great record. Pet sounds. I'm happy to see pet sounds ahead of the Beatles, but
it's I've never seen pet sounds not at number one or two. I love pet sounds. My issues with it are
the long obnoxious instrumentals. And it's only a 12 song album. So like, I skip those every time.
They're not enjoyable to me to listen to. And I don't know. I love pet sounds, but
I may like be I may like other Beach Boys albums more if I'm being honest. The Chronic by Dr.
Dre. Yeah. It's a great record. I don't know that it should be at 19 of again, I would put
straight out of Compton above the Chronic. It's more important in more. Yeah. I guess it's not
about my put doggy style over the front. No, I that's nuts, but you're nuts. You're dumb, stupid,
asshole. I got to listen to them back to back. Sometimes that's what helps me when I watch waiting
for government and mighty wind back to back. I was like, Oh, I thought I preferred mighty wind. I
definitely do not. You got to sometimes compete against each other. Sure. And here we go.
1989 by Taylor Swift at number 18. I mean, that's my favorite Taylor Swift album. Sure,
but even with that, it's a B -plus. I think that's crazy.
Like, you know, Taylor is just not for me, but also it's it's it's it's she's undeniable. She has
done things that no other musician has done. So it's like, I assume she'd be pretty high on the list.
And I respect that. Even though it's not for me, Marvin Gaye, of course, what's going on,
Joni Mitchell, but no, but no, what's going on has been way much like pet sounds has been way
overrated for too long. What's going on is nowhere near his best album. It's got like seven songs on
it. There's just like some real like fruity annoying like instrumental shit on it. And it's very
like hippie -dippy. I like Marvin Gaye singing about fucking. I like the album. Let's get it on.
I like his divorce album a lot here in my dear, one of the angry albums I've ever heard of my life.
Yeah, I don't I don't really love what's going on. I'm never listening to it out of like
desire to enjoy it. I disagree. I think it's the best one. And I'm putting a lot of the social
stuff into this too. And I don't, you know, so I think it, yeah, I disagree, but I hear you.
Joni Mitchell blue, I'm not a Joni Mitchell fan, but sure that she should be here.
You don't got to swap without Joni Mitch. And blue is some of the, you know, again, it's not really my
bag, but the songs are beautiful and insanely well written lyrically. Now to put a del over Joni Mitchell,
to put a del over Taylor. What are we talking about here? I know. It is weird. Adele, like she always has
like two singles where like you hear them and like you got to kind of pull the car over because
they're so powerful and great. But the rest of the album is not great. Adele is like adult
contemporary kind of boring. And then she always has a couple bangers. So I don't understand that.
Rolling in the deep though, you know, that's what he, that's a song. That's an America. Dylan,
you know, you could tell me the guy never existed in his catalog was burned forever. I wouldn't care,
fucking less. I can't stand his music. Well, they put Highway 61 revisited at 14. Dylan has made
4 ,000 albums. The fact that he's only on here once. And for this album is kind of crazy to me.
He's usually got like 10 spots. Blond on blonde is a significantly better album. He made many
better albums than Highway 61 revisited. The blueprint by J. Z. I decided recently I don't like J. Z.
And I think a big, a big like reckoning is coming for J. Z. Much like P. Diddy.
Why do you think that? There's been so many rumors about him. He's tied to the P. Diddy camp.
There are very, very convincing rumors that he had this woman killed who he had cheated on
Beyonce with. She was like 30 years old tops. And as Kanye says, who would know this shit? And
he just, he's talking out as ass like always, but he's like, Jay Z has murdered people. And that needs
to come out. And I just think it's coming out. I think it's not, it's not gang shit. It's not like,
oh, you know, 50 cents. I caught nine bullets or whatever. I think he is one of those types
that as he gets richer and weirder and more involved in like this, this weird, dark lifestyle.
I think that he is doing shady shit. Much like Puff Daddy. And it will come to life is my opinion.
I just think that this album being at 13 is batshit, especially a record where it is frequently
said, no, I don't remember if not said this, but it is frequently said, like Eminem
outshines him on the renegade track. Like it's, this is not even Jay Z's best album to put this at
13 is fucking insane. I agree. I think maybe they did it so that it wouldn't be so awkward at home
between Beyonce and Jay Z when she had several spots on the list. Well, that's my next problem.
The next slot is okay. Computer by radiohead, which I said should have been on here over
today. Yeah. Absolutely. But just one, the fact that the fact that you got people on here with multiple
albums, guys, it's a hundred out. That's it. You get one slot. You don't, they should, yeah, they
should definitely confine you to one slot. Fleetwood and the artist's definitive album. You know,
like, of course, Mac rumors. I'm glad it's on here. I think it should be on here. It should not
be a fucking 11 when so much other shit was way down the list. That's my opinion.
I think rumors works there for me. It's got 11 perfect songs and Oh, Daddy, one of the worst
songs ever written. And the fact that they left off Silver Springs, one of the best songs ever written
in favor of Oh, Daddy is truly nuts. But I love rumors. That's all that keeps it from being perfect.
Lemonade. Again, I don't really get it. But look, let Beyonce is for the ladies.
You know, and the gays. There's not a lot of straight men being like, oh,
do you hear that Beyonce? So it's just she gets women. They get her. And I think it's just something
that's not really for us. So enjoy. Never mind by Nirvana. Never seen it this low. I prefer
in utero some days. I prefer never mind some days. But absolutely belongs here. Yes.
Kendrick Lamar, good kid, Mad City. Excellent album. Kendrick Lamar, one of our great rappers of all time.
And especially of now, this should not be at number seven. Come on, guys. Come on,
guys. It should be way lower on the list. Yes. You skipped back to black by Amy Winehouse,
which is an album with no skips. It is great. But number eight, I got to imagine that is because of
her untimely death. Oh, sorry. Yeah. Okay. Stevie Wonder's got his second record on here. I thought
songs in the key of life would have been here before the other record. I love songs in the key of life.
Yeah. But again, amazing double album with just as alone, as is one of the all time love songs.
Everybody should get one slot. Now, here's where to me, this is and I love Frank Ocean and I love
this album. But to me, the craziest placement by far, this is number five blonde Frank Ocean. And
especially when you just when you see it above songs in the key of life, when you just look up at never
mind and rumors and okay, computer and you just scroll up, you're like, what are you saying?
What are you talking about? That's the craziest placement for me, blonde at number five. And I like
the album a whole lot. A second Beatles album, snooze. Purple rain, you can't deny. It's perfect.
At four, you skipped three Abbey Road. You know, not my favorite Beatles, but okay, I get it.
Thriller at two. If people are sitting around listening to thriller, I don't know who they are.
I know when when a song comes on at a bar, everybody goes, yeah, all right, or whatever, but I don't
think people sit around listening to thriller at home. Maybe they do. Yeah. And put them at number two.
Okay. It's a masterpiece. He's the guy that did it. That is the template. He did the he did nine perfect
pop songs. Yeah. Massive fucking success. Nas modeled Elmatic after Thriller. It's it's perfect.
It's it's perfect. It's you could argue that it should be at number one. I think.
Well, you could definitely argue that the number one spot does not belong to Lauren Hill.
Miss education of Lauren Hill. Me and Jo have talked a lot about this because I was just surprised
to see it at number one. And here's my issue with it. Lauren Hill made one album really. And then
like a really kind of shitty unplugged album. Maybe she's had something else come out that I forgot
about. I don't know. But as great as that album is, I can't imagine Lauren Hill would say that she
made the best album of all time. Oh, she yes, she would. She absolutely would. Okay. All right.
I just I when I when that album came out, I listened to it constantly. I fucking loved it.
I don't think there's really a bad song on it. And I get the love. But number one is nuts. That
should have been like a true legendary artist. That everyone can agree is the best whatever. That's
not Lauren Hill. And you know that. And I'm not only saying that because I've seen her twice. And
the other time she sang a tonal fake versions of her songs that had different melodies because she
had sold the rights to her songs. I don't know. That that's egregious to me. Miss education at one.
It shouldn't be at number one. And it's it should be on the list. It just shouldn't be at number one.
I mean, come on guys. But it is. I just read an eye if it was number 10. You know, whatever. But
it is one of the greatest selling albums of all time. Certified diamond, which is insane. That's
huge. But I mean, that can't be the only whatever, right? The only qualification. And it's not. It's
a great record. But well, to say it's even the best R &B album of all time is a stretch. That's what I was
yeah, saying to you the other day. It's like, come on guys. But but it is her only album. So maybe
that's part of it is like. Then she dropped. By the way, where are the Fuji's? They Fuji shouldn't
not be on this list at all. Fuji sting. Where's pros? Where's the Wyclef song featuring the rock? It
doesn't matter. Here we hear that song. No, nobody cares about the records you sold. It's it's bad.
Folks, that's the list. That was fun. Maybe someday we'll do our own list or top 10 albums for
that'd be a fun show to do. You know, here's my issue. Where's my favorite artist of all time? A man
whose career has spanned. 50 years. A man who has written 200 ,000 amazingly perfect songs. Mr.
the fuck is he on this list? He's not on there. By the way, too. It was a very
American outside of bad bunny. And a few English invasion bands. It was a very Americanized list.
Now bad bunny is here. But he does Spanish some Spanish speakers. I don't know if he does all
or some Spanish -speaking music. But the my point is is like, they're saying albums of all time. No,
this is American albums of all. It's there were no French artists on here. There were no African
artists. There were no, you know what I mean? So it's like, you know, he got to take all this
with a grain of salt. It is kind of dumb. Where's Duky? Which, you know, like that that that would
have fit in on this list is what I'm saying out that it's one of the best. Where's Duky? Where is the
most egregious submission it to me is where is Frank Sinatra? Frank Sinatra is the first ever of any
Michael Jackson Taylor Swift, whatever you want to call Sinatra is the first. Just he's the
free timber lake. There is no any of that without Frank Sinatra. And he's not on the list anywhere.
It's crazy. And he was also, you know, at a certain point in his career, early on he was a singles
artist, but at a certain point in his career he started making amazing concept albums. There's
four or five that would have fit on here. Great. All right. Let's get to our movie, The Coffee Table.
The movie is called The Coffee Table. It is a Spanish movie. It is deeply disturbing and we're
going to spoil it for you right off the bat. So if you still intend to watch it, this would be the
place to pause it. And if you have watched it, I'm sorry because it is a grueling experience.
We're talking about two pretty grueling movies this week, but this one obviously takes the kick.
The movie is. It starts funny. Yes. A couple. Yeah, it's like it's it's it's said on Amazon to be
a comedy, a black comedy. Yeah. It's crazy. One of these cheap furniture stores that sells like
really cheaply manufactured, ugly, gaudy furniture. I've been in a million all the times I've moved
and whatever. And they're arguing over a coffee table. And during the argument, the salesman
is very funny and doing a very funny, not believable sales pitch. Yeah. He's like, this is the
best coffee table in the world. You know, and it's it's made of unbreakable glass. And she's like,
what do you mean unbreakable glass? It's just it's unbreakable. And she's like, you're a bad salesman.
You're just a liar and they get a little argument. And they they reveal some stuff about their
marriage at this point that, you know, he the husband says, you got to make every decision.
Yes. Including having the baby. And she's like, oh, you don't want your son. And he's like, no,
I do. I'm just saying, I've I've let you lead the charge of everything you promise me. I could pick
out the coffee table. This is the one thing you said I could do. And she goes, I don't want this
thing. It's ugly. I don't care. And he buys it anyway. And the credits roll. We're off to the races.
This coffee table, which the salesman practices will bring them. Oh, it's two things.
The salesman says it will bring you happiness if you respect it. Furniture is to be respected.
Right. Furniture is not respected. Yes. Right off the bat.
The couple also has a newborn baby. And it is clear that the husband is maybe not quite loving
the marital life. But they go home. The wife says, I'm going to leave the husband alone for
the very first time. Go out and get some wine because the guy's brother and the brother's girlfriend
are going to come visit later in the day. While she is out of the house shopping, the husband is
walking around carrying the baby who won't stop crying. Won't stop crying. Thankfully, we do not see it.
But the man drops the baby onto the titular coffee table, the glass shatters even though it was a
legend to be unbreakable because he did not respect it. I guess if it is a powerful coffee table.
I actually thought the coffee table was going to be a supernatural thing. And I'm very relieved that
it wasn't. But I'm not. That's what I thought this was going to be. A magical coffee. This
hard thing. Yeah. He drops the baby onto the coffee table. And you hear the glass shatter and you're like,
okay, what where are they going here? How, you know, obviously, whatever we're about to see is going
to be horrific and terrible. But it went beyond my wildest dreams. They do it in like quick flashes.
You know, there's not like long close -ups of the baby or anything. But the baby is not only dead,
but decapitated. And the baby's head rolls under the couch. So, as I said, on the solo corner,
don't watch this movie if you have newborns, honestly. That would be a crazy thing to do.
I told my friend, Chrissy, I go, I would not watch, I go, I'm going to recommend a movie to you
because it's insane. And I think you might want to see it. I go, I wouldn't, and she was
telling me about it. I go, I'm not going to tell you anything other than I would not watch it
with a parent. Yeah. Same. If you're with any friends of kids, I wouldn't watch it with them. It's too
much. Yeah. It's like, you know, so anyway, I told that to friends and they're like, oh, it's a
pedo movie. And I said, no, it's not a pedo movie. But interestingly enough, there is a pedo subplot to
this movie. And that to me was one of the, I mean, it's a strange movie. No question. But he has a
neighbor who's 13. She's a little girl and she's like, she's got a crush on the dad. He comes
home. She's like, why are you always like flirting with me? And you tried to kiss me in the elevator.
And I'm going to tell my mom and all this. And it's a, it's a little girl's crush and it's silly.
But he doesn't shut it down in quite the way that he should. He should have probably gone to her
mom and been like, hey, tell her to quit doing this or whatever. He lets it go. So when the baby
dies and the wife is still out, he goes into sort of a catatonic state. He's sweating. He's stressed
out. He plays it very well. Like I believed he was going through this shit. And in a big shocking
move, he does not like call the police or anything. He wraps the baby up. He leaves the head under the
couch. He tried to pick it up. But he can't do it. He puts the remains wrapped in a blanket in the
crib again. Wife comes home. He's like, doesn't tell her. He keeps trying to hide it. He's like,
I'll watch the baby, blah, blah, blah. So all these things are building. It kind of plays out like
the world's darkest curb episode. I thought at the end, and then another interesting aspect is that
the brother has an 18 year old girlfriend, even though he is 45, let's say. So what I thought was
going to happen, and maybe this was in an original draft, is that the wife was going to think,
oh, because the girl comes in at the end and says he tried to kiss the hell. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, go ahead, though. And to me, my confusion is why was that in there? Just to add to the stress,
I guess, because when she comes in and says that, I really thought the mom was going to freak out like
you're a penophile, and then to find out it was way worse. But that doesn't really happen. And
I thought it was going to be like, you're just like your brother. He likes women that are too young
for him, and you do as well. But these things never sync up in a way that's satisfying or that makes
sense. There's all these fascinating plot elements that are there, and you're stressed out and you're
tense, and you're going through it along with them. But to me, the pieces don't connect in the most
satisfying way. Well, I have a feeling upon many rewatches, all of these different elements would
make sense. I will never know because I will never rewatch it. But yeah, there's a lot of, you know,
there's before the girl comes in at the end, you know, the brother pulls the sweating father aside
and goes like, what is going on with you? Why are you acting so weird today? Yeah. And he says,
I can't talk about it right now. And the guy, the brother says, is it the girl again? You need to go
report her. And the brother goes, she's just a kid. I don't want to scar her. And he goes,
she'll forget about it. Yeah. And that's the moment where you're like, wait a minute. Did he actually
do something inappropriate with this girl? That's weird. And then when the girl comes in at the end,
because he basically goes to the girl, he needs her help. He needs cleaning supplies or whatever.
And then because she's holding him over the barrel about what I want you to tell everybody
where in love, he agrees to it in order to get the cleaning supplies so he can get the blood off the
carpet before his wife gets home and all that stuff. So then later she does end up showing up for this
big announcement. Yeah. And when she's not allowed in the house and the wife, the mother slash wife
still doesn't know what's happening with the baby, won't let her in. The girl says, your husband
kissed me in the elevator and she says it in a way where you're like, I think he might have actually
done that. And you're not sure. You're just not sure. And you know, the brother, the brother having
an 18 year old girlfriend is an interesting detail to add because it sort of confirms your suspicion
that maybe this guy is up to no good. Because I don't know that it runs in the family necessarily,
but it just sort of helps you make that connection, I guess. So, um, so finally,
to be vague, I don't know. Finally, the brother, uh, the father goes into the bathroom. He's
having a nervous breakdown. The brother comes in and he goes, you got to tell me what's going on.
He confesses everything. The brother naturally is freaking out. It's horrible. As this is all
seen by the way, this, this, this cast, I don't, I didn't know who any of them were, but the brother,
the guy, the wife, I mean, these people are excellent actors. Yeah. Everybody was great. I was,
I didn't buy as far fetched and crazy as this is. I was along with it for the whole ride and I was
stressed out. Um, go ahead, sorry. As it's coming to a head, the girl shows up to the 13 year old girl
shows up to the door. Uh, and everything I just talked about transpires. And then you have this
situation where everybody's now in the living room. The husband's freaking out. The brother's freaking
out. The wife, like a comedy far sort of the wife doesn't know what's going on. Um, the girlfriend
of the brother doesn't know what's going on. The dog that the 13 year old girl is walking is in the
house. It's barking. It's barking. It's adding tension, adding tension. The wife is screaming for
the dog to shut up. The dog then goes start sniffing under around the chair where you know
the baby's head is. I started laughing at this point. I'm like, I think this is supposed to be funny
right now. What is it is? And um, there, there may be no darker comedy ever made if it is. Yeah.
And that was not laughing, but I mean, I got that it was supposed to be funny. And then um,
you're like, here we go. And of course the dog finds the head. Yeah. I did, I was upset that there
wasn't like the dog. I wanted the reveal to be the dog walks over with the head and the mouth.
And they didn't do that. They didn't do that. They just because the dog is barking.
Go to the chair and realize what's under it or something. Um, while this is all happening,
the brother's like screaming at the mom like, go outside. Please go outside. You're going to see
something you don't want to see. Yeah. I mean, it's fucking rough. And then the mom sees it and then
we stay on her and we see her grief and pain and stuff. Man freaks out. She goes to the balcony.
The father had said earlier in the film, he was going to jump off the balcony because he couldn't
face his wife and what happened. And it was an accident, but he can't come to terms with it. Right.
She throws herself off the balcony, cuts to a bunch of cops at the police scene at the end
of the movie. The cops are like, what's going on? They say murder suicide. What happened? I don't
know. Husband and wife, they're both jumped off the balcony. Their baby is inside. It's been
decapitated. And then it cuts to the brother and the back of the police car having a nervous breakdown
literally. Yeah. And they said he keeps saying the same phrase over and over and the cops says,
what is that? And he says the coffee table and the movie ends. Yes. It's a it's a perplexing film.
It's it's it's very, very well done. I just don't understand. I mean, I guess they just do stuff
different overseas. I'm just kind of like, why would you want to make this? I don't get it. It really
is like a phrasier style farce that builds to crazy hijinks at the end, but the inciting incident
is a baby beheading. It's almost like a movie was made in a dare or something. So I loved it. I mean,
I love anything that just puts me through the ringer. I love anything that when it ends, I haven't
even glanced at my phone, which is increasingly rare. This movie really just riveted me,
partly because with subtitles, you have to pay attention. But I loved it. My I have one question.
Another thing I didn't get when the salesman, the table salesman comes to the apartment.
Did you feel that he was hitting on the guy? Yeah. So the salesman from the store has to come
to the apartment because the table's missing a screw, right? Which the guy calls for before this accident
happens. Yeah. And the salesman, of course, shows up after everything is going sideways. And the
guy's covered in blood. The salesman thinks it's paint, but he brings him the screw. And he then says,
it's important that you have all the screws on the table. Otherwise, the glass actually could break.
You're like, geez. That baby left. That baby left. But yeah, he's absolutely hitting on the guy.
So that's that's what I mean by all of these elements probably make a little more sense upon a rewatcher
to because that's the second time the guy is trying to get into his apartment to deal with something
important. Right. And somebody who he is not interested in seemingly is hitting on him inappropriately
and being so forward. Right. So I don't know if that's supposed to be see as believable as it was.
You know, that's probably I assume how how a guy would hit on a guy in that situation and keep
it kind of vague and subtle and hope you pick up on the clues. But I did not think it was obvious that
he was hitting on him. When he's like, we should hang out. I still thought at that point this could
be a friendly thing. He does have him turn around. He writes in his back. He's a little, but there's no
moment where like he puts his hand in his shoulder or something and you're like, oh, okay. And that's the
whole movie. It leaves you with a little bit of questioning on all of these relationships and
what's going on. And that's that's sort of what makes it so interesting. But also a little frustrating.
If you thought it was clear, then it was clear. I obviously saw something there. I thought it was
for me. I mean, maybe it's just up to your interpretation. To me, it was here's another person.
This guy is not interested in. Yeah. Or perhaps could be hitting on this guy. And I guess that's
supposed to sort of illuminate why this guy is not doing so well with the responsibility of being
a parent now. And why he was enjoying marriage until this parent thing happened because clearly he's a
guy that was having opportunity thrown at him. Yeah. Whether he liked it or not. And now he doesn't
like it, especially given the sources it's coming from a 13 year old girl and then a sweaty salesman.
Right. But that's just maybe how I was like, maybe that's it. I'm not again, I'm not sure. And then
the brother comes in with like long hair and the flashy shirt and the young hot girlfriend. And
you know, I'm like, this is she even says like, I'm getting the wine for you and your brother. You're
like, you get this hint that the brother is the more fun and fast and free version of what this guy
used to be. Yeah. Yeah. And maybe even I think inappropriate. And you know, criminal with young
women. I don't know. Well, if this woman's 18 and pregnant, you got to figure he either, you know,
he might have met her at 17. You don't really know. But regardless, what you're going to take away
from the movie is the baby shit. And it's hard to even really convey how like the middle half hour
of this movie feels when you're just dreading the mom coming home and seeing this. And maybe that's
why he made the wife a little unsympathetic so that it wouldn't be so brutal. Like the wife is
pretty mean to him. But that man, it's brutal. Like you see a lot of blood. You don't you never see
really any parts of the baby post death. Now where I thought it stretched credibility a little bit
is when they're in the room with the crib and nobody's looking at the baby. But other than that,
I didn't really question anything outside of what we've already discussed. I thought I was
beautifully done. I loved it as much as you can love a movie like this. I loved it further
ride it put me on and the experience. But would I recommend it to anyone? I have to vet them and make
make very, very sure that they were ready to accept it. I agree with that assessment. And I will say
that was one nice thing. They really there's a lot of very good writing in this. But one my favorite
part of the piece of writing was they made the wife so condescending and so mean to it is like really
rubbing his nose and how when she doesn't know the baby's dead and he's like she's like why are you
bloody? And he's like the glass broke for the coffee table and she's cackling and she's got this
smokers like laughs. It's so flammey and when she won't stop and it's so mean until
they have this moment where she almost discovers the baby and then he stops her and they're in the
baby's room. And she just says like you know I love you and I'm sorry I know we haven't been
ourselves and whatever. And then you see her human side and you're like and then from there on out
she's lovely and you're like oh this poor woman oh my god like it is it really
fucks with your head like that man. It's very, very well done. If it were and it puts you right
into what would you do? I mean for me personally and I thought I didn't think I could ever kill myself
but I think that would be an instance where I would just leave a note explaining what happened.
Say I'm deeply sorry and jump out the window. That's what he does eventually but yeah I mean
this second it happens. I what I know I wouldn't have done is try to hide it from the wife but
I just think the guilt, the misery, whatever. And see the other interesting thing is that she tells him
that she doesn't think he likes the baby and she doesn't think he likes fatherhood and whatever.
I thought that was going to factor in where she was like you killed him you killed him intentionally
that doesn't really come up but there's just a lot of elements in it that make you go like where is
this going? And that's that's the beauty of it because how often do you watch a movie where you don't
know exactly where it's going? So I have to really praise it for that. It's super super effective.
I thought it was going to end. It's the only movie I've ever seen
where I was praying for a cliche terrible ending of it cuts back to them in the store.
It was all in his head. He's like you know what I'm not going to buy the table and they walk out.
Like that that's such a shitty trick. Yeah. And it's a trick that I would scoff at
10 times out of 10. This is the one time ever in my existence where I was like please just
please just let it be a horrible fantasy. Yeah. I know. Like it's not. Look my hog is up
for the quality of the film and the execution. It's a great movie. I just would never watch it again.
Yes Sam. My hog is way up. I mean I really really really liked it as much as you can. That kind
of thing. I just thought it was super beyond well done. Folks, thank you. I'm not sure what's
coming out next month. But I think we're getting to a point where we maybe we'll see Beverly Hills
Cop. Maybe I know we're going to get Furiosa Joe. Even though it's two hours 20 minutes,
you're going to see it. Furiosa is possible. I thought Kingdom of the
500 of the apes. It's just these run times guys. I just these it's ridiculous. It's
I loved the other planet of the apes. And I don't even want to see this one. It's the runtime,
it's the reviews. I'm like that was a great trilogy. We didn't need another one. Yeah. And it's
getting confusing. It's like now they are now they're actually saying no it sits right in between
the Heston and it's like then why are you not making it make sense with that then? Yeah.
Like then make it make sense. Like I don't understand. Like what I don't know man whatever it's
I will probably see Furiosa but it's just going to take the right day of blocking out four
fucking hours between drive times sitting there for two and a half. Previews all that shit. But
Nicole Kibman. Is she in it? Oh, oh, you mean when she comes out and tells you to stay keep going
to the movies. We'll be seeing some stuff folks. Don't you worry? We'll be back. We'll see
all the hits. Thanks folks. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.