🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
Folks, we'll see you in hell is back to discuss the fourth and final episode for this month of April. The first omen on the last episode of the month. The first omen. Clumsy title, but, you know.
I think it works. It's better than the last Exorcist Part 2.
Yes.
You know?
And it's better than, you know, like Omen Beginnings or something like that.
Omen .com.
Yeah. And I guess it does make sense if you really think about it in the literal, like, if you think about it in what it literally means, which is, no, this is the first omen that the world receives, that the devil is coming, then that's a good title.
But if you think about it in the movie franchise sense, where they're just like, this is the first one. You're like, no, I know.
Have they ever done, you know, I heard they're rebooting the scary movie franchise for Christ's sake.
What have they ever done?
What is there to reboot? What is there to reboot? It's not a reboot if you're just making a new parody of horror movies. It's not a reboot.
And it'll be, you know, like parodies of, what, Smile?
You know, like, we were really spoofing a movement at that time. Right now we just have a bunch of horror movies about trauma.
Are they going to take hits at A24? Doubt it. They already kind of did that with the Scream movies, the new ones.
I hate it.
Well, that's the thing. It was supposed, it was originally a spoof of Scream. That was the joke.
Yeah.
And the reason it was called Scary Movie was because Scream was a commentary on horror movies.
And then they made a comedy about that, that satirized, the thing that satirized horror movies. It all made sense.
And then eventually it was terrible when it was like, we're just going to spoof every horror movie that's happening.
And you're like, this isn't funny anymore.
Well, and then they, I didn't see it, but they started doing like date movie.
And I was like, you're doing a comedy spoofing comedies. Is that where we're at?
But honestly, that's a better move now than re -rebooting a spoof.
Because there are tropes to parody in romantic comedies.
Now, I'm sorry. I forgive you now because things have gotten so bad.
I understand date movie.
Who knows?
And who's going to be the star?
You know, it was what Charlie Sheen by the end of the Scary Movie franchise.
They bringing him back, bringing him his embalmed corpse out again.
It's just sad.
Anyway, Joe, I did not see the trailer speaking of things that seem like parodies, but they're not.
You were telling me this morning or yesterday that there was a new Russell Crowe picture.
Oh boy, this is wild.
So I'm on Instagram last night.
Because that's a good place to be.
And I see, I think it was posted by Fangoria.
It said, you know, trailer drops for new Russell Crowe.
And I see the word exorcism and I see the picture and it's Russell Crowe as a priest.
And I was like, oh, wow, I guess this is the Pope's exorcist sequel.
Yeah.
And then I look and I realized the movie is just called, ready for this?
The Exorcism.
That's the name of the movie, right?
Russell Crowe agreeing to do that movie one year after the other movie is so nuts.
And that movie actually took the time to give him like some cool character things that they could have kept.
Like him riding around on the little Dumb and Dumber scooter, but instead it's just a different project.
So this is, so the title is just horrible.
So I'm like, I got to look at this trailer.
What is this?
And I was like, maybe the Pope's exorcist sequel is just called The Exorcism.
So I try to Google it.
I mean, forget it.
It's like The Exorcism of Emily Rose, like The Last Exorcism.
Even Google is like, there can't be another movie with exorcism in the title.
What are you nuts?
So I finally get to the trailer.
It's completely unrelated.
It is a movie about, a movie about an exorcism.
And it starts with a character who I believe is his character's daughter.
Who's acting in the movie saying like, you know, these movies were riddled with tragedy.
The Omen.
So it's like cursed movies, right?
Right.
This one, oh, it's not the daughter because she says the actor your dad replaced.
This is what happened to him.
So the premise is Russell Crowe is an actor.
He's coming into a movie to take over a part of a guy that met his tragic demise during the movie.
And in the movie, within the movie, he's playing a priest who's conducting an exorcism.
And I said to Pat, I go, this is like repossessed with Linda Blair.
I'm like, he's doing now like a, but it's not a comedy.
Like he's doing like a movie that's self -effacing about an exorcism when he just did an exorcism movie.
It's so fucking confusing.
I don't understand.
This man was nominated for Oscars.
This is Russell Crowe.
I mean, clearly you can blame the man's agents or something, but something goes on with these guys.
You know, like, so I watch Vanderpump Rules.
I've never made a private matter of that.
I speak about it publicly.
But Lala, one of the characters on the show, who's a real woman, found out that she was married to a man named Randall Emmett,
who was doing a bunch of casting couch shit.
And now she goes on and talks a bunch of shit out of him.
He was a producer on The Departed, like a big time producer, and he became a character on Vanderpump Rules.
Okay.
Now he's directing under a pseudonym because of how badly the show trashed his name.
And he's directing like John Travolta movies.
Okay.
There's something going on in this world where it's Travolta.
It was Willis for a while.
Obviously, Willis is out of the game now.
Crows just entered.
But these were our major movie stars.
And some of them go right on being successful.
You're Clooney's.
Some of them have to go this weird route where they're in this.
Do they tell their agents like give if they're offering me five million, I'll do it no matter what it is.
No questions asked.
There has to be some money thing because Hage Willis for a while now Crow.
They're in five, six movies a year.
My theory is my theory is this with a guy like Crow Travolta just never had any taste.
He has to be led.
He has to be led by the collar to be like, John, this is what a good move to be in this movie.
Like he's never been good at it.
He's always look at his.
Look at the directors he's choosing.
This man worked with Fred Durst.
Yeah.
The filmmaker recently.
What's worse, Fred Durst stepping into a cinema realm with John Travolta or John Travolta guest vocaling on a Limp Bizkit track.
The second, the second.
So I say this is the only person who's seen the fanatic.
It was pretty good.
It's better than a lot of the movies we've talked about on this show.
You'd like it.
And by the way, Travolta is playing a mentally handicapped man.
We reviewed it.
We did it.
Oh, we did.
I thought just I saw it.
Okay.
We talked about it.
I liked the picture.
I don't think we were terribly kind to it, but it was way better than we thought it was going to be weird and interesting.
Yeah.
It had a pulse to it.
That's all I care about sometimes.
Here's the thing.
My theory with Crowe is because the man and I'm not body shaming.
The man's got a gut the size of like he's full on like like suburban dad like like that you're afraid of body.
He's heading into more like Orson Welles.
I mean, I know I think I know fitter suburban dads than you do.
You know, but like the big gut standing in front of the grill yelling at you for being too loud or whatever.
You know, like he's a but he's I think he's just like I've had it with the bullshit.
I don't give a fuck.
Yeah, I like to get drunk.
I like to eat.
Get me movies so I never have to worry about money again.
I don't even want to fucking think about it.
I honestly think that's what he's doing.
I can't tell the story.
It's not my story to tell and I can't say who it is.
But I have a friend who has a story about being in Russell Crowe's presence.
Uh huh.
It's nothing bad.
Yeah, the story is hilarious.
But it's like Russell Crowe is is like not not wild, meaning like out of control, meaning like he clearly doesn't give a shit.
If you like him or don't like him or whatever, he's just kind of on his own, whatever.
So I think that's what it is with Russell Crowe.
Liam Neeson is the most confusing to me.
This is a man.
This man was in Schindler's List and all he does now is another every movie is my daughter has been taken away like and I'm out in the snow fighting wolves to rescue her, whatever the fuck he's doing.
That was good.
The gray is a good fucking movie.
But but it's every movie.
I'm like, what the fuck is going on with this guy?
I picture his agents going to him and be like, Liam, we got something new for you, a little different direction for your career.
In this one, your son gets taken and Liam's like, well, that's not bad.
That's not bad at all, boys.
I like that quite a bit.
Yeah.
Anyway, he is the difference with a Liam Neeson is that's how he found his bank ability.
Taken was this big hit.
And suddenly here we have a new action star that we didn't have before, but he never did anything else.
Why is he not taking the Andy Garcia role?
Romancing Diane Keaton in one of these pieces of shit movies that come out like you're a handsome man.
But each one of his movies and each one of Statham's movies gets a theatrical release and makes a little bit of money.
You can't say that for these other people were talking.
Crow's still getting the Crow's still hitting the theaters.
But this one, by the way, this one, I never thought I'd see this with a Crow movie.
This one's got the shutter stamp on it.
That's not good.
Boy, the shutter stamp.
Wow.
So, yeah, that's not good, boys.
I think that Crow can go either way, much like a Willis at this point, much like a cage at this point of his career.
Some go theatrical, some don't.
I watched a movie that did not that he wrote, which starred RZA and Russell Crow called Poker Face.
I watched it because I love gambling movies, but like.
And maybe that's it.
If Crow's writing a gambling movie, maybe that's why he's doing five million dollar movies.
You know, he might have lost it all.
I just read that.
What's his face?
Bruno Mars had like a three hundred million dollar a year residency at Vegas.
They're like wondering why he came off the road because he's a little he's hot in his career to be doing a Vegas residency.
Usually that's on the way down.
And they come to find out that he's a prisoner now of the MGM casino because he has lost every dollar he has made and then some.
He lives there at the MGM.
Bruno Mars?
Bruno Mars is like deeply in debt and living at the MGM because he's blown it all and still performing there every night and then turning around and losing that money again.
Like gambling, you mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, oh.
So he's like Elvis, like at the end of the movie, he's in that like top floor.
Yeah, he's just in like a prison.
By the way, supporting cast for The Exorcism includes the second lead, Sam Worthington, who I didn't even know.
Aye, aye, aye.
The.
Between avatars, he got two weeks off.
Crowe's character's daughter is played by, ready for this, Ryan Simpkins as a character named Lee Miller.
Guys, can you make one of her names a girl's name so we know who the hell is who in the goddamn picture?
Ready for this?
Simply down.
David Hyde Pierce, who said no to the Frasier reboot and yes to this.
I just read some article about it.
He was like done acting and etc.
He comes back for this part.
He's in this and then rounding it out.
Adam Goldberg.
Remember Adam Goldberg?
This is a big cast.
Not a bad cast.
I kind of want to see it.
These are all people I thought were good actors and are good actors and that I haven't seen.
I haven't seen Goldberg in a while.
I thought Sam Worthington was pretty good, you know, like, I don't know.
Christ, he's a zero.
I mean, you know, look, he was he was another Russell.
He was going to be another Russell Crowe type and he just it just didn't.
That Clash of the Titans reboot.
But here's the one good thing produced by.
Well, if it was written by, I'd be more excited.
But Kevin Williamson is producing this.
All right.
It's directed, of course, by two people because nothing can be directed by one person anymore.
But Mark Alexandre Fortin directed The Final Girls, which was a good movie.
Yeah.
And Joshua John Miller.
Oh, OK.
I'm sorry.
Co writes.
OK.
Sorry.
They co -wrote The Final Girls.
These two, I guess they're partners, it says.
They didn't direct them.
And then they did a thing called Queen of the South.
This is their first direct.
They did two things.
They did The Final Girls, Queen of the South.
And now they're doing the exorcism.
They're directing it, though.
And they wrote it.
I don't know.
Maybe it'll be good.
Speaking of this, every movie has to be directed by two people.
I was in a meeting the other day about potentially, this is the only meetings I go on now, potentially
rebooting or remaking something.
And they kept going like, oh, yeah, you know, we're hoping to get radio silence attached.
And they said it like four times.
Like, I was supposed to know what that meant.
And finally I said, I'm sorry, what is radio silence?
What are you saying?
It is the name of a directing team.
They did Ready or Not and The New Screams.
And this person in the meeting was just referring to them as radio silence.
Okay.
It's a directing team.
It's like if me and Joe want to direct a movie and we were like, call us a phrase, you know?
That's a thing now.
The people that directed that were attached to my movie for a little while and then it's not happening.
But RKSS that directed Turbo Kid.
That's what they went by.
Weird.
I don't think I've ever seen that in a movie.
They directed Summer of 84 too.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
Speaking of, I meant to mention in our last show, I think Late Night with the Devil is the most pre -movie
title cards I've ever seen in my entire life.
What do you mean?
Like the studios that come up, like Paramount.
There was 25 of them.
It got laughs in the theater.
How many people produced it?
I'm not kidding.
I yelled at the TV.
I went, all right already.
It was kind of ridiculous.
Yeah.
Because at that point you're talking about everybody who contributed like a thousand dollars is getting a card for God's sake.
Maybe that's how they made it.
Who knows?
Let's get to that movie corn.
I would like to discuss what I got to say is probably one of my favorite movies, Affliction.
And I think I mentioned it on this show once as like a here's a lost movie.
It's hard to find.
You know, we were doing those kind of like sleeper hits, whatever.
But it's new to Blu Ray.
I can't, I can't talk up the transfer.
It's not a great looking movie.
And, you know, sometimes these Indies that were made in the nineties are just never going to look much better than they did then.
But it's finally out of DVD, which is the format I had it on for ages.
It's a serviceable Blu Ray.
You've got for my money, the best movie Paul Schrader directed.
I don't put it above, you know, Taxi Driver or Raging Bull.
But it's right in the heart of those Paul Schrader themes you love.
It's based on a novel by Russell Banks.
And what it is, is Nick Nolte as a divorced ex -wife hates him.
Daughter hates him and is scared of him to deal with the feelings of having everyone in town kind of think of him as a laughing stock.
He drinks very heavily, which makes him do even stupider and more out of control things.
And then his father comes back into his life in a big way.
His father kind of lives on the fringes of town.
Is it such a notorious asshole that people in the town talk about him?
Like in bars and Nolte overhears people talking about the legend of his father.
But the stories they're telling are about this legendary abuse and what a monster and what an asshole he was.
And that's Nolte's dad.
And also who Nolte fears he is becoming.
You can sort of see why this hits home so much for me.
But his father is played by the great James Coburn.
And as I said on Letterboxd, the best father son casting in like action movie history is Sean Connery and Harrison Ford in Last Crusade.
The best father son casting in like miserable, depressing movie history is Coburn and Nolte.
They talk alike, they look alike.
Nolte is so fucking good.
Coburn won Best Supporting Actor and he should have.
He's amazing in the movie.
But Nolte, man, it's Nick Nolte.
He's like a tough fucking hard ass drinking tough guy.
Whenever his dad is around him in this movie, he slumps.
Nolte completely hunches over to like where his head is hanging.
That is exactly what I do.
My dad doesn't even know that I have a sense of humor.
You know, so it's a movie about details.
It's a movie about like, you know, it's my favorite topic.
What the way you are parented can do to you as an adult.
And actually, that's kind of a hot subject right now.
If you look on TikTok and stuff, people are fascinated into like, how did I get this way?
This is one of the best movies ever about that.
Almost as an afterthought because those two are so great.
You've got amazing supporting performances from Willem Dafoe, who desperately wanted to play Nick Nolte's part.
But then when he saw Nick Nolte do it, he was like, I don't even know what I was thinking.
I wouldn't have been anywhere near that good.
And Sissy Spacek as a local woman who Nolte kind of hooks up with, she loves him,
but she's like, I'm not getting involved with this fucking drama between you and your dad.
Because once his mom dies, the dad is left to like reign his terror on everybody.
It's a dark as fuck movie. A plus five stars. Highly recommended.
Affliction.
I have two that I will be doing that pertain to today's film.
I'm going to talk about Omen, Damien Omen 2 first, because I rewatched all the originals after I saw the first Omen.
You know, I don't feel a need to discuss the original and I'll discuss it a bit when we talk about the prequel.
But, um, Damien Omen 2, uh, these, these part two and three, I'll tell you that I started both of them.
Is two Sam Neill? I've seen one third one.
But I started both part two and part three. And for the first, like, whatever, I was like, I don't like this, whatever.
And then they take turns where I was like, I think I love this.
So the part two picks up when Damien's like 12, he lives with his aunt and uncle in the English countryside.
He's going to military school.
And he's a normal preteen, you know? Yeah. He's got friends and whatever.
But like, and it's kind of weird because you're like, well, I don't understand.
Like, why would this kid be like a normal kid? And they actually do explain that later.
But he's a normal kid and he gets, you know, but when he's pushed in the wrong way, the evil comes out.
And as people throughout the movie slowly discover who he is, they meet their demise.
And that is when the movie gets great.
The deaths in this thing. I mean, they make the final destination deaths look like, you know, nothing.
They are absurd. And they're so fun. They're such crazy set pieces.
You see, there's this whole thing with Meshach Taylor where I think he plays a doctor. I don't remember.
But he or a scientist and he's in an elevator and the elevator collapses and it hits the ground.
And he lives and he's like, oh, geez, like, oh, my God, you know, what a relief.
And then you see the cable snap and the cable rushes down, crashes through the top of the elevator and cuts him completely in half.
And then and then they show a shot of him laying there with his guts hanging out like every death is like that.
It's wild. A woman gets attacked by crows.
And I think having Meshach Taylor say, oh, what a relief before it hit him was a bit much.
We could have scripted something more natural there.
There's a woman that gets her eyes pecked out by crows.
And then because she can't see from her bleeding, pecked out eye sockets, stumbles into the highway and gets hit by a tractor trailer.
And again, they show the body fly up into the air and then get bounced off of the cab of the tractor.
I remember every death is wild.
So I really ultimately ended up loving Damien Omen to particularly.
And this is a scene. This is something I'm realizing with these movies.
My favorite scene was, you know, he's having these like visions and hearing these voices and he's having these urges of like of his power and this and that and whatever.
And he doesn't understand it.
And that's when I was like, oh, OK, that's he doesn't know what he is.
Yeah, they do like this Jesus parallel, which is really cool where he there's a scene where he runs out to the water where he's all alone.
And he's like screaming at the waves and he's like, why me?
Why me? And that's like a Bible thing that Jesus did.
I was like, oh, that's cool. He's he doesn't understand it.
Whatever. So I liked it.
And then at the end of the movie, it you know, there's there's a pretty decent finale on it.
And he realizes who he is and what his purpose is.
And he kind of comes into his own. And that's how it ends.
I like Damien Omen, too.
You're not getting Omen one, but Omen one ain't perfect people.
You know, it's it's it's you know, it's good, but it ain't perfect.
So I think this is a fine sequel.
It takes it in a bit of a zanier, more graphic direction.
But but it's still fun.
I would recommend it.
I think the original Omen is is pretty solid.
Richard Donner kind of classes it up.
I mean, the only franchise I think does not really have a great entry is Friday the 13th.
I think the Omen is is solid, too.
I'm just saying I think people people hold it to to a bit of an unfair standard when judging the other movies next to it.
I'm like, guys, the original's got some goofy shit in it, too.
I got the new 4K of a movie that I have long wanted to see because of its amazing title.
Patrick 1978, directed by Richard Franklin, who did The Great Psycho 2.
He did Road Games, which is super fun and underrated Cloak and Dagger, which is a lot of fun.
He died very young.
He died at like 52 because I wondered what happened to this guy's career.
But he was a big Australian suspense filmmaker, very influenced by Hitchcock.
And I had seen clips of Patrick in the Osploitation documentary,
which is a really fun and and got tons of great clips documentary about Australian.
Yeah, punk filmmaking like in the Mad Max days.
And Patrick was very much a part of that world.
It is a not particularly scary horror movie about a guy, young man who is in a coma, yet he can kill.
He harasses and kills through the powers of telekinesis.
He is doing so because he lusts for his nurse, his female nurse.
And it's fun, you know, it's I like Richard Franklin as a director.
He's got great framing, great shots.
He's good with suspense.
He's let down a little bit by the story here.
It's a very slow burn, very slow, but it really works.
I mean, it's also got that kind of refreshing thing of when a movie is from another country,
they have very different attitudes about like sex and stuff.
Yeah, there's these weird bits where like, you know, she reaches her.
She's cleaning him up and he gets a boner.
And then this guy's like, now you said he had a boner.
Show it to me. Let me get the doctors there.
They're like, so show me how he got this erection.
It's kind of wild, kind of crazy.
It's weird in that it's called it's called an exploitation movie, but it's rated PG.
It would definitely not be rated PG today.
But it came in that window before there was a 13.
It's fun.
I don't quite see why it's a classic, except it's probably a classic in its native Australia.
And the 4K looks great.
But, you know, it's it's not a lost masterpiece.
It's an entertaining kind of be or move.
All right.
I like I like Patrick.
There's an there's a remake.
Didn't see the remake.
I wish I could hold on.
Let me see if I can look it up.
I'm trying to find it here.
Patrick.
The original is one of.
Yeah, 2013 was the remake.
I thought I saw the remake.
I've never seen it.
I like the original, though.
It's one of Tarantino's favorite movies.
Yeah, he talks about how he stole some stuff when the bride is in the coma from Patrick, like the bride spits on that nurse that comes from this movie.
But then there's also Patrick Evil Awakens.
Oh, wait, that is the remake.
Never mind.
I thought there was no there's a sequel, though.
Who cares?
I don't know.
Anyway, Patrick, the other movie I'm going to talk about, obviously, is Omen 3.
The Final Conflict.
It was it was just called The Final Conflict when it came out.
They later added Omen 3 to it for continuity sake.
That's the Sam Neill one.
Arguably.
The best.
Shot of the three movies.
The Donner obviously is a great director, and it's Donner's as well directed.
This one is shot.
It's a much it seems much higher end for whatever reason.
You know, even the first Omen plays a little low budget at times, but it's very well shot.
This was the one where I was like, there's no way this is going to be good.
Despite a very what I found chilling suicide scene towards the beginning, I was like, there's no way this is going to be good.
Damien is now taking up the job that his father in the first movie takes up.
His adopted father, not the devil.
And I was like, this just isn't going to be interesting.
He's fully grown.
He's like a politician.
Yeah.
But it goes wider than that.
He's the head of a global corporation that's having industrial effect globally and all this stuff.
So it does make sense that if you were going to dominate the globe, even as the devil, that's how you would do it.
But again, it takes this turn and it starts probably with this scene where he is in a room.
He's in this like chamber that he has with a life sized statue of the crucified Christ.
And he's doing this monologue to the statue.
And it's unbelievable.
It's an unbelievable scene.
Yeah.
Where he's like, you're a vile stench.
You know, like like he's he's and he's like he's like rubbing the statue almost like seductively.
And it's awesome.
Yeah.
This one gets real dark in a way that the other two even don't.
There's the scene where he's having sex with the woman.
And she's like, you can tell like he's not he's not there.
He's not into it because he's not a fucking human.
And then she's like, don't stop.
Don't stop.
She's like, please keep going.
And then he like takes her and like flips her over and he's like pain is birth pain is life.
And I believe begins to sodomize her.
And then the next morning, it just cuts the next morning.
She gets out of bed and she's got like claw marks bleeding.
Yeah.
Back and bruises.
It's fucking disturbing, man.
Yeah.
The end is batshit.
The plot of the movie is is that scientists are pinpointing the kin.
The moment that Jesus is being reborn up against Damien becoming the the the global power.
And then Damien is on a hunt to kill the newborn Christ like like like Herod was in the original Bible story and and when Jesus was first born.
And that's the plot of this.
And he fails.
And the end of the movie, Damien finally is stabbed by on sacred ground by one of the daggers from the first movie.
And he collapses as Jesus appears in front of him in the sky.
And just as the first two movies showed Bible scripts that was dark and haunting about the power of the devil from from revelations, then it starts showing like uplifting Bible verse and playing like choir music, like church music.
And it's like he will reign.
He is light.
He has risen.
It's fucking nuts.
Yeah, it's a really crazy ending.
You know, the ending is kind of dumb.
But but it's it's so nuts that I was like, I think I like this.
This is a wild ride.
I've been on.
Yeah, people forget how how bizarre some of these sequels get like Exorcist 2.
Everyone just goes, that's a piece of shit.
Nobody actually talks about what happens in it, but it's nuts.
And the Omen, I watched that trilogy over the pandemic and like, I don't remember what was what.
I just remember being like, all right, they didn't play this this franchise safe.
I'll say that anyway.
I'd well I I let's put it this way.
Oh, and then I just just as a side note, I then tried to watch the Omen remake with Julia Styles and Lev Shriver, which I remembered kind of liking when I first saw it.
And I put that disc in because it was part of the set.
I got about 30 minutes in and I was like, this sucks.
I bailed on that one, too.
But I liked these three movies enough upon rewatch that I am I already have the blu rays, but I'm tempted to upgrade to a set that's available that also contains the fourth Omen, which is a made for TV movie that's about Damien's daughter.
Which on lists that I've read that have ranked the movies has put that above part three.
So I kind of want to own all of them now.
But I'm also like, let me wait to see what they do with the first Omen if they make some master box set because I don't think we're getting our second first Omen.
I don't think it's doing well enough.
The Omen box that I have is I think I paid ten dollars for it and it has the remake and the other all four of the other ones.
It's easy to find on Amazon.
I revisited a movie that I just suspected might not be as good as everyone gives it credit for.
And I was right, but I still enjoyed it.
It's called Primal Fear starring Richard Gere, probably cast just so they could say in the trailer, Richard Gere, Primal Fear.
But this movie is always associated with like the usual suspects as being like one of the great twist movies.
Sixth Sense, Primal Fear, another movie that this guy made Gregory Hoblet called Fallen, which is a very cool movie with Denzel and John Goodman.
But there's just these movies that get lumped in as being like the best thrillers, the best twists and Primal Fear.
When I saw it when I was 16 or something, I was like, it's kind of a generic legal thriller, but Edward Norton's great in it.
You know, he won his best supporting actor and this was kind of where he, you know, staked his claim.
He became a really big deal off this movie and then was just huge ever since.
You watch it now, Edward Norton is like the fifth lead, like he's way down in the credits.
They don't give him an and Edward Norton either.
And that's what was really interesting to me.
Even a mid -range movie of that time of the 90s, the supporting cast would be stacked.
No matter what it was, this movie is Richard Gere, Laura Linney, Ed Norton, John Mahoney of Frasier,
Alfre Woodard, Francis McDormand, Terry O 'Quinn, Andre Brauer, Stephen Bauer, like Maura Tierney.
You just keep going down and these are all like still big working actors.
I don't know why that doesn't happen anymore.
I feel like you rarely get a good, you know, scenery chewing supporting role.
You get your star probably because everybody has to be less compelling than the star
and the stars have gotten less and less compelling.
I don't like Richard Gere.
I think he is very boring and bland in almost everything he's ever been in.
I just rewatch or I watched him in the Cotton Club where he's terrible in that movie.
A zero of charisma.
I like him in this.
He's good as a sleaze.
He's good as like a pretty boy sleaze, which is what he is in this movie.
But this movie is basically a high priced lawyer who kind of meets his match in terms of going up against soulless clients.
Like if you don't know the twist of this movie by now, I'm not going to spoil it.
But there's more to Edward Norton than you think.
I think this movie works as fun legal thriller trash.
But as a good movie, I think you're out of your mind.
And I think that gear and oddly Edward Norton are pretty bad in it.
But in a way where it's almost like a joke, like they're it's like them doing like regional theater or something, especially Norton.
You know, he's like, I don't think you want to stand counselor.
You know, it's like it's a little embarrassing at times.
But the movie works because everyone is going for it.
Everyone's committed one hundred and ten percent.
The twist does work.
And like a lot of these 90s thrillers, the twist and the subplot is always about some horrific sex crime, which I also forgot about.
You see like a video of this priest setting up a three way with two young boys and a girl.
And it's like, Jesus Christ, I dug it.
It's just fun trash.
And sometimes that's what you want.
And it made me nostalgic for how these movies just came out every weekend.
You know, just a solid B plus thriller.
That's a lot of fun.
That's got a fun twist.
You know, a bunch of great actors getting together.
We'd have two, three of these every weekend.
Times have changed.
Now you get the exorcism.
That's true.
And Primal Fear, by the way, if you turn to me to find out about 4K, this is not a 4K you need to upgrade.
The transfer is not that great.
I did want to say before we move on, Joe, to our movie of the day, I had set aside and forgot a few great, really good screaming ends, I think.
Well, first off, Julia Garner from Ozark.
You know who that is?
I never watched Ozark, but I'm assuming she's one of the female characters on the show.
Yes.
As is Laura Linney.
She plays the daughter and Julia Garner is excellent on the show.
She's great.
But she is doing and it's already shot, apparently, a movie called Apartment 7A, which is a Rosemary's Baby prequel.
Oh, Jesus.
Set to launch this fall on Paramount Plus.
And let me guess, she's playing the Ruth Gordon character, but younger.
Let me see.
Or Rosemary wasn't the first.
When a struggling young dancer, I think that was Ruth Gordon.
Wasn't she a dancer?
Suffers a devastating injury as she finds herself drawn in by dark forces when a peculiar, well -connected older couple promises her a shot at fame.
So it sounds like that apartment.
Well, here's what they're going to do.
They keep that apartment vacant so they can lure young women in with a deal and give them and it doesn't work.
And then they finally nail it with Rosemary.
I bet you're right.
Here's another one.
Francis Gallupi, who has directed a new thriller called The Last Stop in Yuma County.
That's, I guess, supposed to be good.
It hasn't come out yet.
He has been tapped to write and direct a new Evil Dead movie.
It is described only as an original story that Gallupi developed and brought to Sam Raimi and his team.
They're just like, we love this guy.
We're signing on for him.
And okay, great.
But that means we are abandoning the original Evil Dead, that franchise.
We're also abandoning the remake of the Evil Dead that came out in 2013.
And now we're also dropping Evil Dead Rise, which was critically acclaimed and which made a lot of money.
So why are we starting a new Evil Dead franchise?
You've got three up and running.
It's one of the few franchises that we just keep rebooting, even though they're all kind of good.
There isn't a bad Evil Dead.
They've said that I don't think I'm wrong.
I think they've said that that's how they viewed it.
It could be done a million different ways with different timelines.
I think because the crux at the center of the Evil Dead franchise, the device that fuels all of it is this book that allows for...
In Army of Darkness, when he goes to find the Necronomicon in the graveyard, there's three Necronomicon.
And I think that's what they're thinking.
Because each one relates to a different reality.
So we could get Evil Dead Rise 2.
We are.
He's working on a prequel.
When they listen to the tapes and you hear the priests talking, he's working on a prequel that takes place then.
Where he's like, it'll be like a John Wick priest killing deadites.
I was like, that sounds awesome.
But they said the book in Evil Dead Rise is one of the Necronomicon from Army of Darkness, but it's not the Bruce Campbell one.
It's another one of the books.
I think that's the idea.
It allows for all these dimensional rifts and people going in and out of each other's time periods and whatever.
Well, then maybe it's a good sign that they're developing another new Evil Dead franchise.
It means they're into it.
I don't mind them abandoning the one from 15 years ago or something, which clearly they've done.
But I was like, you don't got to let Evil Dead Rise go.
We all enjoyed it.
Sure.
And then lastly, Aaron Sorkin prepping a social network sequel about the January 6th attacks.
About Facebook's involvement?
Correct.
He says he blames Facebook entirely for that.
Okay.
I don't know where we're at, because Mark Knopfler, who is it?
I'm saying Mark Knopfler.
Whatever you're about to say, it's not Mark Knopfler.
Who's the Facebook guy?
Unless you're going to say who composed the score for The Princess Bride.
The Facebook guy is, I'm honestly very happy I can't come up with his name right now.
Whatever.
Mark Zuckerberg.
Zuckerberg.
Everybody was saying he was like the liberal knight against Elon Musk's conservative whatever.
And it's like, I kept saying when that happened, I was like, weren't we just blaming Facebook for right -wing propaganda
and Chinese subterfuge and Russian subterfuge, whatever country we were mad at that month.
It might just be that it's a horrible tool that people can use however the fuck they want
and the blood's on his hands for coming up with the tool.
But I mean, unless he's got more of a role in this stuff than I realized,
you can't be mad at the guy who came up with knives for cutting bread and then people use it to murder people.
I actually don't think that that sounds like that bad of a sequel to catch up with the guy all these years later
and go, the thing that the first movie, the intent of the first movie where it was this thing to connect people
and here's a man at the end, unconnected and alone because of the thing.
That ending was real good, the ending of that movie. Real good.
And now to take it to go, now it becomes this tool that is fueling literal non -people bots
to bring the worst behaviors out of us and it's not just the worst.
The first movie is, look, it brought the worst behavior out of you.
Now it's going to be like, look, now it's bringing the worst behavior out of all of us.
I don't think it's a bad idea.
All right, fair enough. You laughed when I first brought it up, but now you've come around.
I had to think about it for a second. Yeah, but all right.
Let's talk first Omen. For me, if I'm being real with you, I probably would not have even seen the first Omen.
Definitely not theatrically, even with my AMC stubs elite status.
It had no appeal to me. I'm so tired of first, second, last anything, especially Omen, exorcism, possession, etc.
I did not think the franchise needed more installments. I didn't care.
And weirdly, as much as we try to say what has happened to film criticism or TV criticism,
a lot of great reviews turned me around. I was like, people love this thing.
And I completely did as well.
It was kind of a mix of the great vibes and cinematography and music that I get from,
which Joe doesn't come with me along, but I get from like a Nicholas Winding Refn movie after he abandoned plot,
which he did very quickly in his career.
It's got those vibes that dreamy, whatever you want to call it, neon, A24, that kind of quality.
But it's also got a really, in my opinion, well written and well executed story that here's an added surprise.
I think links up pretty well to the Omen franchise, which it may not have even had to do
because I don't think a lot of today's audiences have seen the original Omen.
But Joe, walk us through the plot, if you will, of the new Omen. You'll do better having seen the original so recently.
I'll keep it fairly loose because there's a lot going on. And I do think this is one.
I'll try not to spoil too much because I do think this is well, we'll talk freely.
If you haven't seen it, I would strongly suggest watching it before you listen to this.
It's a good movie. You should see it with everything else. We live in a world now where if you haven't seen it,
you wait one month and it'll be there for you. And I think a lot of people don't listen to these until they see the movie.
And so be it. You'd never have to wait long in this day and age.
But you should see this. Don't ruin this for yourself.
But the basic plot is a nun, an American nun or sorry, a woman who's about to become a nun to take the vow.
She transports from the United States to Rome.
Rome is where the original movie picks up with the Thorn family going to the hospital to get the baby.
She arrives at a convent slash hospital, which turns out to be the hospital from the original omen that has burnt down
when they are trying to trace the lineage of Damien.
She is there to take her vows, but also assist the nuns in raising these orphaned children
and also assist the nuns with the birthing of these unwed mother, the giving birth from these unwed mothers that are there.
She is being approached by a priest who seems deranged and off.
That priest is the same character, Father Barrett, I think it is, who shows up.
Different actor, obviously. In this he's played by the guy from The Witch.
Anyway, same character as the priest that shows up in Thorn's office in the omen and says your son was born of a jackal.
He is now there warning this woman that something is wrong, something is afoot, something is off.
They think that this girl who is in the hospital convent orphanage place is potentially going to be at the center of a plot being conducted by the church, an evil plot.
You find out through this priest character that the plot of the church is that there are two churches.
There is the regular church that's on the surface doing nice things for people, blah, blah, blah.
Then there's this underground church who is obsessed with power and domination, and they are concerned that society is turning its back on the church.
In order to get society to turn back to the church, they are going to birth the Antichrist to give society something to fear and drive people back into the hands of the church and that gives the church power again.
A plot development that I will say received a pretty hearty laugh from the audience I saw.
Got a laugh?
Then they stopped laughing very quickly and were scared throughout, but I will say that development of we're bringing the Antichrist back to scare people back to church got a laugh.
Even though I think it's actually very cool.
I think it makes sense and it made more sense even in watching the original film.
Anyway, the plot unfolds from there and eventually, obviously they think that this girl is the girl in the home or orphanage is the girl that she's got problems and bad things are happening around her.
Some of them parallel to the things that happened around Damien in the first movie.
They think that she is the one to birth the Antichrist and then it's revealed eventually that there are several women that are set up to birth the Antichrist.
All of these women are byproducts of an unholy union or unholy unions that have been conducted in this facility where they have a jackal that is fucking the women and impregnating them.
And the daughters of these women, when they are grown, the jackal will then mate with the daughters.
It has to mate with its offspring in order to birth the Antichrist.
And they've tried this several times with several different women.
It's gone awry and produced many very malformed babies that die instantly.
And they think that this girl in this home is the one that is meant to do it.
And you find out in a major plot twist that it is not her.
It is actually the nun that came over from the States and that's why she has been brought back.
That's basically the movie.
We can get to the ending in a moment.
Well, there's just, I mean, there's big stylistic swings in the movie.
There's a just, you know, the most shocking scene that I think people will be talking about the most is the birth.
You see a hand come out of a vagina.
That was wild.
Not the birth, one of the births.
One of the births, right.
And you're like, they're really going for this.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, you know, like a gremlin hand coming out of a woman.
And the only time I can recall being that gynecological on somebody was in Knocked Up.
The big, the reason Anne Hathaway dropped out of that movie is because she didn't even want a fake vagina to represent her.
But it's shocking, you know, it really is shocking.
And it's to me, it's a thrill to be shocked.
It's very rare nowadays.
And horror, that's its job, you know, and so rarely does it do that.
There are many moments in this movie that really scared me, made me sit up in my seat, showed me something I hadn't seen before.
The scene that got the biggest reaction is, and I don't think a lot of people realize this,
but it was a, it's basically a shot for shot reconstruction of the very famous scene from Possession,
which is one of the great movies about divorce.
We talked about it on this show, very disturbing movie.
And the lead actress in that movie goes nuts.
She basically has a full body, well, as they say about Elaine Bennis, a full body dry heave set to music.
It goes on and on.
It ends with a bunch of white disgusting stuff coming out of her womb.
And that scene in an odd way is duplicated here, where I haven't really read much,
but I don't know if that had to have been an intentional homage.
I think so.
But I just don't, I haven't seen it discussed much.
It's identical and it looks great.
It's just, I like that.
I like knowing that here's somebody who has some interesting horror influences and not just the same old same old,
like we talked about with Late Night at the Devil, not just a girl with like a little puke on her lip and a couple scars, you know,
like we've seen it a million times.
So I looked up the woman who directed this.
She's done mostly horror and sci -fi TV, Legion, Briar Patch with our boy Jay Ferguson,
brand new Cherry Flavor, which I watched and really enjoyed on Netflix, and Channel Zero.
But I loved it.
I mean, I thought this was, you know, the old expression is style over substance.
I would say that the style is what won me over.
But by the end, I was really impressed.
Like even Joe just describing and laying out the story beats there.
I was like, yes, that all makes sense.
I remember that all happening.
There's a progression of events here.
And I think it's why they get Bill Nye and such great actors to play these elder statesmen of the church is because it just works.
Like even the early scenes where they're dancing in like the Italian disco or whatever, I'm like, this scene looks and feels great.
The music is great.
I want to be there.
Like it looks like they're having a great time.
And it's just it's taking the time even on scenes like that to set a mood when horror movie is usually just jump scare to jump scare to jump scare with a bunch of boring shit in between.
I thought this woman did an amazing job of holding my interest just by her filmmaking.
And I'll I'll definitely see the next thing she makes.
Doesn't seem like, as we said, it's going to be a sequel to this, unfortunately, because people aren't really catching up to it in theaters.
But to me, that's just the title.
It's too boring.
They put one too many new elements in that I assume they were planning on explaining in the next two movies.
You know, look, this is meant to connect to the original movie.
This is not a reboot for a new.
This isn't like Planet of the Apes with these new movies where they're like, we're just retelling the story and we're it's not connected to the Heston movie.
Like this is connected to the original omen.
At the end of the movie, when they are bringing Damien to the hospital, they are sitting in the car saying this will be the father.
And they show a picture of Gregory Peck like it is supposed to be directly a prequel, right, which is great.
But they change some things in the original trilogy.
The mother is a jackal, not the father of the baby.
So I get why they.
Meaning it makes more sense definitely for a man to fuck a dog than for a dog to fuck a woman.
Yeah, well, yeah.
So I don't know.
In the original, it's the mother.
Now, they.
By the way, I don't endorse it.
I merely say it makes more sense.
Yeah, right, right.
They change it.
Now, here's the thing.
It's enough.
The change works for two reasons.
It's way easier to convey.
There's this network of women that they're having get fucked by this thing.
You know what I mean?
Then like a bunch of priests or whatever, a fucking a dog or whatever.
So that makes more sense.
And then also in the original movie, he goes, the priest goes, his mother was a job.
And he gets cut off.
And you're like, OK.
And then in the later movies, they say the mother was a job.
We go, OK, maybe they get it wrong and they think it's the mother, but it's actually the father.
I'll go with that.
That's fine.
But they also say they have that priest, that same character say, I witnessed the birth and God forgive us for what we've done.
And it was like, but he.
OK, this is where I start to get annoyed with things.
Again, I love the movie, but I'm like, so why didn't you just have him witness the birth in this then?
Like, just write that in.
If you're tying it directly to it, write that in like having witnessed the birth.
He doesn't witness the birth.
He says I was at the hospital.
He wasn't.
The birth wasn't at a hospital.
It was that was in this place.
Right.
Well, I guess technically that's a hospital.
So have them there.
But they didn't.
They also in the original Omen, the priest, this character has the 666 mark on his body.
They never explain why.
Now, in the novelization, because I look this up of the original movie, the writer explains that that priest was a was a servant of Satan.
And once he became a servant of Satan, the mark appears on you.
So the insinuation from the novelization, not insinuation, it was what it was, the novelization, whatever, was that that priest was evil and he was part of this whole thing.
Like at the beginning of this movie, Charles Dance is the priest saying, like, God forgive us.
Yeah.
You know, whatever.
So it's confusing because I'm like, well, wait, he wasn't part of this or whatever.
But then I'm like, they were probably going to explain in the next movie.
He was part of it and he was trying to redeem himself.
OK, great.
But if we never get to see that, it's kind of confusing now, unfortunately.
Aside from those two little things, it leads pretty directly up to the first movie and it's pretty consistent.
I also thought that when she gives birth at the end, this is well, this was the one other thing.
When she gives birth at the end, she has twins.
And the first twin, they go, what is it?
Here's the girl.
What's this other one?
Because it has to be a boy, they say, for this to work.
And they go, it's a boy.
And the head evil nun, this gave me chills.
This was an amazing piece of cinema, in my opinion.
The head nun goes, we have him.
And then for the first time in the whole movie, the original Omen music starts playing.
And I was like, this is fucking awesome.
I thought it was great.
At the very end of the movie, you see that the mother has escaped.
That she has the little girl.
And she also is helping raise the girl that they thought was going to be Damien's mother.
And they're living a happy life, but they're in seclusion.
And who shows up at the doorstep?
But the priest.
Again, Father Brennan.
And she's like, get off my property, I'll kill you.
Because she knows that if he's there, that she's going to give away the fact that they're still alive.
They're supposed to be dead, or they're thought to be dead.
And he's like, I just came to warn you, they know you're still alive.
And they will be coming for you.
And he says, the girl, meaning the twin daughter, he goes, she'll be important.
So, you know, I'm like, part of me is, I'm like, they have to make two of everything.
It annoys me that everything has to be more.
Yeah.
We have to set up that there now is going to be, and it's like, there is no twin sister, guys.
It's like, I remember Burr used to get mad when they did the Bourne, the other Bourne movie.
Right.
What's His Face, the guy from the Avengers.
Uh -huh.
And the whole campaign was, there was never just one.
And I remember Burr going, yes, there was.
Yes, there was.
Until you cunts had to make more fucking money.
Yeah, until you made these movies I loved less special.
Yeah, he'd get really mad at it.
But it was, so there's a little bit of that with this, where it's like, guys,
it doesn't have to be a twin sister that now you're going to write this whole other plot.
We know how Damien, again, if you're not tying it to the first movie, then do whatever you want.
But you have tied it to the first movie and we know how that ends.
Unless you're going to ignore the sequels to the first movie.
That's probably what they're doing.
Their assumption is probably, if anyone has seen any of these, they've only seen the original home.
So who cares?
But I think, you know, and we need to say her name, say her name.
Arkesha Stevenson was also a co -writer of the film and the director.
I hope, I mean, I think it got good enough reviews that she'll obviously direct again.
But I want another movie in this franchise.
When was the last time you saw a horror movie where you're like, I want a continuation of this story.
Yes.
But that's how I feel.
And when I'm looking here, it's a 30 million dollar movie.
They say you have to add in 20 million for promotion, although I don't think this movie got 20 million in promotion.
And it says as of now, it's made almost 50 million dollars before hitting streaming.
That's not bad, but it's not really, you know, no brainer sequel money.
So we'll see what happens.
They might let her do it for less money.
By the way, did you know that I didn't realize this at all.
Did you know that Sonia Braga was the evil nun?
I had no idea until I looked at it just now.
No, I was looking at exactly that.
I was like, I was going to say Sonia Braga.
Yeah, it was like, I was like, where's the old lady that plays the nun?
And then this hot Spanish lady, she's not in it.
Then the lead, Nell Tiger Free, was also the lead in Too Old to Die Young, the Nicholas Winding Refn show.
Or if not the lead, she was in it.
She was wonderful in this.
The whole cast was great.
Ralph Finison had a couple corny moments, but he was overall good.
I'm a big fan.
I thought Bill Nighy was amazing.
Love Bill Nighy.
Great to see him.
Nell Tiger Free and Sonia Braga were also amazing.
And not to take anything away from the performance by bringing in looks.
But I will say, the way they took Nell Tiger Free from being like, they made her look like an almost homely young aspiring nun to being hot.
It was like a she's all that level spin around.
I was like, holy shit.
So that was very well done.
Anyway, my hog's way up for the first moment.
I'll buy this movie.
It's the first movie I've seen in a long time that genuinely scared me.
And I really hope we get something else out of this, even though we probably won't, because it was actually good.
I agree.
Couple things I got to say before we go here.
A specific shot in that birthing sequence resulted in the MPAA giving the film an NC -17 rating.
Producer says we had to go back and forth with them five times.
Weirdly, I think avoiding the rating made the scene even more intense.
And then David Goyer, who I guess, is he involved?
He commented, the movie by nature deals with female body horror.
And I do think there's a double standard, and he's probably very much right.
Sure.
But here's the interesting little tidbit.
The first Omen was greenlit for an intended streaming release on Hulu.
So this would have been another like that hellraiser where you're like, I definitely wouldn't have watched it.
But was given a theatrical wide release just because Disney determined it needed to expand their slate after shortages caused by all the strikes.
So it stumbled its way into theaters, which is crazy.
And depressing that we get so much shit in a movie made with this much TLC gets barely a release.
But since it did well, look, maybe we'll get another one released to Hulu and they'll let her do it.
Who knows? Maybe the streaming can help.
By the way, no announcement of a physical release.
No.
Which also scares me.
Every fucking movie, three months before it comes out, there's a Blu -ray for sale for preorder on Amazon.
And there's no even announcement yet for a physical release of this.
It's because they have a built -in pipeline to Hulu.
This is probably the reason, which really sucks.
Yeah. Anyway, I say check it out.
Do yourself a favor.
And that's it.
Yeah. Great movie. Hogway up.
We'll be back next month with something if they release more movies.
I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
Is stuff coming out? They got big summer movies?
It's summer.
Yeah. Well, I have a feeling we'll be doing the exorcism.
Oh, for sure.
Here's my first note.
What else?
Where's the Dumb and Dumber Scooter?
The one thing I liked about the Pope's exorcism.
There's gotta be shit coming out.
I don't know. We'll figure it out.
The Fall Guy.
Yeah, I'd see the Fall Guy.
I heard it was good.
My friend Lauren saw it and she was like, dude, it's really funny.
It looks funny.
I mean, Gosling is one of our bankable comedy stars.
It's sad to say.
Reliable.
Folks, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.