Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out our
exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Reward subject to expiry. Gamling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Take on my dreams and I'll say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
and a happy new year, Christmas time, full of cheer, drink the eggnog. Don't be a
slob. Holy shit. Did you get crazily drunk? Or is this just? No, not drunk at all.
Okay. And which is frightening. I drank two quite stiff whiskey drinks and I'm
not feeling a damn thing. Merry Christmas everybody. No, don't worry about it.
All right, folks, people, Pat just pulled the mic away from his face and went like the
question.
Like do we have an ad?
Well, if we do, we'll add it in later who gets it rats ass, it's Christmas, Pat.
Get drunk.
Have fun.
Well, Papa needs money for presents.
The, how's your, how are you doing on Christmas day, Pat?
I'm doing fine, Joe.
I mean, let's, I'm not going to lie to these people when I recorded this on Christmas
I hope I feel a little more Christmassy on Christmas day than I do right now, but
Anyway, before I forget let's just get on with the Joe and also on shit on with the Joe
Now who's drunk now who's drunk?
Maybe this is why you don't have any Christmas spirit because you're a lush
Folks
Let's just go ahead and get on with the show and at the same time on with the Jew holy night the stars are
Brutally shining right wash with a Johnnie Mathis right style rendition of
holy night sultry folks let's just get on with the Joel little town of
Bethlehem right it's Christmas bitch I'd like to introduce a new segment I'd
like to call inappropriate Christmas jokes.
Go ahead.
In the workplace.
All right.
Because we're in the workplace.
We're in the, we're in the uncut, thick dick house right now.
Well, I'd like to start.
I assume with the mistletoe belt, always a staple of the, uh, well, the office purge.
It's been wearing it since we hit record.
Yeah.
Uh, I was going to give you a, Hey, Pat, Merry Christmas.
Why don't you come over and open my package?
Uh -huh.
I was going to give you that word.
Yeah.
That's good.
Hey, Pat, I got something that can stuff in us in your stocking. You know, this kind of stuff. Hey
Joe, you want to come over here and jingle my bells. Here you go. That's a good one. Right. That's a good one
Merry Christmas. Happy New Year. Happy Hanukkah. Now we haven't discussed this yet. Happy Kwanzaa, but over on your Instagram the other day
I was having a real nice time doing those
was Jurassic Park World 2 folks jokes with you.
I loved it.
And I didn't even watch the trailer.
It is.
The line in the trailer.
So what is so bad about the trailer?
I'm going to tell you.
The line in the Jurassic World?
I didn't see it.
It's average at best.
Jurassic Park 2 is one of the shittiest films ever seen.
Not correct.
We've argued Jurassic Park 3.
I enjoy.
Yeah, uh, dresser at the best of the franchise. I enjoyed it the most. Yeah, but I'll also give Jurassic Park a pass
Jurassic Park is
As a good film movie Jurassic Park 2 is dog shit. It's fine. Jurassic World. No interest. It's I got to tell you
I don't want to I mean I never want to see him like when one of those big movie summer blockbuster movies comes out
And my mom sees it in the theater and she goes it was okay. I'm like this movie must really suck
Yeah, oh, yeah, old people just like going to the show. Yeah, so I never saw but
Jurassic World the fallen kingdom or the lost kingdom whatever it's called
This new one. This is the line Chris Pratt spits out in the fucking trailer. Go on
So we got to go save a bunch of dinosaurs from an island that's about to explode. What could possibly go wrong?
That's the plot of it the movie the the island is going to explode and
and they have to get the dinosaurs off of it.
Is there a bomb on the island?
Or is this explain that part?
Okay.
Who the fuck knows?
It's absurd.
And then, but somebody on Instagram
did respond with a great note.
I can't, I apologize Instagram user
whoever said this, but it was a really good idea.
He said easily equally plausible a concept.
Combine it, call it Jurassic World Armageddon.
Combine it with Armageddon.
And Asteroids gonna hit the island.
You bring back the army getting characters no problem. Yeah, yeah, that makes sense to me. I would buy that over this goddamn thing. Yeah, yeah, so
I'm gonna read you a couple of mine
Okay, in case you're not an Instagram head. Well, I start let's let me read the stab the establishing joke was
Yeah, it was a very funny job
I said folks after watching the Jurassic World 2 trailer. I wish it was this franchise that was extinct folks
Now I'm in the back seat of an Uber, quite intoxicated, Friday night, and I start firing
off these.
Folks, this picture looks like a dyno board.
Folks they had to drop this thing in the Velasa crapper.
Is Velasa crapper better?
No, crapper.
Crapper.
I thought so too.
Yeah, no, yeah.
Heather, my fiance told me crapper with Velasa crapper.
But a shino.
Not my shino.
And here's my favorite, gold bloom.
folks these days we're not even getting bronze blue. That's that one was my
favorite too. Oh, I was kidding about what does Heather know I love Heather. I
love Heather. I know you're pretty funny. Folks, I caught the new Jurassic Park film on an
airplane the other day and I walked out folks. I saw I saw Kevin James say that
joke. It's a very old. It's a great joke but it's it's Kevin James. Remember when
Kevin James and Ray were mounted to that golf special? No, they were like golfing
for charity or something? No, I don't. Well, they were golfing for charity and there's
like, you know, fans could pay money, I guess, to watch them golf and like stand there.
Okay. And they start shitting on each other and Ray Romano starts shitting on Hitch.
Uh, well, that was a mistake, right? Because Hitch is a great movie. Uh, and Ray, and then
Kevin James goes, folks, I was on an airplane today. They showed welcome to Mooseport. I walked
out. It's always funny. It's always funny, but also just the name of the film, welcome
to Mooseport. That really sails it over the fence.
Geekman's final film. How does a man who's been welcome to Mooseport assassinate Hitch?
Maybe it wasn't Hitch. Maybe it was Paul Blart, Mall Cop, which is a, well the first half
of Paul Blart's very funny as we've discussed many times in the show. Yeah, it's, I don't
know. I thought, I thought he made funny. I think, I don't think it was about quality
I think it was just about I want to make fun of my friend back in the old days of the vine app
Which I believe is apparently coming back, although I will not be on it
One of my beloved vine characters was the guy who pays a therapist
to
Voice how much he loves the first half of Paul Plart, Malta
And then wait wait because he knows he's got doctor patient confidentiality, right?
So he always there was so we could just go in and just go in and talk about how much he loves Paul
I'm not which was was me bass
That's very funny movie
Yes, what do you what do you think you're gonna?
We might get you may or may not get on this Christmas from this from somebody special somebody who loves you
Well
There have to be one such person I have I have one person who loves me and I think that she will give me
something great she always does but it's never what I expect and she's telling me
how hard it is to buy things for me but the truth is I'm passionate about several
things movies music I guess that's it television right but that leaves you with a
pretty wide open I know I know what you asked for because you did tell me you
don't remember, but I know you told me you asked for the James Tobak YouTube class, the
master class with James Tobak. Now, Joe, this is been bugging me, but it's not about
filming, it's about how to pick up with it. This has been bugging me and I'm glad you brought
it up. Why did you tell James Tobak to do it again? Uh, it bothers me because I, uh, I was
dating, uh, I got nothing funny. God damn it. The Matt Lauer response was you've heard
of, uh, yes, and an improv comedy, folks, I think I just got a no butt. I'm not going
to tap the Matt Lauer one. You said, why'd you tell Matt Lauer to do what you did? I said,
because I patented the button that locks the door from the inside and he gave me that I
can't think of anything funny about James Tobak. No, he's not a funny man. No. And he's like,
by the way, really depressing movies. I can't think of anything fun. He's never made a movie
we above like a C plus.
Anyway, so you don't know what you're gonna get,
it's gonna be a surprise.
I don't know, and there's nothing I really want.
I know what I'm gonna get from my dad is a check
for a hundred dollars.
And I know what I'm gonna get from my mom,
which is a check for a hundred dollars.
Other than that, I really gotta count on
Heather to come through because I don't get a lot of gifts.
You never know maybe Joe Joe gives you something I'd love it. I'd love it. You never know she gave me you know like a beautiful espresso machine last year
That I use every day and it can make cappuccino's and the whole thing right and I was like I didn't know I wanted this
But I use it every day. It was a perfect gift. Right. I don't know. I'd be happy with whatever all right. I got you
What are your parents you get you tell your parents what you want? I'm going home for the for the Christmas
Christmas, I spend Christmas day on my family.
You know what? I'm gonna I'm gonna air all my gifts right now because nobody because this comes out on Christmas
Nobody's gonna know my our dear friend James Pinkstone
Weeks change gifts every year like it's without fail like with it's we've been doing it forever, right
Got this fucking guy
Got this fucking guy, and I know he wants it
I know he can't find it because they're sold out everywhere got him fucking super Nintendo classic. Okay
They re -release it and you can't find it anywhere.
It sold out everywhere because it's a marketing scheme.
You can't get it anywhere.
But I found a one, every time I talk to it,
I keep playing up that you can't find these things,
you know, because there's like collect video games.
It was like, I managed to get one for like 110 bucks.
It wasn't like stupidly expensive.
And then they released all the games.
They're supposed to be $70.
It's the point.
I was like, you know, I was one of my oldest friends
in the world, like, let me spend a little extra cash
and get this guy this thing.
They released all the games.
In fact, it's got like 30 games on it or something.
Anyway, I'm excited about that.
I tell you everything old is new again, folks.
That's what it says.
Oh, no, it doesn't.
It says that in the 8 -bit.
I bought something where it says that in the,
oh, God, who cares?
Anyway, I got my parents, very excited about this.
Got my parents,
a turntable?
Sure.
Powered speakers and a couple of records.
And I'm going to, again, it's like you're saying
with the expressiveness, you're not expecting it.
It's never done anything new to ask for.
And give it to them and I'm going to say,
I want you to enjoy yourselves.
I want you to set this up in your sitting room area
and you go and you buy records that you loved
from your childhood, you go in there
and you have a romantic night together or whatever it is
and you just, you reminisce and you enjoy life.
These are very nice gifts.
I'm going to tell you this, though, Joe, get him five, six records.
I got him two.
Get him five, six.
I did the same with my sister and I had two and then I was like,
well, Pat, let's say she doesn't make it to the record store for a while.
You give her five, six.
Get her, get him a couple of you sonatras for a dollar, five, six.
Well, I got to, I, I, the premise, I got to, I got to get it shipped to their house.
Okay.
All right.
So get some more records.
Yeah.
And do you think it was a, it was a, you know, you know, good and well,
day one your parents aren't hitting the record store.
They might do it eventually.
No, my mom sometimes goes to the record store in her neighborhood
because I've taken her there.
But well, all right, maybe I'll get her a few more records.
Here's my question though.
Was it in poor taste and I taped a box of condoms
to the back of one of the records?
Should I down it on that?
Well, are you worried about your parents contracting VD?
I assume they're post.
I don't know.
I just thought maybe it was a little too suggestive.
I mean, I think I hope I'm having intercourse that they're it's a part of life folks and we've swept it
out of the rug for too long. Now if I could bring you over, which is which is how my father refers to intercourse
sweep it under the rail from the other room. Hey, mommy, you want to go sweep it under the
rug. Oh, he doesn't do that anybody. Please, I'm just joking made it. I'm just joking. That was because
Reagan apparently used to call his mother mommy, her wife mommy, excuse me, but I asked
for, oh yeah, my mom always asked for like an Amazon lesson. I give it to her. I asked
for, I asked for a couple of video games. Okay. Some old PSP games I wanted and a couple
Nintendo DS games, 3DS games I wanted like Zelda, Majora's Mask and New Metroid and then
And I asked for a Vincent Price box set that I've wanted for quite some time.
And you know, it's nothing, it's crazy, it's like five movies.
And a couple records.
I asked for The Doors, The Soft Parade, which is my favorite Doors album.
And I asked for Mr. Mojo Rice, that's LA woman.
But The Soft Parade has.
I don't like The Doors.
I love The Doors.
The Soft Parade has.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Now touch me babe. Yeah, that's a good song. I'll give you touch me back, but and then I asked
What was that promise that you made it?
Yeah, that's it that I get chills when I you watch the live one where it's them and like the orchestra on that 60s TV show
It's fucking awesome man. Oh, I'm yeah, gonna love here. You know at that period
I forget who his initial favorite singer was at that period, his favorite singer was Frank Sinatra.
He became and he wanted his voice to be better.
I don't know that he got there but.
I see.
I had a good voice.
Well, as Rip Taylor said in Wayne's World 2, he was a crooner stuck in a rock mill you,
which I like.
He said that about Morrison?
Yeah.
That's very funny.
I'm telling you folks, Wayne's World and Wayne's World 2 are comedy classics.
And 2 is not as good as 1, but it has 100 perfect jokes in it.
I'd love to if I could take you over to Pat's movie corner, now Joe, yes, I'm working
my way steadily through the Oscar screeners and here are my reviews. I'd like to preface
this by saying I'm a man who has fallen asleep in a movie five times in my entire 36 -year
life, almost 37 years. Hostels with Christian Bale. I've never been heard of that movie until
Oscar time. I was like, what is this movie? I never even heard of it. It's Christian Bale.
It's got the kid from Call Me By Your Name. It's got Jesse Plemons. It's got Ben Foster.
Who's Jesse Clemens, I think I from Black Mass, the place that I think I most would know
him from Friday night lights or like observant report or Fargo, but yes, he's married to
Kirsten Dunst.
I watched them make out at a party once and I was blown away because he's a real heavy
not attractive guy.
Man's got a real swollen face, especially at the time I saw him, he had just been eating.
He's got a real swollen, looks like he's been stung by bees and there is no one to
me more attractive than Kirsten Dunts.
I can think of very few people.
She is a dream, she's a ray of sunshine wrapped in a moonbeam.
And a hell of an actress.
If you haven't seen Melancholia, I really recommend that.
But any hoot, I was watching this hostels thing and I got 20 minutes in.
one girlfriend woke me up 30 minutes, woke me up 40 minutes, woke me up, went to bed.
And I've never been so bored.
It's a guy bringing a Native American chief back to his final resting place and he clearly
has some sort of hatred for Native Americans.
This thing has gotten great reviews by and large.
It's the guy who did crazy heart and black mass, actually.
Oh, it's the black.
I didn't know that's the guy that did crazy, right?
So I'm going to need to finally watch it again, but I'll say on initial viewing, fully awake,
I was knocked out several times.
I also folks on the Facebook page, a lot of you were trying to get me to watch Wonder Woman
watched it this weekend.
I got 50 minutes in snoring at 2 p .m.
Like a dad on Super Bowl Sunday.
Wonder Woman.
Wonder Woman's a solid flick.
I got to tell you folks.
I mean, uh, Wonder Woman. I wonder why I watched it. I'm watching her in Chris Pine flirt on a boat. I mean, I didn't see a single
Electric lasso making appearance. I was born out of my mind. I didn't watch enough of it. I'm gonna finish the movie folks
But as of right now, I'm just telling you I watched a couple movies and couldn't finish them. All right. Uh, as for movies. I did finish
Wunder struck. You made it through Wunder struck, but not Wonder Woman. Correct. And there's
also Wunder Wheel, the Woody Allen movie, which I made. And there's also Wunder about
the kid with a fucked up face. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, this is what's crazy to me. You
fell sick during Wonder Woman. He was live texting me through Wunder struck. That's right.
Live texting me. I was like, what are you even talking about? I don't even know what this
fucking movie is. Well, they sent it. It's available on Amazon Prime. It's the new Todd
Haynes, speaking of Wonder by the way. Oh, Todd Haynes is always, I know. Heather went
to see Wonder, the kid with the, no, what is the condition the kid has in the movie? I
don't know. I didn't see it, but I was texting her and I was cracking myself up. She did
not find it funny at all, but I was like, I'm telling you, before the picture starts,
going to the bathroom and have a good laugh because you don't want to be the
only one laughing when they unveil the kids' face. She was like, I'm not gonna laugh at
his face. I was like, Heather, you think you're not gonna laugh at his face. Wow,
you're like one of the bullies in mass. I know. Well, it bothers me that in this day
and age where it's like, if you're gonna have a trans character, she should be
played by a trans person. But suddenly we get, we're gonna do a movie by the
with the fucked up face. Let's get the cutest kid in America and slap some makeup on them.
And I also, I'm sorry, folks. Are you know, the man's trying to spread his wings as an actor,
not by an Owen Wilson as the endearing dad. Nope, not happening. I see my son's face. Yeah.
My son is beautiful. What you guys, you know what? Oh, and about my son. Is that he's beautiful?
I gotta tell you. Oh, and I took a look at that nose. This movie could have been about you.
Oh, maybe you should be wearing the space helmet.
He does have a real dick nose.
But anyway, wonderstruck, Todd Haines, you know, Todd Haines, I liked far from heaven,
I liked Carol to some extent, but he makes these very heavily styled lines.
Oh, I'm sorry, Todd Haines.
I was thinking of Todd Solange.
Well, I actually, well, Todd Solange did fucking happen, which is a mess.
Sorry.
I was scoffing at Todd Solange.
Todd Haines has made what?
Todd Haines did safe with Julian Moore far from heaven with Julian Moore. I love far from heaven. Carol and see Carol.
He makes interesting movies and they're done with a lot of love. Far from heaven was great. Far from heaven was a really good movie. Yes.
And it's if you don't know, it's about it. It's a movie about where it takes place in the 50s.
uh, Juliet, uh, Julia, uh, uh, Julian more excuse me, falls in love with Dennis Hayesbert.
Yeah. In a time where white women were not allowed to fall in love with deep voiced men.
Folks, uh, in sports. Now, wait, I remember that movie as being about Julian Moore's husband,
Dennis Quaid being closeted. Well, that's part of it too. I just wanted to get my deep voice joke out.
So he's getting cucked, but he's also S &D on the, on the left.
Second dick. Is that what that? Yeah. No, he's not getting cucked. She starts,
she falls along with Doesisburg because she's like, my husband's gay. I can't be with.
Oh, okay. Yeah. It's a, it's a tragic movie about like nobody can be with who they love
because everybody's so precious. Like they're like, this poor guy can't be with another guy
because everybody's so precious. And this poor woman can't be with the man she loves because
because he's black, because everybody's so pretentious.
Yeah, it's like all the old Douglas Cirque movies.
Yeah, it's based on a series of old three Stooges shorts.
I like it, it was a shimp if I recall correct.
Yeah, Julia Mercer's, I can't date you, you're black.
And Dennis Hesmer goes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, some of the, the only good times my dad and I had it were,
we'd wait up every night and watch the six hours
of three, two, just shorts on Friday night. And it'll come up. We'd be like, oh, every
time we'd be like, come on, baby, come on, baby. And then we'd see that shamp. And be like,
I like shamp. Here's what we got a curly Joe. Have you ever seen a curly Joe?
I've seen them all, babe. Yeah, I've seen them all curly Joe, curly Joe was like the real
substandard version of curly. Shamp is my favorite though. Shamp's really, Shamp's so ugly
that he makes me like, I love shampoo. And people go, no, curly is the best. I say, you know
You know what? Do you know what I say to these people?
Because I say champagne, curly is the best.
Say, curly is never mind.
Shamp is in utero.
Oh, that might be true.
It's absolutely true.
It takes a little more understanding.
You have to get to spend some time with it.
But now here's my issue.
My issue is that Shamp is too close to mouth.
He's not the brothers, right?
Yeah, they are brothers.
They look alike, but he's not.
That's the beauty of the character.
They look too similar or something.
It's I was always a Larry man. I loved Larry. Yeah. I love I love them all. I got I like now
I actually like curly Joe too. I don't I'm not as much as Shemper curly, but
There's only one bad one. It's the guy after curly Joe
That's really bad. There's another guy named Joe something and he sucks
But curly Joe is the one that's very effeminate, right? Once I yes, stop it. Not so hard
Right.
That's still very funny to me.
Yeah, Crowley Joe has someone.
You know, um, but you see the, uh, Fairly Brothers 3 Studios movie, uh, I bought it on
Blind Faith.
Honestly, there's some laughs on there.
There are some laughs in it.
Yeah.
I love Larry David as the nun.
I thought the impressions that the three guys did of the three studios were pretty excellent.
Yeah.
But I saw, I mean, they, they were good.
The guys were very good.
I just hated that it became like heart -felt at the end where like Mo feels bad for the way he's
Come the fuck off that it should have been not my hashtag not my mouth. And by the way
This is the fairly brothers. It should have been goddamn kingpin all the way through. Yeah, make it a ridiculous romp all the way through
Yeah, you don't have to come on. We have this fucking. I hear you anyway. All right. Wonderstruck
Look, I mean, I could try to give you a synopsis,
but we don't have enough time.
It's two parallel stories, one in the 70s,
a boy, mom and dad die,
one in the 30s or 20s.
A girl's looking for her mom, played by Julianne Moore.
That one's done entirely silent.
Oh, God.
It's about a deaf girl.
It's done silent movie style.
Well, it's nice that it's about a deaf girl, but they actually play it like a silent movie
There are long scenes where people are writing their dialogue on a notepad and showing it to each other long scenes
The movie is over two hours. I the only reason I finished it is because I couldn't believe how bad and terrible it was and
in the end
It turns into a at the end there like we better explain what's going on and they hastily
explain what's going on in a five minute stop motion animation segment oh Jesus Christ
this just stop it as far as I'm concerned was one of the worst movies of the year and it
was sent to me for my consideration as one of the best all right do not see this film okay
Okay.
My other is the only other one I got was last flag flying.
Again, I don't even ever heard of it.
What is it?
You'll get that as a screener.
It's a Richard Link Letter movie.
Okay.
It's Steve Carell.
All right.
It's Brian Cranston.
Okay.
And it's Lawrence Fishbur.
Oh, wait, this is the sequel to...
It's to the last detail.
Allegedly a sequel to the last detail,
Which is a fantastic movie with Nicholson. Yeah, I'm Randy Quaid
That's a big leap to make it has almost nothing to do with the last detail
It's the same characters, right? I guess it is and I've got to say as far if you want to see those if you like those three actors
And you want to see them kind of doing some good acting off one another and like having some nice sweet moments
It was entertaining. All right. It was entertaining. I liked it
It's it's nothing amazing, but those three are good Karell as like the guy who's always like
Who plays the nickel shared of it? Who plays the Nicholson character?
Cranston
Cranston who plays really good and who plays really good and who plays the Randy quade?
What was Randy quade's character's name?
Obviously, it's not a continuation because now fish burn is black
There's a new black characters was the last detail Nicholson
So you said it was way in and done.
Oh, I don't know Christ.
All right, well, you look that up.
I'll get into my stuff.
I watched a series of Christmas episodes of television programs, mostly
sitcoms.
I obviously can't go through all of them, but I'll tell you the ones I watched.
I watched, uh, I'm going to save the one for last that I want to talk about.
I watched the trailer park boys live from the North Pole.
Fantastic.
so funny sure so fucking funny sure the premises it's basically just a concert
film where they do a show in Minneapolis but the premises is that Ricky if you
watch the show still believes in Santa Claus and they tell him that Santa Claus
wants them to go to the north pole which is Minneapolis to do a show and during the
show he on stage he finds out that Santa Claus isn't real and then it's very funny
it's very very funny. I watched the I watched two phrasier Christmas episodes which were impeccable.
Sure. The last season one. That's very well written. Yeah, I watched the last season one where his
kid comes in and he's goth suddenly. It was really funny. Phrasier's kid? Yeah, and the last season.
The place phrasier's kid. I don't remember that. Some, I don't know, some kid. All right. But in the last
season for the Christmas one, he comes in and he's goth and the plot is the kid's goth and phrasier's
upset about it. And then the dad, and then Frazier's doing a promo for the radio station or I'm
sorry, Frazier's const up. Frazier's doing a promo for Seattle, like for the tourism board. Okay.
And they love Frazier and they love the dog Eddie. And they put them both in the promo.
And then, and then Niles wants to rebel for the first time so he gets a pot brownie from Raz.
But then accidentally the daddy's the pot brownie of course, and then Frazier watches the promo
I mean, it's so brilliantly weaved together the Frazier watches the promo and they've just dubbed his voice into Eddie
So Eddie's just a dog talking okay with Frazier's voice and then the dad when he's high at the peak of when he's high
You forget that this was even a plot point turns on this video and sees his own dog talking to him and freaks out
It's really really fucking funny
Frazier, you know, it doesn't have the cool quota of cheers or whatever, but as far as
like a well -written sitcom, that's a classic, that's true.
It's amazing.
I watched the cheers, a cheers Christmas episode, the one where Sam doesn't get Rebecca present
and then has to go out and try to find her a present at the last minute because everybody
He also got her something and he, all the stores are closed because it's Christmas Eve
and he meets a stewardess on the street.
He meets a woman on the street and says, are you okay and he goes, I can't find, I gotta
get a present for my boss and everything's closed.
Look, I got all these presents here.
Which take one of these.
And he goes, oh my god, you're so, I'll pay you for it.
What do you have?
And she goes, well, let's see, I've got a teddy, I've got a garter belt, can't have
too many of those, you know?
Right.
And Sam goes, what are you doing?
She goes, I'm an airline stewardess.
And Ted Danson looks up in the air and he goes,
Mary Christmas Sammy.
He's going to try to have sex with the stewardess, right?
I watched The Golden Girls, one of their Christmas episodes, where the plot is they decide
to make each other presents for the first time ever instead of buying each other presents
because they don't want to buy into the capitalistic spirit of Christmas.
Is that a B -author?
Yes.
And then it turns into then being held hostage at Rose's therapy clinic by a guy dressed
as Santa Claus who just wants to have friends.
Okay.
And one of the patients at the clinic is none other than Mr. Whatever's faces from perfect
strangers.
Subella.
Yes.
Yeah.
Also the naked guy on the subway in the Sunphill.
Yeah, no, playing a very different character.
No, no, no, the nigga here on the train and no, no, no, no, the nigga here on the
train and side follows the guy that owns the pawn shop in, uh, perfect strangers.
Yes.
I'm talking about the boss at the paybird, who's like, who's like the sleaze, he's in it.
Okay.
Uh, very enjoyable, very funny.
Some of the best written jokes on television.
Sure.
Of course.
Golden Girls is always great fucking joke.
Great fucking joke where Blanche is talking about Charlie's angels. What's one of the char...
One of the actors, Dr. Fawcett, not her.
Jacqueline Smith?
No, let's just say Farrah Fawcett.
She goes, uh, Blanche goes, I've often been compared to Miss Farrah Fawcett.
Of course, both my bosoms are much perky, right? Big laugh for the audience.
Beat and then Be Arthur goes, not if you were hanging upside down on a trap,
That's a piece, Branch.
That's a great fucking joke, Grant.
Yeah.
Seems a little mean for her to say to her friend, but they say it frequently.
And then finally, this is the one I'll talk about in more detail.
I watched the step by step Christmas episode was on Hulu, they had the whole run of step
by step on Hulu.
I think so, but they had a Christmas highlight section.
Talk about a show I've seen every episode of and could not tell you a single plot point.
I went through the Christmas episodes of TV show section on who found the step -by -step
Christmas episode, turned it on for one reason and one reason only.
Thumbnail?
Don Nuts.
I was like, well, I want to see this.
Sure.
Here's the plot.
Patrick Murphy, whatever the fuck you mean, Duffy.
He thinks Suzanne Summers buys the one kid the train said he wants, it's Christmas Eve.
She says, no, I didn't buy it.
He says, oh, I thought you bought it.
I didn't buy it either.
It's too late.
They can't get the thing.
The next morning's Christmas.
Patrick Guffy goes, while I've been remodeling that toy store, I still have the keys.
Let's just go down.
I'll put the money in the thing when I'm choosing Summers.
That's crazy.
That's breaking an anointing.
It's like, it's not.
We're going to leave the money.
It'll be fine.
They go into the toy store as they're buying the stuff
He picks up a toy squirt gun and he's like, well, this is cool. I'm gonna get him this, too and who walks by
But Don Nott's dressed as Barney Fife
Looks in the window the whole like
Yeah, and then arrest them and then the whole episode is them in jail as
As Dodd not like sits there and they're like it's Christmas day. Can you please let us go into our families?
Don't you want to be with your family's like I don't have a family nobody's ever put a saddle on this state
He's like he's like 90 by the way. Yeah, you just you just sold me on the episode on it's it's it's it's enjoyable. It's enjoyable enough
I had a good time watching it. I've been there. I've been watching like a kickboxer
That guy who was like the poor man's canna Reeves Sasha something. I know you're talking because it's always like whoa
This is yeah, I don't know
But anyway, you used to watch just the 10 of us
I mean when I was very young. I barely remember it. That was a decent show too. We got to start our commentary here folks
We're yeah, it's Christmas day. Let's start the commentary. We're gonna do commentary on the how the Grinch stole Christmas
It's not the Jim Carrey version, the classic 1966 animated picture.
Now, folks, if you want to watch along with us, this is on YouTube, Joe has typed in
in the search box, Grinch Stole -Crist Mad and even that brought it up so you should have
no trouble filing.
I think a few versions will come up, but the one you want if you want to watch along
with us is how the Grinch Stole -Cristmas exclamation point parentheses, 1966 full movie and parentheses.
So go get that now and if you got it set up on the count of three and then play, one, two,
three, play.
Hey.
Are you sure this is the one we should be doing?
Yeah, I watched it already.
All right.
I mean, I checked it already.
Well, you think it's gonna be like wrong?
The problem is it's watching on a television.
You gotta watch it with this.
We don't have it on a hulu or something?
No, I checked everything.
And I bought the goddamn blu -ray.
All right.
And we can't watch blu -rays while we do this.
We can only watch streaming stuff
because of the way the setup is and I went to see like I was like well I'll rent it again I guess
for three bucks right there. You can only buy the goddamn thing for $9 .99. I should have brought it
over. I own it. No, I own it too. I'm saying we can't watch a disc. Oh, we do this. We're going to
need to tell them again which YouTube video we're looking at. We already said it. They can rewind it.
Right now it says, I'm going to tell you what's on the screen. We're just coming to Dr.
is how the grand stole christmas that should be filling up your screen. Yeah, and if you're
watching the correct version, it's the one that has the Mitsubishi television mock up around it.
I'm blown away by how low rent this podcast is that we're watching this YouTube video of nobody
can see it. That's true. So who cares? All right. Who cares? Now, this is a movie about people that
but love Christmas, I guess, you know, I don't know.
Now this is so much louder in my headphones
than the perfect strangers.
I'm gonna lower it, give me one second.
On our Patreon episode, Joe and I did commentary
on the episode of Perfect Strangers called Fright Night.
So you can look forward to that.
If you're a Patreon member.
If you're a Patreon.
If you're not, you're fucked.
Yes.
And Joe, you said you would never seen
the Jim Carrey Grinch, correct?
I watched it the other day.
And it's entirety?
No, I got about 20 minutes.
I couldn't do it.
It is very bad.
A shit show.
It's very, very bad.
It's terrible.
And it should've been an easy slam dunk, by the way.
I didn't think Ron Howard was capable
of making a movie that bad.
It's a very inept movie, yeah.
It's really bad.
And then I hate, I hate, hate, hate,
that immediately they tie in like the capitalism thing
about Christmas.
Yeah.
Yeah, like where like the first line in the movie is the daughter is the like the little girl from the story going to her dad
Dad isn't this a bit much is this what Christmas is really like you're going this direction with this
Just make this fun. Make it about a creep on a mountain. Yeah
Now what's great about this 1966 version other than the magnificent
And he's also the voice of the Grinch.
Does the hell of a job?
Yes.
Is this your favorite of the old Christmas specials?
I mean, I have a very soft spot in my heart for the,
the claymation ones.
The Rudolph the Red Nose Rain deer.
I own all of those as well.
I always thought the animated frosty was kind of like,
a shitty. I like it. But the the rank and bass with, you know, with a bombable snowman
and all that. I mean, great. Amazing. Amazing. It's great. I've taken a reason like
into Mr. McGoo's Christmas Carol. Never seen it, but I'm sure it's great. I love Muppet
Christmas Carol. Muppet Christmas Carol is great. I really like the George G. Scott one. Yeah.
That's a really good one. It's very dark. Yeah. Scrooge is great. But no, you know, my favorite
Christmas special of all time is I don't and I own it on DVD and I leave it at my mom's just so we can watch it every Christmas day
What is it rich little's Christmas Carol where he plays every character in this cast but as a famous person
Are they puppets is it an oh no, it's just like they shoot it where he just plays everybody on video
Oh, wait a minute.
It's old, it's very old.
So he's just like sitting on a couch doing voices?
No, it's the whole thing, it's the whole production.
But he plays every character in it.
Oh, so he's like, with camera tricks.
Okay.
So you know, they have a body doubles,
he's talking to somebody and then they, really?
But I mean, yeah.
But it's like he, so it's WC,
it's him doing WC fields is Scrooge.
They just Johnny Carson is Bob Cratchett.
When did this air in the early early 80s on television? Yeah, I think I'm like showtime or something
Can I say that it sounds terrible? It's I it honestly if you watch you probably wouldn't think it was great
But it's awesome all three ghosts all three ghosts are detectives. Okay, so the first one is getting worse the first one is bow guard
the second one is
Oh, who is the second one?
I can't remember who the second one is.
The third one is Inspector Clueso.
Uh -huh.
A comedy character.
I never understand impressions of comedy characters.
Well, that's just the one.
Who else?
Oh, oh, Bob Cratchett is Paul Lind.
So, I believe you just said Bob Cratchett was Johnny Carson?
No, sorry.
His nephew is Johnny Carson.
Oh, Feziwig.
No, Fessie Wing is the boss. That's Groucho Marx. Oh, my God. His nephew is Carson. So his nephew comes in and he goes, he goes, I wanted to invite you to
Christmas dinner, wherever he goes, okay, and he goes, he goes, it is cold out there tonight.
And he goes, he goes, okay, and he goes, he goes, it is so cold and so cold. And then from the, from off camera, you hear Paul
Linda's Bob Crouchy go how cold is that he was so cold I saw two I saw two
cockroaches with jumper cables trying to get a mouth started and then it
bombs and he goes may all of your children be you know whatever that
saver behind the cars he's doing it sounds it's fun I love it I fucking love it I
watch it every year it's on YouTube I'll look it up I watch it every year I love
It's so much. All right, but I just look I liked it as a kid. It's it's I've carried it. It's rich little playing the women
Yeah, he does Edith bunker as Mrs. Cratchit is he wearing wigs and show tiny Tim is a is
Truman Capote. Oh my god
Is he dressing drag
For Edith bunker he does that's the only woman he played
I think it's the only female character in the whole story.
No, there's more.
You ever see these Zemeca's Christmas Carol with Jim?
I love it.
That's pretty good.
I think it's great.
Yeah, it's decent.
Well, that one too.
One of the first three ladies all that goes.
Yeah, he does.
That was one of the first 3D pictures, I say.
I love it.
I think you like polar express.
No, polar express is shit.
Well, I mean, it's just not meant for me.
Also terrible animation.
It's not meant for me.
It's, that's meant for children.
Little baby, honestly, baby.
Children yeah, and maybe children with like learning disability. Oh stop it saying I'm just saying something like that on Christmas day
I'm just saying why would you say something like that on Christmas day? You know, sorry
I got a gift for you. It's the gift of enlightenment. Oh shape up or ship out
Now do you think the Grinch fucks this little dog while they're up in the mountains? I mean it must get lonely up there
I don't think they fuck but I think the dog has seen the Grinch jack -off on many occasions
Do you think the look at that screen on the Grinch? Do you think I bet she's not a grin? Oh, God
Now Joe what's your favorite Christmas movie of all time?
Well
Now let me let me throw this by you. I'm up at the smokehouse the other night
Local restaurant the crack house that you hang around yeah, yeah, yeah, and I see a dad from health. I see us
I see Matthew Brodrick. Oh, yeah, he didn't dinner holding court with who Sarah Jessica Parker. I didn't certainly not Sarah
Diske Park. All right. I feel like that marriage is a champ. I feel like that too a little bit. Yeah. Brodrick's sitting there and
Everybody's talking about how old he looks and I'm like guys
Ferris Pooler was 30 years ago people age. Yeah, I was getting kind of angry about him. Heather's look bloated these days still of course of course
He's a I think he's a big drink. I think so too but
This guy Chris Diamantopoulos is playing the dad in the Christmas story that was by the way
That was a Dennis Miller name if I've ever heard of
Diamantopoulos fucking. I'm sorry folks. I'm not fucking Chris Diamantopoulos
But he's playing the dad in Christmas story the old man. They're doing it for Fox
No, they do these these reboots and who the fuck is broadrick played and my root off is playing the mom
Who's Broderick playing but the whole time I was assuming that Broderick was playing the dad, but then all of a sudden
I started in steppin' my brother up a little sis. So then I started thinking who the fuck is Broderick playing?
He's narrating it a bit.
Oh, he's playing Ralphie as an adult. Yeah, he's narrating it. All right, well that's cool. Who's playing Ralphie as a kid?
Some new kid
But I might watch the new Christmas story. I love a Christmas story. I
And I saw that Ken Jiong is in it.
So clearly he's gonna play the guy in the Chinese restaurant.
You don't know that.
That's not just a assume that that's what it's gonna be.
You honestly believe that in 2017, they're gonna do the phara ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra
ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra ra
No.
Folks, folks, that's a horrifically racist thing.
Well, I mean, look, I've always laughed at it, but it is promoting some pretty offensive
stereotypes.
I don't think it's, hold on a second, I understand why it could be construed as racist.
I don't think they're trying to promote any stereotypes.
I think they're just making a joke.
It came out around the same time as 16 candles, which people are also looking at with a new
lens.
You know I get I get the new lens thing. I'm not denying that at all
I'm just saying like I don't think the producers were saying they're going let's promote this stereotype right now
You're probably right up, but a Christmas story is a favorite of mine
I love bad Santa. I love Christmas vacation. I got a bit. I got a bit screws
But what is your favorite Christmas movie? I had a bit I want to do answer the question. I have a bit
I want to do all right, I had a bit I would do folks as you see this new rendition of a Christmas story
I was enjoying it until the lamp sued the dad for inappropriate behavior
My favorite Christmas movie I mean look Christmas stories way up there
Favorite Christmas movie
Scrooge just way up there. Can I well my number one without question is that's a wonderful life because that's one
That's one of my top three favorite movies of all time
Um, but I got to tell you folks. I'm gonna many I love home alone folks. I got to tell you I'm gonna put love actually at number one love
Actually, it's fantastic. It makes me cry every time I watch it. It's a fantastic picture
Uh, and the the the storyline alone with what's his face from um show under the dead Alan Rick
Oh Alan Rickben's is great Alan Rickman. I'm a top of the story is the best story in the whole thing
Uh, and it should be its own movie. I would dislike an incredible story. I love that story
I don't think it's the best and the whole thing my best those are so good in that the best and the whole thing in my opinion is
The God the dad from Sean to the dead bill nine the bill nine one kills me
It's great. It is great. He's a he's verbally abusive to his heavy set manager the entire film
Yes, and then when he goes to his manager's house on Christmas Eve and says I
Realize you're my family and you're who I love and I want to spend my Christmas with you
And it's literally just a guy yeah
Just just stating his friendship for somebody that's taking care of him for somebody
Yeah, it's just it that that destroys me that part. I saw love actually in a theater in New York
I hadn't spoken to a human being in months and I cried like a bitch
I cry every time I watch home
It is and honestly you're kind of stupid if you say otherwise the end with
with like the airport thing at the end and like I almost
are crying right at the top. I must cry right at 11 bit. Yeah.
No, no, the night that the airport thing at the beginning, I
must start crying when it's like the look how happy they are when
like the people are like coming together in the airport and
everything. It's like that's like they say that people in 9 .11,
we're calling home. That's a great. Oh, they do say that.
You're right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's it's just a fantastic
stick fucking film it is and they they keep it they keep it a lot of balls in the air and
pretty much all those stories are at the very least entertaining and in some cases they
make grown man cry yeah I love love actually I guess I would put that as my number one
and I would put um I would I would put scrooge just a close
scrooge just scrooge just just really and scrooge will make me cry when he's doing that
I've been at the end of the movie, that kills me.
And you feel like that every day, it kills me.
Murray, his voice, horse with cocaine.
Really?
Apparently Murray's most coked out picture was scrooged.
I never knew he was a big coke.
That was him at like a crazy level of coke.
Oh really?
I didn't know that.
But Alfred Woodard and the kid, I mean they did that,
they did that really well that movie.
It's one of a life is a top three of all time for me,
So I gotta pick that who makes me cry like a like a small bitch like a little bitch
Um, I love it. I don't know why you have to put a label on it
But all right, you know whatever like a like a small bitch. Yeah, he says, but you know folks
Just just let you know what we're at we haven't even looked at the picture of movie
The bridge it's the best part
It's the montage where he's stealing all the guests from the hotel and it's playing the Grinch song
Which is such an awesome song. Yeah, you're a mean one mr. Grinch
Great tune now. Do you like night member of four Christmas? Never saw it. It's really good never saw it
In fact, I was talking to Greg Proops. Yeah, comedian Greg Proops
I'm a big fan of that a party the other night all right
And I was praising him because he's in episode one. He's a voice in phantom menist and I said you're part of my favorite universe ever
your part of Star Wars. And he was talking about how he'd just come from New York to do
a live rendition of Nightmare Before Christmas. I go, I go, dude, don't kill me, please.
I've never seen it. No, I get it. He goes, most people didn't see it. He was like, it
became popular much later. And I was like, well, I was a pot in college. And all my friends
were acting like that was sacrilege that I'd never seen it. It's a very good movie. I'm sure
it is. Yeah. I've just never seen it. I remember I was in a Christmas movie or Halloween
It came out the same day as the Adam's family values.
It is both a Christmas and Halloween movie,
which is why it came out around Thanksgiving.
Oh boy.
But yeah, it blends the two worlds Halloween and Christmas.
And it's a Tim Burton.
Okay.
Great animation, great songs, it's very entertaining.
I bet you it's not as good as these newer Tim Burton films.
Christ, the man has made a good movie in 15 years.
What was his last picture?
Big eyes? No, it was big, it was big eyes before it was dark shadows. Big guys it was a very
average movie and it was his best movie in about a decade. Big eyes might have been his last
picture. Yeah. His last picture. Um, what Pat? I, go ahead. Love. We're all listening.
Home alone
I like home alone. I like home alone too better though
I think the home alone one is a hundred percent better. I know I know that home alone one is a better film overall
But I like the finale of home alone too better the the the final 20 minutes of home alone two to me is funnier
It's pretty relentless. Yes
If for nothing else it's got the non -stop
electrocution of Daniel Stern thing where he literally is turning from a skeleton right it's
it's a total of John Hughes. Yeah, it's fucking hilarious. But let me tell you this
speaking of plans for his own bills. Home Alone 2 does not have Mr. John Candy.
Well, John Candy only pops up at home alone one for two minutes, but it is one hell of a scene.
It's funny, he's plays the Polish guy with the, he's got an accent, doesn't he?
One is the classic and to me too is like, everything is ripped off to such a cheap,
pathetic degree.
Yeah, two, two's not, like I said, one's a much better film, but two, look, I feel like
the whole point of home alone is you're trying to get to that fucking traps and gadgets
finale.
But honestly, I find the rest of it just is entertaining really I do I will say now Jody you think die hurts a Christmas movie
I'll count die hard. I love die hard. I love die hard too
I saw die hard to once in the theater and I don't remember it die or two is fantastic
I just remember all of us kind of being like yeah, it happened to Christmas again. It was good. I liked I
would you know
No one is the best and then two and three are pretty neck and neck for me beyond that
it's unwatchable.
I love three.
Three is great.
I like live free or die hard.
The fifth one sucks.
The opening scene of dire with the vengeance is one of the ballsiest things I've ever seen
in an action movie with the I hate and word son.
Yeah.
And then he has to team up with Samuel Jackson who hates white people.
I really like dire and I also like that it's the brother and the terrorist from the first
one.
German is great. It's I really like die are with a vengeance. That's right. It took some like cool chances
but two I mean
just the fact that so
When when he ejects out of that plane and
His seat comes all the way up so I could nose touching the camera. That's like a shot. You know, I've almost never seen before since and
Screamies
when he a lot the he
He shoots the gas tank so it's leaking gas.
Then lights the gas tank on fire so the trail of fire goes up and blows up the plane.
But then the trail of fire becomes the light that guides in the airplanes.
That's pretty genius.
Yeah.
It's pretty genius.
I don't remember that at all, but sure, it sounds good.
All right, Jim.
I just feel like that's in up there as well.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot about that.
Santa. That's way up my list. That's way up my list. I, back to die hard for a second.
A die hard, too, to me, is like the, um, oh, God, damn it. I just had a perfect analogy.
It's like the, um, oh, fuck. I'm sorry, Pat. That is a perfect analogy. I've, uh, I've had
a bit of whiskey here and, uh, and, uh, you know, what are you going to do? It happens.
here you go. Let me top you off buddy. All right. Give me just a little dab there for your glass.
All right. It's the holidays folks. Don't judge us. It's early. Who you judging? It's us. It's not
really early. It's a Sunday night. It's 10 times. We're in 10 times. Pat us to work tomorrow. I do.
I have to do getting dug with high tomorrow. You'll be fine. The Grinch has stolen all the who
people's gifts and he's know up on his mountain just reveling in it he's very
happy yeah now here's why the movie fucked up right this is the climactic moment
in the cartoon he's happy he's like I ruin Christmas for these cock suckers
down there I stole their gifts now they're not going to enjoy it but then they
come out and they sing and they're still happy and they're still celebrating
Christmas and that's when he realizes Christmas isn't about presents it's about the spirit it's about love
Right, and in the goddamn movie they immediately started with this capitalism bullshit
Right, and it's like it ruins it. It takes it way out of Dr. Seuss. That's right. That's not what Dr. Seuss is
That's right, Joe. Dr. Seuss is a magical, wonderful world where people don't do stuff like that
Joe, you know, I just I'm sorry, Pat. I get fired up. I know. I'm thinking about starting an Alex Jones kind of a
video show. Joe, I feel like that's maybe maybe three years off for you.
Now, where I just discussed Dr. Sousa adaptations. So, it's an episode
want to be Grinch episode two in Cat and the Hat. After that, we're gonna have a
hard time. Let me throw some Christmas titles at you. Let me know what you think.
Jingle all the way. Never saw it. Schwarzenegger, Hartman, and Sinbad. Jingle all the way.
I'm gonna shoot you. I'm gonna shoot you straight. It's funny. I don't doubt it. I
Schwarzenegger and Sinbad.
Yes, there's going to be laughs.
He made it to the wrong time.
I came out when I was in college.
Yeah, I was like, it's just, you know, it wasn't, you know, it's got some laughs.
Let me throw the Santa Claus at you.
Never saw it, but it's a funny move against it.
It's a funny move.
I'm sad that the third one is so poorly reviewed because that's the one that weren't
short.
That's right.
Let me throw a prancer at you.
Never saw a prancer.
I saw Prancer of the Dollar Show and I, I, I sobbed. I was nine years old. Prancer is a really good movie with Sam Elliott.
That was just because of the guy that took you into the bathroom show ladies and gentlemen. I'm sorry people.
This is, you know, we talked truth on this.
Let me.
Now do you count Batman Returns as a Christmas film?
Of course, and one of my favorites. I love Batman Returns.
I like it if I watch it through the filter of it's a Christmas movie.
Okay.
If I watch it as a Batman movie, I hate it, okay, but if I watch it as a Christmas movie
Guys, we just got a commercial here on YouTube and if that's happened to you, we're sorry. Was it over?
No, no, no, it's not over
We're right at the part positive you need to the dog is being pulled up by the sled and the sled's gonna fall over
Grinch is going up to say the dog
Like it matters. I know you know, nobody cares anymore
Oh, he can't, there's no quality in any of this anymore.
Uh, let me throw you Ernest saves Christmas.
I remember loving that.
I didn't like it.
Saw that at the dollar show as well.
I saw many Ernest films as a kid.
We've discussed this.
I hated all of them except Ernest goes to jail.
I loved it.
I loved him playing the two characters.
Jail is very fun.
Uh, throw a couple at me, Joe.
Don't leave me hanging.
Uh, well, Gremlins classic Christmas film.
Remlins is one of the best Christmas films.
Absolutely.
I love them.
A great Christmas episode, not a film,
tells them the crypt, the episode with the escaped
mental patient who dresses as Santa Claus.
I haven't seen it.
Oh God, you're missing out.
It's Benny from L .A. Law.
The guy that played the better...
Dr. Giggles.
Yeah, Dr. Giggles, Drake and Dr. Senn.
Yeah.
Dr. Senn is out of his mind.
Which one was your line?
Mine was the doctor is in Senn.
But on the box, it said the doctor is out,
not the dot of his mind.
Very good, both are very good.
Yeah, thank you.
So I enjoyed that quite a bit.
What else?
Tell us in the dark side has some really
tremendous Christmas episodes.
There's one called Seasons of Belief.
I love about a family, two parents telling their kids
about this monster, I think called the Gringer.
Okay.
And they're making up the story.
It's this whole goofy story.
and the kids are terrified and then at the end the monster actually becomes real and comes
in and kills the parents.
So that's fun.
Do we do cramp us on this show?
I think we did.
Crampus is cool.
This is kind of suck.
But it's all right.
It was okay.
It's fine.
There's another tale from the dark side.
Oh, Hattering and Jack, which is about a guy on Christmas Day and a demon is haunting his
house and the demon is trying to get the best of him but he can't get the best of him
because the guys got too good of a spirit.
But it's enjoyable, you know.
What else? I'm trying to think of Christmas movies.
I mean, we've really seen it.
I'll be home for Christmas with Jonathan Taylor Thomas
and Leslie Nielsen.
No.
It's not great.
It, I wouldn't imagine it is.
I mean, anything post naked gun three
with Leslie Nielsen,
you're getting into some trouble territory at that point.
Folks, the Grinch just came to an end, Jesus.
Everybody's happy.
they won, you know he became good. Yeah. And it's a nice thing for everybody. I hope you heard about
at least one Christmas picture you have insane and I hope you check it out. You know the long kiss
Good Night's a great Christmas movie. That's a Christmas movie. Absolutely. Really. Gina Davis,
Sammy Jackson, great picture. I don't doubt it. Kiss, kiss, bang, bang's got a lot of Christmas stuff in it.
I like Chris Christmas bang bang. I like Chris Christmas bang. I like confidence has some Christmas shit
But it's not a Christmas movie come on you're you're stretching now. I mean there's a lot of movies that have a Christmas moment in them
You know what beautiful girls. That's where I put my Christmas list. That has no Christmas in it at all
But it's all Thanksgiving. Yeah, I love beautiful girls, but doesn't he go home? No, he goes home for Thanksgiving
Okay, I like it's I don't even think it's Thanksgiving. I think it is. It's just his reunion I believe
Oh shit, you're right, Jesus.
All right. Well, it feels like a good person for me.
Um, folks, I want to wish you a Merry Christmas.
You, you end your kin and a happy Hanukkah and a happy
Kwanzaa and a happy Hanukkah and a happy Kwanzaa.
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh, uh,
Joe DeRose, a comedy on Twitter and Instagram.
We love you guys.
We miss you guys and we wish you in yours a beautiful day.
That was a headgun podcast.