🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
I just got my colo -guard results. Squeaky clean. Shit in a box. What the hell's colo -guard? The shit in a box.
Oh, what are you doing that for again? Again? I never did it. What do you mean?
I think the only person who's ever told me about shitting in a container was you, unless I'm mixing you up with someone.
Well, shitting in a container is -
Maybe you just seem like a person who would do that.
Shitting in a container is one thing. I'm saying this is the only time I've done it for health reasons.
A colorectal exam. Is that what they call it?
Yeah, yeah. So because of my - you're supposed to get your first colonoscopy at 45. I did not. And because of my switching into -
I'm not that age yet, so I haven't had that conversation.
Yeah, it's coming.
Kind of a spring chicken over here.
Because of my switching to, you know, kind of leaving New York to work on this thing and then going to Austin, with all this stuff,
my health insurance was New York based, so I had to start figuring out new health insurance.
Point is, I knew I wasn't going to be able to get a colonoscopy until the new year. And my doctor said -
And you've been begging them.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I said, you know, Doc will come to your house.
Exactly. Your wife can watch, like we discussed.
So he said, look, why don't you do the box thing, and then, you know, if you get clean results, that gives you some peace of mind,
and then you get the colonoscopy when you can. So that's what I did. And he literally just texted me, no colon cancer, squeaky clean. So that's good.
That's a nice text to receive.
Not bad. Not bad.
You know what, Joe? And I wouldn't do this. I don't appreciate anything, but just sit and think what the flip side of that text could have been.
And now sit and enjoy your cancer freedom. You know what I mean?
Yes. Yes.
Appreciate the gifts.
Well, I immediately said, I do know what you mean, but I immediately said, yeah, but I don't know my family history because I'm adopted.
Do I need to worry? And he said, we just if we do this every three years, it should be good.
We just have to stay on top of everything. Now, that said, I still will get a proper colonoscopy.
But I would imagine if something I would imagine it's sort of like the covid test or it's like you could get a false negative.
But if you're positive, it's that that second line comes up pretty fucking quick.
You know, so anyway, whatever, let's just try to enjoy.
I still haven't had the I haven't had the finger up my ass that the doctor yet. And it's time.
I mean, the my dad had.
Well, brief prostate cancer scare that he only told us about it years after it happened.
I'm like, no, I need these things for my own life to live. I need this information.
You can't just shut down and and not tell me about your health scares.
Well, I didn't want to worry out there in California.
It's like, no, it's it's crucial.
The number one question they ask me when I have my yearly doctor visit that lasts four minutes is, does your dad have anything?
And I go, well, he's insanely unhealthy, but I don't really know.
He doesn't want to worry me. So he doesn't tell me his illnesses.
And the doctor's like, oh, OK, cool. Then you're probably fine.
And we high five and I leave. No, I need to know.
Yeah, that's up there with that kind of exam is up there with does your father have anything is right next to.
Well, you don't look sick. What are we doing?
Exactly. What are we doing? Yeah, that this is still family.
They'll do that. Any family history of depression?
I'm like, do you have six hours for me to just tell you about the people that I've met, not the people prior to my birth?
Yeah, we can go into my history.
And then you tell them and they're like, yeah, well, definitely something to watch out for.
Click their pen and walk out the door.
You're like, hey, hey, patch, I'm not done back here.
OK, Mr. Adams, I got a few more cues.
OK, my doctor's name is Patch Adams.
It's not I'm not doing a bit. It's not the patch, but it is.
I saw that movie theatrically.
I remember nothing about it except Philip Seymour Hoffman and Robin Williams going head to head.
I was excuse me. I was just old enough.
Yeah, that movie dropped to be to be that was like the first one where I was like, you know what, Robin Williams, fuck you.
I was just old enough that I was cynical and I was like, I've had it with this with this guy.
Yeah, I've seen this. I saw some picture the other day.
It was like some Paramount 100th anniversary event.
And it was like, look, everybody in the photo is happy.
It's like Walter Mathau and these people all smiling and all these legends.
Then it goes, except and then the sad music starts playing and it zooms in on Robin Williams,
who happens to not be smiling in this Paramount 100th anniversary photo.
And it's like, you never know when someone right next to you might be struggling.
It's like, guys, now, come on.
Maybe he just you ever got a photo back you thought you were smiling and you weren't smiling.
We know the man was depressed.
We don't need to dig back through his photos.
He's doubled over laughing two seconds before the picture.
Yeah, he pressed a whoopee cushion in his pants, right?
But probably right when that picture was taken, he was pressing down on it.
The yeah, guys, can we take it again?
I don't think I was smiling. No. All right.
That's all right. Don't worry about it.
I don't be that guy. Let's just go.
And that's the incident that made him suicidal is that they wouldn't retake the photo.
Maybe that's what they were trying to tell me.
That would be like a that'd be like a Mr.
Show sketch where they like work backwards from the suicide to figure out what happened.
And then it like finally realized it's that photo.
Like that's literally like what I feel like a Mr.
Show sketch would be.
Joe, I just got some some casting news this morning that I thought you in particular might enjoy.
And I was trying to remember, was it you and I that saw the the Broadway Glen?
It wasn't we didn't know each other.
A buddy of mine and I saw the Broadway Glen Gary with.
We have Schreiber.
I saw that to Alan Alda. Yeah.
All right. Alan Alda played.
I saw one with Tambor as well.
I might be crazy. No, no.
Wait, Alan Alda was not in it.
It was Pacino played Levine.
Lev Schreiber. Oh, no.
No, I'm sorry that I didn't see that one.
I saw the one with Bobby Cannavale and Pacino.
I didn't see the Alda Lev Schreiber one.
How was it? That's the one I saw back when I was in New York.
It was it was fantastic.
I mean, it's hard to mess the play up.
The only thing you can really have a problem with is a cast member maybe not stepping up to lemon Pacino,
you know, which is a big shoes to follow.
Anyway, they're doing a new revival that I thought you might enjoy.
It's always fun to hear who gets the parts.
But you got as Shelley Levine, Bob Odenkirk, Chicago's own.
Wow. Which I was like weird.
But then I thought, no, he plays the great loser.
He's Chicagoan. I like it.
I wouldn't maybe put him in that part.
Very cool.
But he's great.
Then in the Levine role.
No, he's Levine.
Odenkirk.
You're right. I'm sorry.
In the Roma role.
OK.
Is Kieran Culkin.
Is that the kid from?
I know you don't watch Succession, but.
He's awesome, though. That's great.
He's a very good actor, I guess.
And he's probably the same age as like Pacino when he did the movie.
It's just he seems way too young because I picture him as the kid
who drinks too much Pepsi and pees the bed and home alone.
But no, he's great.
I think that's good casting.
He'll be great as a hot shot prick too.
He'll be great in that.
Yeah. Yeah, he'll be great.
Suspenders, I'm imagining.
Then you got as Moss, your boy Bill Burr.
Burr is playing Moss.
Burr. That's right.
That's accurate casting.
That's all they've been out so far.
And it's Patrick Marber, the guy that wrote Closer,
and he directed the play that you and I saw with Krumholtz, Leopold Statt.
But that might be a little trip back to New York.
I mean, it's one of the great plays and I like that cast.
So we'll see.
It's always been.
It's always been my dream.
Excuse me.
To play Williamson in that play,
because I have a take on it in my head for years that I'm like,
I've never seen anybody do it this way and I would want to do it that way.
But I don't think I have a shot at getting into a Broadway play right now.
You never know.
Spacey really was excellent in that part.
I mean, it just.
What a fascinating man.
I mean, he was he was Hollywood's greatest weasel for a year.
When that seven usual suspects, that was all like the same year.
He was in like every movie that came out.
And then you're like, oh, this guy's not just a weasel.
He can also play like cocky assholes and stuff.
This guy's amazing.
He just kept being more and more to the onion.
And then sure enough, there was too much to that onion.
Oh, yeah. In the long run.
That onion made you cry in the end.
Exactly.
They just sold his house.
It was considered the finest house in Baltimore.
He had like a secluded house where he would bring his his bows
and just sold for like three point one million.
I was like, how shitty is Baltimore if the top property is three million dollars?
Well, he was on Piers Morgan.
The clip went viral where he cried and said, I am flat broke.
I'm almost homeless.
I saw that.
So that he said he owes.
You know, the dildo of consequences is rarely lubed, Kevin Spacey.
I read that the other day.
He of consequences rarely arrives.
He said he said for those of you that didn't see it, he said he owes millions of dollars
in legal fees.
And I don't think that that sale of that house is even going to scratch the surface.
I mean, you know, you're dealing with a guy at that level.
Legal fees are God, I can't even imagine what the fuck that guy must owe right now.
It's weird.
I mean, unless he were innocent, which I 100 percent believe he is guilty.
Well, he was acquitted, though.
I'm not saying I'm saying I'm saying it's hard to sympathize with you.
I'd say you going broke, spending all your money on legal fees, and then they got you off
of these horrible crimes is a huge win for you.
Now, go back to your lair and leave us alone.
You know, that's how I feel about it.
Yeah, you don't have any money and you don't have your house anymore because you ruined
dozens of men's lives.
So that's fitting, Kevin.
Jesus Christ.
It's weird.
It's like he's got this whole thing.
It's because everybody, pardon the pun, but everybody sucked his dick for so long.
You know, celebrities can't understand when that changes.
I don't even know what outside of the 14 year old kid one where he said, yeah, I might have
gotten a little handsy, which is troubling.
The other ones, I don't even know what the accusations were.
Like, if it was the one that I was always like, come on, man, was the guy that like
he had my undercarriage in a bar.
It's like, yeah, come on, dude.
Fine.
You know, that sucks.
It's a controversial stance.
I even find Terry Crews and I would never say this anyway.
Here I am on a fucking public podcast, which I always is going to keep me up tonight.
But like, if someone I had never met before walked up to me and grabbed my dick.
I think about as far as that would go would be me telling a couple of my friends, this
guy walked up to me out of nowhere, grabbed my dick.
I just don't imagine being traumatized by it.
I'm sorry.
But he did lots of other things.
Just watch that documentary.
And there's, okay, there's what was, what was most interesting to me, to me about the
documentary is, and I don't know why more wasn't made out of this.
None of the men that they interview filed claims against him.
They're just like, I'm just here telling you what happened to me.
I'm receiving no money for it.
And that's every story in the documentary.
As far as I know, it was just guys.
Like the guy who talks, doesn't save a private Ryan jackoff story is like this huge buff
military guy.
And he's like, yeah, it was mortifying.
And he starts crying in the middle of it, but he's like, I'm not trying to get money
out of him.
I just thought it was fucked up.
I find it.
I actually don't find it hard to not believe that I find it impossible.
Right.
I get that.
I haven't seen the documentary.
Didn't really seem like a pick me up.
And I'm, I'm battling enough mentally right now.
Do it back to back with the Michael Jackson one.
Yeah.
Anyway, anything else?
Well, speaking of which, this was a new psycho, you know, look, I'll take the wheel on this
one and, and, and deal with any potential backlash, but this Coppola thing seems kind
of, I don't know, man.
I don't understand.
Like, I saw the, I saw the video clip.
He walks up and kisses a pretty lady on the cheek and he's an 85 year old man.
You know, again, if that happened to you in the middle of a grocery store, you're not
going to report it.
And then I see the woman that they had this like headline news and she's like, uh, it
was, uh, uh, I, I went in, I went into a state of shock.
You went into a state of shock.
Yeah.
I mean, look, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
There are claims that look, here's where I always think things become a little questionable.
When the rest of the cast is not coming to the defense.
And by the way, the, you know, I'll cite Adam Driver.
Adam Driver is a guy historically in interviews that has no problem saying what he does or
doesn't like on a movie set.
Uh, in fact, in the Bill Burr interview, he talked about like, I don't, I can't stand
phones on a set.
I don't wait.
He makes his stance pretty well known and he does a lot of charity work.
And I'm not saying because Adam Driver didn't come to your defense, you're lying or it's
not a big deal.
We saw a video.
It's not a lie.
It did happen.
But I'm also like, was this just a guy walking around hugging and kissing people and just
being like, Hey, we're having a party.
Like it's a fun time.
Come on.
You know, and just being, I don't know.
Is it not appropriate?
Sure.
I get it.
We live in a time where you can't just go up and hug a person you're supposed to ask
permission and all.
I get all that.
But at the same time, it's like what was Coppola's and I've never heard a story once about Coppola
prior to this that he was in that way inappropriate on a set.
I've heard stories that he can be explosive.
I've heard stories that he can't keep his movies within the budget, that he can't get
it done on time.
But, you know, it's kind of like this Charlene Yee thing with Time Bandits where she left
the show and claimed that she was assaulted in a scene with a scene partner being too
rough with whatever the scene is.
I don't know what the scene is.
And I'm sitting here going, when even Taika Watiti is doing an interview about it and
saying, we love Charlene, we investigated this to the fullest extent, you know, unfortunately,
nothing came up that says that there was, you know, validity to the claim or that somebody
had done something wrong.
I forget how we phrased it.
I'm just going in this climate where everybody immediately is ready to be like, I don't approve.
I don't this.
I don't that.
We are handling when that's not the reaction, you start to go, OK, well, maybe this is a
misunderstanding that somebody is is making into something bigger.
I don't know. You know, I don't know.
Well, if you look at, you know, you know, somebody like Charlene has a long history
of these incidents and.
I got to tell you what, I hire her for a show, absolutely not.
It all it almost seems like putting your future, your fate, your career.
In a person's hands who clearly can't handle, excuse me, sorry, but I got to say it can't
handle this business, maybe can't handle it sounds like leaving your house is an issue.
I mean, she's got there's I guarantee in a fight scene or whatever this was on Time
Bandits, nobody is trying to harm you physically.
And if something happens in that moment, there are a million people on set that you can
tell, starting with that person.
Hey, you were way too rough there in that previous take.
Did that happen? I certainly hope so.
I imagine that guy didn't go, well, fuck you.
I meant to do it. He probably said, I'm sorry.
She claims that she did address it and that she later that day heard him laughing about
it, which, again, this is getting it gets into a lot of fear.
Saw him laughing from 100 yards away and thought in her mind that he was laughing at
her is my guess.
So who knows?
But, you know, again, I don't want to set everybody's moral barometer to Lisa Kudrow,
but it's like when when Lisa Kudrow were, you know, these these very like openly liberal
artists that are part of a show that are not these like kind of money grubbing scumbags
that so many performers in this business are when they're when nobody else is coming out
and saying, I feel really bad that this happened and it's unfortunate or whatever, nobody's
saying anything.
I'm like, that's when it starts to get a little suspect.
Whereas the guy like Spacey got a ton of people saying things and going, this is a
problem. This is this.
This is that. You know what I mean?
So I don't know.
I think that's it.
I think it's as we've discussed on this show for years now, context always got to play
a role. And at some point, four or five years ago, context just went out the window.
It's never discussed.
And, you know, my my tendency is to believe a victim.
There's no reason to expose yourself to all this if it didn't happen, whatever it is,
whether it's minor, major, anything.
But, you know, there's been four news stories in the last decade about Charlene Yee having
what seems like an easily resolvable issue with somebody, but it's being brought to a
national attention.
And I find that odd.
You know, she said David Cross was drunk in a bar 15 years ago and said something offensive
to her. And this was like in the news cycle for a week.
It's like, what's going on?
David Cross apologized for that, but did say, Charlene, I'm not saying you're lying.
I'm saying I think we have two very different memories of what happened that night.
Yeah. And then he later said, I'm sorry that I hurt you.
But also that he was doing a redneck character and whatever.
Now, again, it's OK to say, hey, dude, I know you're doing a character.
I don't like it. It's not funny. Fine.
Yeah. But to have had it clumped in with the issues that were going on at that time and
are still going on with, you know, the black experience in America, Asian hate, all that
stuff, I felt like it was kind of like, I don't know, man, it's like, come on, we got
to. I don't know.
It's it's I don't know.
I'll say this on the plus side, none of these people.
She also went after Rogan and Franco, which obviously Franco has his own Piccadillo's
as well. But it's like what you go after Rogan for for his shit.
Franco's out of this business.
She went after them for let me look it up, but it was basically just like being bros on
set during that decade where they were bros on set and celebrated for it.
Charlene E. I think she thought they were drunk, like on the set of Knocked Up.
Oh, oh, Seth Rogan. I think you meant Joe Rogan.
No, no, no, no, no. Oh, OK.
So she said. Charlene Ye called out Rogan for continuing to work with James Franco was
that issue. She alleged that Rogan bribed her with a bigger role and heftier paycheck
after she threatened to quit the disaster artist over the sexual misconduct allegations
against Franco. OK, that's something different.
Look, I'm dumb to blame for this, too.
Sometimes you got to read the specifics and they're not as great as you thought.
But. It's just.
There comes a time where if you're always finding fault with every work environment you
have, you can't blame people for your career going away.
You know, it's just like, well, here we go.
And that also doesn't mean shut the fuck up and be silent in the face of abuse, as I've,
by the way, done for huge chunks of my career.
Just look the other way on things, including when they were directed into my face,
screamed into my face.
I said, well, I'm going to keep my head down.
I'm not right there either.
There's no real right or wrong.
But this is a business where you have to develop a thicker skin than.
In most, you know, it's not MMA fighting, but it's definitely you're going to take a
lot of fucking verbal abuse through the years.
I get a lot of I get a lot of.
You know. Teasing.
Whatever you want to call it from from my friends of.
Yeah. Being an argumentative guy, being a guy with that.
Sure. You know, I'll own it.
But you've gotten much better since I've known you.
I've worked very hard on it.
But I also am a big believer and always have been a big believer in.
I want to settle this right now.
I don't like what just happened.
And I'm not patting myself on the back and saying, that's how you have to do it.
But yeah, I do think we've lost something.
In this culture, where everybody is behind their screens now and,
you know, I've been saying this for years.
When you're when the when the predominant.
Social interactions you have,
the predominant amount of social interactions you have, can be rectified
by literally eliminating a human being because you've blocked them and erased them.
Yeah, that's going to translate into real life interactions.
And you see.
People unable to have a difference of opinion, people have to walk away.
People get into arguments and they're shaken by an argument.
People don't want to talk on the phone because it could lead to an interaction
that might be uncomfortable or a confrontation.
Everything wants to be text only via email.
When I've asked people, hey, can you help me with this actor?
I know you've worked with this actor and I'm really struggling working with him.
Can you help me?
It's always a this needs to be a phone call,
as if you're in all the president's manor or something.
That's, you know, but it's terrible.
I've had arguments with people.
That I didn't know very well, where I have felt, you know what?
I was I was I want to own the part of that where I was wrong
and I want to apologize to the person and I will not send an apology in writing
and I will not send an apology on a voice note.
I want to speak to them. Why?
Because we live in a time where anything that is documented
can be then captured and used against you.
I mean, this is sick where we're living now, where even when you're trying
to apologize to somebody, you have to strategize with an apology
because you don't know what the other person may or may not do.
It's sad. It's a sad state of affairs.
And that's not. Victim shaming or blaming or anything like that.
I'm saying we're suffering
because we've lost an ability to interact with one another.
You know, I have friends that that manage
younger people in their job role.
They're in a management position and they have said I have to tech.
I have to first text a person when I'm going to call them to say,
I'm going to call you.
Please do not have any anxiety.
It's just about a work thing I need to talk to you about.
And this is nuts that this is where we're at.
Like it's it's but it's it is what it is.
I'm not sitting here as the old man at the back
of at the back table in the room saying things need to change.
They're not going to change.
This is the direction we are headed in.
Oh, and there's something I want to talk about.
And it's not going to stop.
The thing I want to talk about is is and this is, I guess,
sort of an extension of this.
But on the last episode,
I complained about sitting in the movies and seeing these
these A .I. commercials before the movie starts
and that we're just steering into this A .I. curve.
And now we're being sold on the greatness of A .I.
by companies like Google and whatever.
And they're using your phone as the example in the commercials.
And it's very dangerous, but it's going to happen either way.
Nothing's going to stop it.
But this latest one I saw, which was before Trap,
which is the movie we're discussing today.
It's a dad.
And this is for Google A .I.
This is Google.
It's not some other, you know, third fucking side party company
that nobody cares about. It's Google.
This is a leader.
The commercial is the dad talking about how his daughter runs track
and how he ran track and she idolized him.
And that's why she wanted to start running track.
But now her idol is this Olympic medal winner.
I don't know the runner's name.
I don't know the world of track and field.
But the commercial is the dad saying, A .I.,
can you help me write a letter?
From my daughter to this track star.
To let the track star.
So this is where we're at.
It's it's six months ago.
There was a panic that kids were using this to circumvent
responsible behaviors or practices such as writing a term paper,
writing something you have to write for school,
completing a school assignment, whatever the least
amount of stakes you could ever have as a young person
in creating something is writing a fan letter to somebody you look up to.
So now it's not only saying don't have the child learn how to do that.
It's the parent not even saying I will do it for you.
The parents saying, A .I., can you do this for me?
In in turn for my daughter, where are we at to teach your daughter?
If you really love somebody, ask a robot to tell them.
What a great lesson.
It's so nice.
But it's bad. It's bad.
My my thing for what has caused the erosion of society
and there's all these factors all factor in.
But for me, it was the doing away with hugs.
I was not a big hugger.
I'm not a big I don't didn't necessarily love
hugging hello to everyone 100 percent of the time if I wasn't in the mood.
But there is there was something about it.
It's breaking a small intimacy barrier with another human being.
Maybe women have had incidents of guys pushing themselves up against their chest
or something weird like that or grabbing a butt.
OK, then that's bad. Yeah.
But I think we should have done away with those incidents like I couldn't imagine
now outside of my close male friends walking up to anyone
and giving them a big hug of greeting.
I don't do it anymore.
And nobody does it to me.
And it used to happen at work constantly.
You know, the even the executives, you say, hey, how you doing?
And a big hug or whatever.
And it just. Puts you in a more community mindset.
Physical touching.
So like, I don't I guess hand shaking is kind of still there.
That went away with covid.
But hugging, I think, went away for some other sexual reason.
Because Lasseter got fired from Pixar for hugging.
Like the only thing they had on him was hugging employees
and he got fired as the head of Pixar.
So, like, again, I there's a there's a there's a little pattern on this
on this particular podcast of me saying, like, hey, you know,
let's look the other way on thing.
That's not that's not me at all.
I'm saying your your average person should be able to discern between a how are you hug?
It's good to see you.
And that guy really violated me.
Sure. But I don't know.
I feel like even when I see my friends for breakfast,
there's like a nod hello and a polite smile as if we're colleagues.
And I hate it.
But then again, I'm not going to be the guy like, hey, where's my hug?
No. Yeah. You're a predator.
Yeah, it's weird.
It's weird that and I know times change and I know this.
What I'm about to reference is from 30 years ago, but.
It's like, it's just weird that a sign
that does the was up frogs.
It's weird that a Seinfeld plot
is now something that's considered scandalous.
Like, it's weird that there's that whole episode of Seinfeld with.
What's her name from?
Oh, God, and I'm a huge fan.
Wendy Malik, where she plays the the chiropractor or whatever.
And Jerry's like, yeah, I'm on a kiss hello basis with this woman.
I can't stand it. I don't I don't want to do it anymore.
And then there's the gag of like, she's trying to kiss him
and he's like ducking in the refrigerator or whatever.
It's like. Right. But my point is, is like.
A lot of the times, that's all it is.
It's just like, I don't want to do this. It's annoying.
And as we continue to be more and more
unable to address that and just say, hey, dude,
I don't want to do this with you anymore.
It's one thing Burr was really good at.
I remember when I remember we I hung out with Bill a lot back in the day.
But I remember like.
I remember one time in particular, there was a comic
who we had all been out having a few drinks and the comics like, Bill, man,
I want to give you a hug. And Bill's like, no, no.
And the guy's like, come on, man.
And he's like, no, no.
And the guy's like, really? And he's like, yeah, yeah, I'm serious.
No, I don't want to hug you.
And it was a little awkward, but that was it.
He's just like, that's it. That's where we're at.
Now, I know we all can't be Bill Burr, but yeah, I don't know.
That that would devastate me, I think, if somebody refused a hug.
And I think it would devastate a lot of people.
And that's why nobody goes for it anymore.
I had an incident, not even an incident, but five plus years ago.
Where this woman that I'd known for years, she comes up,
she me and my buddy arrived at a party together, she hugs him.
And she's like, what's up, Pat?
And like kind of, you know, punches me on the shoulder, puts her hand out, whatever.
And I'm like, oh, he gets a hug.
I get a punch in the arm.
And her face looked as if I had offered her some candy to get into my van.
And in that moment, I said, I'm never going to approach a woman again
in this manner, because I just saw that going awry.
I saw her being like, excuse me.
And like a party, you know, Larry David style, turning to look at me or whatever.
And I was like, OK, that was a billion percent.
Not my intent in this moment to have a where's my hug moment.
Well, you owe me, you know, put push your body against mine.
But as soon as I start getting defensive on that front, I look horrible.
Yeah. I become the Joe DeRosa I met 10 years ago,
yelling at somebody at a barbecue, you know.
You can't be that guy.
So I just went, OK, let it go.
And then I thought on it and I was like, well,
I was this person's boss at one point that might add weirdness into it.
We're just hanging out at a party.
All I'm doing is trying to create a little funny bit for the group.
And you could tell it was like, you're not going to be the guy
who decides who I hug and who I don't.
Now, that made me feel horrible.
That probably just like Bill Burr made that guy feel horrible.
But if you're standing up for your boundaries, then what can I say?
And I get that maybe you don't want to hug hello
because you're not the kind of person who can say, no, I don't want to hug. Sure.
Maybe you've been assaulted.
You can't stand to be touched.
I actually get it the more I'm talking about it.
I'm just saying it's added to the erosion of society.
I miss hugging my friends, for God's sake.
Yeah, I look, I get it as well.
Again, not dismissing anybody's bad experience, not anything like that.
But I'm just saying we should have.
Look, it doesn't matter.
It's the society has changed.
Interaction has changed.
And that's just where we're at.
And I whereas five years ago,
the average person would have said,
how dare you say you don't want to work with somebody because of
their claims of past experiences or whatever.
And we all would have said, no, you're right.
That's fucked up.
And and it would have been defined only as victim shaming at that time.
It's getting to a point now
where it's barreling so heavy in one direction that people now understand
when you say, I don't know that I want to talk to people anymore either.
And I don't know that when I interact with people much and I'm freaked out.
The average person now is going, yeah, I kind of get it.
And it's weird.
And I don't know what's going on.
And it's just developing and changing so quickly.
And it's it is what it is.
So let's all stay in our houses.
Let's all never phone call again.
And let's only communicate a Scientology joke on a Zoom last week
that I have I have woken up and gone to bed thinking about every day
of this week of me being like, what if one of the four people on that call
were a Scientologist? You fucking idiot.
Literally, I say that to myself in the mirror.
We're in L .A. One in four people are a goddamn Scientology.
It was just like, I need to start being like a company man
and treating these Zooms like.
You know, the job interviews, they are.
I just there's a there's a comfort I've enjoyed in this business
of you don't have to do the rigid by the book shit that has gone away as well.
And maybe that's for the best, too.
I saw a young man at Costco last night.
His boss was like, would you just leave?
Did you just leave at like 7 p .m. last night?
And he goes, yeah, I had to get to whatever.
He's like, your shift was until nine.
And he's like, I know, but I had to get to whatever practice or something.
It's like a 16 year old kid who works at Costco.
And I really think that that's kind of the new norm.
Is this like what you're going to tell me what to do?
Like, fuck off. I kind of like it.
Like, I wish I could go back to my bosses at Blockbuster Video
or Dearberg's grocery store and be like, I'm not listening to you.
I don't respect you.
But once that goes away entirely, then society is gone.
They do have to be like, this guy's my boss and I have to respect him.
That is a part of life and the workforce.
But yeah, and the guy you could see in his eyes, the boss was like,
I can't go off on him about this.
I just have to kind of be like, well, in the future,
don't leave two hours early without telling anybody.
But he certainly wasn't getting in trouble.
Yeah, I can I can tell you.
As a business owner,
and not that we've had a lot of problems with employees,
most of the employees have been really great.
But I can tell you, we are not living in a world anymore
where it's just like where you can just be like, you know what?
Your attitude sucks. You're fired.
It's just you can't do that.
And like you said, there is
there is a
oh, God, what's the word there?
There is an honor in.
The ability to say to someone, I don't like you,
I don't like the way you act, I don't respect you,
and therefore I'm not going to.
That's fine. Great.
More people need to stand up for themselves.
I don't disagree with that. However.
We are now doing it at the expense, as you said, of a society
when, you know, I don't think enough people in this country
and I'm speaking to the majority and by the majority,
I mean, the financial majority in this country,
which is mid to upper middle class
or even regular, just even lower middle class.
We've got too many people that don't are not.
I mean, my parents never had money.
So it was like, if you don't work, you will have no money.
And then my mom said to me,
you are not allowed to live here anymore.
And that was it. Yeah.
That's why you have to take the lumps, because you're like, shit, you know.
And I think too many people now.
And it is it is an epidemic that's happened.
You know, they've economists and stuff have talked about it.
And a lot of it has to do with the COVID lockdown stuff.
But, you know, there are economists are talking about, like,
there is a generation of people that will not leave their parents' homes
and are living off of credit cards. They will never pay back.
Which is why you're seeing a boom in luxury industry and all that stuff.
It's part of it. Right.
And it's creating an economic crisis.
And, you know, more people need to be faced with.
I can't just sit here and work out
what will work for me in life and what won't.
Like, I have to go pay some dues and take some hits.
And that's gone. That's not totally gone.
But that's very well so evaporated.
If you don't at age 16, go and have that experience
of some fucking awful, miserable 40 year old guy,
you know, getting on your ass every day about being tardy or whatever it is.
You know, because school's not that anymore.
School can't be that.
School can't be like an asshole teacher, you know, writing you.
Your work can't be your boss writing you.
Everyone's walking on eggshells.
And I also get people's, you know, if you're making $10 an hour,
it is hard to take abuse from these assholes.
But you are learning how to be a member of the workforce.
Is that great? No.
But that is America. That is our country.
You have to learn how to be a member of the workforce
or you will become a bum, Lebowski.
You will become a bum.
And I hate authority.
I despise authority.
It's a real problem of mine.
I have to create an enemy at every job I have
because I need that anger to fuel myself.
That's not good.
But that comes from having a bunch of shitty bosses.
You get used to it.
You know, like if you're 35 and you still can't take orders from a boss,
that's how you become a guy who is at the drawing room at 6 a .m.,
you know, doing shots in the morning because you have nowhere to go.
It's it's we need structure.
Plus, I'm at the age now where my friends have kids.
And I see I even see it between the parents.
It's usually a very nurturing, very let let the child
explore mother and then a father who's like, hey, stop doing that.
And then the mom's like, don't talk to her like that.
The dad's like, what?
I just said, stop doing that.
I have many couple friends like this with their kids.
And a hundred out of a hundred times I'm siding with the dad.
A dad should be able to say, stop doing that.
Or else your child will be L on earth.
You wonder how we get these entitled monsters in society.
It's because no one ever said, stop doing that.
Now, it's different if your dad's throwing a work boot at your head.
But stop doing that should be in play as a parent.
Yeah, I don't want to have kids for that reason.
I don't want to invite the the jurisdiction of other parents into my life.
And I would never say anything to a parent, specifically a mother, about,
hey, I disagree with what you're doing.
She would be well within her rights to kick me in the nuts at that point.
A single childless 43 year old man.
But I certainly have my opinions on it.
I'm just like, you're creating a generation of entitled brats.
And a lot of them also feel like their childhood was robbed from them by COVID,
which I get, I understand.
So they're like, I'm doing nothing.
I'm letting this kid grow and just be happy because they had such a stressful childhood.
Good luck with that.
Good luck with letting the kid do her thing.
See how that works out for you.
All right. Well, folks, that's the show for today.
And now that we've alienated everyone today had a weird sort of
public radio vibe to it, like, what's the next issue we're tackling?
That's usually not the show.
It's I always get a little nervous talking about this stuff.
I don't. I do, too.
We're two straight men.
We're talking about it, you know.
But we're two straight men talking about it.
I, you know, I never want it to sound like.
We're male gazing the hell out of everything or we're not understanding
the other side of this equation.
You know, and we're also not blaming one side or the other.
It's just it is just kind.
And also, we're older and I don't want to sound like we're the old guys, but like.
It's just a conundrum and it's something that I don't think we're all discussing
quite a bit, you know, so.
I don't know. My parents can't, you know, the thought of bringing it up is
is stressful, even in a even at like a dinner, you know, it's like
because you start going on on it and people start talking and tempers rise.
And then the next thing you know, it's out of control.
I'm not just saying this, by the way, to to counter what you said.
Most of the parents I know, it's the opposite.
The mom is the one that's like, stop fucking around.
God damn it. You know what I mean?
And the dads are way more like trying to be cool, dad.
And sure, you know, I think that's a New York, L .A.
difference, because in L .A., the moms are all into the organics.
And, you know, the kid has the lollipop in their mouth
and they run over like they're chewing on a knife.
Like, you know how much processed sugar is in that?
It's like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I know more moms.
I'm not kidding in especially in the suburban region.
But I know more moms that have quietly called their children cunts to me.
Male or female. Yeah, yeah.
Then the dads are always like, oh, no, man, you know, let her do her thing.
And, you know, you know, I'm like her, meaning the wife.
Yeah. But parenting is hard.
Of course, it's hard.
But again, here's a couple of single white
males in their 40s talking about motherhood and being in a family.
But I.
Do not think I know,
and I'm probably throwing some people under the bus here.
I don't think I know a couple with children
who seem super happy.
No, no, I they always look
drained of color, exhausted
and very, very, very unsatisfied with their life.
And I think that's leading to more and more people not having them.
But I don't even have the I think as I've discussed on this show,
I'm browsing vasectomies, I'm online, I'm looking.
I know some parents,
the happy parents I know are usually parents that did it later on.
OK, that you're not missing out on as much.
You know, but the parents that I I think so many people become parents
just because it's like it's almost like a box to check.
It's like, well, that's what you do.
You marry this person, then you buy the house over here
and then you get the car and you have a kid.
And then those parents, to me,
there are higher numbers of ones that do not seem thrilled.
But I don't think they're thrilled in general with anything.
You're right. Yes. In their lives.
But the parents I know, not all of them,
but the ones I know that did it older or later.
Like kind of waited it out a bit, ended up adopting whatever it is.
They seem they're they're the one they're the only ones I've heard say,
dude, that's this is what it's all about.
This has been amazing.
Steve Martin's a great example.
I don't know him, but his the way he now great.
He's a multimillionaire that was able to.
Yeah, have a kid at seventy five.
And he probably, you know, it seemed like in the video,
that was the one time a day he runs into his daughter.
But no, I cried watching that because there is,
even though I'm saying all this, there is a part of me.
I don't have whatever they what do they call that when a woman has it, Joe?
Ticking biological clock or so till May.
Yeah, biological clock is thick.
Yeah, I you don't have that as strongly as a man,
but I definitely even as I say, I'm never going to have kids.
There's a pang with that comes with that of like, boy,
I really thought I was going to.
I really thought that would be my life.
I think I would be a good dad.
There's a sadness that comes along with it.
And I think that's what keeps me from getting the vasectomy.
Also, at the same time, I think it's time to end the Walsh line.
It it's done.
This ends it ends with me.
Yes, in the matrix.
We got to get to this.
We're we're like an hour in here.
We got to get to the. All right.
I don't I only have one thing for the corner.
I'm just not getting I don't have a lot of chance to watch much.
Yes, given the corner situation, so.
I last night went to Quentin Tarantino's Vista Theater
in my neighborhood and saw a 35 millimeter print of Sorcerer
Billy Friedkin's Sorcerer, a movie that was
not critically acclaimed upon release.
It was actually got pretty bad reviews.
It was a box office failure.
There's a very funny story when you read about this online, where the editor.
Went to see Star Wars, and he's like he calls Friedkin up and he goes.
Bill.
Our the trailer for Sorcerer just played before Star Wars.
It looked like we were on a television screen.
Then the curtain just kept opening and opening and opening and opening and opening.
And this ship starts coming in and he's like, we are dead in the water, Bill.
Our movie is nothing like he's like, we have failed.
And he was right. Star Wars was sweeping the nation.
All the theaters that should have been playing Sorcerer
could not because everybody needed to see Star Wars 10 times
competed, by the way, competed, by the way, only you know,
challenged, I should say, at the box office, only by Smokey and the Bandit.
The second most grossing film of that year.
Yeah. Well, they both still hold up, you know, I'll give them that.
Yeah. But Sorcerer is now considered sort of this lost masterpiece.
There were those two competing Friedkin documentaries and a great
Friedkin autobiography that came out in recent years.
And Sorcerer really is hailed as like up there with The Exorcist and
The French Connection as the best of his works.
So sold out 4 p .m. screening.
It's been playing all week at the Vista.
That's look, that's my reason for really truly loving L .A.
is the film community.
It's like a 4 p .m. on a Wednesday showing of a movie from 1977
sold out at a big theater is really cool to me.
But sure, the movie's dope.
I just remembered it as it's a remake of The Wages of Fear,
which is an awesome movie from the 50s, a French movie that even Friedkin
Friedkin claims it's not a remake, even though it clearly is.
It's the same story. Updated, of course.
But I remembered this movie as Roy Scheider and a team kind of like in Ronin,
a team from all across the globe uniting to get a very heavy truck
across a bridge that is collapsing like a Temple of Doom style log bridge.
And that's in there.
And that is it's some of the most riveting actions filmmaking ever made.
But it doesn't come till pretty near the end of the movie.
It becomes a big action movie in the home stretch.
There is an opening 20 minutes of this thing that's about as boring as can be.
I never got how difficult it's to follow.
You never saw the movie.
I never finished it.
That 20 minutes has sent me out of the room every time.
And I'm just like, I'll do this later, I guess.
I'm just bored. It's brutal.
I saw it with Vince and Matt McCarthy.
And we talked about it briefly after like this.
This is this is why we need a Joe out here.
I'm like, so what are we doing after?
It's six p .m. And both of them are like, well, go ahead home.
I'm just standing there on a sidewalk with tears forming in my eyes.
They go walk to their cars at six p .m.
Go to Rosa would have been like, well, we have 12 hours of drinking ahead.
Obviously, I was in bed by eight.
But the movie is look, when the action comes,
you know, you know, freaking an action, you've seen
French Connection and all this stuff.
He does amazing things with with like just the action filmmaking side of it.
The other stuff in Sorcerer.
It's not it's no masterpiece.
I think people overwrite things.
It's like Starship Troopers, you know, if everybody hates something.
And then later you realize it's actually pretty good.
We don't have to say it's a masterpiece.
We can go. We were wrong at first.
This movie is pretty sweet.
But Sorcerer is DOA for 30 minutes.
I mean, it's boring as shit.
And then it starts to pick up.
But, boy, is it a slow burn?
The action is well worth it.
I would have definitely benefited from having subtitled.
It's another sort of interesting thing there.
They had a vintage poster up in the lobby for Sorcerer.
And this is how bad they knew Sorcerer was going to do against Star Wars.
The poster is all words.
There's not no picture on it.
And it says the first 20 minutes of this film
are in foreign language with subtitles.
After that, we promise it's just an English language action movie
because people were walking out.
Well, they're like, I didn't know it was a foreign movie.
No, it's not a foreign.
But it's not just a foreign movie.
It's also boring as shit.
I it's weird.
And I'll say this, Friedkin.
The Exorcist opening is also kind of boring as shit.
When we're in Iraq, certainly as a kid, I can deal with it better now.
But there's 20 minutes at the beginning of the Exorcist
where you're checking that watch.
It at least throws creepiness in, though.
So you're like, it's spooky.
And you're like, all right, this is unsettling.
I'm not quite sure why yet.
It just is. And then and then it goes.
But Close Encounters also opens with a 20 minute prologue in the desert.
And you're like, come on, guys.
I yeah, I'm not a big I recognize Close Encounters is a good movie,
but I'm not a big fan of it because again, it's the Star Wars problem.
It's like, here's Spielberg's answer to Star Wars,
which is an alien movie and a space movie.
But 90 percent of the space movie is Richard Dreyfuss
looking at mashed potatoes or whatever.
And you're like, I'm like, all right, I guess he's so good at it.
He's great. But it's just it's just I don't know.
I don't I don't it's not it's not for me.
But anyway, well, I don't know if I shared this on here,
but I found a paper my dad wrote in college.
My dad went to college when he was.
I was like 13 or something. He was in his 30s.
And he had written a paper on a film class about his 10 favorite movies.
And it was like the Blues Brothers,
the Big Chill.
And I think number three was Close Encounters of the Third Kind.
And in the paragraph that he wrote about why it was one of his favorite movies,
he talked about relating because he never knew I would see this.
I found this in the basement.
He talked about relating to Richard Dreyfuss.
Electing in the end to leave his family and go into space with the aliens.
He's like, what father hasn't thought about this?
But that's like why he related to it.
I was kind of like, I guess I won't mention this to him that I saw this.
But it it helped me understand him a little better that he was waiting.
The reason he wasn't a strong father is because he was waiting for an alien ship
to rescue him from having to father us.
And now I understand him better. I get that.
Yeah, my only entry today is the aforementioned Time Bandits.
I haven't finished all the episodes yet, but I'm most of the way through.
It is the one thing that I've been watching.
You know, I turn this on kind of scoffing,
thinking it wasn't going to be great.
I adore the original film.
And you know what? I got to say, my hat's off to it.
It's very kid friendly.
Jermaine Clement,
Taika, Wattiti, and the third guy is Ian Harris, I think.
Yeah. They made a great
kids show, and it's got a lot of very funny,
kid friendly humor in it.
It's very charming.
It has stakes. It's fun.
Did it need to be a full series of, I think, 10 episodes?
I think it probably could have been a little shorter, but
I'm enjoying it very much.
And Lisa Kudrow is very funny in it.
She plays the lead bandit.
Taika. What's her vibe?
Is she playing dimwitted or what's her vibe in it?
She's not dimwitted, but she's she's doing the Kudrow like.
You know, the like, she's kind of bitchy
and she's kind of just like, I don't know then, whatever.
Whatever you want to do.
You know, like, it's the it's the like, I can't be bothered kind of Kudrow.
Right, right. There's a funny.
There's a really funny sequence where they're going to steal the Trojan horse.
Yeah. And the kid's like.
You want to steal the trojans?
Because the hook of the show is the kid knows everything about histories
of history nut and they know nothing about history.
They just want to steal stuff.
So I like it. Yeah.
He's like, you want to steal the Trojan horse?
Like, that's crazy. Yeah.
And she's like, yeah, we're going to steal it.
It'll be fine. And he's like, it's too big.
You can't steal it.
And she's like, it'll be fine.
And then they when they get to it, she's like, well, now that we're up close,
it is probably too big to steal.
You know, like it's it's that Kudrow.
She's very funny. Everybody's very funny in it.
Especially her, Germaine and Taika.
Taika plays the supreme being and Germaine plays evil.
And they're perfectly cast like Taika.
Yeah. Plays the supreme being.
You know, kind of like almost like a like a like a millennial style.
Like, he's just very funny in it.
And Germaine Clement is awesome as a guy that is super evil.
But also kind of dumb.
And, you know, it's it's perfect casting.
It's it's and for two guys that put themselves in their own project,
it makes perfect sense.
My only problem with the show
is I don't understand the not casting of little people as the time bandits.
There is nothing in that original movie that is exploitative
or mocking of little people.
And I can say that as a child, seeing that movie,
one of the most beautiful takeaways to me.
To get a little sappy for a second here was the fact that I watched a movie
that much like The Wizard of Oz, introduced me
to people that appeared different than I did and.
Presented it as as normal as it should be.
And there was no part of me as a kid that was like,
oh, look at those people, they're different.
I just loved them as characters.
And I feel like this was an opportunity to cast six or seven
little people in something and make them heroes and make them awesome
and not in any way make it an exploitative venture.
And I think it's a shame they didn't do that.
Now, there's little people cast in other parts of the show.
But but that's the only criticism I would have.
I find it very funny.
Matt King shows up, which was a delightful surprise.
Super Hands from Peep Show.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They do a really funny thing with him where he's the.
He's the henchman for the for the sheriff of Nottingham.
And they're he he he basically brings the people in for torture.
He's the head of torture or whatever.
And they convinced the army under the sheriff of Nottingham,
like, you don't have to take orders.
Don't you see you're your own people?
And you watch that realization go all the way up the ladder.
And like when Matt King finally realizes it, he's like
he's like, I'm not going to do whatever I want and I will torture.
And if I have and if I break code, I'll be tortured.
And they're like, but who's going to torture you?
You're the torture.
He's like, right.
I never thought of it like that.
And he becomes this like
hippie ish, like I was walking through the forest today.
Is anything more beautiful than life?
It's very funny. It's a very funny show.
All right. I like it.
And I'm curious to see how it goes.
And I'm curious to see how they.
How Charlene's character goes away, because she's only in six episodes
and she's one of the time bandits, so I'm like,
I guess they're just going to say she dies.
She dies or something.
I don't know. You know, like, I guess that was a lot of going back
to his home planet. Yeah.
Rewriting on rewriting on set on that one.
Anyway, time bandits, I recommend it, especially if you have a younger person
that you want to show something fun and funny to that you can both enjoy.
Yeah. Have you seen the poochy episode of The Simpsons, Joe?
No. Where they try to introduce a new character.
Oh, boy, is that funny.
You're not a fan. I know.
But that's that's one you could check out and change your mind.
I'm not not. I can't imagine somebody being like, I'm going to watch The Simpsons.
I'm going to just start at episode one and watch The Simpsons.
I mean, maybe if you start at the beginning of the pandemic, you could do it.
But like, Jesus Christ, I consider myself a huge fan.
And there's 20 seasons I haven't watched.
I'm not not a fan. I appreciate it.
I think it's funny. I've just never been.
I'm just not a big animation
comedy animation guy for whatever reason.
It's like Rick and Morty. I recognize it's very well done.
I just I'm just for whatever reason, I'm not into adult
cartoon comedy.
I've never was a big adult swim guy.
You mean either.
I mean, South Park, I enjoy and I've got my shows I enjoy.
But there comes a breaking point to it where you're like, I'm a grown man.
Do you have anything else for the corner or do you want to just go to the movie?
I'll do one more. I rewatched You Can Count on Me,
only available on DVD.
Even though streaming has promised us that everything will be available
on streaming, you cannot find you can count on me anywhere online.
It's a real great movie.
I remember when I saw it, I was like, this movie is everything
I want in a movie.
When I saw it now, I would not get down from being five stars to four.
It's Kenneth Lonergan, who's a great playwright, screenwriter, director.
I think he is playing with material here that he perfected in Manchester
by the Sea. A lot of people love Margaret.
I think, you know, that would was maybe my third
favorite of these three that a sort of grief trilogy.
But I love this movie.
When I was in high school, I think this was the first time
I had ever seen Ruffalo.
And I was like, this guy's the next Marlon Brando.
This guy's the best actor I've ever seen.
And when I watch it now,
I think it's just because we're used to Ruffalo's tics.
We're used to like he kind of does the same thing every movie.
Not not a judgment. He's good at it.
But he did not jump off the screen as much for me in this viewing.
Twenty years later, Laura Linney jumped off the screen.
Always loved Linney, but she is incredible in this movie.
And she has the less showy role to Ruffalo.
So you don't notice when you're like 19.
I think when you're 19, you like more that Pacino explosive kind of acting.
That's what good acting looks like to you.
And then you grow up and it just kind of changes.
They're both amazing.
They're a believable brother and sister.
You never see a brother, sister relationship in movies.
Certainly not one this deep.
And it's a really great movie.
The side plot with Linney and her and
she's sleeping with her boss at the bank, played by Matthew Broderick,
who is cheating on his pregnant wife.
It's got a lot of the kind of sad
comedy that election had with Broderick,
where he's just a guy who's just not making good decisions.
And that's all funny.
But the real tragedy of the movie is that Ruffalo is clearly trapped
in this kind of extended adolescence that he will probably not break out of.
We all know people like him in this movie.
He's not holding up liquor stores.
He's just a guy who cannot get his shit together.
And we got another Culkin in the mix, Rory Culkin, as Laura Linney's son.
And she wants her son to be friends with her brother.
But she does not like the influence that
she the Ruffalo is having on her son.
It's it's a simple movie.
It's just about human relationships.
But few people do it as well as Kenneth Lonergan.
Check it out, Laura Linney.
And we're moving on to wait, wait, Laura Linney.
You'll appreciate this. She was in my bar.
Yes. Oh, yeah.
I guess she's directing a movie
and they were shooting across the street from the bar.
So they they asked they like.
Rented the bar for a little while
because they had to set a camera up in the window to shoot.
And she was in the I wasn't there, but my my business partner, Paul, was like,
yeah, Laura Linney was in the bar today.
That's cool.
He said she was very nice with with Jude Law and Jason Bateman
as brothers that looks pretty cool.
Yeah. So he said she was very sweet.
He said she's very short, which I was surprised to hear.
Reads is a tall one.
Wouldn't know. She does.
And he has been excellent in movies for my entire life.
She's just a really great actress.
And then Ozark talk about a kind of a home stretch.
Not that her career is over.
I just mean, it was like, oh, man, she had all this in her, too.
She's got a little Lady Macbeth side to her.
Great actress.
We are talking today about.
Trap.
M Night Shyamalan's trap, and I just kind of saw it on a date.
I'm like, oh, yeah, this is starting.
We'll go see this.
And I texted Joe right when I got out, like, oh, we need to do trap on the show.
There's much to be said about trap Shyamalan.
Got to be on drugs at this point.
Got to be on drugs.
Something's going wrong.
This movie.
So apparently Shyamalan's daughter is an actual pop star.
So he has built a movie around her where basically you can imagine
that it's Taylor Swift, essentially a big concert that a lot of young
screaming girls are at.
And Josh Hartnett takes his daughter to the show.
And we learn after about a half hour or so that Josh Hartnett is actually
a serial killer on the loose.
And while they have him at this concert, they're going to try to get the drop on.
When I say we, I mean, the police and the FBI, the FBI here led, of course.
By Haley Mills from the parent trap.
The original parent trap.
She's 87 years old wearing the blue FBI jacket.
From from there, the movie gets increasingly ridiculous as it goes.
It's kind of a nifty little premise for a thriller at first.
And then, boy, does he lose the fucking thread.
He's also including full songs from his daughter as though it's a music video.
The songs are lifeless, no melody, not catchy at all.
The dancing is is or the choreography is pathetic.
And he he doesn't seem to have been to a concert before as as Hartnett and his
daughter walk into the show and the opening act is playing.
There are seven people in the stands, probably because they didn't want to pay
for CGI, but I have never been to it.
I've never seen the opening, opening, opening act of a concert and not had the
opportunity to see the opening act of a concert.
I mean, it's it's a movie that seems to have not done, you know, how you'll
sometimes you'll see a movie about like Jack the Ripper and you're like, did
they even do any research here about the time period?
But what's weird about this movie is it gives you that uncanny feeling of like
nobody did their research, but you're just watching cops talk to each other.
Like it seems like Shyamalan's never seen a cop show before.
He doesn't know how people speak anymore.
No, no.
This is a disastrous movie.
It's I would ask her argue.
And this is saying a lot at this point could be Shyamalan's worst.
And if it's not as worst, it is right up there with the happening and Lady
in the Water. I mean, this movie sucks.
Yes. Well, my friends on Letterboxx, they're either like me and they gave it
one or two stars or they're given it four and five stars.
And I'm clicking on these reviews like, what the fuck are you talking about?
And it turns out that all of them are appreciating this movie on a plan nine
level on a this is one of the all time great, so bad, it's good movies.
And look, I don't know if I agree with that or not, but at a nine PM opening
night showing this thing played like Anchorman in 2003.
I mean, people were howling, laughing throughout this movie.
It's it's a terribly, terribly lazy film from a writing standpoint.
There are several things I could refer to.
I'll just hit a couple.
The first is the fact that all of the exposition
with the setup for what's happening, which is, and I quote,
this entire concert is a trap.
Nobody's allowed to leave after the show because they know the killer is here.
That entire premise is conveyed to Josh Hartnett by who?
A merch salesman that just seems to think he's a nice guy
and gives him top secret FBI information.
So I want you to think about the ask here to the audience.
They're already asking the audience to believe that the FBI would take
over a venue and somehow get the entire staff of the venue.
Not undercut. They're not planting undercovers.
They get the actual venue staff to be in on the scheme.
That right down to the vendors, down to the people selling merch.
So that's that in and of itself is insane.
The second part is the concept that the FBI would be able to do this secretly
and somehow not let anybody leave the venue.
It's insane. It's insane.
And then they clarify later only the men aren't allowed to leave.
It's crazy. It is crazy.
The first the first person who out of, you know,
how big are these concert places to twenty five thousand seats or something?
Thirty. The first. Yeah. About thirty thousand.
First person to leave.
First person who was told you can't leave this concert.
That becomes a big deal. Yeah.
They don't even use that as a plot point.
It makes the movie more interesting if we see somebody try to leave
and they go, hey, I'm sorry, nobody out of the concert.
And that person starts causing a big scene.
Then we have a real conflict that generates from the story,
the absurd story you've created.
So but we don't get that.
And that's the biggest issue with the movie.
There are several scenes where there are cops.
There's a scene where they're doing the briefing.
With the SWAT team in the break room of the venue.
That to me is probably the worst written scene of Shyamalan's career.
And that got the biggest laughs
when the chief of police, Hardin, that's in the room
listening to the police plan how to capture him.
And by the way, the detectives that are supposed to be solving the crap,
none of them turn around and go, what the fuck are you doing in here?
Who are you? They just don't care.
He's walking around talking to everyone.
So you've got a mysterious man walking around in the room
where all the police are discussing their plan to capture a mysterious man.
And nobody thinks to check on the one that's behind them.
And while that's going on, so the whole setup of the scene is false.
You don't you're just not buying anything that's happening in the scene.
And while it's happening, the policeman is going,
I'll treat any one of you who catch Josh Hartnett,
who was steak dinner.
Yeah. And you're like at night that that would be stupid
in a 1930s cops and robbers movie.
That would be that would be stupid.
You know, you'd go, God, we're cops like this.
A hundred years ago, that's ludicrous.
He's having normal everyday cops talk like this.
Oh, it's not the other thing.
What did this guy do?
There's there's there's 20 ,000 little girls in the stadium.
And you decide to set a trap where he's surrounded by little girls.
That seems like the right move to you, FBI.
It's it's nuts.
Josh Hartnett is getting all of the information about this sting operation
via luck instead of.
And I said to Pat after I saw it, what they could have done was
have him realize what's happening because he's seeing too many cops
and then him doing actual his own detective work
to get to the bottom of it.
And that's then showing why he's great at being a serial killer
because he's wily and he's and he's smart and whatever.
They do none of that. It's terrible.
The other thing they do is they do none of it.
And I'd argue I'd argue if they had done it, you know,
they couldn't have pulled it off because Hartnett today,
just as he was back in the 90s, can not act.
I have seen people raving about this man's performance.
I think he was bad.
He couldn't do a wheels turning performance because his wheels aren't turning.
I didn't think he was bad. I bought him in the part.
It's competent. He's competent.
But but here's the thing.
And this, for whatever reason, this detail really bothered me
because I was like, this is just lazy fucking writing.
Shyamalan is dead set on this whole thing
taking place in the same day.
OK, fine.
It's it's hold on a second.
It's it's it's.
The it's sorry, I got distracted.
My manager texted me.
It's fine.
I'm sorry. He wants the entire thing to take place over the course of this one day.
Fine. If that's what you want to do, fine.
But because of that.
He sets the concert at 12 o 'clock in the afternoon.
It's absurd.
They're in this concert, as you're supposed to believe, for hours.
It just keeps going and going.
And they keep going.
Josh keeps leaving the audience to go investigate some stuff,
you know, investigate in heavy quotes.
And every time he does, it is broad daylight outside.
And I'm going, what fucking concert is happening in broad daylight?
So then I thought, OK,
maybe they're saying it's an early show and it's like the summertime.
So it's just not dark yet.
Later in the movie, you see a sign on the main street in the town
that it's the fall festival.
And you're like, OK, so it's the time of year work.
It's dark at four forty five p .m..
This fucking concert must have happened at 12 o 'clock.
This is nuts. This is.
And this is this is where Joe, there are script supervisors.
There are people who do this stuff on on Disney Channel shows.
No offense to Disney Channel shows.
But there are people who are who are paid to go, well, wait a minute.
It can't be this time of day because this they're annoying as fuck,
especially when you're running a show and you're against a schedule.
And they're like, I caught an error here.
He wouldn't he wouldn't be able to go to this at this time.
But you need them.
You need that sort of logic obsessed person.
Otherwise, movies have these holes in them.
I refuse to believe nobody went to Shyamalan and said, dude,
lots of this is not adding up.
You know, it's the the concert during the day thing.
Just like what you're saying, Joe, let's say you and I are writing this movie
and we let's say that these are our objectives.
We want to do a daylong concert.
There's there's a couple of ways to do it.
Number one, what you said, it's a special concert for young girls.
It's a it's an early curfew thing.
You could even tie in the serial killer.
There's a serial killer on the loose.
There's a curfew.
So we're keeping our concerts early.
You could do Taylor Swift does three hour concerts.
You could say, you know, she's so competitive with that.
She's a fictional pop star.
She's so competitive with Taylor Swift.
She wants to do six hour concerts.
You know, she thinks she's got to be doubly good.
You could explain this away.
I'm not saying it would be satisfactory, but you could explain this away
with one line, and there's so many flaws with this movie
that could have been explained away with one line.
And it's not there.
Shabala, he's at a point, as I was saying to my friend yesterday,
he's at a point clearly where when he's given a note, he is saying,
nobody cares about that.
Nobody's worried about that.
Nobody's going to notice that.
And it's like, no, everybody is noticing it.
By the way, the only thing that could make this movie interesting
is how does the killer get out of the venue without getting caught?
They're that's it.
Yeah, that mouse, all one setting, whatever.
They leave this goddamn venue.
And by the way, when they left the venue.
I was like, OK.
Uh, this has got to be the home stretch now.
I looked down at my watch.
It's got like another hour 20 or something.
I was like, oh, my God, I can't.
This is the only movie and I'm serious, people.
This is the only movie I have ever seen in public
by myself where I was talking out loud to myself
in the theater while I was watching it.
It was so fucking stupid and are Jewish and whatever.
They end up going back to Josh Hartnett's house.
Where you meet his family, he's got the singer with him.
Why does he have the singer with him?
Because the fucking person managing the concert tells him
the only person that gets through security is the singer
without being checked.
She then walks out of a venue with a strange man and his daughter.
And the FBI is like, that person must be not be the killer,
even though he fits the exact description.
He's with the singer.
It is so insane.
So anyway, he sort of.
Well, yeah, they they go to Hartnett's house.
And at that at that moment,
I don't know if you had this experience, Joe, but I thought
I am watching a movie that is almost beat for beat, long legs,
different characters, different situation, of course.
But when they went to that house, I thought of them going to Blair
Underwood's house at the end of Long Legs.
Both movies have like a psychic
pro FBI profiler lady.
Weren't they saying she was like had some sort of powers?
I don't remember that.
And you explain this.
I need you to explain to me what she's doing in this movie, Joe,
because I just I thought I missed something.
Two reasons. The first is said, well, the parent trap and trap.
I didn't even make that connection.
That's one. I'm positive.
That's where it started.
And the other part is she I looked I looked up Haley Mills.
I think she's 73.
I think Shyamalan is just going, well, if Tommy Lee Jones
can be the head of the FBI in something at 73, why can't Haley Mills?
All right. It's a fair point.
But it's like, well, it's not good casting.
He was he was 55 back when he used to play the head of the FBI.
But that's my guess.
Is it's is that's and it's it's like, fine, then cast an older woman,
but cast an older woman that seems believably the head of the FBI.
Not this. Yeah.
The this it's distracting casting.
And then the English accent doesn't help.
It doesn't help.
No, it doesn't help.
No, nothing helps.
But when they're sitting in that living room
with his family, to me, I just immediately flashed to that Blair Underwood scene.
And I was like, God, these movies are very similar in a lot of ways.
I prefer long legs, of course.
But they're the only real saving grace
is the performance of Alison Pill, who is an actress who used to be in a lot of
things as like a young girl, and I haven't seen her in a long time.
But she's great.
She plays the wife.
And honestly, her commitment to her little supporting role
is all that sort of barely keeps this movie hanging together
as it as it goes lower and lower and just bottoms out.
But it's not good.
Nobody in it is good.
They're supporting performances that I would say are notably bad.
Hartnett runs into a girl from the daughter's school
and they have a little, you know, young girl fight brewing between them.
And Hartnett meets her mom,
who plays like kind of a small supporting role in the film.
And the woman that played this mom is awful.
She's awful in a way you just don't see in movies, you know,
like a supporting part in M.
Night Shyamalan movie.
Did you did you watch one audition tape?
That woman was not an actress.
Well, it's it's and then she threatens Josh Hartnett.
It's it's the writing is just terrible.
She starts as a sort of overly zealous mom.
And then the mom's like, yeah, he runs into her again later.
And she's like, let's get the kids together.
And and he's like, yeah, that'll be fine.
I can't talk about it right now, but that'll be fine.
And then immediately she's like, don't fuck with me.
I'll turn your life into shit.
And I'm like, what is happening right now?
So Shyamalan is also and has always been.
After his third or fourth movie, guilty of injecting comedy
in a way that just doesn't work and doesn't make sense.
It's also one of the I would say maybe the most glaring example is
the rapping white kid in the grandparents won the visit.
And just like just like in this movie, he brings the rapping kid back
for like a literally like a sitcom tag over the credits.
And this movie does the same thing.
They bring the merch guy back for a credits tag,
like a literally like a sitcom, not like a Deadpool thing, but like,
hey, let's check back in with this hilarious character we all love.
And you're like, no, dude.
The bit when they bring the merch guy back at the end
and he's watching it on TV and they show heart in its face.
And the whole bit is the guys like, man, I'm never trusting anybody again at work.
Oh, this is crazy.
Whatever the the sold out audience was silent.
And it's by the way, it's a comedy does not work.
It's a complete rip.
It's a complete rip of the scene in Get Out with Lil Rel when he realizes
what's going on and he which is a very funny scene where he goes, see, man,
that TSA should be tingling. I knew something was wrong, you know?
And it's a great scene.
I brought the house down when I saw that movie in the theater.
Yeah, huge, huge.
He just rips it off in this and it's terrible.
It's a terrible movie at the end.
When Josh Hartner, you know what I thought of when he first goes
to the merch guy, when he goes to this, he goes to this merch,
goes like, hey, what's going on?
The guy's selling T -shirts and he looks over and goes, well, apparently
they got a serial killer trapped here.
You know, he knows everything.
I thought of that scene in Wayne's World where they go up to Chris Farley
and he tells them where Mr.
Big is going and does the and then Wayne looks into the camera and he goes,
boy, that guy knew an awful lot for a security guard, didn't he?
And then shrugs and walks off.
Classic, perfect bit in Wayne's World.
Especially when you see it 25 years later
that we're still doing these stupid cliches.
But when Josh Hartner is finally abducted at the end of the film.
In a lazy scene where his wife
somehow in 10 seconds is able to do a sleight of hand and poison his pie
that he eats. Oh, God, yeah.
And and he doesn't taste the poison, which all right, fine.
I guess we're just supposed to know that he would use a tasteless poison
of some kind, but anyway, she drugs him.
Quick pause.
I forgot this movie ended with a poison piece of pie.
Thank you for reminding me, Joe.
It's ridiculous.
It's ridiculous that he believes that it's all fine.
Yeah, it's ridiculous that.
Yeah. Up until that point, this character,
why would you eat a piece of pie in that moment?
And he tells her he's going to kill her and then kill himself
because it's the only way it can end.
He says that several times
when when they're closing in on him after he escapes the venue.
The only way this can end is for me to kill myself.
And he's saying it like I'm a bad person and it needs to end somewhere.
When he finally does get poisoned, the cops come in.
He's under the influence of the drug.
He fights with all of his might to not be abducted, which doesn't make sense.
Then he's finally awake.
The cops, the FBI walks him out.
He asks to to be allowed to to his daughter's bike is tilted over on the lawn.
He asked if he can stop and just set it up right in like as like
in a good dad moment or whatever, he does so.
They bring him into the truck.
The final scene is him getting out of his handcuffs in the truck,
which makes no sense since he wants to get caught.
And how does he do it?
They reveal he's broken a bike spoke off of the wheel
when he set when he stood the bike, which is he doesn't do that.
You watch him stand the bike up.
It doesn't it would be impossible.
Exactly right. It would take forever.
It would be noisy.
They would see that he's doing it.
It's so crazy and it's so lazy.
And it's it's Shyamalan riding backwards from a twist.
He gets a dumb twist in his head and he goes, Oh,
then that would have that happened.
OK, well, how are you going to pull it on?
The issue is the issue is with this one, the the twist is revealed
at the end of the first act.
By the way, the twist is actually revealed one second into the trailer.
So that's kind of the problem with advertising these types of movies is
that whole first half that's supposed to be suspenseful.
What am I watching? Who is this guy?
What's going on? We know he's a serial killer.
We've seen the trailer, but.
He. Shyamalan gives us that twist and then he's trying to keep it surprising
and moving as it goes, but the mystery is gone.
So these twists are, as you're saying, like with the spoke thing are just stupid.
You don't buy it.
He's trying to top the initial thing that heart and that is the killer, but you can't.
That's your big twist.
And you've already shown us.
So he's got this weird thing.
Now Shyamalan, where it's like I know he considers himself
a master of the macabre or like a Hitchcock type.
He does that. Actually, he's good in the movie.
He has a small cameo. He's one of the more natural performers.
Oh, but how about that part?
But how about that part?
Hartnett just walks up to him randomly and he's like, yeah, I'm I'm the singer's uncle.
You know, she brings a girl on stage every night and he's like,
I'm going to lie and say my daughter has cancer.
So they bring her on stage and and it's it's fucking ridiculous.
The whole fucking movie, it's ridiculous.
Every minute of it is ridiculous.
And Shyamalan used to be a guy.
There's a very funny picture making the rounds on the Internet
the past couple of weeks where there's a guy at a premiere
holding up a picture of that alien in signs.
And it says, thanks for the childhood trauma.
And it's M Night with his arm around the guy.
And he's like pointing at the picture because you forget
Shyamalan used to be a guy who would always have one
terrifying scare in his movies.
Sixth Sense, you know, the girl puking signs has that alien
popping up, which everybody screamed when I saw that in the theater.
That's what that poster is.
But this movie,
because we're kind of in a way rooting for Hartnett,
it's not like you're rooting for anyone else per se.
You're rooting for him sort of to get away with it as a serial killer.
So they can't make him too bad where he's murdering all these people on screen.
So what we're left with is he pushes one lady down the stairs.
There's weirdly no investigation, even though we know
there's a serial killer in the venue.
He pushes a lady down the stairs and calmly walks away.
And that's it. By the way, she's dead, I guess.
By the way, pushes the lady down the stairs. Why?
Because there just happens to be, in the second he needs it,
somebody so drunk at one p .m., they can't stand up barely.
And he shows and she's standing at the top of a staircase.
It's right. And oh, God, it's almost like in Dirty Rotten Scoundrels
when that trailer, when they pushed the lady into the fountain
and it's like a big laugh.
But you're like, so wait, he just pushed this lady down the stairs,
risked his life just because he in that moment
wanted to kill one more, wanted to claim one more body.
That's not how serial killers are.
A serial killer doesn't push someone down the stairs.
They want to be close. They want to experience the kill.
Like, it's just basic things.
Don't make any sense. He does it as a serial killer.
He does it as a distraction, but he does it as a distraction.
Oh, you're right. OK, well, yeah.
But that's what that makes it more egregious.
He does it. It's so convenient.
It's dumb. Yeah, it's just don't even that.
In that moment, the other distraction he causes is he blows up.
That's in the trailer, too.
But he blows up these oil tanks or whatever in the in the fryer
at the concession stand.
So it blows up and you just kind of hear it and you're like, oh, shit.
Like these glass bottles just exploded in this woman's face.
Now we're going to get the big horror moment
because there's nothing even remotely suspenseful or scary in the film.
And you're like, all right, here comes the big gross out.
And they cut to her face.
It's like a very tasteful, reserved makeup.
M. Night, you're making a horror movie.
We just saw two bottles blow up at close range in a woman's face.
And you made her look like she's got chicken pox.
It's give us the gross out.
Raise our pulse and night remind us that we're watching a thriller.
Even with even with the down the stairs push,
that could have been there's somebody at the top of the stairs
because it's a staircase.
They're not so drunk. They don't know what's going on.
He shoves them. The person falls.
The person starts screaming, somebody pushed me.
And now he's got to duck into the crowd and not get caught.
There were a million ways to make every moment of this more believable,
less convenient, more suspenseful, more anything.
And he fails at every turn.
And of course, the end is this stupid cliffhanger.
By the way, what you just said is exactly right, Joe.
It's like he's not bending logic.
To support the suspense.
You know, it's not like he, you know, maybe maybe the fugitive
Harrison Ford wouldn't jump off that that thing into the water.
But boy, does it up the suspense and you're like, fuck, what's
what are these two men going to do now?
You know, this movie has none of those moments
because he's not stretching credibility because like, you know what?
I got this amazing suspenseful set piece.
And even if it's it's maybe not quite believable,
I think it's worth it for how scary this is, let's say.
No, what you have is things that aren't believable.
So you're taken out of it completely and not suspenseful.
So you just don't know what he's doing.
Yeah, it's conclusion, Joe.
You said I interrupted you.
So the conclusion is at the end, Hartnett gets free of his handcuffs.
It's this dumb cliffhanger where there's going to be a sequel, theoretically.
Oh, yeah. And Hartnett looks into camera, breaks the fourth wall and starts laughing.
Because of this stupid thing that he had in his head of how he wanted it to end,
he then incorporates stylistically throughout the movie
several moments where a camera where where a character is talking directly
into camera and you're looking at that character peep show style
from the other from the person they're talking to perspective.
And it makes no sense.
It's got nothing to do with anything.
It doesn't add any. It's distracting.
And again, it seems to me like Shyamalan decided at the end
he wanted Hartnett to look into camera and laugh.
Therefore, well, I've got to do this now throughout the movie.
So it's a style choice.
And we're not weirdly breaking the fourth wall at the end,
like it's some kind of goofy sitcom.
None of it works. Trap is terrible.
I'll give it one star for the performance of The Wife.
And I thought Hartnett was decent.
But my hog could not be more down and deflated.
I mean, just disgusted, just disgusted.
My hog is way, way down.
My hog actually feels like it's in a trap, like a Chinese finger trap
or maybe like a bear trap has just chopped down on my genitals.
But I'm looking now at the Shyamalan filmography.
I mean, this guy, let's just do it wide awake.
You know, his little indie from from early on. Fine.
The sixth sense. Unbreakable.
Right. Modern classics signs.
I haven't seen it since the theater, but I think everyone agrees
it's a slight step down, but a whole lot of fun.
And you got fucking Gibson and Joaquin Phoenix.
I saw signs opening weekend in the theater for my birthday with my parents.
I was extremely excited.
I hated signs, but I thought it had its moments.
But that was when I started the swing away stuff, the water stuff.
Yeah, it's tough.
Why would the aliens come to a planet
that's made up almost entirely of water if they don't like water?
Yeah, I've got issues with it, too.
Then comes the village.
The village is really, you know, really all about hang.
It hangs everything on a twist that barely works.
But the village is effective.
It's well acted. It's a good movie.
And then comes Lady.
Yeah, it's got it's got things to recommend.
Lady in the water, folks.
It don't get much worse than Lady in the water
until you go to the happening with Marky Mark.
Saw that.
Now, that's another movie that got a lot of big laughs when I saw it in the theater.
Marky Mark is a scientist.
Bad. Then comes the last Airbender.
I never saw that shit.
And then three years later, After Earth with Will Smith and his son.
After Earth is considered the low point of his career.
I never saw that either.
I never saw the comeback trail.
No, it didn't see Airbender or After Earth.
Then the comeback trail, the visit.
A lot of fun, except for the wrapping, as we said.
The visit lit. Hold on.
I think the visit sucks.
I said it when we watched it.
Aside from the old lady crawling around in the dirt at that one part,
the twist, I guess that twist six minutes into the fucking movie.
I think the visit sucks.
Well, I'm comparing them to like, you know, Lady in the Water, I guess.
Sure. So.
And it's easier for me to like a scrappy ten million dollar movie than,
you know, I would imagine Lady in the Water.
The making of Lady in the Water book is a must read for any fan of like
disaster films. It's it's it's fascinating.
Then you got Split and Glass, which we both kind of enjoyed.
I think Split more than Glass, if memory serves.
And here's the thing, Split is solid enough,
but kind of boring and I didn't care.
And then the Bruce Willis twist at the end.
And I was like, oh, wow. OK.
Where are we going? Glass.
And it ends in a parking lot. Yeah.
Glass starts awesome and then goes to shit.
Old is.
It's terrible from a logic standpoint.
I thought Old was such a great looking movie and all the pieces were there,
but I really thought that one sucked.
I really thought it sucked and Knock at the Cabin.
I actually watched a second time and Knock at the Cabin is a step up for M.
Night. I agree. Like I don't I don't love it,
but that's the kind of shit he should be doing.
Like if they're not going to give you the big budgets anymore,
don't flagrantly show us how little money you have.
You know, do a movie with four characters in a cabin.
Don't do something like this where we're we're questioning
literally every plot point.
It's like, no, that wouldn't be like that.
That wouldn't look like that. This wouldn't happen like that.
There's nothing that takes you out of a thriller quicker than that.
You know, the two things I said to Pinkstone were M.
Night Shyamalan. Look, he's our John Carpenter.
He's got some real smash hits and then he's made some terrible
fucking movies. And you're like, I don't know.
He sure has. Sometimes it comes together.
Sometimes it doesn't. When it does, it's magnificent.
When it doesn't, it's pretty disastrous.
I also said to Jim and I texted him this during the movie.
I said, I'm watching Trap.
This could be the stupidest movie I've ever seen in my life.
I'm talking it is dirty work, stupid.
However, this movie is only unintentionally hilarious.
I was like, dirty work at least is really funny,
but it's a moronic movie and it's somehow more believable
than this movie. The premise of dirty work is more believable.
By the way, I, you know, I love dirty work,
but it's also just a junkie movie, meaning it doesn't look great.
Shyamalan, I used to say, like, why doesn't this guy direct
somebody else's scripts?
He should start doing that.
You know, I don't think he's ever directed somebody else's script
that I know of unless I'm forgetting something.
But that is what the man should be doing.
I used to say because he's a great director, but his writing has gone off the edge.
Then I saw this movie and I'm like, I don't think he's a great director anymore.
No, no, this is I mean, this was bad.
This is this is a game changer in the worst way.
You watch this and you're just like, I don't get it, man.
I don't get it.
Well, I think I think he's as good as the people around him.
And he's either not listening to the people around him
or he's not surrounded by qualified people anymore, one or the other.
I'm not sure. But well, the well, the book,
the Lady in the Water book about the making of it,
it was supposed to be this guy going along to like,
you know, chronicle the next triumph in M.
Knight's career, because that's what everybody's expecting.
He's this guy with these huge, huge heads.
And like the first chapter of the book is Shyamalan
turns in his script for Lady in the Water.
And his last four movies have made a billion fucking dollars.
And he's on top of the world.
And he turns it in and, you know,
Disney or tries to whoever the studio was, rejected it.
They were like, dude, we want to be in business with you.
We love you. We know that you're on fire right now.
This doesn't seem like the project for us.
And he gets he gets so pissed.
He's like, how dare they?
By the way, so would I if I just made a billion dollars for Sony or whatever.
So would I. But if everyone is telling you something doesn't work,
in that book, everyone, every step of the way is telling him
this movie don't work.
And he's like, fuck you. I'm right.
And that's a it's a terrible headspace to begin.
You know, you kind of need it to be a director at times.
But if everybody's telling you you're going the wrong way,
you're going the wrong way most of the time.
And Shyamalan, you're going the wrong way, pal.
Hogs are down.
Not sure what's coming up on the show.
Probably Maxine.
I think that hits streaming in a few days, at least for right.
Yeah, I think Fall Guy will be next month
because that move to August 30th is streaming.
I saw Maxine Joe hasn't, but we'll discuss that one as well.
Yeah, yes.
Anyway, just quick plugs.
If you haven't gotten tickets and you're in the area,
come out to the Phoenixville warm up shows the 10th and 12th of September
prior to the taping on the 14th.
Other than that, come out to Joey Rose's in New York.
And I will in the new tour for 2025.
We're announcing very soon the Joystick Tour.
I'll be back in the comedy clubs instead of the rock venues this time around.
Tons of dates starting in January.
So I hope to see you.
And prior to that, I'm doing a big holiday show in Somerset, Massachusetts.
Tickets are available now on joderosa .com.
Folks, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.