Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MDM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MDM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MDM and Game Sense remind you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bedmgm .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non withdrawalable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gamling problem called 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Welcome to We'll See You In Howl.
It's a podcast.
It's a podcast about movies.
It's a podcast you listen to to get information about movies.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Pet Walsh and I'm hearing what?
The ice cream man again?
Something loud, something, something out of my ears.
It's, you know, what can you do?
The cons jumping off the couch.
You know, today we're doing a special 4 -20 episode since this will drop on 5 -6 or something.
4 -26 or something.
But last night, Joe and I went to the Wiltern Theater and we saw Friday, F. Gary Gray's Friday, starring Chris Tucker and Ice Cube.
And we said, you know what?
It doesn't always have to be gloom and doom and blood and guts.
Let's talk about a comedy for the kids Friday.
Right.
So that's what we're going to do.
And, you know, there's a bit of a power edge to the movie.
There's the threat that they're going to be murdered by big worm.
That's true, throughout the film.
So that's also the horror of watching young men corrupt their minds with the devil's lettuce.
Marijuana.
We go down to this thing.
It's the 4 -20, what the hell was it called?
The 4 -20 Fest?
4 -20 Fest, but it was just a movie at the Wiltern.
They did nothing special.
There was no way to make pen.
I got no vape pen.
Yeah, there was no fest.
Nothing, just a movie.
Maybe something happened after the movie.
We left.
We did, but there was nothing happened after the movie.
Yeah, maybe there was.
I don't fucking know.
Maybe that's when all the vendors and stuff came out.
Who knows?
Maybe, you know, you read today, like Cypress Hill did a free show after the movie or something.
I'd hurt.
You know, the only thing they might have done is that it listed all these vendors and free samples and stuff.
They might have said, let's do it after so people take the weed and go home as opposed to take the weed for the movie.
Then we got a bunch of stoners in our hands, but it's 4 -20 Fest.
You got to assume they know people are going to be high, and it's fucking legal.
Well, people were smoking, not in the room, but yeah, smoking the garage around the, you know,
on those mean streets, yeah, around the palladium or the Wiltern, I mean.
I like the Wiltern, it's a great venue.
We tried to visit one of our favorite bars, Frankenhank, for pre -game.
They were locked up until 6 p .m. they don't open till.
So then we went to a place called, what was it called, beer busts, busty beers or something?
We went to, I mean, it was a hotel little side bar.
Well, that's where we ended up.
Remember we first, beer belly, beer belly, they didn't have liquor.
Right. Then we went to another place, wide open, tired things wide open, we walk in,
the guy goes, yeah, we're not open.
Right.
So then we ended up in the holiday in, I got the impression that guys didn't want to serve us.
I got the impression too that it was racial, yeah, it was a racial thing.
But we did wind up at the worst bar in Los Angeles.
I had actually drank there before.
It doesn't even feel like a bar.
They're loudly watching a game.
You're sitting kind of what feels like at somebody's house.
Yeah, that you're not really welcome at, you're not welcome now.
It feels like you've shown up at your buddy's place and it's clear his wife is not happy
about it.
And you're just kind of sitting at a countertop, quietly drinking, like afraid to speak.
Right.
And then she comes in once in a while and is like, how much later do you think it's going
to be?
Yeah.
Hey, Glenn, how much later do you think it's going to be?
It's total, I want you guys to have fun, but you know, we do have in the morning, yeah,
the call with the, the realtor, a little too real for you.
Jehovah's Witness, yeah, that's real.
No, it's, I've been in that position.
My wife does not put me in that position.
She lets me do whatever I want.
And that's what I want.
All right.
Maybe sometimes you want that position.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
Wink, wink.
I guess.
This is sex thing.
Oh.
Sex talk.
Folks, let's, if I may get on with the show and at the same time on with the, now you're just
somebody that I used to Joe.
Right?
Very good.
Gautier.
What happened to Gautier?
Who?
He's somebody that I used to know.
Who's Gautier?
He recorded that song, somebody that I used to know.
Dear God, by speaking of people, you, you don't know that song?
You just thought I was making up a melody.
I think, no, I think I know the song.
I didn't, the guy's name was just Gautier, G -O -T -Y -E, G -O -T -A.
Okay.
Speaking of singers with names I'm unfamiliar with, our musicians, some names I'm familiar with.
It's like another rapper, another tattooed face rapper that's like a massive trouble, like
murdered two people.
Text 69.
No, that guy got in trouble first and she's 69.
Yeah, now this other guy, his name's like smelly TK or something.
Okay.
And he's in trouble now.
What do you do?
He murdered two, his two, the way I read the story, I think it was, he murdered his two
best friends and then tried to make it look like it was a drive -by.
Why, he murdered.
I didn't read that far in, I'm reading it and I'm going, who is this part?
His name, I thought it was a location of something.
It always be your own bitches, you know?
Yeah.
And I'm like, why, what happened in this place, I've never heard, then I was the guy's name.
But that's big with rappers now, is a lot of facial tattoos.
Right.
And you don't see it as much in the comedy writing world.
No.
You don't.
Last I saw it was a, Bruce Valanche had gotten some tear drops put on and then, you know,
as you know him now, he covers it up with powder, he's embarrassed by it.
That's not actually, that's not powder.
That's not powder, that's actually sugar from donut he was eating.
Folks.
Whoa.
He's a big guy.
Bruce Valanche sits down to listen to his favorite podcast and he's got to hear that slam.
The only slam he hears is when he sits down.
Oh.
I was in an Italian restaurant, bottled a red, swoo, bottled away, saw Bruce Valanche.
I saw Bruce Valanche once at the LAX baggage claim.
I still have the photo.
He's big and fat and he's in a tight t -shirt.
It was exactly Bruce Valanche.
Oh, I thought you were going to say his bag was lost, he was yelling at somebody.
Nice.
And very friendly.
Okay.
Well, yeah, we had a time last night.
We stepped on over to the, the tailors, the steakhouse, the old school steakhouse.
I left not just my card, as I often do at a bar, but my wallet.
So I, getting ready to leave today, I got no wallet, call the lift driver.
He was like, no, man, he seemed very scared that I was calling him, but sure enough, it was
at the restaurant.
So I got my card out paid and then must have just set my wallet down on the bar and left.
You were in a state yesterday, I was in a bit of a state.
You started.
Well, the before I did the bottomless mimosas.
And then when you start your day with that, generally, you just go home and go to bed.
But I was like, no, I'm doing something.
Now, what time did you do the mimosas?
We did the mimosas at like a one, okay, at a one, yeah, until what, three, because you texted
me around three and said something like that.
And I quote, if I make quote, I'm going to get super fucked up and go see Friday at the
will turn.
Right.
For 4 .20 fast, do you want to go?
And I thought, he's in a, he's in rare form today, he's, you know, not that I haven't seen
you get fucked up before, but I have never seen you phrase it like that.
Like it was such a, sure, a mission.
And then, you know, and I said, yeah, I was going to stay in, I was napping on the couch
at the time.
Mm -hmm.
I thought, well, what am I going to do?
Just lay here alone.
Let's go cover 4 .20 fast for the podcast.
And, uh, not much of a fuss, but we did have lobster tail.
Yeah, tailors, we got some London broil joke came into some money apparently and some lobster
tail money.
I didn't have to spend quite frankly, but I'm tired, I don't give a shit.
You fake it till you make it.
Yes.
Uh, some reason I was just ordering all day, whatever Joe ordered, which was so stupid, he was
trying to catch up to me, but I'm like matching him, drinking shots because I hate shots.
I don't want them.
I hate them.
And I just drinking them, stupid.
I appreciate that you're doing this right now because there was a moment today on the texting
where you kind of tried to blame me a little bit.
Oh no, I wasn't blaming you.
I'm just saying that last time, wherever we went to the other bar, you know, it was tequila
shots in a beer right, why does we sit down?
I'm just saying, take, take me off your order list.
I prefer a mixed drink, a vodka soda.
I keep telling you that's over tequila won't do you bad.
I woke up today fine.
I was fine.
I just, I don't want to do shots.
That's fine.
I had beer and silver tequila.
I woke up.
I was solid to that.
Okay.
Uh, didn't leave my wallet right anywhere, right?
But now how much?
I leave my card at places.
Stone's over.
I do it all the time.
Huh.
That's that's upsetting.
I mean, about your golden years, you get the card, you sign, you hand it back, there's
like one too many steps, you know what I mean?
Then they like, without even getting your attention, we'll just kind of set it back
on the table.
And I'm like, all right, well, I'm paid.
I'm done.
Let's hit the highway.
I will agree with you.
I'll sit in the, in the holster.
Yeah, they will just kind of set it down without saying anything.
Right.
They want you to leave it.
But it was a good, it was a good meal.
It was a good time.
We saw a good movie that we've obviously seen before.
Right.
And I feel like today we could probably branch out and talk about some weed movies in general.
Sure.
With Friday being our centerpiece, I have absolutely nothing for the movie quarter.
Oh, geez.
Because we're recording very close when we last recorded.
And I haven't watched anything new.
Not that close.
I would probably a week, usual, standard.
No, it wasn't a week.
We record on like Friday and it's Monday.
All right.
We record on Thursday.
And gotta be right.
I will take us over to Pat's movie corner and what I'd like to do, and you can believe
this or not, I was telling Joe, I sat down on Friday.
And I watched three John Singleton films in a row.
I watched higher learning, which I had seen when I was younger.
I watched poetic justice, which I had never seen.
And I watched baby boy, which I saw at the theater.
And then the next day, John Singleton is trending because he suffered a massive stroke at the
age of 51.
Oh, no.
Is he okay?
My hope is that John Singleton is okay and as a little tribute, let's shine a light on him
in the movie corner.
Okay.
This was such a wild coincidence.
Like generally somebody dies or gets sick or like, oh, I gotta check out what they do.
But this, I felt responsible for the man's illness.
Anyway, did you watch the three movies in a mirror?
I did, and I was saying Strokey Mary at the time while I was watching them, which I don't
even know why I was saying them.
That's a famous Tina Turner too, isn't it?
It's Strokey.
Strokey.
No, but in all seriousness, I'm tired to get back to that after singing.
Strokey Mary.
But John Singleton, I watched these movies and was like, man, this guy was the fucking
shit.
And then he did too fast, too furious, and like four brothers, which kind of sucked.
And, you know, I want the man to get back to his roots a little bit.
A lot of times, you get the money and then you kind of keep going that way.
I like to see him make those personal films unless you just can't get him made, I don't know.
But obviously he started with Boys in the Hood when he was a very young man.
Got nominated for Best Direct Tour.
Boys in the Hood is an incredible movie, no sense talking about it here.
Hopefully you've seen it.
His follow -up was poetic justice, Tupac Shakur and Janet Jackson.
It ain't great.
It's, I think lately, I started hearing a lot more about it.
I think it's Kendrick Lamar just gave him a little shout out that song poetic just, you know
what it is.
That's just how I feel.
Poetic Justice, the movie is a pretty standard road trip romantic comedy drama.
These two really fucking hate each other.
I mean, 20 minutes into this thing.
It's not like when Harry met Sally.
Two pox grouers was like, God on my face, you fucking bitch.
I'm like trying to throw her off a bus and I'm like yikes.
The other couple there with is Regina King and her boyfriend.
He slaps her across the face at one point.
So it's kind of like out of these weird tonal shifts.
But clearly he was trying to do something other than a Hood movie.
Friday, what makes it so special, it was, you know, it treated the hood as, wait, Boys in
the Hood do you mean?
I'm talking about Friday.
Oh, you're a place that can be fun.
But for a long time, these Hood movies were just all about.
Oh, I see.
You know, killing Friday was the first to shine more of a fun light on it.
But ice cube actually offered the lead role in poetic justice.
He said his fans would never buy him in a romantic vehicle.
He's too hardcore for that.
He turned it down.
But then he plays so goofy and stoned and lovable and like dopey in Friday, just a few years
later.
But maybe he wished he had done poetic justice.
Who knows?
Well, he trained, I mean, he might have just also not liked the script.
Of course.
He said that he transitioned, you know, he he transformed, I should say, very quickly in
the business.
Yes.
Not that long after Boys in the Hood, he also did, are we there yet?
Which I never thought I would see.
That was 15 years later though.
I was 10 to 10 maybe 10, let's say that's a pretty, you know, 10 years of big swing.
But anyway, I never saw poetic justice.
I remember seeing an interview with John Singleton when it came out and he said the way he got
the idea to do the movie was he woke up one day to his radio alarm clock.
And I forget what was playing, but he was like the idea popped into my head.
That's going to be my next movie.
I'm going to do a movie about a poet and her name is going to be justice and it's
going to be called poetic justice.
And I remember, it's a strange way to get a topic, get a idea for a movie.
Well, yeah, and I kind of remember thinking like, that sounds like, you know, you're working
backwards there, but, but, so I never I just never had any interest in the film.
It's the story doesn't interest me at all.
I jumped back in at higher learning, which I love.
But it sounds like I didn't miss much with poetic justice.
Although I would have liked to have seen Tupac.
Yeah, and he's good in it.
And Janet Jackson is very charming and good in it.
It just kind of doesn't really take off.
And the poetry stuff, you know, this poetry is written by my angel, my angel is in it for
a little bit.
I mean, none of that connects with me at all personally, but Regina King and Joe Tori are the
other couple.
But I'll tell you, it passes the time.
It's a nice movie.
It's got a couple funny moments.
And as with all these early John Singleton movies, it's got a great sense of time, place, character.
He makes even boys in the hood, the only thing that really dates that movie is their like
outrageous magic eight ball jackets that they're wearing and the four color shirts and everything.
All right, poetic justice feels very timely and current.
It was great.
Now higher learning.
I know a lot of people who love this movie, a lot of my friends loved it back in the day.
And I loved it.
And I thought, this is going to be one that's embarrassing now.
One that just doesn't hold up.
One that tries to oversimplify race relations and so forth.
That would be my concern.
It does to an extent.
And that was the criticism of it at the time that it just tries to, it's going on, my washing machine.
Oh, okay.
You looked so startled by your own washing.
That sounded like a real rush of water.
It did.
For a moment, I was terrified that water was shooting everywhere.
Fair.
Yeah, people thought it was a big mess and tried to take on too much and blah, blah, blah.
It does, but I mean, it's so well done.
And they don't get enough time really to go, you'd like to see a three hour cut almost.
But like the Michael rap report coming to school, it's like takes this weirdly sympathetic
eye to a guy becoming neo -Nazi skinhead.
And they follow his whole story as he's ostracized.
He feels left out of different friend groups.
And finally, he finds his people.
And that's like a weirdly loving take and like how people get caught up in that.
Generally, you just see the monster and not what brought him there.
But rap reports great in it.
Ice cube is great in it.
He also in a weird way, like he gets a lot of sociology out through the Lawrence Fishburn
character who's great as the professor, but like ice cube is pretty militant.
And he's always walking in and like cranks his music when he comes home and rap reports
like, Hey, what would you do if I came in and was blasting my music and he's like, it wouldn't
happen.
I'd kick your fucking ass.
And I guarantee these were like laugh lines and cheer lines and stuff, but it's just pants
a very balanced portrayal.
It's like, yeah, what they're doing is annoying.
They're blasting their music to this guy when he's trying to study.
And he never, Singleton never does what even Spike Lee is quote guilty of at times, seeming
a little one -sided in his portrayals of things.
It just felt very balanced and very cool to me, especially for how young the guy was at this
time.
Singleton, you know, if he's 51 now, I think he directed Boys in the Hoan, he was like 21
years old or something.
So higher learning, I just think is awesome.
It swings for too much.
There's like a lesbian love story in it that, you know, yeah, it tries to hit like every
damn or great.
Every damn good.
Yeah.
Our old friend, Jay Ferguson, date rapes, Christie Swanson, which I did not need to see because
he is such a sweet, sweet man.
And I never knew that was Ferguson.
It's Ferguson.
He's like in a real like douche.
He plays a evil frat guy very well, but anyway, I highly recommend higher learning if you've
never seen it.
But it's kind of in its way, it's like the movie Crash, but at college, but directed by
a black guy who's got a lot more to say than I think the crash did.
I loved it.
And baby boy, so between those, he did Rosewood, which is a great historical drama, Shaft, which
is, I thought it was a very fun update of Shaft with Sam Jackson.
Then baby boy, and how was he not involved at all in the new Shaft?
I don't know.
Sequel to his Shaft, and it's like he's not anywhere far or credit or something.
I don't think he does.
But baby boy is the one, I think most people have not seen another role that was going to be
given to Tupac Shakur, but went to Snoop, no, no, no, no, Tyree Skibson, Tyree has a giant
poster of Tupac in his room as kind of an homage, but Tupac died obviously and couldn't
do it.
Funding fell out.
And then years later, he came to do baby boy, baby boy is awesome, Snoop Dogg is great in
it.
Taraji P. Henson in her first role is great in it.
The movie is stolen and should have been nominated by Ving Rames, who is fucking awesome as Tyree
Skibson, the baby boy in questions, new sort of father figure, he's fucking his mom.
It's got to seem where he comes out in the morning, he's been listening to his mom and this guy
fuck all night, he walks out, Ving Rames stark naked cooking eggs at the stove and he's like,
can I make you some eggs?
Like turns around, doesn't cover his ass or anything.
There's a scene where Ving Rames is carrying the woman around the bedroom, fucking her doing
leg thrusts as he fucks her that is insanely funny.
And the movie, I loved it whenever I saw it like in college, but seeing it again, it's a
real kind of lost gem.
Singleton makes these quote hood movies in a way nobody else did.
He made them very special, very personal, very visually, very cool.
I also watched Menace to Society, which is another great one by the Hughes Brothers.
But for some reason, watching a lot of these movies, they're great time capsules of LA as part of it.
But I had been watching a bunch of them, which brings us to Friday, which is sort of ice cube saying,
why are all these movies so heavy, I used to have fun in the hood, let's talk about that.
Right, a couple of screaming ends before we hop over.
Yes.
Do we talk about Guardians 3, rehiring James Good?
We didn't, but yeah, that happened.
I mean, that's not even new news at this point, but look, I'm very happy for the guy.
I'm glad he went back and I'm also glad he told Disney they're going to have to now wait until he's
done with his suicide squad adaptation. So that's interesting news.
I mean, Disney, the Oscars, all these people, they just take these big swings.
And they're like, yeah, we're not going to do that. We didn't mean it.
Like the Oscars were like, let's have a most popular film category. Everyone's like, I hate that.
So they go, okay, we won't do it. No one has any convictions.
No, but you know, I thought it was bullshit that he was fired.
It was bullshit. But if you're going to do it, you have to stick with it.
I mean, like, it doesn't mean it wasn't it discussed at the time.
All they did was like, they probably called in the day after.
Let's sit time until this blows over, you know.
Like it's just, I mean, well, yeah, it's like it's like Mitt Romney coming out and being like,
I am second by Trump's lack of responsibility and behavior with this.
It's like, oh, shut up. It's like you're just, it's so gross, hell, you know, like, oh,
so because you want to run again. Yeah, now you're second. It's just funny.
These, these people, also to another screaming and quick one, stranger, stranger things,
three trailer dropped. I got to say people not looking good.
Okay, the trailer for season two was so outstanding that they had to play it twice at Comic Con.
This trailer is, I mean, they tell you very little, but it does not have the,
it does not have the swagger that the second season trailer had.
It does not have the intrigue that the second season trailer had.
They're aiming for a different part of the 80s that's clearly not quite as fun.
88. I don't know, but you can, you'll see when you watch it, what I mean by that.
88 was the least fun here of the 80s.
The kids are starting to look a little too old at this point.
And also too, it's two cool kids now, you know, it's cool kids stuff now.
Like, they're putting this Finn Wolfguard kid into, I forget what he just got put into,
but he's quickly becoming somebody that I don't want to see in things because I'm like,
it's distracting to me. It's the stranger things kid.
You know, but, you know, doesn't mean he shouldn't work.
Doesn't mean he's not talented, but it's just, you know, it's one of those things.
I don't know. Let's see. I was a little skeptical with season two.
I was wrong. I thought it was great, but season three, I mean, just even the structure of the
trailer is, it's, it's, it looks like they're reaching into their bag of tricks.
It starts with this situation that's supposed to look sinister or menacing and then there's
a switch and it's, it's something goofy, you know, it's kind of like, they're kind of just like
painting by numbers in the trailer. And it just doesn't look that great. But then again,
maybe they're just kind of showing you what they can show you without ruining it at this point,
but I don't know, I don't know. I wasn't, I wasn't, I was excited to see the trailer and then
I was kind of like, yeah, I didn't say it, but, you know, you can't judge a show by its trailer.
Well, you can, but I will say I sometimes get a good sort of sense with these things.
My spoty sense starts tingling, you know, I mean, let's, let's just, let's just put it out on
the table, Pat, I called it. I said, Twilight Zone's going to suck. Yeah, you said no way.
You do say most things are going to suck, so it just stands to reason to be right. Sometimes
my gut starts to go and I, you know, I just, I will say this, when I feel swept away by a trailer,
often I enjoy the film, when I feel man about a trailer often, I'm a little disappointed by the final
product, you know, and I feel a little mad about this trailer. Okay. I was annoyed going into
season two with the amount of publicity that was going into it. That was irritating, but I,
I thought the trailer was fucking phenomenal. Yeah. And it seemed like they got some shit to say.
At this point with this one, I'm going to kind of like, they can't not do a third season.
And now these kids are all off doing other things. And it's kind of like, okay, well,
scheduling, when can we make this work? Did we get a, you know, what, what could the story be for
a third season instead of we have an idea for the, you know, that's just to me what it feels like.
I could be wrong. All right. I mean, strange things have happened.
And scary stuff. I've been done one of these in a while. Folks.
If you're a fan of the Atari 2600, as I know many of you are, you need to go out and buy the
Retron 77. This is an amazing, and again, we never, none of this has paid promotion or endorsement.
This is just a product I love that I think you'll love. I hope it's about to get scary.
Let me often with video games. Why do you doubt that I'm not, why do you think I'm doing it wrong?
Go ahead. I'll get to it. I mean, a man's recommending a 40 -year -old video game system on scary stuff.
That's not what I'm recommending. All right. If you're a fan of the Atari 2600. So you're saying,
if you get this ancient product that no one will buy, you're going to recommend like a Frankenstein
monster game. Why don't you let me do what I'm doing? All right. Did I go to you? Oh, hey,
baby boy. I hope you're getting, I let you say the thing. Let me say your piece. It's a segment I
talk about movies I've seen. And I talk on scary stuff frequently about video games that have,
you know, a sci -fi vibe, right? Do I not? So let me get to it. If you're a fan of the Atari 2600,
which I know many of you are, it's probably my favorite system. It has been grown into becoming
my favorite system of all time. Why? Because there are so many fantastic sci -fi games on it,
and horror -themed games on it. And I like them a lot. There are a lot of fight the aliens games on
the Atari 2600. And I know many of you are saying, well, you know, I was a big fan of asteroids. I was
a big fan of Mega Mania. I was a big fan of haunted house. Joe, I'd love to play these games,
but I can't because my damn Atari 2600 won't hook up to my HD flat screen television. Well, folks,
I got great news for you. There is a product you can get. It is called the Retron 77. It is a
fantastic product. It is, it is a new product. You can get this thing for about 60 or 70 bucks. It is
HD capable. It hooks directly into your HD television via HDMI. And it is compatible with all
Atari 2600 cartridges. It also because it's a new system, it allows you to save your games,
which if you know how hard Atari 2600 games can be, that's a huge bonus.
So you can stop and pick up where you left off when you got to go eat dinner or go away for a week
or whatever it is. It has an updated version of the Atari 2600 controller. That is the best version
of the Atari 2600 controller I have ever experienced. They have loosened the stick,
so you can say goodbye to those blisters. And it's just a very, very fun, easy controller to use.
And it makes playing the games much better. It makes it a better experience. So if you miss those old
sci -fi and horror Atari games, you want to play them again. I'm telling you, go get yourself one of
these things. They even gave it some fake wood paneling and not around the sides, but on the top.
It's a nice looking console. You can get a second, comes with one controller, you can get a second
controller for 15 bucks. I can't recommend it enough. I think it'll bring a lot of joy to your life.
And that's it.
Didn't matter what I was going to say, you were going to react like that at the end of it.
No, no. It's not my thing. What's not your thing? It's not my thing when you discuss these game
machines. Really? I don't think it's what the people come to this podcast for. You think they're here
to hear about poetic justice? I do. They hear about movies. I do. A lot of people write to me about
scary stuff. They don't write to you about scary stuff. You don't get messages. Yes, I do.
All right. Thanks for recommending that game. I love it. It's fucking awesome. Okay. You know, all right.
I didn't know you were the boss of the podcast. I'm not the boss. I was ready to move on to the next
next thing. Well, I had a segment I had to do. Sure. Sure. We talk about music on here. I'm saying once
it's done, I was ready to move on. I didn't say a word. You're reading too much into my
heavy sigh. My weary, heavy sigh. Right. All right. Well, let's move on.
Friday. You know it. You love it. You've probably seen it. Watch it again. The movie is a classic.
It is a comedy classic. It is too often left off of great comedy classic lists.
I think that that's racist, frankly. It's so funny. Most of the lines of dialogue are funny.
Ice Cube is hilarious. Chris Tucker is hilarious. DJ Poo was going to play that role. New
line was like, no, you can't do it. Now he plays the guy with the big shiner gets punched in the face.
DJ Poo is the funniest person in the movie. Crazy. It's not crazy. He's hilarious in that movie.
You only see him for two seconds. Yeah. But he is tremendously, tremendously funny. He co -wrote the
movie. I know. Also. But he's got all the best gags in the movie. I mean, that's crazy. It's not
today. Crazy thing to say. It's not a crazy thing to say. DJ Poo is good in the movie as well.
His comedic instinct in the bit, the way he delivers, well, why don't you stick up for,
you know, you guys just stood there while Debo bullying me and they go, well, why don't you stick up for
us last week when he beat me up and so and so's yard. His instinct when he looks to the side takes
a beat and then goes, oh, that was different. It's the funniest part in the entire movie and you
can't teach that kind of thing. You can't teach it. Tucker's hilarious in it. But Tucker, let's be
honest, gets by a lot on voice. Tucker has been blessed with an absurd voice. Yeah. So it's not the
same thing, you know, because he could just go, you know, I mean, it's funny. Ice cube, those lines
are not. If any other character do those lines, they wouldn't be funny. You know,
okay. Yeah. All right. I like the crack head. I don't know who that, I don't know what that actress
name is. Everybody in the movie is funny. Who got zero credit for that flick? So I'm getting his back
on this one. Well, he got zero. In fact, he had a huge falling out with ice cube afterwards,
which they've made a man's over. But, you know, he was not, he was cut out of the sequels. He got none of
the press or publicity. Well, it's interesting. Who went on to do the wash, which is a very bad movie.
Right. And then all the Friday sequels to my recollection, at least, are massive steps down and
not good. It's cube did all those without poo, poo did his stuff without cube. You got to kind of
look at it and say, maybe these two needed to ride together. Well, yeah, the players clubs and okay,
movie that cube did solo. But yeah, the stuff they did separately was never great. He just
directed players club, right? He didn't write it. That I'm not sure about. He may have read. And then
he wrote some movie called janky promoters that the Weinstein's just put out. And he wasn't, it wasn't
edited. It wasn't ready to put out. They edited it without him and just released it. Who did Harvey
Weinstein? No, no, no, who you said he did a moot, which one ice cube cube cube did? Yeah, janky
promoters, which I've never seen. But that was a big controversy. And player club was written
and directed by cube himself. I'm a big fan of DJ poo. He, for those unfamiliar with hip -hop,
he was King T's DJ. And King T is one of the, you know, one of the gods of West Coast gangster rep.
I'm a huge King T fan. So I think poo is a really cool guy. I'm impressed that he's able to write
comedy and act comedy this well. And it's a shame that it didn't go a little bit further for him
because I think he really has a talent for it. Maybe if they get this last Friday picture off the
ground that cube and Chris Tucker now is also teasing would Tucker do it because now he's no longer
a born again Christian. He didn't do the sequels because he became born again and didn't want it cuss.
Tucker is saying Jehovah's Witness, one of the other. Tucker is saying that by the way,
did you know there was a Friday animated series? I did. I never saw it. But I never saw that either.
Tucker is saying, you know, he goes back and forth. One interview he says he's going to do it. One
interview he says he's not going to do it. You know what I mean? So who the fuck knows? Yeah.
You know, who knows? But you know, there has been talk that ice cube is going to do this final Friday
and it's going to be called last Friday. And he's going to bring everybody back. I think it's a
great idea. I love to see it. I actually love the third Friday movie, which introduced me to
none other than Kat Williams. I was the first thing I ever saw Kat Williams in. Right. And I was like,
this guy is fucking hilarious. Also Terry Cruz was very funny in it. And Mike Epps is just to me
just a fucking genius. Like Epps is great. But you know, it is kind of weird when Smokey's not there.
You know, you want to, you know, I'm not trying to say, I wasn't trying to say Chris Tucker's not
funny earlier. He's hilarious. But, uh, but, uh, you know, he's no, he's no, he's no, it's crazy.
Just just wrong. You're, you're, you started laughing even trying to say it again.
I laugh it out. Disgusted you yet. I love, uh, you know, when Chris Tucker's like, I didn't put
the joint in your mouth. And he goes, well, you might as well have come on, Chris, blah, blah,
blah. And then Tucker's like, why are you bringing up old shit? It's like something happened like an hour
earlier. He gets him high. Well, that was like our shots thing. Yes. You were like, cube might as well
have come on. Do it, do it. Do it. Why are you bringing up old shit? hilarious. John Witherspoon should
have not just been nominated for best point of actor, but one he is, he is the funniest part of the
movie. John Witherspoon by about a thousand percent. Now listen. Witherspoon is great. He did not
deserve a best supporting actor. I think he should have won. And when he gives his speech to cube at
the end, that would have been his speech. When he comes in and he's like, this is what makes you a man,
holds up his fists. Sometimes you win, sometimes you lose, but you live to fight another day. So,
you don't think the scene where he's spraying, uh, air fresheners, he's taking a shit, should have
been the clip they showed at the Oscars. No, it wouldn't have been the clip. But I'm saying he lands
those big, huge, broad comedy moments. And then when he comes in to like lay down the dad less
and it's very, he's very believable. He's very effective. He's very good. I got goose pumps watching
it. Um, I thought it was a great performance. Better than I even remembered. I always remember him being
the funniest part of that movie. Bernie Max hilarious in the movie. You just got a lot of great people.
The, uh, Neil Long is gorgeous and very, very funny. Um, there is a pretty ugly, uh, fat shaming scene
in it that I would say didn't feel great then. And now it just feels real clunky when she tells him
her friends coming over. And the friend says she looks like Janet Jackson, bitch, because out of the
car, look, I'm more like Freddie Jackson. Um, but the amount of time they spent like Chris Tucker right
to his fit, right to her face. Like he just keeps making like disgusted. Something always had to do
in those movies. Like if a guy wound up kissing a woman who was fat or something, they'd always,
instead of just making it mean and gross, they have them like mime puking. Like Christopher,
he's making these faces like, uh, uh, uh, like you're just talking to a woman in the street at this
point. I'm fucking her. And even if you were like, what, what is this? Why do we have to do this?
I felt bad for the actress on the day. I never found the scene funny. It's the one kind of spot in
Friday. I'm like, come on. Doesn't bother me. One bit in a, in a movie where in a movie where in
another type of movie, it might have been out of place. Friday is a very blunt, very candid,
very raw humor movie. Everything is on the table. And plenty of other stuff has made fun of, uh, you
know, it's like, you know, in a movie where they're dropping multiple slurs throughout the film,
sure, uh, where they're talking very candidly about male to female relations where they're making
fun of people for being broke where they're making fun of people for being addicted to crack,
where they're making fun of the fact that Asian people run all the quote black owned stores in,
in the ghetto, uh, when they're making fun of drug dealing and they're being mean to children.
It's like, uh, uh, fat joke fits right in there with, it's to me, you know, it'd be a little,
it's, it's out of, it went on too long. Like, it's just like, he doesn't need to continuously
mime. Like, he's going to be sick talking to a woman. I didn't get it. I didn't get it. But, of course,
the Janet Jackson, Freddie Jackson thing is very funny when he talks to me along about it. It's very
funny. I just don't like it when the woman is there. Like, and not given any sort of pushback of
around. I mean, in this one, she's like, just like dying to get laid, I guess it's her whole bit,
but whatever. It's something that, you know, of course, would never be in a movie now.
And sometimes I'm like, yeah, well, I missed those kind of jokes. This was not one of those cases.
It felt, felt ugly to me. Didn't bother me. Well, yeah, sick man, Joe.
You know, it's the lady in the comedy club laughs at everything. And then you go, you go, and then how
about these democrat, you know, whatever, how do these Republicans, you, I'm offended now.
Say, well, I made fun of everything else. You want to offend it offended. I mean, I shouldn't say
anything to qualify, but gender offended. I rarely, if ever, get offended. I'm saying I'm watching
this and I'm just like, why? It was keeping her there. Sometimes there's just ways of handling these
things where now I think about the actress. I used to have a boss who I'd be like, do you have to
write in the script like Jesse comma a fat bitch with no hope of ever getting laid? And he'd be like,
she knows what she is. That's what he would say. Well, that's evil. Yeah, he was an evil man, but
now I hear you always think about the actress like, oh, I'm going in for the giant woman that
everyone laughs at for five minutes, simply because I'm large. It's rough. It's all so tough.
That said, when they're all making fat jokes that get John Panette in the sign -fled finale,
funny. It's not about a being a woman that, that to me, that's, well, that's sexist. I know.
I agree. That to me, I was going to use sci -fi as an example where I say it doesn't work. Uh -huh.
It's making fun of that fact. Yeah, it's so needlessly. That show was bad. They got to go to jail.
It's got to be that extreme spoiler alert for the finale. I mean, it's such a stupid,
ridiculous premise, but it's why the finale sucks. I loved it. I don't god. You loved it. No,
you didn't. It's not a favorite episode, but it's passable. No, I thought it was great. You
thought it was great? I did. I love when it's on because I never err at them. I was like, oh, great.
There's big laughs on him doing the stand -up at the prison hilarious. That's funny at the very end.
But that's where it didn't, because that was never, to me, that was never sign -feld. It was never like,
hey, we're going to mercilessly make fun of this person. It was always a person did a thing
true that was offbeat to them. Then they would dissect it to add nauseam. That was what sign -feld.
Sometimes that would become mean that the only time we get mean is when they would go to extreme
lengths to fulfill a goal of theirs. When he steered, give me the bread, you old bag. Crazy shit,
because he needed the bread. It was never we're going to sit here and just make fun of somebody.
That's why I was like, that's just like mean. This is how we're sending off these characters.
It's not a great last impression. Yeah, I totally get why people didn't like it, but I liked it just
fine. That was in line with a spotty last season of highs and lows. I mean, they could have ended it
with that backwards episode in the last season. That goes pretty well. Nobody would have been happy
on the ending either. You can't please people. Anyway, Friday, great movie. Yeah. It's a true classic.
It's an awesome movie. I think Ice Cube is not going to have credit for how likeable and funny.
He isn't it right out of the gate. It's just a great cast. His obnoxious girlfriend is hilarious.
The crack cat again is hilarious. Big worm. The hair is a bit much on a recent viewing,
but the character is absolutely hilarious. My favorite scene in the movie, my favorite line is the
DJ Poole line they said, but my favorite scene in the movie is when big worms got the snack truck
and the little fat kid is where he goes. He goes, what what you want, boy? And he goes, you got
chili free or he got everybody says and he goes, boy, what the fuck you want? You know,
chili free dose. And then he gives him a tube and he gives him the dollar and he doesn't give him the
free dose. And he gets the call and he's like, all right, we're close. The kids like, what are my
free dose? He's like, my money. And he goes, my money, close fat boy. Yeah. Slams the thing shut,
drives off it fast forward. Well, he's 10 times the kid's size, which makes that fat truck very
funny. But then, yeah, when they go to the Benny Hill speed up of him getting in the driver's seat,
don't know why that happened. I don't know why that happened. But the movie is great.
Really every movie I mentioned on this show earlier, all these kind of quote,
hood classics, menace society, I'm working my way through them and they've all been really strong
movies. I know there are some that don't stand the test of time. You don't talk about them,
but a lot of these movies were really good. And then in terms of weed movies, Joe, I mean,
is this your favorite? I think you got to say Lebowski. Lebowski's my favorite, but
Lebowski is the ultimate. This is a close second. Are you a Cheech and Chong fan?
I love Cheech and Chong is comics. Their movies never really did it for me, but I like up in
smoke. You know, up in smokes of classic. Got its moments, but much funnier as a child than an adult.
And I've never seen any of the sequels. I used to look at the boxes of like the Corsican brothers
and be like, this doesn't look like it's going to be good. Cheech and Chong is pirates.
Well, Corsican brothers is like on the way out. It's like the teetering out of Cheech and Chong.
Would you consider office space a weed movie? Not really. I think there's only one scene of,
you'd have to call nine to five a weed movie. That's a good point. I mean, they're pretty few and far
between. My friends, I think I told you wanted to do a, well, I shouldn't tell their idea on the
show because it might still happen. Yeah, you should. Yeah, kind of the ultimate weed movie, and I hope
it happens. But anyway, go watch Friday again. There's a great four pack. You can buy on Amazon,
you know, the four discs and one thing. It's an ice cube pack and it's the three Friday movies,
plus all about the Benjamin's. All about the Benjamin's is not a great movie, but Mike apps
is just astoundingly funny in it. I mean, I don't think I've seen it. It's worth watching
just for the Mike Epcines. I'll, I'll, I'll put it in and just flip through the Mike Epcines.
Mike Epc is a hilarious scene and soul man with Bernie Mack and Sam Jackson, which is a pretty funny
flick. But this funny is part, he's got this scene with Bernie Mack, like one scene and he's like,
so what are you going to do about the kids, Bernie Mack and he goes, man, fuck them kids.
The cover to Mike apps and he stares at him and he goes, man, you just say, fuck the kids. It's
like, I can't do it anywhere near as funny as it was, but he looks like hurt by it. Man, you just
going to say, fuck the kid. It is incredible. That, that line is surely on YouTube. It's classic.
I remember that exploding the theater when I saw that movie, but are you a rush hour man? One,
two, three. Yeah, I like rush hour one and two. I think three sucks. I like one and two and three
does suck. But yeah, Chris Tucker for me is a guy I never loved outside of, I guess those movies
and Friday, but like fifth element, he's too much for me. Yeah, I mean, the classic line in rush hour
is which one of y 'all kicked me? Yeah. Or is that rush hour two? That's the funniest thing in all
the rush hour movies. Yeah. All right, let's do our shout outs for this month. I'm going to put,
at Joe, there was a comment on Instagram. That's my only plug. I'm on sort of on Instagram and
Twitter at the Patrick Walsh. Can you, do you mind starting the not at all shout outs? I got to turn
the oven on. Are you baking us something a brief? I'm not baking you a goddamn. I ain't baking
you a goddamn thing. That's something to be aligned in Friday. No, I got to heat up some turkey.
Okay. Anthony the Manito. I ate all the egg sandwiches, but you better not act like I ate all,
I guess the egg sandwiches is what we mean after that. Matthew Lynch. Superfan Giovanni. Taylor
Staten. Mike Flynn. Austin Arbigast. Nicholas McCauzland. Zachary Martinez. Sam McDonald. Kelsey
Cannevelle. John Cooley. Josh Gardner. Highton Davidson. Aaron Griffith. Slutty Trinkets. Mike
Gerbino. Alexis Taylor Alcridge. While I got you, we just love to say I think a lot of people came to
the Patreon this month for our Pat Cemetery episode. We're hearing it's a lot of people's all time
favorite. It's about an hour and a half of just pure Pat Cemetery talk. We don't do as much kind of
bantering around as normal. It's just talking about those those movies, shows, books, etc. And I think
it's a great one. Check it out. Carmen Chris Goodnight. Marco Van Wassenhoaf. Samantha Gordy. Jazz and
Daisy. Jeremiah Caleb Sorenson. Steven McGinty. Austin Scarborough. Adam Crowe. Edmund Agaboo.
Gustavo. Jack O 'Steal. Ray Tyler. Billy Goatpuk. That's charming. Thomas Koza. Brittany Schultz.
Brianna Wire. Chris Peters. Heather C. James Mitchell. Scott. Will Foley. Dan Garry. Tyler
LePoint. Alex Breerley. Matthew Robinson. Christopher Yarborough. Chutoy McCoy.
Jaronne Sanderson. Chuck Armstrong. Matthew McGuire. Anthony Adani. Reg. Last name sounds Asian.
Sorry. I don't know what that means. Alexa Lique Ardello. Haley Griggs. Lucas Cifuentes.
Coy Cook. Scott Birchette. Rebecca. Michael Borland. Michael Rios. Rebecca. Papa Spush.
Kelsey. Dan Hapanowitz. Abram Wright. Robert Moran. Scott George. Refarda. I love you. Janet C.
Comedians of wrestling. Oh, that's Dan Black. Hey, Dan Black. Danny and Jamie Lee. Thank you. Yeah.
Thank you. Boasting. You were listening to it the other day. We appreciate it. Listen to both of their
podcasts. Yes. Jed Patton. Isaac DeLorenzo. Steppenwolf Gangbang. Seaman Demon.
Weston Thomas Hividjid. Tom Van Curran. Ronan Farrity. Joe Miller. Pat Flanagan. Haley Twist. Glenn
Beesmans. AF Bradstone. Richard Howenstein. Chris Larson. Casey Sturgeon. Mike Grant. Ben
Wright. Jaden Brady. Patrick C. Brenner. Tom. Matt Pahoe. Patrick Driscoid. Pat. Melinda Ring.
Shelby L. Rocky Hawks. Sousseau. Mike Cook. Alexander Thomas. Laura Johnson. Matt Murphy. Joe Kennedy.
Bessie Talley Afero. Sophia Anderson. Samantha Deschano. Mike Wills. Michael Burke. Brooke Adams.
Braden Love. Jeff Henry. Nick Beck Beck. Katrina Ellis. Gozen. Andrew Tellichen.
Preston Anderson. Bryce Buckmaster. Martin Murray. Marcus Potish. Scott Riggs. Max Unwraff.
Nicholas Uey. John Devers. Sinji. Nicholas Edward Fallon. Albeck. Evan Barrett. Christopher Klinger.
Bugman. Thomas Braille. Christianson. Marcus McGay. Peeve Jared Pakwin. Christopher Mutual.
Daniel Pashaal. Brandon Coolhandsome. Funny. Nicole Quinn. Will Nolton. Jonathan Sprouls. Brian Shactor.
Taylor. Lindy West. Kevin Swistowitz. Not medium rare. Tom Holt. Justin Tyler. Big gay Al. Baby
Alexander Monterubio. Matt Chairs. Martin. Dan Jarchow. Ryan P. Hall.
Hi Ryan. Christopher Reynolds. Patrick Baxter. Julie Bailey. Violet. You're turning Violet. Violet.
Sam Elliott. Brett Urway. Patrick Wathen. Truth Crab. Dave DeWitt. Cole Rathaker. Waffles.
Sam Mitchell's extra wide socks. Kelly Amaroso. Beth Gaston. Sharifa. David Denahee. Devlow. Joshua
Christianson. KP Flynn. Elva Enriquez. Jackson Lomire. Rain. Purple Peacock. Christopher Sabella.
Oh, no, no miss boner. Drew Tiberius. Paul. Steve Smith. Loop A. Peter Pacheo. Tone C. Zonjic. Matt
Robin. Kevin Ragutti. Joseph Christian Reynolds. Josh Malridge. Kurt Ziegler. Sean Floren. Danny
Rudd. Natalie Hartline. Leo Lopez. Emily Rooknought Rock. Scott Hugh. Dave Del Greco. Kurt Ziegler.
Chloe Paget. Dennis Ormston. Travis Hines. John Weasen. Gruber. Angela Porcaro. James O 'Brien. Matthew
Moon. J. Fisher. Sean Lyle. John Hollywood. Jake McAlvane. Meredith McWilliams. Tenning Chatham.
Jesse Janicki. Mike Greenwood. Brianna Alcirae. Matt. Supportive guy. Oops. I said that last one wrong.
Anthony Rodriguez. Chris Passmore. Casey Jones. Take it, Joe.
Sinji Robert Haynes. Natalie Hattley. Will.
Little Flem there in the throat. Rough start. Will Pittman. Kevin McNanny. Kevin Driscoll.
Jen Wessels. Joe Hoffman. Scott Sweeney. Jay Miller. Clayton Stamper. Amanda Lancaster. Michael
Bolas. Ethan Gammage. Derek Adams. Sean Hall. Adam Loundsbury. Vincent Franks. Joseph
Riggosa. Anna Demario. Bo. Aaron Roberts. Scott John. Ben Methe. Fucking Rich Tillman. Sarah
Catherine Paul. Fucking pig person. Merchie. Scott Sweeney. Carrie. Kara Kahnini. Kara Kahnini.
Chuck Andrews. Tom Laverick. Tucker Rouch. John Smith. Andrew. Brian Bolaureer. Will Helms.
Jennifer Anna. T. L. Mon Holland. Jake Bullock. Slaybodies. Not reindeer. 0foxtrot .com. Matt
Crawford. Richard Deming. Brian Callis. Tim Drain. Michael Madrigal. Go to Mr.
suit records in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Bretton Fraser. Sean Luke Fisziak.
Karen Kilgarif. Listen to Karen and George's podcast. My favorite murder. Nathan Baskett. Gary
Minor. Gary Myron. Isn't Carrie Minor an actor? Gary. Yeah. Somebody. Gary Myron.
Gary Myron. Okay. Dylan Larr. Phil Burrell. Edmund Dillon. The black magic ninja. Scott Pauline
Cyril. Daphne Kellogg. Tristan Avery. Steve Polly Kronopoulos. Julie Aguire. Charity Ferguson.
Hank from Dan Cakes. Nick Weather. Walter. Excuse me. Nick Walther. Alexander Alexander Stein.
Emily Marvel. John B. Wat. Visit Zambian's horror crafts on Etsy. Mori Benjamin. Nicholas Burns.
Alex Nelson. Jeremy Cool. A cocktail called a duro so would consist of what? It's a great question.
Alex Shipley. Sean Penock. Amanda Liebsen. Timothy Letso. Shane Nazarene. Hey,
Samantha Kiefer. We're married now. Crazy. David Bellinger. Hunter McDonald. Justin Bohagger.
Adam Benbenek. Mani Rios. Demani O 'Rubio. Brandon Gash. Brandon, how are you? Jake Farot. Rob
Blinds. Jacob Barrett. Jordan C. Maxwell Ashcroft. Barbara Allen. Chris Bowen. Mike Gibbons.
Donnie Joyce. Michael Dawson. Jennifer Smith. Connor Denahy. Andrew J. Gujardo. Annie Johanison.
Timmy K. Megley Brands. Scott Blickensturfer. Brett Lemmer. Anthony Gujardo. Jared Blair. Richie
Verdugo. Chris Hopper. Emily Florence. Hi, Emily. Thank you for all you do. For us and the fans.
Sean L. Abby Manuel. Jonathan Galott. Mani Tinkels. Hog wallop. Stephanie Power. Diego Campos.
Stefan Maso. Zoe Blazkovic. Aisley Kivinsland. Dan McLeod. Lorenz Bunganiers. Alejandro Salgado.
Tracy Reddington. Sean Thomas. Amanda Elzimuro. Jason Weibel. Mike Curry. Sam Mitchell. Aaron Milanowski.
Scott Nolan. Ben. Misty Zavar. Hey, sport. Coca -Cola. Daniel Duer. Erick Lamora. Kevin Marcenek.
Lawrence Anderson. Jared Smallridge. Will Pottoff. Natalie Craig. Kyle Kinslin. The man whose name we
cannot speak. Ani Babaduk. Scott Patton. Lindsay Julianne Crew. Gabrielle King. Sam Street. Kevin
Willing. Hum. Willing. Kevin Willingham. The block watch. As usual, completely overwhelmed and touched
by the amount of support you all are showing as fans. Just awesome. It's overwhelming each time, folks.
Just a thought we're talking about doing away with the shout outs aspect of Patreon.
Would love to hear your thoughts on that. I think there's probably a more
valuable way we could, you know, or something better to give you for that money or something alternate
to just reading everybody's names. It's sort of, you know, we've been doing it for a while now,
and I think maybe it's time for a change. Bonus episodes aren't going anywhere, but we'd love to
hear your thoughts on the shout outs. That's it. Thanks for listening, folks. See you next time. We'll see you in hell.