Welcome to We'll See You in Hell, it's a new year, and we're still here, folks.
2024. We're still fucking here, baby. What is this, year 12?
Yes, we've been doing it longer than we've known each other. Happy 2024. Yeah. There's no new
feeling in the air. Nope. But I think it's going to be a good one. No, it won't. I think the end
of the year is going to be bad shit because of the elections. That's going to be a wild time.
Yeah. But I think we got six months of good coming our way. That's my prediction.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I have to believe that, Joe. I have to.
Well, I mean, you're doing the thing we all do. We all have to do now where you go.
Yeah, if I just close my eyes, I'm not on a roller coaster.
No, you are still going to feel that. It's going to feel bad.
And then you get hit in the face with a goose like the Fabio back in the day. Remember that video?
Do you remember that? No, no, no.
It's huge news. Fabio was asked to like premiere a roller coaster back when he was a huge star,
by which I mean, he appeared in, I can't believe it's not butter commercials.
On the cover of romance novels and a couple of early Fox sitcom guest stars.
You know, yes, I think he's also in Exorcist three, correct?
He is, but he's not famous at that point. He's just he's just in the dream sequence and that gets
weirder retroactively because he got famous and then Fabio's in there. But in the original,
he's just a guy. He just looks like an angel or whatever. Yeah. Originally, he, you know,
he's the celebrity premiering the new roller coaster at like Busch Gardens or Six Flags,
one of those places. And he's on the ride in the front, a full size goose hits him in the face.
It, when it ends, his nose is like gushing blood. His face is covered in blood.
And the funniest part of it is they interview him like weeks later and he's so angry about it.
He's like, I cannot endorse this. You know, what if, what if it had happened to God forbid a child
it's like, no, it was a freak occurrence. Fabio he's like mad at Busch Gardens because a goose
made him look like a idiot. Do you think Fabio is a good man inside? Like, do you think he's
got a big heart? In other words, here's what I think. And this is the most I've ever thought
Fabio in my entire life. I think back in the day when everyone was telling him you're the hottest
man alive, I think he was repellent and awful to be around, but time has mellowed him out much like
a Kenny G. You know, I think some of these guys let the fame go to their heads and then eventually
in their old age, they're like, all right, that's enough. I can't keep being a prick.
Wait, was Kenny G was a monster at one point? I don't know about a monster. I just, I actually
really liked the HBO Max documentary about Kenny G. It was part of like a documentary series they
did on musicians. They did a DMX one and a few others. Kenny G one's probably the most interesting.
He's not an asshole, but he's despised by the jazz community, obviously, because he had a billion
times their success and a fraction of the talent. And as white as you can come, the whitest possible
version of white jazz. As with like Carrot Top, you know, those guys just become miserable. You
can't be anything but miserable when the entire world hates you and you're a punchline. But now
when I see Carrot Top interviewed, when I see Kenny G interviewed, they seem like great dudes. I think
sometimes it takes till your old age till you realize how to be a person. You know, I noticed
that in my dad when I was home. I was like, he's managed to cobble together some semblance
of a human being at age 65. And I commend him for it because he wasn't able to do that.
That's good. Multiple decades. We had a nice long conversation.
That's good. That's huge. Actually, it was, you know, this is, this is a little personal,
we're a personal show. I asked my dad, point blank. I was walking in there and I was going
to talk to him about my childhood and tell him how much it bothered me that he thinks he did one
tiny thing wrong when I was three and never messed up again. Sure. And not say, you know,
you fucked up and have a PowerPoint presentation for him or something. Sure. But just kind of say
like, Hey man, I didn't grow up like as flawlessly as you seem to think. I have a lot of issues
coming from being raised by you, et cetera. Instead, I took it a different way. I said,
I'm, they didn't want to ruin Christmas. You gotta, you gotta be careful with these
parents, as you know, Joe. Oh yeah. You can, you set them off and then you don't talk for 40 years
or something, especially in an Irish Catholic family or in your case, you know, Italian Catholic
family. Yes. I go, dad, I'm working on a show about how, how depression can affect a family.
It's about having a history of depression. It's about a big family in the Midwest. Didn't even
ask if it was about our family. Cause I don't think he thinks we have any problems. I think
he's in complete denial about it, but he's like, what's your question? And the show you're referring
to is the reboot of Herman's head that you're working on. Yes. Yes. Herman's ass. It's more of
an R rated. We were inside his ass and he's gay. So there's all sorts of action happening and that's
dark retelling of Herman's head. I'd watch it. Actually, uh, the Pixar movie inside out was kind
of a dark retelling of Herman said it was the exact same premise. Um, anyway, I said, I'm making
the show about, about depression and I'd like to ask you when you first became aware of your
depression and when you first became aware of grandpa's depression. And it's like his eyes lit
up. He was, it was like for the first time in 20 years, we had a nice four hour conversation
about life and not about, you know, movies or filler or whatever we, we talk about to kind of
fascinating aspect of it. He said he didn't realize he had a problem and get on antidepressants till
he was 50 and it made him so angry. He didn't say it made me angry at my family. He just said,
it made me so angry inside. He thinks he didn't share that with us. He kept his anger inside,
which is hilarious, but he said, as soon as I got it, I was so angry and sometimes I'm still angry
when I think about how much different my life could have and probably would have been.
Okay. If I had had an antidepressant when I was 25 years old or something,
he goes, I felt so much better so quickly that I got, I got angry. You know, I just really got angry
at all the time I had missed. And I was like, wow, made me understand my dad in a way I never had.
Then he goes, my grandpa, who was like this lovable, he loved puns, you know,
just a big bald, like hilarious old Irish guy. And that's all I knew him as till I was 10 when
he passed away. I just knew him as like a ball of fun, but I knew he struggled. So I asked my dad,
I go, you know, grandpa, I always heard I had these problems and I know I got electroshock
therapy. So like, how did you guys realize this? He's a hard drinking Irish guy, a construction
worker. What made him realize something was wrong? So he was building Thunder River, another Six Flags
ride that I've been on a million times and it's these giant rocks. And he was building it when
he was like 60 years old, bald, red faced out in the heat, you know, not in the best shape,
always like barrel chested, but kind of like, you know, shouldn't be out in this heat lifting
giant rocks. And he passed out in the heat. The next day, my grandma wakes up, he's sitting on
the edge of the bed staring into space and she's like, John, it's nine 15. You've never been late
to work a day in your life. What's going on? And he goes, well, I'm not going to work today.
Darlene, I've made a decision. I'm going to kill myself.
Jesus God. Completely matter of fact, as if he was saying he was getting a bagel or something
like that. My dad's telling me this. Now here's, here's the fucked up life of a writer is I was
thinking first and foremost, this is going to be an amazing scene in my show if it happens. Yeah.
But second, I was like, and I didn't bring it up to him because people come to things on their own
timelines, but I was like, why wouldn't you share that piece of information? As I've been struggling
with depression my whole life, it's like, so we all, we all just act like grandpa, like just kind
of had a heart attack one day and there was nothing wrong. But I'm like, that's a big family story
that you should be sharing. I feel like, so anyway, starting things off in a very heavy note,
but, um, did he kill himself? He did. And I asked that, well, he, you know, they found him in the
garage. So I asked my dad, he was going, going into bag groceries at work. And I said, um, hey,
I gotta ask, you know, they found him in the garage. So my question is,
did he kill himself? And I've asked mom this and she said, no, but I want to ask you. And he said,
no, no, no, no, no, not, not what happened. And I believe him because we were having an open,
honest conversation, but he did get the electroshock and he was like,
you know, basically age 60, he had stopped drinking and just like picked it back up again.
And this is like, it just made me think about how like, of course people were depressed in the old
West, you know, or people were depressed in various times of life with nothing to do. Like
you couldn't even go to therapy back then. Well, much like in the film, uh, we are discussing today
the killers of the flower moon. Yes. There's that whole thing and we'll get to the movie
obviously, but there's that whole thing with the, with the one guy where they keep going,
he's a melancholy. Yeah. Melancholy. He might, he might hurt himself. You know, like you're like,
God, that's just how they referred to it back then. Like they just put a tag on you and they were
like, what can you do? The guy, they're all drinking a half bottle of brown whiskey every night at the
saloon. I mean, these guys must've just been fucking miserable. Yeah. Yeah. So, uh, all right.
Well, good for you on the family. And speaking of drinking and doing the right thing and learning
lessons, you chose last night to go out and get shit housed. You told me before we started here.
Yes, I did. I do what I do every year, which is, uh, say I'm going to do a sober January.
Then I remember my birthday is on the 5th of January. Uh, tomorrow. Happy birthday.
Thank you. So I go, you know what? I'll kick things off on the 6th. And my first day off back
at work, um, is this Sunday, the 6th or the Saturday, the 6th. Um, so I'm starting then,
but, and I'm calling my shot here, my goal. And I, I hear the laughter in the headphones,
folks. It doesn't, doesn't bother me. None. Who's laughing. Nobody's laughing.
I'm not drinking in 2024. Look, that's great. I'll say what I always say to you.
Don't make such a lofty goal. Just say, but I'm doing not, I'm going to not drink in February.
Let's see how February goes and then go, Oh, now I'm not going to drink in March. Oh, now I'm not
going to drink an acre. It's the loftiness of the goal that, that makes the goal not happen.
That's why January 6th, the date of, you know, obviously one of the most important days of my
insurrection. You mean the premiere of the film Star Trek Insurrection?
No, I actually mean when all that, all those years of practice and planning came together
on the steps of Congress on that beautiful day, January 6th, um,
you're going to go for the whole year, despite AA saying, don't do it that way.
I'm going to do Jan and Feb is what I'm saying. I'm going to be down in Atlanta. I think it'll be
quite easy. And then we'll see where we go from there. I'll say that. But last night I had a hinge
date and we sit down, we talked for like a minute and she was like, do you just want to get like a
shot? Oh yeah, baby. No, no, I don't think any woman on a date has ever asked me, do I want to
get a shot? And I actually, I talked about you on the date, Joe, because I was like, I don't do them
anymore. And she's like, anymore? What happened? And I explained that you drove them out of me.
So, um, I go, I can't do them anymore. I won't do them. But she's like, well, I'm,
I'm just like weirdly nervous. I find you strangely intimidating. And I was like, oh,
sorry. She was like, I thought like comedy writer, like, I just kind of thought you'd be more bubbly.
I kind of laughed and I'm like, I think I'm a funny guy. I said, I'm definitely not bubbly,
you know? And, um, so we started drinking and we just had a lot of fun. And then, you know,
I haven't had one of these nights again, since you lived here, Joe, where you just, you know,
it's a bad idea, but keep going. Um, she goes, she brought up Vanderpump rules and I go, you know,
the Schwartz and Sandy's bar, two of the guys have a bar together, Joe on Vanderpump
is five minutes from here. And she goes, oh my God, can we go? Like, let's do it. I drive her
there. Place is closed. I'm like, huh? First date. I'm not asking. I'm not fucking anybody
on a first date anymore. I'm done. I'm done with that life. But I go, you know, what else is open?
Little place called Jumbo's clown room hadn't been there in ages. What a blast. This place is,
it's, it really is an LA must. It's a classic dive bar, fairly reasonably priced drinks,
but half the place is a stage and gorgeous non stripper type women dance. I don't mean like,
you know, people off the street or something. They're, they're, they're beautiful women,
but it's more of a suicide girls kind of vibe, Hollywood vibe. Um, and there's a jukebox right
next to the stage and they play the weirdest musical choices and do like interpretive dances
and acrobatics to them. They remain in like very revealing bikinis, but the place is a blast.
And if you got a fun, obviously open -minded date, it really is a blast.
Pat is, uh, Pat is describing one of the locations that made me leave Los Angeles,
which you hated Jumbo's that much. I despise it. I think it's everything wrong with Los Angeles.
I think it's, I think it's such a nice night there last night. I'm not saying you can't have a nice
time there. I've had friends that work there. I, we spent part of a friend's bachelor party there,
but, uh, but, uh, I just, I don't know. What are we talking about a school here? We're not going to
say out loud in case he wasn't supposed to be there. But, but I mean, that's a pretty tame
bachelor party. I know you're talking about it. But my point is, is, uh, no, I hate, I, I despise
the place. I felt like it was, it's just like, uh, it's just, it's just like every place in LA
where they're like, this is a dive. And it's like, no, it's not. They're cheap. They're cheap
drinks. No, they're not. They're strippers. Not really. Hey, jukebox is good. It's okay.
Look, I've never once walked into this place where they weren't playing Danzig's mother.
That says something, you know? Sure. Sure. I like, I like the vibe. I think I'm not, I have never
really been a strip club guy. It's not like I've never gone, but I do think, you know, an $8 Jack
and Dyett is a pretty great fucking well price when you're seeing half naked women as well.
You know, it's not, it's not somewhere I'm going every week, but I like it.
An $8 is a standard, uh, price. That's, I think that's what we charge at my bar. But, uh, but, um,
And what are the rules? Like some, I know in sub clubs in Vegas, you can't show
beef if there's alcohol. You know what, you know what my problem is with Jumbo's clown room?
It's where every hip LA douchebag went and pretended he wasn't horny. It was like,
it was like the way, it was like Maxim magazine. It was like a way to be like,
oh, I'm not one of those gross guys. I only look until the thong and it's like, oh, fuck you be a
man and go to a strip club and get a hustler magazine. It, that, that, that's what bothered
me about it. But I agree with you wholeheartedly is a great place to go on a date. It's a great,
it's a great like, let's not creep each other. Exactly. Well, it freaked, it freaked, you know,
definitely she started talking about like, what percentage gay do you think you are? She's like,
as the older I get, I think I'm more like 40%. And then she's like, can we sit up there? And like,
she seemed variant. It was a lot of fun. Well, that's when you go right down to cheetahs.
Oh yeah. We did like a classic, but you know, bar public make out, which like I haven't done in a
long time. It was, it was just fun and nice. I told her, I'm like, yeah, it was good evening.
Now I'm going to Atlanta for two months. It's like, my schedule is this like Bob Seeger vibe
where I'm making out with girls and titty bars and then like, I'm going to Atlanta for two months.
Maybe, maybe I'll hit you up when I get back. It's ridiculous. That's funny. Well, all right.
You had a good night and you're, you're, you're having a good send off for the birthday. And then,
and then you take a little time off. Sounds like a good plan.
For sure. Go to, I'm trying to go two weeks here until I would love to go dry January, but I got,
I mean, the world just won't let off. I was like, I'm going to go dry January. And then it's like,
no, I'm not. I go to Austin on the 16th and I'm there for three days before my shows at the
mothership. And then I leave from the mothership to go directly where? To Miami to get on to the
jokers. Uh, Eric, uh, uh, Eric Andre, Eric Andre Cruz. I'm going to die. Yeah. There might,
there might be a drink hoisted on the impractical jokers. Eric Andre Cruz is my guess.
Uh, we went, I went with, uh, Brian Quinn to the Eric Andre show, the live show at terminal five.
Yeah. And at one point during the show, it was chaos. It's Eric Andre. At one point during the
show, I turned to him and I go, we're going to be on a boat with these people. I was like,
what the hell is this going to even look like? I got to say those, those cruises do not sound
fun to me. Ms. Pat was just telling me she was on the Burke Chrysler cruise. And she was like,
if I had to see one more giant hairy white stomach, it was too much for, I mean, she's a
50 year old woman. I understand. She's a, she's a mother, a wife. She doesn't need to be out on a
cruise. Yeah. Let me, let me tell you why you'd love it. There's a casino. I'm in there's a buffet
and there's bars. It's you would have a great fucking time. I probably would. It's just,
it's the thought of being trapped on one of those cruises, like that try, you know,
triangle of sadness vibe and the diarrhea flying everywhere that that scares me. But it goes just,
I've only done one of them, but it goes just long enough. Like the fourth day you're on the way back.
Three days I could do. Yeah. You're like, all right, I'm, I'm ready to, to, to, to,
it's like going to Vegas. You're like, all right, four days. I'm, I'm pretty good. Let's, let's get
it. Yeah. I was, Pat, this is, I don't know if it's that interesting. It's certainly not as
interesting as the heart to heart with your, oh wait, well that's your Christmas recap. I wish I
had a Christmas story to tell you here. I, I, I, I hosted my parents and my cousin and my niece at
my new home and I cooked for everybody and it was nice. And that was kind of Christmas, you know,
I had a big blowout as I do every year with the guys that grew up with a fight, you mean, or
a blowout, like fun. Like we do a thing called the Eve Eve every 23rd, we bar crawled and give each
other presents. It's quite fun. So we didn't slang for head. Yes. Yeah. But that's kind of it. My
New Year's Eve was, I mean, it was a, it was a nonstop party, but I would call it almost disgraceful.
You mean the voucher us or what? Yes. Yeah. It was, it was a scene. One stop I made though,
and this is very interesting. I stopped by my buddy, Seth Herzog's karaoke party that he has
every New Year's Eve. Yeah. And I talked for quite some time with Keegan Michael Key who was there
and he wasn't shooting something. He wasn't. No, I talked to him and embarrassed myself because I
went, Hey man, I just performed at the venue you and Peele started at. And he was like, uh,
in LA. And I was like, no man in Detroit, where are you from? And he was like,
well, I'm from there, but he's not. I didn't meet him until and I was like,
I'm thinking of Tim Robinson. Sorry. Oh dear. Uh, but he was gracious about it. But
the highlight of that, uh, night was, and I, I want to get his, his full name here.
Hold on one second. Give me, I got to just look this up. I should have had this ready to go.
Uh, I, I am walking through the party and I'm talking, you know, I'm talking. Sipping on
Cardi. Yeah, exactly. And I meet this guy and he's like, Hey man, dude, I'm a fan of yours.
And I'm like, thanks. And I go, you look really familiar, man. And he's like, he's like, yeah,
man. And he goes, I'm an actor. I go, what are you in dude? I know you. And he's like,
I was on spin city and it's Michael Boatman, the guy from spin city.
Yeah. I hung out with him for like two hours at this party. We just really chopped it up. And
he was like, what, what standup comedy? That's nuts. You know? And I was like,
I was like, I think acting's nuts. Like, uh, and we, we just talked for a while. He was very cool.
And, uh, we swapped numbers. I might be friends with Michael Boatman now.
I love it. Uh, and then I blacked out. I went to my bar and blacked out completely
went to bed at 9 a .m. Don't remember anything. So there you go.
Okay. Yeah. But my, uh, my new years, I had people, I had ordered blood, so's barbecue,
where you and I have gone a few times and I order the party platter for some friends.
So I had our mutual friend, Lizzie, Cooperman, fantastic comic, um, my buddy, Kevin Porter,
and a couple other friends over very low key. And I told them, I want to start at five,
and I want you guys to leave before the DUIs start up. You know, I'm like, I'm not,
I'm not even going to midnight. And I didn't, I was asleep by midnight. Um, so they bring this
party platter. I set it out. It's like nothing. Yeah. The sides are, sides are like thimbles.
Yep. And there's no food for anyone. And I'm having a New Year's Eve party and it arrives
when I told them to 5 p .m. So now it's five, I'm getting the text, Hey, we should be there in 10
minutes or whatever. And I have like the lightest of snacks. I told everyone come starving. I'm
ordering pounds of meat. So I was furious and I had also taken an edible. So I made this into a
much bigger situation than it probably should have been. But I start panicking and I call them and I
well, you know, that would be this many pounds or whatever. Like, well, I guess send that over
because now I'm having a party and I feel really like I'm, I'm under equipped. My friends come in,
we eat, we barely put a dent in the, in the party platter. You know, it was two women who are not
going to be like chowing down on ribs or anything. We all had our fill, but we didn't even need
the second tray that comes in. Now I'm flying back to Atlanta Saturday morning, 8 a .m. And I,
my refrigerator has pounds and pounds of barbecue in it that I will not be able to eat. And I wasted
so much money. When I saw what they charged me, I can't even tell you what they charged me.
I almost blacked out. Barbecues is the biggest hustle in food. It is such a fucking hustle. I
never ordered it before. I didn't realize. So that's why I thought I was going to be, you know,
coming through a, Hey, I'm not going to have pizza. I'm getting something cool, special, whatever.
$500 later, I guess I am telling you how much I spent in the fucking bar.
Five hundred. Wow. That's, that's, I didn't know it was going to be that steep.
Well, that's with Postmates and all the other shit and probably closer to four or something.
But, and it was, I was putting on a new year's party and everything and I get that. And that's
reasonable for throwing a nice little party, but it's a dinner party. Um, it just made me realize
like I, Postmates hadn't been on my phone in six months and I immediately deleted it the second it
was over. I'm like, what a, what a awful racket this is. I, uh, these, these sides wouldn't be a
side if you were eating a lunchable, you know, like I just, it was infuriating that they put this as
a party pack. Yeah, that sucks. That's lame. Um, I, uh, I, I'm excited to get to the, uh,
to, to the movie corner because I, uh, I have watched a good deal of stuff, but I,
Christmas leftovers much like your barbecue leftovers. Yeah. Uh, that I, that I'm excited
to talk about. Okay. Great. Um, I have, I'm actually going to do Christmas on this one and
the next episode. Uh, but I will tell you, can I start? Please. I, I, I have to talk about this.
I watched, I, I went, I did three versions of the Grinch. So these are all Grinches.
I watched the Grinch musical. Uh, that's the one I'll start with the Jim Carrey one.
No, there was a made for NBC. Okay. Like one of these, you know, shot on stage, you know,
when they were doing all those musicals. Yes. There's a Grinch one, apparently I didn't even
know it existed. I don't know any of the actors that were in it by name. I was unfamiliar with
everybody. Um, but the main character of the musical, it's a, it's terrible. It's, it's there's,
it has nothing behind it. It is the worst of any Grinch adaptation by far. Yeah. I'm including the,
the Benedict Cumberbatch one, the Carrey one. It's, it's, it is, these things get thinner and
go with the Grinch because they keep trying to make it even more human and accessible. Uh,
right. And further ruining the story because they're so terrified they're,
they're going to get in trouble for adapting a Dr. Seuss thing who was,
they think that we want the motivations of the Grinch. What made what, what one of them,
maybe the Jim Carrey one had a childhood flashback of the Grinch. That's the Jim
Carrey one. I'm watching this because you know, the Dr. Seuss controversy happened and I think
they just keep doing more and more to be like, they're almost quietly apologizing as they're
adapting Dr. Seuss now to be like - Who's portraying the Grinch in this musical?
Never heard of him. Uh, he was in a, he's, he's sort of famous. He was in a, he was in some TV show.
I don't know. Anyway. Okay. Even my mom gives me a better description of an actor than that.
He was, I, he was, there's so much stuff I don't care about anymore. Yeah. And then all the stuff
I don't care about is spawning actors. I don't care about. So great. I just looked up the Grinch
and learned that the boy who played a childhood Grinch died two years after the film wrapped.
He's this God, uh, Matthew Morrison from Glee was the Grinch. Yeah. So that was,
that's the point I'm making is like they make these shows where they'll be, you know, you'll
see somebody who's starring in a new movie. Yeah. You know, who is, who was this guy? Who was,
who was Charles Rudnovich or whatever. And they'll be like, well, Charles Rudnovich, he starred in,
in, uh, block parties, the Showtime smash. And you're like, what, what is that?
And then you look it up and it's like, it went for 11 seasons. I've never even heard of this.
I don't even care. Whatever. Anyway, this Grinch musical, it sucked. There's nothing to report.
It sucked. There's no, it just sucked. It's not worth watching, but the craziest thing I've ever
seen in my life. And we've talked about this on the show. We've talked about how bad shit it is
with, you know, we're not against diversity. Obviously we're human beings, pro diversity,
but it is nuts when they, when, when it'll be like a white son and the dad's Asian or something.
And they're like, they don't explain it. You're like, this doesn't make any sense.
So that, that was like one crazy year. I feel like that started and stopped pretty quickly.
This one did the craziest thing I've ever seen of it. The main character in this, the narrator
is a dog is the dog and it's a human playing the dog and the dog, it starts with,
I figured that Joe, I figured the dog wasn't actually narrating.
Well, I didn't mean that. I meant like, it's not like an animatronic or a puppet or something.
It's like a guy that it's clearly a person with dog ears on his head or whatever.
They make it a humanoid dog. So it's a white guy. Yeah.
And they do a flashback sequence where they show the dog when he's younger
and when he's younger, he's played by an Asian kid and you're like, what the hell is going on?
And there, there are people in Hollywood and I have heard this said and just bit my
tongue or whatever, but they'll call that like colorblind casting. And it's like, but
what are you talking about? What are you talking about?
Colorblind casting means like, okay, James Bond can be Idris Elba and he'd do a kick -ass job.
That's colorblind casting. It's like, no, making somebody Asian when they're a child and white,
when they're an adult, that's just stupid casting. It's confusing. You're like,
wait, is this a different dog now? Like, we don't know what the hell's going on.
You're on the Wikipedia page for the Grinch NBC musical in the dog facts section,
trying to find out what the hell's going on.
Yeah. Is this from the unabridged text that wasn't published? There was two dogs.
It's so crazy. And I know that there are people probably listening right now that are saying,
oh, so you believe in a Grinch and a talking dog, but it can't be. And it's like,
yes, I guess so. I don't know. I just think there's some sort of continuity where it just
comes distracting. It just gets confusing to me.
I'm not saying make them both white. I'm saying make them both Asian.
Exactly. Well, that's the point I'm getting at. God forbid. I have a joke about this in my act.
They won't make the dog Asian. They won't make the lead guy Asian. No, they can't do that.
We're not seeing Simu Liu as the Grinch.
Yeah. I mean, it's wild, the racism that they display as they're trying to prove they're not
racist. It's so insane. So anyway, it sucked. Don't watch it, the Grinch musical.
I won't watch it. That's a guarantee. I also have a couple of musicals to report on.
Wonka and The Color Purple. Just to start, they're both bad. They're both bad movies.
But Wonka is a musical about how sweet and delicious chocolate tastes. The Color Purple
is a musical about sexual abuse. I just don't understand. I think it must have worked better
on the Broadway stage where I did not see it. But of course, I have read The Color Purple. I
read it in school. I saw the movie, the Steven Spielberg movie, which admittedly I haven't seen
as an adult in this very drastically changed world in terms of representation. Obviously,
today Steven Spielberg would not direct that movie. But I remember thinking the movie was
kind of fantastic. Everyone I work with cites it as one of their favorite movies of all time.
It's a huge movie in the black community. It's a huge movie. Yeah. I always say
there's the black version and the white version of the icon movie.
Color Purple's black version in terms of endearment is the white one. Those are the two
that cross all racial boundaries. I told you about the argument I had with my friend,
Ray, when he was yelling at me that I'd never seen The Color Purple. And I go,
well, you're a black guy, dude. It's like me yelling at you that you never saw Terms of
Endearment. And he goes, Terms of Endearment is the shit. Yeah. It's crazy that you say that. And if
I had Inspector Gadget Arms, I would pull into frame that I just got delivered seconds before
we started recording the new 4K of Terms of Endearment. Just showed up. Crazy coincidence.
Anyway, that's just what I wanted to say is like, yeah, you can have musicals about serious
subjects, but man, it's jarring to me, you know? Yeah, there is something. There's a whimsy that
comes along with the musical, even in a dramatic musical, because of the performance aspect of it.
That's where I never quite got Les Miserables, where it was kind of like, it's people who are
depressed and in the midst of tragedy, but they're singing about it. It never just seemed
to make sense to me. No, and every version of Les Miserables, and I've seen several, bores the
shit out of me. I don't like it. I guess I don't really like musicals in general. I liked them when
I was a kid, but now they're tough sit for me. How bad is Wonka? So yeah, Wonka,
the best review I saw of it, I love reading people on Letterboxd that I like. There's all
kinds of great critics and some famous, some just average Joes, and I like writing little reviews
and stuff on there, but this guy was like, hey everybody, he gave it one star or something,
and he was like, just because this isn't as horrible as we all expected it to be, does not
mean it's not horrible. And I was like, yeah, exactly. That's how I felt about it. Both movies
were like a two star out of five. So we're talking like C minus at best. Wonka, what does it have
going for it? It has a pretty cool, obviously Wes Anderson inspired world. It's the same director
that did Paddington and Paddington 2, which nerds jizz about all the time. And Paddington movies are
like Wes Anderson for kids. Wonka is also that, but it's up against one of the greatest sets
in movie history, the original Chocolate Factory, not Johnny Depp's of course. So like Tim Burton
could not improve upon what was done in the seventies. So you're not going to be able to do
it either, Paddington guy. It just kind of winds up looking sort of neat, but at the end of the day,
it's not what we all know and love from our childhood. So it just kind of doesn't register.
What you saw in the seventies, and it's not entirely the fault of the modern day director.
It's primarily the fault of the studios that we're dealing with now and the money and the industry
itself. But what you saw in the seventies was an ability in a director to truly be a director and
to understand where the humanity and character lied, laid, whatever the term is, in a film,
in a story. And they knew how to bring it out. And they knew if they were good, what needed to
surround that in allowing the other participants in the film to bring that tone in through their
different department or whatever. And that's why you get a guy like Bob whatever his name is,
Bob Clark directs Black Christmas, Masterpiece, and directs a Christmas story, Masterpiece.
These movies are worlds apart. The guy directs arguably the quintessential slasher holiday movie
outside of Halloween. And then he also directs the quintessential Christmas movie.
And I don't think you have that anymore. I don't think you have somebody that understand
or is allowed or maybe isn't allowed to understand that because of the studio.
And then these actors, I mean, again, let's talk again about this. As they virtue signal, they
demean. So you're not going to cast a little person as the Oompa Loompas?
No.
Because you want to prove that you're beyond that. So instead you'll shrink you, Grant,
to a little person's size and have him play it and then take the job away from
you.
Dinklage was so upset about Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs and now they're like talks of not
even releasing the movie. They're doing these reshoots. It's like, so what's that going to be?
We're going to have seven grown actors miniaturized?
They change the dwarfs to like magical beings or something. That movie's in a lot of trouble.
Apparently the lead girl has said some crazy shit, not crazy, but not great stuff. But there's a lot
of people that spoke out. My friend Dylan, he's Horn Squoggle in the WWE. He's a wrestler,
pro wrestler. He played Leprechaun in Leprechaun Virgins. There's an interview clip with him on
YouTube where he talked about how he thought that that was bullshit that Peter Dinklage did that.
He's like, okay, yeah, if you're Peter Dinklage, you can say that.
There's a lot of us out here looking for work, man.
So I just don't quite get what this... God, it's just... And then to add insult to injury,
Hugh Grant comes out and he's like, and I love Hugh Grant, but he's in his interviews being like,
I absolutely despised getting into this stupid makeup. And everybody's like, oh, isn't that so
charming that Hugh Grant is so honest? And it's like, you know how many little people are like,
go fuck yourself, dude. Well, so he comes into the movie at like the hour 10 mark.
He's in the trailer. You'd think it was a two -hander with him in Chameleon or Chalamet,
whatever the fuck his name is. He comes in one 10 in, then he disappears again. Then he comes back
for a little bit. But I'm like, guys, he's the star power here. Hugh Grant comes in and he knows
how to land a fucking bad joke. And he's not on screen nearly enough. I know what you mean about
him appearing to be a genuinely angry, bad person in every interview. And John Stewart, the only
person that ever got banned from Daily Show was Hugh Grant. And whenever they asked Hugh Grant,
he was like, oh yeah, it was a proper Tulsa. I was an asshole, you know, like he'd never
apologize and doubles down on it. And it makes me like him. And of course I like him in movies,
especially when he plays an asshole, but it's weird that he's allowed to just keep being an
asshole. You know, like I thought we stopped that. I thought we were trying to create safe spaces
for people. I never know what's going on, but the movie, the only time it kind of like comes to life
are these scenes with Hugh Grant. That's a little bit of star power. The rest of the movie, you know,
I feel like it's something you'd put on above your kid's crib to keep it entertained and make
it fall asleep. You know, the songs are fucking awful. They're just fucking awful. There's not a
memorable chorus in the whole movie. Chameleon or Chalamet can't sing. And look, I was talking
at a Christmas party back in Missouri about him and several women and men in the party stood up
for him. And we're like, oh, you don't like him. You don't like it. No, I don't. I think he is
void of charisma. I don't get it. Another fucking, you know, it's like the Robert Pattinson
Batman. It's like, I'm sorry, guys. I don't want Fiona Apple taking up the screen. It's like this
moody, droney fucking like, you know, guys, Greta Gerwig did it best. She's the queen of the Mumble
Corps. She did it great. That's it. We're done. Let's move on. We need, we need people with,
it's not charming on anybody else. It was charming in that link letter window for 25 minutes.
And that's it. We're done. Like, come on. Like, don't get it. He's just without,
without charm and without star power to me. And I've never, I've never felt that more strongly
than with Wonka because it's the first time where I've seen him like the star, the movie is called
his character. And he, to me, he can't pull that off when it, when he's the hero of dune.
It's the same thing as Kyle McLaughlin. He's a prop amongst all the sand and dragons and all that
shit. You don't notice it as much, but this kid cannot, cannot carry a movie. I'd watch McLaughlin
over Timothy any day of the week in dune without question. I'd watch, I'd watch Kyle McLaughlin
over Chamolais and anything, any day of the week ever. But I just, I dread it. It's like when it's,
when we started with, and luckily we kind of flushed him quickly, but Ansel Elgort,
when he started up, I was like, am I going to have to watch 30 years of movies starring Ansel Elgort?
Well, I'll say this. He's in the movie we're doing next, the next episode in Oppenheimer.
And I will say positive things about it. Oh, wait, you see it. Wait, isn't Ansel Elgort,
wait a minute. I'm sorry. Isn't he Han Solo? No, it's Adam Driver. No, no, no. Adam Driver. Wait,
Han Solo. You know, you mean Aiden Heidelreich or whatever. Is that what you're talking about?
Who the hell's Ansel Elgort? I mean, what the hell is going on with these names?
The guy, the guy who played Solo in Solo was, is Aiden Heiselreich or something who's in fair play
and a good actor. He should have changed his last name. In the Coen Brothers movie. Yeah, exactly.
Okay. Who's Ansel Elgort? Ansel Elgort was Baby Driver and he was in West Side Story,
Spielberg's West Side Story. But he also looks like a Nazi. I gotta look it up. All right. I have,
you just did two. I'll do these two and I'll be done because it's not worth breaking them up.
I re -watched the Jim Carrey Grinch in light of the Grinch musical. And also because Eddie Murphy
said in a recent interview on, I guess it was on Kimmel, that one of his favorite Christmas movies
is the Jim Carrey Grinch. And I was like, well, maybe I didn't give this thing enough of a shot.
Who said that on Kimmel? Eddie Murphy. Oh my God. Okay.
It's not a good movie. It's not a terrible movie. I mean, by compared to the fucking musical thing
I watched, it's a masterpiece, but it's just not that interesting. But I will say Jim Carrey is
extraordinarily charismatic and good in the role. You've also got Jeffrey Tambor who always delivers.
You've got a great supporting cast in this thing.
And it's at least worth it for the moments where Carrey's on,
some of the Carrey moments, not all of them. It's not like, oh God, but at least most of the
time when he's on screen, it's good, it's worth watching. And when he's not on screen,
you've still got Christine Baranski and Molly Shannon and other people who are talented. Bill
That said, it gets the job done enough. And it's good enough that you could throw it on
a Christmas and not be mad at it. But I understand why when this came out, what year did this come
out? 2011 or something? No, 2000. Jesus God. When this came out 24 years ago, I understand why it
kind of a lukewarm reception and relatively panned. But again, by today's standards, it's fine.
It's good enough. And this is all leading me to the final Grinch thing, which -
Well, now hold on. I never finished my color perp.
Oh, all right.
So I love Spielberg's color perp. The new one. I felt a little uneasy
talking to my friends at work and being like, I got to say, I prefer the version that the old
white guy directed over this new version. But that's the consensus. I think everyone agrees
that that is the classic. I saw Taraji P. Henson interviewed. Apparently she has stopped giving
fucks as they say, but they were like, what ran through your mind when they offered you this part?
She was like, well, first I thought, why the hell are we remaking the color purple?
And then she like holds the look into the camera for like 10 seconds, like pointedly,
which I'm sure old Oprah didn't care for. But the movie,
maybe the, maybe this was amazing on Broadway or something, but it is a slog has the exact
same problems as Wonka. The songs are completely unmemorable. There are transitions from sexual
assault to like, you know, a field of people dancing happily and like a happy upbeat song
and tonally it's kind of all over the map. Both movies, Wonka and color purple sort of look alike.
They were put out by Warner Brothers and they just kind of feel the same fake compute, whether
they are really computer generated or not, they look computer generated lifeless movies that just
get under the skin in any way. Like to tell this story at two and a half hours and get as far as
I'm concerned, zero emotion out of it is nuts. It's a very powerful emotional story. I felt like
everybody that was cast in this new version, it has to be compared to the original and none of them
equal up. You know, like Fantasia Barrino, I only know her from American Idol. She is not,
again, much like Chameleon, not the lead of a movie. So it's just not a compelling, the songs stink.
I hate to say it, but that's two musicals down. I think that that's a genre that maybe we can put
to bed, maybe give us two Westerns a year and just put the musical to bed. It's not working anymore.
I see at least David Allen Greer was in it.
Yeah, yeah. That was on the big screen. No comment.
All right. My final Grinch is, I was going to rewatch the old cartoon and instead
in my record collection of Christmas records, I found, and I forgot I even bought it because
I'd never listened to it, was a Zero Mustel reads The Grinch Stole Christmas.
Okay. And I put that on on Christmas day.
People, this is where we're at. Now I'm reviewing two productions of this story,
one from 2000, one from 2020 or something. This final one is from 1960 whatever.
It's a record. It's not even a visual. It's a record that one man reads and performs.
And it is leagues, leagues more entertaining than any of the stuff they've committed in recent years
to film to tell the same story. For all the money and all the bullshit and all the stuff
Star Power and all the flash and all the whatever, they still can't even tell the story as well
as one talented performer reading it on a record. And that is not the old man in me talking.
I do not come from a time of radio. I'm not saying back in my day it was better. I am saying
I pulled the thing out from before I was born and listened to it out of curiosity and found
that it was more entertaining than the multi -million dollar productions that they've
executed over the last 20 some years. If you have a chance to hear it, check it out. I doubt it's
that was somehow better. And of course the cartoon is great.
Anyway folks, our movie today, speaking of money and big budgets, Killers of the Flower Moon,
Martin Scorsese's 100 million dollar Apple TV production starring Robert De Niro,
starring Leonardo DiCaprio,
starring Lily Gladstone, starring Jesse Plemons, featuring Martin Scorsese himself
and a Brendan Fraser somehow looking worse than he does in The Whale.
I hadn't seen this movie in months and I looked up the Wikipedia page and I was like
John Lithgow and then I immediately remembered him and Brendan Fraser and just laughed out loud
at Brendan Fraser's performance in this movie which is insane.
He's okay. He's not great. Lithgow delivers as he usually does. Lithgow has not aged
so he either has always looked 70 or he's just not aging. I'm not sure which it is. I think
it's probably he's always looked 70. I think it's all yeah. Hackman always looked 70.
This movie is about the systematic slaughtering of the Osage people
in the 1920s as not poor but more poorer and some in some cases destitute whites are trying to
get the power of the oil that's in their land away from them and in their own control.
The movie is three and a half almost four hours long.
I'm gonna just say right out of the gate. I hated it. I think that this movie is a slog.
I think that now let me say this. Martin Scorsese is so brilliant that I feel maybe I missed
something. Maybe I need to rewatch it but there is not one twist or turn in this film.
There is not one surprise. There is not one development of character. It is a point A to
point B story. They identify immediately who the villains are and what it is they are trying to do
and what it is they are doing already actively even though they're saying they're not doing it.
They show you the viewer that they most certainly are. They jump right into that with both feet
and the biggest misstep of this movie is they don't make you enjoy watching the villains in
any way shape or form. Now I know that the response that could be well how the hell are
we supposed to enjoy watching people who are committing a genocide? That's not what I mean.
What I mean is Martin Scorsese has made plenty of movies about bad guys where you know where they
stand at the beginning of the film but you love to hate those bad guys. This movie had it been
executed in my opinion like There Will Be Blood for instance a period piece also about oil also
about greed also about in the similar time period also about a man who will stop at nothing to build
his own empire his selfishness whatever and destroys himself as a result. The movie works.
Why? Because you love to hate Daniel Day Lewis and you want to keep watching and also
in the telling of There Will Be Blood they make you the viewer believe for a while that this man
does have some humanity so it becomes about the investigation of well where does he lose it and
did he ever have it? This movie Killers of the Flower Moon there's none of that. They establish
right off the bat that they need they want the oil they want the land and that's it and then you just
watch people suffer for three hours and a half hours including the villains. I don't understand
it. No it's a tough sit an unpleasant sit and I liked it more than you but I have pretty similar
issues so like it's just about to start streaming on Apple TV that's the way to watch it over two
nights you know but it's Scorsese not wanting to put an intermission in it and all that kind of
stuff the first time in my entire life I've ever like not understood Scorsese I'm like what do you
think you're doing force forcing people to sit through this three and a half hour suffering
without a break without going to the bathroom whatever like what do you think you're accomplishing
and it's this weird thing I never would have expected from Scorsese where I think he kind
of got lost in the sauce a little bit on trying to convey the story of the Native American people.
Look in our current society the way in our current culture Scorsese should not have directed this
movie. I don't think he got under the skin of the Native American people. I do think he did a better
job of getting under the skin of Leonardo DiCaprio who's playing an idiot and as Paul Schrader said
this week three and a half hours is a long time to spend in the company of an idiot and I agree
with him. I agree with that too there's nothing interesting or captivating about Leonardo DiCaprio
he just plays a fucking moron and he really does yeah and his name's Ernest to boot so you're like
he's a hick to boot so you know and De Niro was just like plain evil and that's sort of I totally
see what you're saying your issue with the movie is Joe is that he has he has this reverence
for the Native American people but he doesn't really get under their skin in my opinion the
way he does under Italians because of course he would but then the villains the bad guys
I get that you can't show the quote fun of killing Native Americans and trying to wipe
them out for their money that's a hard thing to show the fun of and and maybe this movie
shouldn't be fun you know no I'm not I'm not saying let me be clear I'm not saying it should
be fun like Goodfellas right but like because there's a difference between um you know holding
up a liquor store and you know killing a woman or children of course of course of course what I'm
saying that's what I say there there will be blood is the best example yeah for sure you you
don't make it fun what you do is is you convince me that the here's what he could have done and
this is what would have made this a challenging film where you show more of the um affluence
of the Indian people yeah show more of the beauty and the love and the compassion amongst them
not to mention also show more of the wealth show it and then show more of the desperation and
destitution of the white people and then now you've got a situation where when they commit these
horrible deeds you're challenged as the viewer going well Jesus said that's terrible but at the
same time were they so desperate that they felt they had no other choice what now you're asking
hard questions you're you're confused that's how you tell it in my opinion or no I agree
those early looks in the movies at at the Native Americans in you know fancy clothes fancy cars
etc that was super interesting I had never seen that before but it is just kind of glossed over
really quickly to show them getting exploited but yeah if you spend a little time knowing that
they were running the show when these white idiots showed up to take it from them
but Scorsese in my opinion never gets comfortable with the Native American life so that's why I
don't think we're spending a lot of time with them because I just don't think he feels as
comfortable in that world now we know too much about this movie because it's been in development
for a really long time but originally it was going to be DiCaprio in the Jesse Plemons role
and a pretty traditional investigation story where they come in it focuses on the cop who's
investigating what went on DiCaprio reads a draft that Scorsese and Eric Roth who's a great screen
writer they had written and he's like where's the heart of this movie I don't get it I don't
where is that where's the end so they restructured the entire thing kind of quickly from what I
gathered and I think that's the issue with the movie and it's it's my complaint is when they try
to address everybody in a movie often the movie loses focus naturally well also so I think making
it a making it a a white savior procedural might not have been the PC thing to do but that's what
acclaimed book was and that's what Scorsese would have been much more comfortable with
however the movie would have faced an unending backlash as it did in its current form by the way
it doesn't there's nothing yeah there's there's exploited no just for exploiting the Native
Americans yeah there's no there's no sorry not compassion there's no passion in the movie no
exactly I agree there's no I could have gotten behind a guy going down there yeah now you've
got a story a white guy goes down to investigate the murders his cohorts or colleagues are like
who cares who cares about Indians whatever and he's like well I there's something wrong being done
here maybe you make the cop a little racist whatever that means that's what I guarantee
that's what this movie would have been I guarantee and maybe that feels more like a Clint Eastwood
90s kind of directing vehicle or something but those movies are remain modern classics we love
them so it's tricky I get it but Plemons comes in he's dumb he's dumb doesn't seem to care he's
super uncompelling as a character and I love Jesse Plemons and here's the problem when they in the
beginning of the movie where they're trying to establish the affluence of of the American
it's it's it doesn't even resonate because the movie is was so marketed as we all know what this
is this is about white people doing a terrible thing to to the uh oh for god's sakes the the
the name of the the try I just said it now I've forgotten Osage Osage people we all know that
that's what the movie's about so that part where the where she's uh where Lily Gladstone's talking
to the um you know the banker guy whatever and he's like your mother spent 350 dollars on me
don't you think that's because he's managing the estate or whatever and she's like yes I do
I didn't even get that that was supposed to be like oh that's supposed to be like look how much
money they have right I thought it was like he was saying like I thought he was being like racist
toward her so I like this is my point like it's within three minutes of this movie starting they
brutal murders and and and footage of dead uh Osage people and her voiceover is saying so and
so dead no investigation so and so dead no and it's very clear that they were all murdered
yeah there's something when you show that right off the bat I know what's going on there's no
mystery anymore this should have been right it's a it's a flawed it's a flawed construction from
the start it could have it could have way it yeah go ahead it just could have shown
keep me guessing about De Niro for an hour right you know yeah you there there is you're you're
absolutely right there is no guesswork there is no suspense really and the violence and by the way
this might be better design Scorsese is obviously a genius but the moments of like violence just
like and they should you know but it's like yeah there's no release the whole movie you can't make
a three and a half hour movie that's kind of a wallow in misery on all sides with no release
but in addition not really give us a compelling enough story to follow because we already know
the pieces Schindler's List is a good comparison I didn't even think about there will be blood
although that is the perfect comparison to this movie but Schindler's List okay now already you
have a Jewish man telling a Jewish story so better but the story of Oscar Schindler himself
and his sidekick is a fascinating story and a story with a clear a to b journey I mean that
guy is a aristocrat who gives up everything to save the Jewish people it's an amazing story
this movie's story at its core the one we're following is a very dumb man being manipulated
by a racist kills everyone he cares about like that is not a compelling story for three and a
hours also too also too speaking of DiCaprio's dumbness in the movie yeah
you're sitting there several times going Lily Gladstone wouldn't fall for this
yeah she's too smart for this they established that she's too smart for it like why would she
into this why like there's no explanation of that there's no um and then by the way
just real quick then then comes the part in in our 245 mark or whatever where um DiCaprio's son
dies or I'm sorry daughter dies right and uh because she gets who who whooping cough and uh
and and it's he's devastated and I don't even know what the fucking point of it is it's like
he's devastated but he's purposefully poisoning his wife but he loves his daughter poisoning
himself to deal with it yeah but then I can't I'm not like on I don't like the character so
feel bad for him but I guess I'm supposed to because a kid died and I just don't know what
the fuck I'm supposed to be thinking about any of this that's exactly what it is and I think that
maybe and and it'll be a while but if I were to have a second viewing of this movie I don't have
any real compelling reason to certainly but maybe it'll sink into me a little more what he was
trying to do I'm just saying your average person coming to this movie is it's a tough slog I agree
with Joe I did like it more because to see a Martin Scorsese movie you know I saw it here
in the IMAX or the biggest screen or whatever and um there's amazing shots in it I mean even
his stuff with the Native Americans it's like I said he wasn't really finding the soul of them
but there are some amazing uh scenes and sequences um in Native American villages it's it's very well
shot as with all Scorsese stuff um and it kind of held my interest I didn't get up and go to the
bathroom for four hours which is pretty impressive I didn't check my phone so I think there's
something here to like I would break it into two parts my big uh notes are pretty much all the same
as Joe's I think we felt almost exactly the same about it and I think you lean me more towards a
lower review of it frankly but um yeah it's what what what I noticed today right before this is I
read the Wikipedia page to refresh my memory I haven't seen it in a few months and the beats
of this story are so boring when you see them spelled out in Wikipedia it's like Robert De Niro
has Leonardo DiCaprio kill this guy then Robert he has him kill this guy then he kills this girl
then he kills that girl that like that's what the plot of the movie is and when you see it laid out
like that you're like well no wonder you know that this movie kind of drags along it's like
there's there's really no compelling plot and I think it's it's I'm not blaming the woke agenda
or something but that's what led us here I think that in a desire to be all things to all people
I think Scorsese wound up letting down quite a bit of the Native American community and also
letting down people who wanted to see this great book adapted nobody really got what they wanted
here but I love watching Martin Scorsese's shit and it's it's hard for me to give him a bad review
but yeah I'm sorry I'm siding with you more and more Joe as I as I look at it with some
distance I don't I don't see much that I remember loving about this movie. My hogs down unfortunately
I as you all know I love The Irishman which is also a four -hour Martin Scorsese film that's also
focused on villains but also a movie that I felt showed the deterioration of a man becoming the
victim of what his own albeit flawed ethical code was and it and it leading to costing him
everything he was trying to protect that's why I like that movie this movie I felt like wasn't that
so my hogs down but perhaps one day I'll re -watch but that's where I'm at. My hog is up
but no real strong desire to re -watch it is it one of the best movies of the year
yeah but by default you know I don't I'm not seeing this as being some great movie here as others have
said I would compare the DiCaprio character here to Jordan Belfort in Wolf of Wall Street
there Scorsese glamorized the life of a scumbag to the point that he still takes criticism for
that movie as if he didn't know what he was doing with that movie but and I I I compared it in my
head also to Wolf of Wall Street it's funny because they talk about the wolves in this movie right but
here's the difference Jordan DiCaprio as Belfort is compelling to watch number one and number two
there's still a character arc you still see that in the beginning he's humble and he's trying to
figure it out and then he realizes oh if you just kind of bend the rules a little bit you can get
this far and then he becomes further and further and further corrupted and then becomes arrogant
and then he there's there's a journey to go on and there's just no and also too to go back to
the original point uh or where we were at the least in the beginning conversation you can make
now the people that were victims of Belfort did not feel this way but you can there is a way to
tell the wall street movie story in a flashy crazy fun right comedic way yeah you can't do that
obviously with this but what they could have done in my opinion again I don't need to repeat it was
was give the characters a journey of some sort uh yeah but they did they didn't but anyway well
yeah he no he got accused of glamorizing him and still gets accused of glamorizing him and I think
in this instance he went so far to defund the proceedings although these are not proceedings
that would be easy to make fun but you know what we you know what we mean by that yeah yeah it's
to make it a compelling sit a compelling watch is all I'm saying and I think he was determined to
not do that with hence fighting the intermission so hard it's like dude at some point you have
to cave a little bit you have to like let people enjoy themselves or else people aren't going to
like the movie obviously um and it's also one more thing it's also a very very important story
to tell and it's a very important part of history which is why I'm complaining that I don't think it
was told right for this medium in the way it was told in this medium I would rather just read a
non -fiction book about it so I'm not watching a movie feeling like I'm reading a book and then
top of it guessing what's real and what's not because it's a movie you know so um so that's
that I I do think the story is quite important I just don't think he did it justice in this medium
so anyway we'll be back with Oppenheimer another three hour biopic thing yes we'll be back and
oh wait I got a plug before sorry uh I have big shows coming up people please come out January
13th the 13th Gramercy Theater in New York City please come out please get tickets uh the week
after I'm at the Comedy Mothership in Austin Texas uh please come out to those shows as well
Jodorosa .com for all tickets and following that I've got tons of shows through February and into
March Jodorosa .com to get tickets I'm hitting the west coast I'm hitting Cali I'm hitting the
south I'm hitting Tennessee uh but first up is New York and then Austin for the two day or well
the two well it's four shows in Austin one show at the Gramercy I hope to see you Jodorosa .com
thank you