Huff, Puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
More Puff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players' favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly, 21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania,
and West Virginia only, void in Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -Terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59pm, Eastern on August 31, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another. No other sportsbook has
been offered this good. With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now
until October, if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash. If you bet on
football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash, guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatic Sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called winning 100 gambler, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, the podcast now part of the Fangoria Podcast Network for
more info about this network, including other programs or how to follow our show and
find past episodes of We'll See You In Hell.
Visit Fangoria .com and that is the same old intro I've been saying for two full seasons
and it has not changed for episode one of our third season, which this is happening right
right now, this is it. We're kicking it off. Very excited. Episode 301, as they'd called
in the TV biz. Yes. 301. Not 301. No. Season 3 episode 1. Really, we're just calling
them seasons because we very quickly lose interest and have no attention spans and keep changing
the format. Yeah, but it's good to be back talking about movies again and we're sitting
Joe prepared us both a Tom Collins. Yes as if he were a Southern plantation owner. I'm dressed like
a Django with a blue suit with frilly white necker chief. Right and the spurs don't leave the
spurs. America is in the toilet. It's Friday a couple days after the 4th of July and since Independence
day, not that the world was going great by any means, but we've really taken a sharp
turn downward.
And I agree, that movie was a true disgrace to the business, and depending on the
resurrection.
Yeah, insurrection.
I didn't see it.
I heard it was terrible.
I heard it was unwatchable, yeah.
Which I didn't think it looked that bad.
I hate the first one.
I didn't think it looked that bad.
Oh, I like the first one quite a bit, but I saw when I was 16.
You like the first one quite a bit?
So when I was 16, I mean, that's no, that's prime time.
I'm so excuse as I always say on this thing most people like independence day
Have we talked about independence day? No, I just you always are like very dismissive of things that the entirety of America
Loves right. I thought independence day was
Pretty entertaining action movie the entirety of America loves people magazine. That's true. I'll read a people now
No, I don't think and you and you'll like independence day
This is the problem.
I like that it had 30 stories and it kind of kept you like, you know, you never got
two board with any of them.
I like Jud Hersh.
I like Jeff Goldblum.
I'm a big fan of Jeff Goldblum.
I'm a big fan of Jud Hersh.
I'm a big fan of Randy Quaid.
Sure.
I'm a big fan of Vivica A. Fox.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Playing a stripper in that one.
And I'm a medium fan of Will Smith.
Yeah.
I'm fine with him.
He was much more likeable at that time.
Tell you, I'm another fan of Bill Pullman.
in different you know but I mean you pull you pull a great cast together
doesn't make for a great movie evidently you know the huge huge smash I
thought it was fine when I saw it I prefer Mars attacks now they're terrible
terrible movie I really enjoy Mars attacks for this day it's the worst CG I've
ever seen in my life I mean it's just it's just horrific didn't bother me it's
just horrific the only the only character I like is the guy that's like annihilate kill kill the
crazy general oh who's that George C scum no but it should have been it's like he was
a rod stiger yeah I felt that uh term Tim Burton was clearly trying to do his doctor strange love
and uh didn't didn't happen no but I thought it was a fun movie who else is in it Marty short
Jackie Nicholson, Sarah Jessica Parker, another great cast. Yeah, a lot of good
people. Big fans of all these people. I think Jay Fawkes is in it. Jay Fawkes. Yeah,
great cast. Lucas Haas. Yeah, a lot of people. Well, that's two bad movies that you
like and are incorrect about. We haven't even gotten to our topic of the day. For
those of you that haven't been caught up on what the format changes is, it's we're
back to talking about movies again last season it was all sins now we're
talking about movies and we're not watching the movies we're just discussing a
different movie each episode that falls under the umbrella of you know horror
sci -fi fantasy anything that would be in some way related to fangoria the magazine
and for this first episode we've chosen one that we've had much debate about off
the mic. And now it's time to have it on. Tremors. Tremors. And much like our old
commentary podcasts of season one, you know, we're not gonna be talking that much
about these movies. Well, we might be. Because I think you've only seen
Tremors the one time, right? Did I introduce it to you? You did. Okay. Yeah. You're
the one I can blame for wasting two hours of my life with that movie. Tremors has
always been a favorite of mine. One of my playing to me why? One of my big debates that I always
wonder about is if you see a movie when you're 10 or like we just discussed Independence Day
and you love it that kind of means you're gonna love it forever. You don't see its flaws when you
watch it as an adult. You watching tremors at age 49 however old you are now. I mean look if you
You want to start throwing early cheap shots because you're going to lose this debate.
You can, but it's unnecessary.
I just don't know.
It's hard to say.
But I think tremors watching it now is every bit as fun and enjoyable as it was when
I was a kid.
Now granted, it's going to be more fun to a kid because it's scary without being terrifying.
It's a comedy horror.
but the chemistry between Kevin Bacon and Fred Ward is off the charts.
I love the charts.
Love the two of them together.
Off the charts.
A term I would reserve, literally, for like Jack Lemmon, Walter Matval chemistry.
You're saying that they're at that level.
I'm saying they're a little below it.
Okay, just a little.
When I say in their electric together.
Okay.
Bacon and Ward, I think that the jokes, the dialogues,
is way funnier than it needed to be the scares are not terrifying they were to a
young boy when I saw it but you know the monster effects are pretty good the
story is pretty good it spawned a bunch of sequels that are terrible I don't
argue that but tremors again is a movie that many many many people have a great
deal of affection for and I did it really threw me for a loop when you just
flat out didn't like it. I thought I'll introduce Joe to a real gem in the horror genre. And he's
spat on it. I didn't, uh, I don't consider it a horror movie at all. At all, I consider it like
a, like an action movie that kind of has a monster in it that I grab don't really give a shit about.
Giant worms aren't scary to me, but whatever. I've never been a, I've never been a fan of the,
first of all, I've never been a fan of the giant insect or giant organism horror movie,
giant ants attacking or giant spiders or, you know, we're overrun by worms, whatever,
I'm not a fan.
So big worms in the desert didn't really freak me out at any way, shape or form.
So I mean, to me, it just felt like an action movie where the bad guys happen to be worms.
you know I mean look far be it for me to to say that the one of the great as you
think horror movies of all time stars Michael Gross of Family Ties and Fred
Ward who I don't know that anybody's ever applied the word electric to
before with bacon so these are first for everybody you've been great in a couple
movies Miami Blues with Alec Ball when he's great any pleasant creepy scumbag
detective another great underrated movie that Joe would probably hate
tremors is not a scary movie I grant you it's really kind of it would be like
the absolute best sci -fi channel movie but putting those in the complete dust
those movies are all terrible I've written one of them and it was terrible right
um but you know it's in that vein I don't I think it's intended to be an
entertaining action comedy with horror sci -fi elements and of that genre which
which is very difficult to do correctly.
It's almost never done well.
I feel like it's a classic of that very specific genre.
I will give you that it's a passable movie.
It's passable, but at best, it's passable.
It's not funny.
There's really the carons of funny lines
and a ton of funny dialogue.
If you're 12 and you think like Ernest P. World was funny,
it's like Ernest goes to camp funny.
Like it's like cartoonish hick funny.
Like I got a bunker with guns in it.
Well now we're bringing up a whole another world if you're going to just casually dismiss
Arnaz P. Warle. I 100 % am in it and please defend him so my point can just be proven
about your taste this early on and we're not even 10 minutes in.
Again, movies I haven't seen since I was a kid, but Ghost of Camp saves Christmas, goes
to jail in particular are funny. I saw Arnaz go to camp when I was nine years old when
and they released it.
And I had been allowed to use the phrase,
piece of shit, that's what I would have said.
Crazy.
I rented, Ernest goes to jail, three years later.
And I thought it had more redeeming qualities
than any Ernest movie I'd ever seen.
Sure.
But it's, I don't think I got through the whole thing.
I mean, I'm putting them up there with the tremors.
I don't really see the comparison.
But Michael Gross and Reba McIntyre play gun nuts and a bunker, which is really more
timely than ever.
I mean, again, and it's no offense to Reba McIntyre anytime she's acting.
I don't even want to see it.
She's great in tremors.
she's uh to me fine funny it's yeah they're not getting a top shelf cast because it's
I think not only clearly a b -movie but intended as a b -movie it wasn't a b -movie though
it was released in theaters uh Kevin Bacon was quite famous at the time as sort of an
homage to like driving movies it destroyed Michael Gross's career that was his big chance
to transition after family ties and they were like, well, no, tremors did okay, but he
was like the fourth lead in it. It wasn't falling on his shoulders. He carries the series
now. Well, yeah, a series which is now introduced Jamie Kennedy into the cast. Now you apparently
watched that one. I tried to watch tremors five. It was as unwatchable as the other sequels.
The first one is watchable. The other ones are unwatchable. Tremors two, I remember, right
off the bat, they they have one of the tremors was walking around like a dog. And I thought,
well, your whole your entire premise is that these things are under the ground. The tagline
for the first one is there's nothing new under the sun, but under the ground. Dot, dot, dot.
Sure. Yeah. Tremors too. They immediately have them up on their feet like dogs. So whoever's
guiding the tremors franchise is obviously an idiot. Now it's see now it gets interesting to me.
terrible movie but yeah now you got a worm dog now we're talking this is a
monster I like to they flew in the third or fourth one did they they had
flying one I only saw two and what happened is is the is the birds the the
underground grab a wades beget the ones on the feet the dog ones and then the dog
ones beget the terror act of ones or something and then the terror act of ones
Shit out eggs and they become the grab boys again. It's like a circle of life
The the first one was written and directed by Ron Underwood who did city slickers
I'm a big fan of that movie me to heart and souls, but the guy does like light comedy. What's heart and souls?
It was a really fun
Robert Downey Jr. movie where he dies and he's got like Herman's head style ghost follow him around. Oh, I remember that movie kind of fun
And I might be remembering the plot completely wrong, but
You know the guy don't think you're directs much anymore. I think he made a movie it was on NBC all the time a lot of affection
I have for it because me and my friends used to really love tremors is that it would air on NBC and it was the worst
edited movie of all time meaning
It's only PG -13 but should be R for language and probably would be by today's standards
They dubbed in the most ludicrous
Substitutions for these swear words on NBC. Well, give me some of it. What did they do? I think I still remember them
Michael grows at one point screams after they
Shoot millions of bullets into it and kill it
Michael gross and the movie goes broke into the wrong goddamn rec room didn't you you son of a bitch?
Okay, on NBC he goes dub with a apparently a black man's voice
It starts out gross. He goes broke into the wrong
long, then a voice goes, gold, earn,
rec room, didn't you, you big jerk, big jerk,
big jerk, you can say other things on NBC.
Why wouldn't they just change it to son of a gun?
I have no idea.
And there was a lot of that in there.
If you get a chance to see it edited,
it's on USA sometimes now.
I believe Kevin Bacon is doing a series of tremors now.
He, the TV, they're doing a TV series
and Kevin Bacon is appearing in the TV series.
Yes, I read that.
Okay.
I mean, do we need a TV series?
What the hell is going on with this business?
That a movie isn't good enough to spawn sequels
that go into the theater and now it gets a TV show.
And the guy that said no to all of it
is gonna come back now and do the TV show.
I'm baffled.
I mean, the fact that Bacon would do this
makes me think it must be pretty good
because he had that successful television show.
He's his movies are still he's still in movie his show didn't do that well that reason one
It only went like three seasons. I thought it went five
But he got shit on the guy. I'm just saying, you know people don't remember though that Kevin Bacon and his wife Kira Sedgwick
We're taken by Bernie Madoff, so chances are he needs some money all of his money pretty much was taken
Now old Sedge she was in a hit TV show
The closer the closer yeah, which for the first year that it was out
I'd never seen the an ad for the show. I just saw billboards and I thought it was the closer the closer
And I thought it was about like dead people or something
I was like what does that mean and then I saw that and I was like oh the closer
She's like at the back of the closer. She closed cases like she's like a no -nonsense detective or something or she's the
District Attorney. I always love Sedwick. She's got an underwear scene in singles that really haunts my dreams
Yeah, she was delightful in that film. Yeah, she was delightful in that film
I you know that he did well for himself and she did well for herself bacon was quite a looker sure shows his hog and wild things
It's it's ample you see his dick in it. Yeah swinging around see that's what I would have liked to have seen in tremors
Is bacon Kevin's bacon's dick and maybe maybe it's a one of the graboids and the camera pulls out and you rise
It's just Kevin Bacon's dick. Yeah, sure something like that would be good to me. I mean you heard it here folks
That's what maybe they can do that if it's is an HBO series. No, but I think I could let me see if I can get staffed over there
All right, you probably could I don't think and then and then here's you in the meeting
I'm a huge fan of the original. I love the series. Yeah
Yeah, I can't believe those weren't in theaters. You know who stole the show was Michael Gross
I was president said his career on fire and the chemistry between warden bacon off the charts off the charts
He says yeah, followed by describing the movie is fine
Which is what you did tremors. Yes. No, I would never say it's a fine movie. I
Would never refer to tremors as fine. You said it a minute ago. I mean it said it's a fine film fine film can mean like
You in it like a won't like a fine wine. Yeah, exactly. Well again
I mean this is just an absurd proclamation. No, I mean I if you would ask me before we rewatched it recently
I would have said tremors was one of my favorite movies and rewatching it, you know, it shows some
Some seams. I think it's a blast. I think it's extremely well written. It moves really well
Even the romance has handled well, and you kind of give a shit about it
They got that James Hong the old Asian guy is super funny and trying to make money off the grabboids. I
Don't even remember these people. What was the romance the girl with this sunblock? She's like a seismologist
just she's out studying the ground.
Oh yeah, there just happens to be a hot scientist out here
and a gorgeous male hick.
Yeah, who has to take her pants off at one point
because they get cut on barbed wire.
Yeah.
But, you know, this is the freezer's rattling.
They keep a lot of things going where like,
there'll be something rattling and moving on the ground
that will lure or anger the tremors.
The rules are very clearly stated,
which is to me when horror movies go wrong,
When they don't clearly state the rules or when they deviate from the rules and they make up their own shit
Tremors they're trying to figure out what's going on they figure it out
The audience is tipped off as to what those rules are in a very clear and concise fashion. They never deviate from it
and in terms of a of a horror screenplay or an action screenplay
I think it does a fantastic job of hitting all the beats and introducing new obstacles and
never sheeding the audience.
Yeah, for a simple -minded movie, it works.
It's a simple -minded movie.
It's a paint by numbers movie.
I would completely disagree with that.
It's so much better than it has to be,
and that's not what paint my numbers is.
I disagree.
I think that is a movie that started with a title
and they worked out from there,
and it was one of those in five minutes.
Oh, it's so simple.
It's called tremors.
It's the Earth shaking.
Why is the Earth shaking?
There's giant worms under it.
these people are trapped in the middle of nowhere they got out with the worms and kill them somehow.
Well, how do they do that? Well, there could be a militia guy with all these guns.
They sprint, you know, they know if they're on, it's kind of like the shark thing, if you're in the water it's going to come get you.
If they're on the ground and making noise and movement, then it senses it and comes after you.
They hadn't really been done. Kevin Bacon runs toward the edge of that cliff at the end and then it goes blasting out the side of the cliff.
and dies. The gross out effects were gross and fun. I couldn't have I couldn't have
dreamed although I should have known that you would not enjoy the movie. Why do you
see that? What is that? I would just I wouldn't think you could show tremors to
someone and they would not like it and yet you are notorious for not liking
exactly those things. What name one other example of that? Well or liking things
that everyone hates. We had this discussion via text very recently.
Well, and you said...
You said things that weren't true.
You said that I just like things that people hate.
And that's not true.
No, I'm saying there's a lot of things that you love
that everyone in the world hates.
But I could say the same about you.
And a lot of things you hate that everyone in the world loves.
I could say the same about you.
I don't know that you could.
I could easily.
We've seen movies together and we'll both go,
I can't, why does that only have a 21 %?
We've done that.
And but the difference is that's if I watch that same like Terminator Genesis when I saw
it on the theater I went where I saw it with you and I said I can't believe it's got a 21 %
or I ate a great time tried rewatching it I was like you know what this movie is not that
good.
I like it when I saw it because I can admit what I'm wrong which you can't which is why you're
clinging to this notion that tremors is a fantastic masterpiece of a film and it's just not nobody
even dies in it.
I don't think one person died several people die in it who died there's an elderly couple that is killed
Their car is sucked under the headlights go up in a very effective
Coolly shot saying yeah, I remember that part, but I'm saying in the main crew
They pick up a hard had at one point and there's brains inside of it
I remember that but I'm saying in the main crew when they're when they're the old Chinese man who you don't remember who has a
Saisie dies. He's eaten by it. Okay, but yeah gross McIntyre bacon warred the girl. They all live
Because there were supposed to be a little girl on the Pogo stick lives right the girl from Jurassic Park, right
But I can absolutely admit and I've gone back and watched things even recently where I thought they were amazing and I've questioned what I was thinking
But that's what I'm talking about it. It goes back to
I
Think that's a very interesting argument or discussion to have is
Does seeing something when your kid just cemented as that's your opinion of it?
no that's why you use the phrase it didn't hold up yeah and I've said that
before but sometimes I just wonder if I'm still loving something because I've
always loved it you know for like when I watch 16 canals with my girlfriend she
liked it a lot but she's not seeing it as I did 80 times when I was a kid look
there I liked kingdom of the crystal skull more than I should have because of
nostalgia. Sure. Absolutely. If I saw Temple of Doom now, I'd probably take more
issue with it. It's fantastic. That I did as a kid. I love it. I love the movie.
It's the best of the series. But, you know, there are also plenty of things I
watched as a kid that I loved and then when I read, you know, look, I own the movie
Flash Gordon. I think it's a lot of fun. It's a piece of shit fucking movie. It's
terrible. Yes. You know, but when I was a kid, I thought it was a masterpiece. And now I
watching. I go, yeah, it's not great, but it brings me back. And I just like watching
it for company reasons. Now, the difference between you and me is I would never invite
you over here and say, we need, you need to see Flash Gordon pet.
Tremors is not Flash Gordon. I don't consider Tremors a campy or a joky thing at all. I think
it's a good movie. No, Flash Gordon isn't joky or campy on purpose.
Well, then I'd love to watch by accident. It is right. Tremors tries to be campy and joky
and fails, and isn't either.
Tremors knows exactly what it is and for that style
of tongue and cheek, horror, comedy action, whatever,
I think it's about as good as you can do.
Because it's a genre that never works.
I thought Slyther was like a pretty good attempt
at that kind of...
The Sharon Stone, yeah.
That's Slytherium.
William Baldwin vehicle?
No, that works for exactly what it is.
Jerk off material for a 13 -year -old boy
who steals the VHS from his dad, but slither, slither, James Gunn's slither, uh, did you see
that?
No.
Okay.
It's got a similar vibe, it's much more orrated, but a comedy horror, they don't go hand
in hand because if you're laughing, you're generally not scared.
The best kind of feeling for me is like, misery, a ten -clober -field lane, where it's very
intense and scary and you're laughing at it almost out of nerves right the whole thing
of going for jokes and also going for scares usually you're you're not really succeeding
with either ghost busters I gotta be honest with you folks because ghost busters coming out
in a week right ghost busters doesn't necessarily hold up the original film it's good it's very
entertaining it's not a great movie folks well that's always been my argument with I don't
I don't think the new one looks good.
I'm not interested in seeing it.
I'll see.
But that's, I won't not see it.
I just don't, I'm not gonna run out to watch it.
But that all being said, I don't understand
what all the hoopla was with people criticizing it
and being so hard on the going.
The franchise, the franchise, like,
the franchise is one pretty good movie.
Like the second movie is dog shit.
The cartoon sucks.
I think Ghostbusters one watching it the other night.
I would have always again said that was
one of my favorite movies. When I watch the other night, it's got real long slow patches.
Bill Murray is mugging in a way that I've never really seen him do and he's just like
he's talking too much. His lines aren't as funny as they normally are. Sometimes he
lands a perfect one liner, but there's also times where he's just like annoying to be honest
and he's one of my favorite people in the world. Right.
Why?
Acroid, you know, is almost given no jokes.
He gets blown by a ghost in one of the most ludicrous scenes I've ever seen.
And is that a dream he's having?
It is a dream.
I confirmed it this time.
I watched that with my girlfriend who had never seen it.
She was like, is this a dream?
It's very...
She never saw ghost busters.
She was raised religious and not allowed to see anything with specters or Harry Potter or
anything.
Jesus.
But, you know, she was like, it's fine, but there were 30 -minute sections where we just weren't laughing.
I think Rammus is good in it, Marannus is kind of steals the show,
in a role that was written for John Candy,
and the whole time I was picturing John Candy.
Why did John Candy not do it?
They didn't pay him enough.
They had blown their load with the other actors and Sigourney Weaver,
who was excellent in Ghostbusters.
Yeah.
Yeah, but candy wanted, I think, a million dollars or something, and they wouldn't give
it to him.
And Miranda stood it for half that.
You know, well, it's like how Eddie Murphy was supposed to be the Ernie Hudson role.
They would have had to maybe add him a single joke if it was Eddie Murphy.
Yeah, the only joke Ernie Hudson gets is, I've seen shit that will turn you white, and it's
a tremendous joke, but that's his only gag in the whole movie.
A lot of what I liked about it is like it's so clearly a painting New York whenever they're up there with
Gozer and stuff like it had kind of a charming sort of like an early Tim Burton feel that when I was a kid
I always just thought oh I'm looking at New York City. It's a very obvious painting for most of the movie. I will readily admit that I am a big fan of the movie
But I it's very very very seldomly have the desire to throw it in and watch it. Yeah, which speaks to your point. I'd give it a
a B plus and maybe an A minus out of nostalgia,
but the people sobbing about the new one,
it's like, who cares?
But that's my point.
I don't think the second one was terrible either.
Oh, it sucks.
I thought it was half as good as the first, maybe.
It's, you know, it's not a disgrace, but it sucks.
Yeah.
But that's my point.
It's like, everybody's like, they're ruining it.
They're ruining it.
What are they ruining?
There's not there's it's it's it was one movie 30 or 40 years ago, whatever it's been
There it has it. It's been ruined three times over already like by by the stuff that the original people were involved with
What nobody seems to be able to answer is if it's a remake if it's in a world where the original Ghostbusters existed or if it's an entirely new story because the trailer goes library
Black Ghostbusters comes in and joins the crew. I'll tell you what it is
It's the exact same thing.
I'm gonna tell you what it is.
All right.
It's a remake, and the powers that be know that remake is a four -letter word, essentially,
with fans.
Yeah.
So, to get around it, they keep skirting the issue and saying, it's a reimagining, it's a
fucking remake.
Yeah.
It's a fucking remake, but that word has such a curse attached to it that you can't say that
so they're saying all these other words.
It has to be a remake.
It is.
and they got the, the hot, the god damn.
And he was playing and it was, uh, man is in it.
Is that true?
Yeah.
I haven't seen him in any of the trailers.
The latest trailer, he gets shot in the dick
and goes, uh, yeah.
The marshmallow man's in the movie.
So it's slimer.
I mean, what are we doing here?
Pat Oswald tweeted today, or yesterday,
he saw a screening and he praised it.
He said it was funny and great and scary and he said there's a post -credit scene that's
supposed to be amazing.
Okay.
I'm excited to see it.
Honestly, I think all four of those women are extremely funny and, you know, I didn't
love Spy but Paul Fig has done some great shit.
I'm excited to see it.
I like the heat.
I did not like the heat but I've been told I should revisit it.
I don't know.
I enjoyed the heat and, you know, freaks and geeks, obviously.
the comedy of the heat and spy and almost all movie comedies nowadays is telling
people you look like a homeless man fell into an ugly bucket you know what you
look like if Bert Reynolds got kicked in the nuts by a cleated boot right you
know and that's all every joke and spy was you look like or you smell like right
go especially this is probably going to be a lot of that you look like to ghosts I
I saw Mike and Dave need wedding dates last night. I was telling you before we started. I got to tell you folks
It's a funny movie. I'm sorry. I know it doesn't look funny. I just don't understand how I saw you know at 11 o 'clock with a packed house
It's it's written very well. It's directed very well
It doesn't have that thing when you're watching like two guys trying to fuck girls where you're just kind of grossed out the whole time
They're like you like them. I think I'm divine is funnier than he's ever been. I think Zac Efron is fine
The girls are funny. It's a funny movie, but there are so many you look likes in it that in the post -credit outtakes
They show you 20 ults for each you look like right you look like a waffle that got well
This is what I'm saying. This is why you confuse me. It's lazy with your words. Okay, you confuse me
You're saying it was a funny movie and you enjoyed it yet you're saying it's riddled with the thing you're tired of I can I can both
Praise and criticize
It doesn't make sense pick a side. There are some you look likes in it
It's not like spy where that's all the dials there were 20. There's probably 20 on there
That's a lot of you look like jokes in a two -hour movie
But because there's a lot of you look likes that doesn't to mean negate the really funny stuff that's in it all right fair enough
I'll tell you an underrated movie that I saw recently, that I thought was very funny,
was Hot Top Time Machine Part 2.
I think we talked about it on the show, both of those movies are very funny, written
by my dear friend Josh Heald.
We did talk about it on the show.
My apologies.
I can't remember.
And you know what?
Honestly, Hot Top Time Machine has some you look like as well.
Now at a time of them the first and they can be funny if if they're if they're accurate
They can be funny the first time I remember it was in knocked up for the old Virgin
You know the beard thing you look like Serpico you look like whatever
If it's if it's dead on it's funny when it just seems desperate
It's not I don't know why that's all joke writing is nowadays, but for me if a movie attempts jokes
I'm willing to sort of look the other way
They do a few in Deadpool, which I thought were unnecessary. Yeah, TG mode does a bunch. And I enjoyed Deadpool. It's a funny mode. I also saw the shallows
Blake lively in the shark couldn't have couldn't have less interest in it. Blake lively looks fantastic. It's almost like a sports illustrate one of those old sports
Illustrated VHS's
And it's moderately
Suspensable and entertaining. It's quick
It's it's it's it's so basic a girls like I'm gonna take a surf
Shark has a stranded on a rock for 90 minutes, maybe 80 minutes
Again, I'm willing to kind of give a movie if it's doing an okay job in its genre in this day and age a bit of a pass
I think the shallows is fun, and I think Mike and Dave was a much better than average comment
The shallows to me is just a
Re -visit to deep water which you know, oh no no no
Deepwater was doing the fake documentary shit, right?
No, Deepwater was about, wasn't that doing the,
oh I'm thinking of open water.
No, open water, that's what I'm talking about.
Are you thinking of deep blue sea?
I'm not, no, but deep blue sea is also.
Yeah, sharks, that's cool, Jeff.
Open water is two people stranded as shark circle
and what's gonna happen?
That's open water, yeah, it's a whole movie.
Wasn't that a, was it just so low budget
that I thought it was supposed to be a documentary?
I mean, I can't imagine how it's a documentary
when it's two people stuck in the water the whole time that's true I can't
remember but but open water was was was boring to me the shallow I thought it
was boring too that's why I don't want to see the shallows shallows is very
well shot and I like looking at Blake lively and the shark stuff was moderately
suspenseful and I liked it now yeah the surfing shots for some reason annoyed
me in the trailer okay where she's I don't know I look I don't like a lot of
things. I'll admit to that. Yeah. No, I, I really tried to overcome my desire to like they have
that great South Park about you hit a certain age and you hate everything. And that's I feel that
rising in me and I try to kind of push it down. But I think that, you know, when I hear people are
like, but one of, and you know, everyone I know does this and I'm sure I've been guilty of it too.
you. You like that scene when, you know, Zach Efron gets kicked in the balls, which
doesn't even happen in the movie. But you know, if that ruins a two -hour movie for you,
I can't help you. You have to sort of say, okay, that scene didn't work for me, but this
scene's really funny. And if a comedy has three funny scenes in this day and age, it's
a masterpiece. Three. I can do it as way more than three. But if a comedy makes me laugh
three times. I'm talking the last ten years. I consider it a success.
That's an outrageous statement. I never laugh at comedies anymore.
That's an outrageous statement. Because they're not good. So them not being good doesn't mean
that you have to pretend that they are good. If a movie, if a good one, look, I don't laugh
as much at comedies as I used to. But when I watched Hot Top Time Machine too, I laughed through
the whole fucking thing. I thought it was really funny. Yeah, so that would be a way better
an average comedy which Mike and Dave is. I watched when I saw vacation even though there's a lot
I could say bad about vacation. Cation is I think I enjoyed it. I talked about it I think too
much on this podcast. But vacation is a perfect example of a movie that has terrible scenes in it.
When they get into that swamp and it wreaks of shit and they're pulling shit covered stuff out of
their mouths and you have to sort of suspend disbelief. Why did they get in this brown water that
that smells like shit.
And then now that they're submerged in it,
now they start realizing that it smells like shit.
Ludacris.
Right.
You know, it's a terribly written and performed scene.
It's disgusting.
There's gross out stuff in that movie
that's way too gross for comedy and doesn't work.
But then at least half of that movie is really funny.
So to me, that is a huge success.
I enjoyed the movie.
I didn't know this was the first podcast
we've done since I've seen it.
I enjoyed the movie.
I thought it was funny.
I watched it with my parents.
Okay, it's a good thing to watch for at least with my folks. It was a good thing to watch right
Those were not my beefs the the my biggest piece of the movie my two biggest piece of the movie were
two it's way too gag heavy
Where stuff doesn't make sense. Yeah, why is there a button that makes the windows explode on the car?
That's just stupid. Yeah, it's not a thing that would ever exist ever ever ever. It's just done
so that two gag heavy and
and they ruined the characters, I thought, except for Rusty.
Helms and Applegate are terrible.
No, no, no, no, I was fine with Applegate.
I was fine with Applegate, I was fine with Helms.
Applegate seemed bored and Helms, I think,
tried so hard to not be Chevice that he was nothing
and unlikeable.
It was, I was fine with Helms and Applegate.
I was fine with that.
I didn't like how suddenly Rusty was the mirror,
this is what was wrong with it, the characters.
Rusty was suddenly the mirror image of his dad which made no sense. Rusty was always not like his dad
He was always rebellious. He was always like a poo -hound like yeah
That's always the way they did Rusty and that that for some reason they just threw that out the window
And now he was well not Clark was a poo -hound as well. Yeah, but he was exactly what he wasn't nerdy though
That was the whole thing with Rusty and his dad was nerdy and that's where where the disconnect was
He chugs the beer in the first one. Yeah. Yeah, in the second one. He's fucking going after those French girls like
like, okay, so that's that Audrey was like the smart, well -read, sophisticated daughter.
Now she's like this bimbo who is fucking this beefcake and like, and then they tell
you later they cheat on each other and you're like, yeah, that's not what Aubrey would
be like.
Like, she was always like ahead of her, she was always wiser than her years.
In the first movie, she's like, smokes weed, you know, and this, but why can't you just
look at this new movie on its own terms that didn't that doesn't bug me at all
because it's the same characters yeah but it's not you don't you don't it's a
true it's a sequel it's just that to me whatever choices they want to make
30 years after the original doesn't bug me all right well let me keep going all
right I don't like the twist of Clark Griswald now being like a sociopath yeah
who's like, Griswold wasn't clueless, he was nostalgic and nurturing or whatever you want
to call it, to a fault, and the things that blew up in his face were because he was
trying so hard to do something right.
To do the best thing possible for his family.
And then this movie, he's like, he's like a fucking psychopath.
I agree. Beverly, D 'Angelo, you know, would you have one line? It was like, I don't even know why they had her in there.
Chase looked ill in the remake. He did.
You know, so those were my, and then also too, he opens the garage door.
Not granted. I got excited when I saw the car from the first movie.
Sure. And vacation place or holiday road place.
But the car was destroyed in the first movie.
How does he have the car?
And also, they just happen upon the bed and breakfast
where his parents work.
They don't mention that at any point before that,
like, we're gonna see grandma and granddad.
Like, that's what it should have been.
Along the way, we're gonna visit the grandparents.
And of course, the pep talk from Clark to Rusty
should have taken place way earlier in the journey.
They were already at a breaking point.
It's like they'd been at the breaking point like four times
Comedy's I have I have sold two comedy screenplays neither produced as of now
They are noted to death. There is a very good chance that
The people who wrote it had way better instincts that were just kind of shut down
You know for me
Vacation is a very successful remake and there's stuff. I hate in it
My point is not a remake. No, it's a sequel
To sequel
Okay, sequel it is, but I mean that there's a difference that needs to be noted
Yeah, I guess that's true. So what is I forget that what is Ed Helms? He's he's not
Clark Rizzwell. He's Clark Jr. He's rusty. Yes. Oh, yeah, okay. Well look. It's been a while. Let's see you saw it a week ago
Well, I mean, but how could you forget what? Who did you think Chevy Chase was playing now now?
I say give me why I just went through every character now. I got it. Yes. Yes.
So you're saying when you were talking about
Rusty and Aubrey you were talking about applegate and Helms
Rusty is not married to a sister first of all. Oh Aubrey is Leslie man. Yes. All right. And I'm saying I forgot that detail
Yeah, it was disappointing to me that Aubrey who was always this sort of
like world
She always had a bit of a worldly knowledge to her is the daughter. She was beyond her years. She gets in the second movie.
She's got like a 45 year old alcoholics depression. Yeah, no, I assume that you were talking about the kids, but the two boys
invocation whatever their names may be in the new vacation are hilarious. I like him quite a bit. Do you know what I'm talking about right now?
I completely understand. I'm not convinced. Yeah, no, I completely get it.
Yeah, so don't reduce Aubrey to like a girl who's like just fucking some beef cake
She's fucking Chris Hemsworth. Yeah, and then like later in the movie her dad and mama like oh, they just cheat on each other all the time
It's terrible and it's like and they don't even care. It's like no, that's not sad. Yes. I agree. Yeah, I think what I
Definitely knew what I was watching. I watched this movie a year literally over a year ago
Not an excuse. I mean, it's it's like but they call it vacation as opposed to like that's why it's a little confusing for me
The first one is also called vacation. There's a scene in the movie. I got it and I got it when I wanted to explain
Why this is different than the original vacation? There's literally a scene where he does that no
What you're not getting is that you watched this movie a week ago and I watched it a year ago
I got it now. Of course. Yes, Clark, Griswold is that so in a year you're going to go,
man, that force awakens what a weird remake that was. Maybe I sort of viewed it as like a reboot
anyway, because I definitely look even now that you're telling me I'm like, Leslie Mann was playing
Audrey Griswold. Yes. And I get that, but that's not something that's really. It's terrible casting
Because when I see that one of the Audrey's looked like Leslie man in any way at home
It's kind of believable that he's rusty Julia Lewis doesn't look like the girl from either the other one
But they all have dark hair. Julia. They all have dark hair. Hey, maybe she died her hair
I'm saying that what's what started this whole thing is you got to kind of like let shit go
Especially with comedy the only thing that matters to me with comedy is did I laugh and I laughed quite a bit in vacation
Now, a comedy can be horrifically bad.
I think dirty work is a disastrously -made movie, directed by Bob Sagitt, who never directed
again.
It's a terribly -made movie.
I haul laughing all throughout it, so it's a great comedy.
You know, I'm saying you got to kind of go into a movie with an open mind about certain things
and know what kind of movie you're watching, and et cetera, and many people can't.
I'll try to do that.
I'm not sent to you. Listen, no, I will try to do that when I watch tremors five, which
is a remake of the first tremors, even though it's called tremors five. You have to know
I'm not vouching for anything in the tremors. I'm making fun of the fact that you don't
know the difference between a sequel and a remake. I got it. And of course, they go to
visit Chevy Chase, yes. But I did not remember Ed Helms playing Rusty until now, I think
about it. Yeah, of course he was playing Rusty. He did not seem anything like Anthony
Michael Hall, which was your point. Now I got any of the Rusties, but when you were saying
Rusty, I was thinking of the funny kids in the new vacation just because I, that's
how I picture. No, no, no, no, I was saying, I'm saying the young, you said during the
discussion, Rusty drinks the beer in the first movie. Yeah, I know that that's what Rusty
does. But to think of, to think of Anthony Michael Hall growing up to be Ed Helms makes me
a little sick. And maybe that's why I'm forcing it out of my mind before you got here today.
I came straight from work straight from work. I've had a single drink. And there was nothing
in that iced tea when you walked in except iced tea.
It's from Starbucks.
I don't know.
This is a weird movie.
Yeah, no.
Yeah, I drove here drinking an alcoholic beverage from work.
Folks, I mean, if the, if the, if the ending here this podcast doesn't prove my point that
tremors is a bad movie, forgive me for everything going on in the world, not remembering.
Oh, the top five points.
Dare pull the mother Teresa card on me.
This is when I walk out of vacation I go okay, I can flush that out of my head
I don't need to remember you told me for four months
I had to see it because it was so goddamn funny and then I finally see it
You don't even remember the fucking movie. Now again, I never I'm never insisting you must see vacation
I said it's way funnier than you'd think and you would say it is not just plug what do you got a plug?
well
If this were to go up before Sunday and it probably won't I'm doing a stand -up show at UCB
Sunday night in Sullivan and Sean O 'Connor show in LA in LA at UCB Sunset if you live in LA shows called those called
She's called chiral church church
The show is called church
No, I'll do them then all right. That's all that's coming right out. I'll be in Scotland for the Edinburgh Fringe Festival in
August
I'll be in Dublin for the comedy festival at the end of July come out and see those things Jota Rosa comedy on Twitter
The Patrick Walsh by Twitter Instagram.
You've been listening to We'll see you in hell presentation of the Fangoria podcast network,
which also by the way is launching next week my there might be this week when this comes
out my new fiction hard fiction column called some severe situations.
So keep an eye out for that.
This is produced by Thomas Defeo and executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment
for press opportunities advertising inquiries and information about we'll
see on how contact can at fangoria dot com