folks it's we'll see you in hell we're here in the back half of may
pat walsh and myself here not to talk to you about a specific movie today
but to talk to one of those rare guests we bring in we don't bring them in often but when we do
they are juicy and today i mean the only guests we've had are what crumholtz oj simpson david
crumholtz um kato caitlin we were the first interview with kato caitlin which was exciting
the bar is set very high that's true i love that everyone still knows kato caitlin's name and
his entire life was living in a pool house behind oj simpson we all still talk about him
and don't forget our upcoming interview series uh titled we'll see you in hell calling did he
didn't do it did he or didn't he the yeah that sounds like a good uh good stance to take i was
talking yesterday joe we got two joes here it's a pat and two joes joe
ramone is here but um next time you see on instagram an article about the diddy trial
check the comments and see how many men in this country are like she loved it it's deeply
disturbing i was just looking at that before this thing started people uh we won't we won't
get you into controversy here uh joe no you can oh just this is just so bizarre for me because i
feel like i'm watching my favorite show and like i'm not
supposed to join in so you'll have to know we want you to join if for a moment i get lost in
what i'm looking at right now because i i guess i want to start by giving a shout out to our mutual
patron uh jason patterson okay was the one who let me know on my patreon account that you guys
had brought me up and without that happening i wouldn't have known um not only about the shout
out but about your show i don't think yeah and i don't advertise and i've just listened i've been
binging the back catalog guys i've been enjoying it so i'm not supposed to join in so you'll have to
so much i've told you both that individually but thank you yeah thanks joe we greatly appreciate
that i mean uh and back at you i joe was telling me about your stuff your podcast and stuff when i
got on to watch it i realized that over the pandemic i had watched 90 of your content
without having any idea who you were i found one of those like uh it was nothing but trouble
it was like uh you know a 20 minute in -depth look at nothing but trouble and i love shit like that
i've seen it in the past and i'm not gonna lie to you again but i'm gonna say that like i never
would have left my house i never would have done anything with my life i was always seeking out
that kind of material but last night i feel like i watched the other 10 i mean these videos are like
they're gold like and it must be so rewarding like i i i guess my first question is do you when you
sit down to record 20 minutes about trial and error michael richardson and jeff daniels a movie
i saw in theaters opening night is there a part of you that goes is anybody gonna give a shit about
this that that was the genesis of the entire podcast that you've been doing ever since so i'm
channel uh yeah like especially those early ones and like the first three were you know gene walder
who has a relatively well -known but then i did shemp howard and following shemp i did jim varney
and i'm like this is it i'm gonna blow the lead and no one's gonna no one's gonna watch these but
i found the more like niche and unknown topics i went for the more the audience was there and
that jim varney one was the one that really kind of exploded well that's what drew me into the
channel initially and also thank you so much for the kind words i'm i'm floored to hear it from you
um oh absolutely and we're bad hosts can you tell us quickly your name what you do where your
channel is and then we'll get into the the talk my name is uh joe romano as joe called me in the
last uh shout out you guys gave me now joe ramone i run hats off entertainment on youtube if you've
have any
you
in movie retrospectives particularly dealing with 80s and 90s stuff you've probably been
suggested one of my videos at least and i do a lot of pieces just about kind of the forgotten
movies from around that time i try to profile movies that i feel deserve a little bit more
attention and we have a podcast as well uh called almost cult classics that's basically a spinoff of
some of the work i've done on the channel but it's since grown into so much more and honestly
that's been why i've loved your podcast
it kind of feels like i'm listening to us do our podcast you guys just hit so many of the same
points and as i was going through your back catalog i want to say it was this is way back
with hubie halloween i was going deep i was going through all the the episodes and joe had just
re -watched robin hood men in tights yeah and you guys get into a conversation that was damn near
verbatim to a conversation we had where on our podcast we typically pick a movie and then we
watch the director of the show and we're like oh my god i'm gonna watch this movie and i'm gonna
watch the director of filmography leading up to that movie and we did silent movie mel brooks
a silent movie figured out it's not one that people talk about my my co -host hadn't seen a
lot of the early mel brooks stuff and like we started the episode and my co -host was just like
dude mel brooks stinks yeah it was a big realization it was one of those like i woke
for me it was space balls it was sitting down as a grown man and watching space balls as a
massive john candy fan and just being like this stinks because you loved it as a kid right
i i adored it yeah i couldn't get enough of it the uh no but but real quick we appreciate the
kind words and it's uh i'm floored too because um you know when we first talked about you and
then you responded uh i was i was up in pennsylvania with uh as i referred to her my
my lady friend uh jamie and uh i was i remember this she was laying in the bed and i was standing
up looking at my phone and i was like great she's like what are you smiling about and i was like
this youtube usually there's no smiling in this bedroom none none and i said why why'd your
blindfold off uh so i how'd you shake the gag loose so i said this youtube channel i love hats
off entertainment uh we shouted them out i go i've been listening to this guy for years and he
responded he just dm'd me and i can't believe it and she's like that's so cool and i was like i
love this
like i love the channel so much so i'm a huge fan and the shemp thing is the reason i'm the huge
because i that was not the first video i saw i i found your videos very calming very soothing
i would put them on just before bed and i'd watch one and then the second one would play and i'd
slowly drift into sleep i found it extraordinarily calming almost meditative and the shemp one though
because i'm a huge fan of the shemp thing and i'm a huge fan of the shemp thing and i'm a huge fan of
i've said for 30 years shemp to me is the funniest of the three stooges and people are like what are
you nuts and i'm like he was my dad's favorite he's he's mo's brother right yeah and he's to me
he's so much funnier than mo he's amazing people go no curly i'm like curly's awesome but shemp
is like this unsung genius i haven't seen the shemp video i'll watch that right after we record
today it's great um but anyway i did i love i was a huge earnest fan as a kid how do those hold up by
the way like i haven't seen one of those in 35 years you know what's weird about those earnest
movies is that the one thing i always praise about them is that it's remarkable that disney
just plucked this nashville tv character gave gave him and the and the director john cherry just like
carte blanche make whatever you want make make this movie and not only that when they parted ways
they kept the character and the rights to him and so to this day they that disney has nothing
really to do with earnest but i guess funding really dried up so like eventually they went
direct to video and then that was too expensive so they went direct to video but only filming in
south africa so some of those like later like earnest goes to africa i never saw earnest goes
to africa that was that felt wrong to me it's legitimately that because yeah they were filming
in south africa so they were like well i guess we should just let's let's not mask this for
minnesota we might as well yeah are there any uh any racially questionable moments in earnest
oh plenty
there's that classic three stooges gag in it where at one point earnest has to disguise himself as
you know the belly dancing girl with the face mask and there's some brown face elements to it
as well but it's like you know i love i love those scenes when because jim varney not as earnest a
handsome man but of course like the the prince or whoever the villain is like that's the girl i want
bring that new one to me like let's get like it's that joke you've seen a million times before
yeah who's this striking beauty yeah it's it's in uh i think it almost not that it's a great movie
to begin with but wild wild west has that at the very end with uh when jim west does it and and
yeah kenneth brana is like oh you said you seductress like it's you're just like what is
this i don't remember anything about wild wild west but the spider well the spider do you know
the spider we must have addressed this before the spider famously is the thing the guy told
kevin smith to put into it the spider is the thing that kevin smith told kevin smith to put into it
the superman script yeah it was like why would he fight a spider john peters yeah and then he got
booted from superman and then wild wild west came out and kevin smith saw the trailer and he's like
well he got his spider he got it in there somewhere somewhere the man was obsessed yeah
the thing with earnest you know jim varney obviously we pluck today uh stunningly beautiful
19 year old girls from tiktok to be our actors can you even imagine today
plucking a 50 year old not particularly attractive hick and giving him like a 12
picture disney deal it's i mean it's madness to me yeah but they're funny he was funny
yeah there's a i actually heard that so when disney first acquired earnest uh or wanted to
go into business with him and john cherry they didn't know if they wanted them to write their
own script and i don't know if it was eisner at the time but he was like hey we've got this script
we can't really do anything with it you want to just put earnest into it and it was ace ventura
wow john john cherry was like no we'll try to write our own thing but that that ace ventura
script had been bouncing around for a lot there were rewrites uh rick moranis was doing it at
one point i think whoopi goldberg was attached they just couldn't figure out how to get it made
but i just find that so crazy that it was almost earnest p warrell pet detective no one would have
no one would have been better than jim carrey obviously that's an iconic performance but
i'd certainly be interested to see jim varney's take on ace ventura his delivery of i can you can
say earnest p warrell pet detective and like it does kind of resonate it makes sense the um i just
got the whole like the north american cockatoo yeah yeah yeah i got the entire hey vernon it's
earnest tv series which fits on one disc believe it or not guys uh is that how you got the girlfriend
joe you showed her that you had the yeah i have it displayed in the uh in the apartment in my
movies i usually that's how i get them back to the house right you know you want to see something
yeah
it's earnest i got it at a flea market for a dollar it was still wrapped and i was like what
a great find at a flea market that is amazing yeah um those those earnest movies the ones that
were not made by disney are whoever licenses them like like you always see them in bargain bins at
that uh like dollar stores like i think they're just very easily and there's that one dvd company
you'll get you guys will know they put like the paper they just put discs and paper sleeves and
like yeah bare bones and stuff like that so whoever's
um but there is a there is a documentary a feature documentary in the works i've joined
the kickstarter a while ago i don't know what the deal is with it but apparently they are
trying to tell his story on a bigger scale i've heard that yeah he was you know i know he's a
shakespearean actor and all that but um at least from my memory of ranking them as a kid my favorite
was goes to jail i thought that actually i imagine watching like that chewing on the pen scene today
i would still laugh goes to jail is the
is the white album of the earnest i agree i think it was a kid even i was like this
destroys earnest goes to camp like yeah and i liked camp but i also loved christmas uh but
and i think for me we while we did scared stupid on the show which didn't really hold up but i don't
know that i went beyond that in terms of actually watching the movies have you seen everything i've
seen all of them is there is there a lost classic we need to watch yes absolutely oh wow awesome
yeah earnest rides again
is uh one that i don't think they even knew how to market it because the poster there's two posters
the vhs release was just earnest with a crown on and the the other poster i've seen is just like
earnest face right up there with like confetti around him it's basically like an earnest type
indiana jones adventure and it does something that i think really aids earnest it gives him
a straight man character oh yeah in the form of it's weird that he never has
somebody rolling their eyes at his antics it's just him cut loose it's it's you know i'm a big
fan i've gotten into a lot of debate with people in the uk about the mr bean movies but i love that
97 bean movie because of peter mcnichol i think giving yes mr being a straight man to play off of
really aids the comedy joe i gotta say uh i'm glad you brought that up because i had a
demonstrative thought sitting alone
just two days ago came from out of nowhere where i was like my god i hate mr bean
it was so clear in my head i don't even know what made me think of it and i was like
i oh i remember what it was uh my buddy adam and i were talking about let's talk about famous
funny things that have never made us laugh that actually stink and we really went deep
into like the different members of snl casts and whatever and
i was thinking i kept thinking about that and i was like i should have said mr bean god damn it
uh please it was it was sitting with you like george costanza's jerk store line you were just
like oh i should have yeah i like rowan atkinson and i think his like stand -up pieces are very
funny and i think black adder is funny but man mr bean just well that's that's so i i don't think
he likes mr bean i think if you watch any interview with him he's just like yes you know we did it and
i would like to move on to other things
it just seems like it's it's much like jim varney it's one of these things where
the actor can't escape that role and with rowan it's got to be exhausting because it's worldwide
um and you know and those those mr bean socials get on tiktok like it's millions and millions of
views all they do is just recut bits from the show and the movies and it the popularity comes
from overseas it comes from china and so it's like did you see the thing he did on netflix
called man versus b yes no i heard about it at least that it's like all right i feel like he
wants to still do that type of physical comedy but getting away from was that just mr bean fighting a
b essentially half hour or feature film it was uh 10 minute episodes it was like yeah it was
serialized it was i actually really this came out at a time when like those curb episodes were like
hitting 50 minutes so it was nice just to have like
a 10 minute little but i feel like it was it was probably shot as a feature film and they're like
we gotta chop this up a bit every 10 years they put something out where it's a guy fighting a
little thing in his house you know mouse hunt yeah i'm sure i'm blanking now but you know there'll be
like one where he's got to catch a spider for two hours you know what i mean they do one of these
every 10 or 15 years well i don't know i know you guys are pat especially john hughes fans and i'm
fascinated by that and i'm fascinated by that and i'm fascinated by that and i'm fascinated by that
by the john hughes projects that never happened yeah and yeah one that he was hell -bent on getting
made in the i guess early to late 90s it was just called the b and that was the that was the concept
it was uh an architect was designing and working on a mansion a b comes in hijinks and so he
originally hires daniel stern to write and direct it or i'm sorry direct and star in it and that
falls through he meets with rowan atkinson and jackie chan
and i think hugh larry and it just i'm fascinated by like sorry the skies have opened up here in
philadelphia um i don't hear anything yeah i'm fascinated by post home alone john hughes and
just with that how that movie totally changed his career yeah what do you my little theory about
about that is that when john hughes who has written you know he's got an ego you can tell
by watching him in interviews and he always talked about how he writes
he can write five movies in the time it takes him to direct one so he was turning out a lot of
shit and by the end there the quality control was slipping a little bit obviously but i think the
fact that he chose not to direct home alone and that became far and away his most successful thing
like this giant juggernaut i think it probably made him feel a little left out of its success
and that made him triple down on kiddie movies and slapstick because he was trying to recreate it but
he's got more and more desperate they didn't have any of the home alone magic something like baby's
day out has none of the heart of of home alone uh that's just my theory i don't know but it's like
what he really did just abandon adults i would i would i would argue too though that and this
has not been documented as far as i know anywhere but i would argue that this is probably or
possible at least you know the the pc wave hit in the early 90s if you watch sitcoms of the early
90s particularly like a married with children or something irreverent from back then the jokes they
make about pc culture are very similar they could play now they're the same exact jokes
i would argue given the fact that in recent years you've seen this weird sort of post
uh posthumous backlash against john hughes and could you believe he put this in the movie and
can you believe there's a picture of a girl in her underwear but she's 60 whatever i would be
willing to bet that when the 90s hit and home
alone hit and all that part of it was maybe him just saying i can't make the edgy teen movies
they're not going to let me there's too much pushback i don't feel like fighting with them
i'm just going to go in the other direction and make the most milquetoast shit that's going to
keep the checks coming in you know what i mean yeah i mean he wrote flubber yeah i mean he like
he was putting he was using a pen name when you're like i don't know how you decided
which ones to not take credit for but like flubber um it started that started with uh
beethoven beethoven yeah beethoven was set up to be a john candy movie uh it doesn't happen but
it's beethoven works though because of groden well it's the same thing like it happened throughout
the rest of his career it was like studio when home alone came out hit success numbers that i
think broke records then all these studios were like what john hughes scripts we got in the drawer
that we can dust off beethoven happened to be one of them he saw what they were doing there in terms
of being like from the from the writer of home alone and said i don't want my name on it uh
make it edmond dantes and i think what you were saying about home alone changing i think you're
right because daniel stern put out a great memoir and he says that hughes was way more involved in
home alone 2 being on set being there being around being he said the home alone one you know not not
many people saw him he was there i think the day they shot the john candy stuff and a couple others
but he was very that says a lot to me yeah also too he probably wrote home alone thinking which
oh this one isn't for me i'm just writing this goofy little thing about a kid and when and then
it turns into this cultural phenomenon and he's like oh jesus i better get over there is i'm sure
you guys know this but chris columbus is hired to direct christmas vacation yeah shocker doesn't get
along with the star of that film and uh goes to john hughes and this is a point you know chris
columbus is very young it takes him a lot to have to go back to john hughes and say i can't do it
and john hughes is like all right well i got this other christmas script if you want to
hop onto this instead god what a i mean
that chris columbus must thank chevy chase being an asshole every day of his life yeah
and the other one was uh howard deutsch who was a protege of his so i learned from from your videos
that howard deutsch used to cut hughes's trailers edit them and that led to him direct becoming a
director which is kind of awesome yeah but um so he does pretty in pink and then he's gonna do
planes trains but then once they cast steve martin john hughes goes no i'm a huge steve
martin fan let me do it yeah pushes howie over to great outdoors that's one that worked out
obviously for for hughes but both good movies i mean when you go to research somebody like like
john hughes great outdoors whatever what is your research process because it's clearly not just
imdb trivia page and wikipedia i i've i've i've read those i used to have an office job i've read
every trivia section for every movie i've ever seen and because i love that shit but you always
dig up stuff that i didn't know and i've been studying this for 44 years so what uh is your
research process a big part of it is that i've been studying this for 44 years and i've been
is believe it or not uh digging through old newspapers i i go on newspapers .com i search
keywords and i just start digging and um because i mean that's the stuff that was actually reported
at the time and a lot of that same same with you like when i've discovered the imdb message boards
and trivia as a young film fan it was like oh my god this is amazing oh yeah it's so much of that
trivia that we took for fact and basis is just you realize complete bullshit yeah um it's just
like i remember when i did my bushwhacked video
with daniel stern and the the trivia there said this this film began as a spinoff starring marv
from home alone and like i'm like it just took me like five seconds to go through and like no
that's not it was made because they knew daniel stern appealed to that fan like they could tie
into the home alone fan base but at no point was it ever going to be a marv movie so it's just
newspapers have been great digging through old trade stuff and honestly i was in the back of
a library at the microfilm machine
that's what i always expected this when i when i when i saw myself credited as film historian on
one of those blu -rays which i've since had them change the it's now it's now hats off
entertainment's germany because i'm like i'm one of the reviews of the blu -ray referred to me as
critic joe ramone and i was like ah this isn't i'm not yeah i'm not i don't want to be tied to that
so i i that's what i felt like i felt you know to me film historians were uh twee jackets and
they talked about why uh the kubrick
made the curtains a certain color and one of his shots like that was film school to me
and i think for what i wanted to do is i just wanted to i think there's a story with every
movie you know every movie even the ones that have been dismissed have really great stories
and in particular the movies that like nothing but trouble like some of these movies that have
been universally hated and panned like there's a really interesting story there and yeah when i
set out to explore a movie it's usually it just starts as like a thread and i'm like
i did the mr magoo i was just gonna you know talk about that movie and then i'm like oh wait
this movie was boycotted by the blind federation of america then i start just digging there and
it takes it in a new direction i think that's most of the interesting stuff uh you know one
of my favorite musicians mike patton uh you know he he very much celebrates the unfound music out
there like that's a that he's that's a big part of his musical pursuit is digging through
crates in record stores to find the things that nobody is buying basically the unsung stuff and i
always find that to be the most interesting in a in a in a director's catalog in a band's catalog
the project where everybody goes and this is the one where he made a hard left turn and nobody knew
what the fuck he was doing i'm like i want to start there you know i never listened to neil
young in my life i started listening to neil young this week because i found mistakenly an
album called trans from
the 80s where neil young does like a robot synth album and i'm like that's interesting to me the
acoustic guy that's interesting to me so it it applies very much to what you're saying about
a nothing but trouble these weird movies that as you call them almost cold classics or also
it's not that bad right yeah these things that are out there that that there was a
you know i knew i was into nothing but trouble as a kid because i loved rap
music and digital underground was in it that's the reason i saw the movie and then i'm sitting there
expecting a sort of like who's the man or some kind of hip -hop comedy and i'm like what the
fuck is this that's the only appropriate reaction to nothing but trouble i mean everything being
made i saw it nothing but trouble at the dollar show i remember what is demi more doing and nothing
but trouble i mean there's a million questions coming off ghost by the way coming off ghost yeah
it's like i i that movie when i was a kid i was a kid i was a kid i was a kid i was a kid i was a kid i was a kid
there's a reason there aren't champ i'm sure there are channels i just don't get fed them but
the making of avengers endgame you know i don't give a flying fuck like that and it's not just
because i don't like those movies but we know how it happened they've made a hundred of these
they all cost 500 million dollars and make 501 million dollars and they're machines i want to
know who the hell thought nothing but trouble was a good idea well
in it well you know who decided we were going to play two parts each i need everything about that
i think your answer there at all it's all one man's name so that is the answer to all those
questions which is dan akroyd yeah it's it's really it comes down to his power coming off
ghostbusters and yeah i mean it's it's fascinating that i think there are there was a lot of studio
meddling there uh they were distracted by bonfire the vanities so there was there was a little bit
of a hands -off to it but i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't
know they changed that title very last minute uh and i think that hurt it i i really do i think
had the movie been titled vulcanvania it just would have given it more of kind of like a creepy
instead of like a screwball vibe nothing but trouble is an awful title for them terrible
terrible terrible title and then they released it along with i want to say it's silence of the
lambs it was one of those big movies that just like a double feature yeah you know uh we were
talking about judd app but pat's working with judd app and he's like i don't know i don't know
you know judd apatow said in an interview once uh you know he got when he got the cable guy he was
like that's it i made it i got the next jim carrey movie nothing's all uphill from here and uh and
then it flopped for jim carrey it flopped uh and i nothing but trouble very similar i mean think
about it it's like demi demi more coming off ghost her people and her are probably like let's
do something different now let's not get typecast what if we did something lighter something funny
great there's a comedy
you ready for this john candy dan heck right jeffy jade they're going this can't miss
i know i always feel bad for john candy because it's like he turned down lois tully there was
it was a bit more complicated than that i don't know if you ever really heard that story but he
wanted to play that part as a russian man with a lot of dogs he wanted to own a lot of dogs and i
think it was ivan reitman who was like it's just too much going on it was the right call oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah and uh i so i think him he was always regretted that
to a little because he much like pat you were saying with john hughes like it seemed like after
that he just accepted anything that came his way and he really did i it's a bummer now like whenever
i'm going out with a guy i'm going out with a comedy now and i'm it's like we need a 50 year
old really funny guy it's like there's nobody you know there's way less 20 year old funny guys now
there's none but there's there's nobody i mean it's like you're getting people there's josh gad
there sure is he gad i'm gonna write an expose about josh gad called cannot get you need to dig
into the amount of projects the man has announced that have never happened oh yeah well he's in the
new space balls i know that much that's his project yeah i don't i don't i don't know what
that ends up happening you guys know anyone involved i do know i know the director of
space balls it's in progress now so i lord knows what that's going to look like i don't know if
they're spoofing the the neck the last 30 years of star wars i would assume
but i mean how is josh gad the guy that gets moranis out of retirement i mean this isn't it
now i thought he was coming back no he so he one of the things he was trying to do i think it came
very close to happening until it got shut down was the honey i shrunk the kids reboot where he
was going to play the grown -up yeah the linsky kid uh joe johnson was returning to direct uh
pandemic i think was killed that yeah uh but i'm assuming he has the in there to get moranis
and space balls i would imagine so moranis was confirmed to come back for the tv show i remember
that that they announced it and then the show never as you said material but it's just what
devil you know hell spawned did josh gad sign a fucking blood contract i would say he's a studio
executive's idea of who american audiences want to see more of it's just right yeah and i you know
i mean i posted on twitter when space balls got announced but it was i went
through and screenshot all these articles where he announced things it was a reboot of gilligan's
island he was going to write and play gilligan and this is like 10 years ago so this won't happen
josh he was supposed to play sam kinnison in a biopic he was supposed to play roger ebert
alongside will ferrell in a russ meyer uh making of the beyond the valley of the dolls movie
yeah there's just been so many he's then that chris farley biopic they they that news came out
that's paul walter hauser right yeah now it is yeah the um
we had a moranis on uh one of my first shows i wrote for bob and doug it was the animated
adventure i wanted to ask you about that because i i know you're associated with it it was for
canadian television it was during the first writer's strike so it was like sketchily allowed
because it was canadian tv or whatever and i don't think i was in the writer's guild at that
time but he wasn't voicing his character dave thomas ran the show to this day one of the funniest
people i've ever met in real life he's he's he's weirdly one of the least remembered people of sctv
is he funny um and he told us he had moranis where there were still good friends there was
no bad blood between them um but dave i i well i don't know how much i should say about this but
he lost five million dollars of his own money trying to do a strange bruce sequel that moranis
fell out of so there was a little bad blood okay that sucks dude like you told me you were doing
this so now when the animated series comes around moranis says cool that's something and they were
accommodating him to such a great extent we'll record in your home and we'll record in your home
you don't have to leave your family etc and at the beyond the last second he dropped out
and we had dave coulier impersonate rick moranis's character and it was flawless nobody knew
but um yeah he might i don't know at first the story was he's got to stay with his family and
fantastic who can argue with that his wife passed away but it's a thing now where i feel like maybe
he just is it fear does he attach to things and then go i can't do this anymore i don't know but
i miss him yeah
last time i saw him was performing a country song on the today show because he had a country album
he did yeah he does these music albums that are the least funny thing that have ever existed and
i'll just he did a voiceover part on the goldbergs by the way he did do that oh okay he voiced dark
helmet uh it wasn't it was a body double but he did the voice but also too oh it's funny because
i was just joe we were talking yesterday that i was i was gonna buy the streets of fire uh uh 4k
what's his name that starred in it the guy from eddie and the cruisers oh yeah michael yeah michael
appare on the wikipedia page they have a bunch of quotes from him about making streets of fire
rick moranis is in it and they're like it's like michael appare on rick moranis and he's like
he was a little shit uh all he did was make smart ass comments and where i'm from you punch a guy in
the fucking face for that but i wasn't allowed so whatever i would i get it now but anyway yeah
i was gonna say he's a good guy he's a good guy he's a good guy he's a good guy he's a good guy he's a good guy
rick said that their first meeting rick said to him so are you a real tough guy or you just play
a tough guy in the movies yes yeah all right we just we just did a walter hill episode on our
podcast so that came up yeah hilarious a lot of those comedy guys were just such pricks you know
to each other and the ego's going crazy especially the 80s like have you read i'm sure you have um
it's a it's the the movie about like 80s comedy or the book about 80s comedy wild and crazy guys
yeah like the the amount of just blind ego and and people fighting and and and taking shots at
each other well we watched i miss it i mean now nobody will say anything you did an interview
like so i heard you had a hard time working with so -and -so i'd like to talk about something else
please that's everybody like you never get juiciness we watched that saturday night live
movie and i i said i was like i i always admired the guy i watched that movie i'm like
i i would have strangled andy kaufman if i was around him like the the annoyance
and the ego and the arrogant like get out of my face man yeah like oh my god i can't even imagine
what it was like to deal with i joe by the way i think i think they ripped that movie the ending
off from your real life because i was i've listened to you on pete's uh podcast where you
talked about how when you know the the world opened back up and you're eating lunch outside
in new york and you're like this is what new york is to me that was like the thesis of that entire
movie at the end when young little 14 year old lauren michaels
was like you know i want new york to be i went saturday night live to represent all of these
all these moments in new york i do know jason uh schwartzman jesus christ i do know jason
reitman a little bit and i have done one or two things with him it sounded fishy maybe he stole
it from me he has been in my car jason reitman has been in my car i also love the end of that
movie when uh oh quick quick everyone let's get a photo before we begin it's like they all run to
the stage and get the exact photo that that classic iconic stairway photo it's like i know
reitman been in your car joe what's that why has jason reitman been in your car because we were
friendly and knew and when i lived in la i never introduced him to you i knew better you sure
didn't uh no he used to come to roast battle every week he loved roast battle and i judged it a lot
and we became friendly and then he did a little mini doc that's somewhere on youtube about roast
battle he came to my house and interviewed me and then one time me and annie letterman were
leaving roast battle and going to to to the whatever
that that jewish uh canters yeah and he was gonna come he was like yeah i want to go and he
came in my kia okay probably first and last time in a kia for mr reitman yeah
joe what are your top five all timers oh let's see well my favorite of all time is the poster
behind you planes trains and automobiles i figured it was yeah yeah it's it's it's great we have a
i mean our childhoods must have been identical i don't know your age but i know and yet i'm here
we have two joes from pennsylvania and yet you know no i mean when when the movies you pick
are like the you know i have definitely seen like trial and error more than citizen kane probably
like i would just rent these comedies cons and at the looking back i was studying how to write
comedy but um they're they're so unfairly reviewed especially then you know like everything was just
missed the only people who gave it any credit were cisco and ebert campaign i remember was was
on cisco's 10 best list ebert gave it like three and a half out of four um well because trial and
error they both gave it two thumbs up it's like they they they recognized okay maybe this isn't
designed for me a 60 year old like film historian but it's funny like we've lost that ability to
even say yeah it's a really good comedy that movie very solid cisco and ebert were midwest
east coast right right film critics and i think that's why i think that's why you look at that
la audience watch anybody do comedy and jokes in front of an la crowd in an award show that
isn't one of their own they sit there with their arms crossed you know joe coy didn't have the
funniest opening monologue ever at an award show but but for for christopher nolan to look literally
like like joe coy made a holocaust joke or something when he made a joke about the length of
of oppenheimer they they they sit there with this attitude of oh you think you're funny and
that's why they malign these comedies so much it's like they're sitting there with a challenging
stance to begin with yeah yeah exactly right i watched cisco and ebert give a i believe two
thumbs up to out to sea and it's just like it's it's but when you like you look at that you're
like what like how did that uh you know again i i heard you guys recently talk about the post
i think there's some of them are better than others but i like odd couple too i enjoy i do as
well i don't like grumpy or old man and out to sea to me is i wish it had not had happened but
it did but hey i love grumpy and grumpier and then the other ones are all kind of you know
i implore you to revisit grumpier i'll do it today yeah it's not uh it's not as good as you
remember but well i i like odd couple too a lot and it's uh howard deutsch yeah so it that's that's
it's just yeah it's but so many of those movies that just kind of slipped through the cracks that
you realize like why is this so unfairly maligned like why why are these movies punch lines and why
are they what let like ishtar is a movie that now like finally now people are being like oh that
it was just a punch line because it was in the press and it was a big bloated disaster but as
far as like being in a watchable movie it's not yeah um it's not great but it's not like on on
the par with some of those really bad you know disasters of course i mean the biggest turnaround
i've seen lately like that is clifford uh all the alt comedy people are like this movie is kind of
genius and it you know i i loved it as a kid i um there's not a lot of rediscovery of them though
because they're not on streaming and they never get upgraded certainly not to 4k let alone blu -ray
like you can't trial and error is probably going to be stuck forever on dvd yeah and i still have
that yeah like that half -ass so it's it's i didn't think we get nothing but trouble for the
longest time and then um not that i think i had i had any pull but when when i come across a movie
like that that has no blu -ray release i really do make the case for it in the video and uh there
have been a few instances where it's like not that i've ever been credited to it but i think i have
at least driven a conversation and shown a desire that people want to see this movie do i need to
is that what i'm picking up from you guys it's one i picked at random because i watched that
like the second before i fell asleep last night but it is a really funny movie it's the same team
as my cousin vinnie and it's you know three -fourths as great as that movie which is really good i mean
it's essentially the kramer i mean he's playing kramer okay i'll kind of more of a mild kramer
but it's it's great yeah he jeff daniels plays a a lawyer who oversleeps uh after a bachelor party
that his best man michael richards threw so he
ends to be him for the initial hearing and then it just he has to end up going with it and it's fun
the uh that's interesting um along the seinfeld lines one of the videos you did that i loved
where when you talked about all the failed seinfeld sequel not sequels but unofficial
sequel uh curse files yeah the curse files i loved seeing all the stuff about the jason
alexander shows that i was unaware of
the kramer the michael richards show in particular i was very sad that it didn't work because i was
like this seems funny this just seems kind of like kramer goes west and becomes a private
investigator like this seems like a funny show and you know i followed them all but i watched
the first episode of everything and i was like oh the only one that really worked was watching
ellie actually everything julia louis -dreyfus did new christine and all that those were all good
shows um but yeah they kramer as a private detective should have worked absolutely
yeah if you i really recommend his recent book he gets i have it on audible i haven't listened yet
he gets into what went wrong with that i wish it you know i mean that's the sad reality is sometimes
i do these projects and then a book like that comes out that really adds some context that i
could have used but yeah he basically just said like it was those seinfeld writers spike ferriston
and a couple others who are like no come on man it'll be great we got it like come on it's gonna
be there's a no -brainer like and he really was never quite into it because he just thought it
would be kind of a you know it would be kind of a it would be kind of a it would be kind of a
and then slowly but surely it was almost like the gervais thing in extras where it's like
they have this good idea and then it just becomes this generic kind of yeah sitcom that got away
from them and you know not only that then at a certain point they're like no we're gonna call
it the michael richards show and he was like but my it's i'm not playing like why yeah yeah
we'll call it michael richards pi but i'm not a private investigator no you are we've got your
license and then he turns down monk as a result yeah he turned down monk yeah
oh he turned down monk yep monk monk was going to go on abc with him in the lead and that
experience kind of factored into him turning it down it would have bombed it and then and then abc
drops it ends up at usa with uh shalhoub and that should have seen monk but from the clips i've seen
shalhoub is monk yeah that that should have happened exactly like that that's that's that
was the right move the um i uh um i i'm surprised maybe he's turned it down but i don't get the
impression he has
i am shocked that that and it's it's a thing that woody allen has said where he's been in
interviews and somebody will say why don't you do more acting and he's like nobody asks me
yeah he goes i would love to play like a walter mathau grumpy man next door or whatever he goes
i think i'd be good at it and he's like nobody ever asked me jason alexander they wanted woody
allen for richard drivers's part and what about bob which would not have worked i would i would
well yeah it would not have worked um but i'm shocked that we don't seem
more stuff with jason alexander where he's cast this guy as a guy that flies off the handle
like what are we doing that's the thing i've really come to love about your podcast is you
guys are very um vocal about these same six people that we see a lot of in movies and it's
it's it's hard like that there's this new um the office kind of spin -off show coming out called
the paper with dom l gleason and it's like man that those that are
remake of the office like part of the reasoning that really worked was all those people felt like
real people and you didn't know any of the cast for the most part and it was like gave us fresh
faces and launched careers and it's just such a shame even corral had hair plugs on the first
season of that show yeah but i'll say this i'll say this in defense of that show uh when you watch
the original office it's very funny obviously and and everybody there is very comedically gifted
you get dom all gleason of course because he is if nothing else is hilarious i mean more to be
funny the and by the way the paper what is this the 17th thing named the paper how many things
are they going to make called the paper it's so bizarre to me it's like ricky gervais one of the
biggest comedians on earth and originated the role steve carell one of the funniest performers on
earth took the reins
where would they ever think you don't need a comedian for that role it makes no sense at least
a person with a sense of humor unless he's been hiding it from us for his entire career also too
nobody knows who the fuck dom hall gleason is no unless you watch movies they think it's a big get
that the people the studios think that's a big get no one in the world cares i always ask myself
does my mom know this person's name right and if not you're not getting any financial gain from
casting i can't i can't imagine
to teach a boomer the name domo it's just it's not gonna happen no my guess is this with with
that casting and i'm being serious my guess is they brought in spader at the end of the american
office run they saw that spader could be funny who was a guy that always played somebody sort
of straight and sinister and they probably thought who's like a new spader type well
dom all gleason maybe let's give that a shot what's just got up to we got we got just got on
the phone
uh okay and i now we cut you off you're yeah i cut you off uh two through five
oh two is probably jurassic park beautiful that was my favorite for years such a that that was
an important movie to me as a kid because that was the first movie i started reenacting with
action figures that was like the first time i really felt like i could yeah take ownership of
the scenes uh your little uh richard attenborough with the kung fu grip yeah no you know what's
they never gave us richard attenborough but they gave us nedry they gave us a wayne knight action
figure no no that is weird isn't it uh i'm gonna buy that today i'm gonna buy the wayne knight
action figure there's a couple of like since the lion shirt remade like recently but there's an
original he's got like a red sweater on but it's it's yeah it doesn't it doesn't look much like
him but it's so cool to see a dennis nedry uh i think three is probably uncle buck
sure yeah it's it's so hard to i like to space out the john hughes but i i just love uncle buck
and four i would say is the goonies sure and five a big trouble in little china
there you go very specific they all kind of feel in a similar
yeah were you a video store kid oh yeah for sure yeah yeah i was i was a hollywood video kid oh
was good i've been there good i worked at blockbuster and i still remember i i charged
this 60 year old man he had like a 299 late fee and he was yelling at me it went on and on and on
and that now it would be a classic karen video he went on and on and on i'm 616 at the time
and then he goes well i'll take he had a weird accent he goes i'll take my business to hollywood
then they're happy at hollywood you walk through the aisles they're happy at hollywood i was like
sir go to hollywood video then jesus god i also had a local independent store i think it was called
superstar video but it was one of those ones where you could if you angled yourself just right you
could see under the beaded curtain the porn section yeah yeah our our porn uh our mom and
pop porn uh store was family video it was called it's like back here we got stuff for the kids and
then in the back something for mom and pop i was like don't don't call it family video with a porn
section well you know this is the reason that
you know
every porn store had cowboy doors to the point like why was that the universal we just agreed
we all just agreed i don't know there's something about i think that style that makes men want to
just walk through it's i think it yeah promotes men family video because i used to rent porn from
family video uh they had mirrors like it was almost like a touch of you or whatever that lady
from shanghai like the entire room was mirrored so that they could make sure kids didn't go in
but all of a sudden they were like oh my god i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
but all i felt when i went in there was like any any movie i picked up they were zooming in to see
the title or something it was very awkward i was like i don't like them watching me while i'm in
here we would do a trick where you take because because at one point in the video stores they
they the tape was in the case on the shelf like then they switched that because of theft
but we would take like you know goonies or something like that sneak into the porn section
take goonies out of the case take debbie does the neighborhood out of that case
put that into the goonies case go up and if you were lucky they wouldn't check the tape
and yeah look like you were renting goonies and then some poor bastard oh fucking rock hard gets
home and finds goonies inside his porno tape goonies is a great name for a porn store i mean
now goonies means gooning means edging for the new generation oh well all right that's another uh
belated sequel they've been threatening for 30 years at this point it's apparently confirmed
and happening right now that there's a lot of news right now that it is actually happening
and that they're all but the weird part is is like so chunk is coming back jeff cohen is a lawyer now
he was my lawyer for a little while and he looks nothing like chunk he's extraordinarily thin
and fit more like hunk am i right yeah but i mean i i wouldn't be surprised if brolin came
back i mean brolin you know you know well i'm almost positive knowing how hollywood works
and i respect them and understand the studio system that the movie will not center around
their children that uh we we we don't care at all about it's not going to have anything to do with
those characters and then they'll show they won't show up at the last like 10 minutes no no it'll be
totally how many times do you think that stranger things has been mentioned in discussions about the
goonies movie seriously like it's got a yeah yeah how long do we have before it's the stranger
things with their kids i think they're going to wait about six years
before they do some kind of age up time jump but do you remember this is so wild
we all forget that when the force awakens came out none of this had been done yet this was all new
i remember sitting in the theater and there was the reveal that kylo ren was han solo
and princess leia's son and it was like whoa that's really cool man like it wasn't even in
our heads they're going to do something like that and then they're going to do something like that
something real interesting with this yeah i was like this exactly and then yeah but then now it's
it's prototypical that that's it's it's every movie is it's the kids and and like you said
they show up in the last seven minutes or whatever josh gad will play son of barth in space balls too
i would assume oh you're probably right yeah no he must i actually imagine or son of dark
they're not putting him in a space suit no i think he's going to be the son of dark helmet
i think he's gonna i think he's that high on himself
and he's going to be dark helmet he's going to be young dark helmet there i i would bet my life on
that and if he's not young dark role i would if he's doing both jesus christ well separate at birth
guess what if he's doing both this is what i was going to say if he's not young dark helmet i bet
you he's going to be young lone star because the gag will be my dad was this you let yourself that's
funny han solo type and i'm kind of a mess but uh but they can't they can't put 90 something
brooks in prosthetics at this point and expect him to walk on his knees though i don't think
that's going to happen my guess is they still have him play the yoda character yeah maybe like
in motion capture or something like kind of put his face on the guy that plays gollum you know
have you seen the uh space balls the animated series have you ever looked into that it's one
of the worst things i've it looks like it was made on flash it's terrible it's awful what year
oh this it was on g4 so whatever the the height of g4
was i want to say like 2005 or four maybe around then any of the original cast voicing anybody
bill palman no not bill palman i think daphne i think she was there i got zuniga i gotta pull it
up uh a comic you guys might know named tino insana was voicing barf character actor uh
and mel and uh yogurt has a female a wife named yenta so it's very uh
the humor is the humor is just so great that's in the cast in the cast list in the google search
uh reno romano as bill pullman they didn't put the character
tino asana as john candy yeah
uh d bradley baker from whose line is it anyway right no diedrich baker right
now i just later no d bradley i don't know who this guy is but yeah mel brooks is as joe said
daphne as joe said and joan rivers came back oh okay wow unless this cast list is incorrect
to speaking of barf and candy again to close my candy loop from earlier i was talking about how
you know there's no actors to go out to but my dream my wish that i was working during that time
because you were saying he agreed to everything and that's where i come in like i'd get i'd get
him to be in whatever movie i made because he did seem like he would just say yes to any comedy and
uh and then suddenly uh sarah dakier as her kind of super hero like that uh the you know the main
i heard ughi
lev in an interview talking about a movie that i mean i love john candy but even when i have never
ever sat through it uh speed zone oh i've seen speed zone that's cannonball run three yeah yeah
and but it's crazy when you like that came out the same year as uncle buck and it's something
else who's harry crumb like same year is that he and he did speed zone and eugene levy like
said that john candy called him it's like hey we got this we got this script it's not very
good but come on come do it we'll hang out for a few months we'll have a good time like
who cares it's not like he genuinely just seemed to enjoy hanging with his friends and
it's kind of as i've gotten older i really started i've changed my tune on the adam sandler
stuff because i've seen a lot more as that i just see a guy who wants to make movies with his
friends and hang out in exotic locations and it's kind of i get i a hundred percent get that
but why not make it funny too you know the funniest people on earth
just make it funny
make it funny but but maybe that's the thing maybe they're like look guys here's the formula
we shoot it right up the middle we're not offending anybody it's gonna make a lot of
money it's gonna be cheap and one of the reasons it's gonna be cheap is because it's gonna be easy
because we don't have much to do here so maybe that's just all it and i get that christ these
guys are pushing 60 they're like yeah i don't want to fucking yeah you know i'm not climbing
the mountain anymore did you see that uh david spade's going was going on one of the podcasts
and he revealed that he got pitched tommy boy too a few years ago uh that was would have been
focused on their sons yeah i saw that with uh madness it was theo vaughn play those parts
the sons yeah i mean josh josh gad it's always gad um yeah i i also saw that akroyd on your
on your video yeah that akroyd wanted to do a great outdoors sequel without candy that's like
that's not happening what are you with
with what it's like it's it wasn't even that big a hit so like to and you're taking away the key
element i mean candy's it yeah akroyd's hilarious in that movie as far as i know he wanted to call
it the great outlaws and it was supposed to be about like one of his daughters was now marrying
someone and they had to go on the run from the something like that yeah yeah i also really
appreciate in your great outdoors review that you call out the pathetic it's awful romance subplot
between the teenagers it destroys and you nailed something that i was never able to
to pinpoint why i hate it so much is that they use the same little score in every one of those
scenes it's the same exact score to me and oh yeah no i was just going to say i don't i don't
i don't know if in john hughes's script if that was something that got more fleshed out i i know
he wasn't happy with the final product of the great outdoors i always took the teen love story
in that which is terrible but i took it as to me the great outdoors to me feels like the bridge movie
on hughes between what he was doing and and planes trains because planes trains was a weird thing at
the time because this is the teen movie guy and now he's doing a thing with no teens i felt like
the great outdoors was something he wanted to do with an older cast and thought well my brand is
this so i've got to slip in something for the 16 year olds with this room and it didn't fit and it
didn't need to be there and you know he wanted it to be more of a family comedy and and but
my question is you are still to this
day considered the finest writer of teenage romance and comedy you are still referenced
as the gold standard why just abandon your skills for one movie it doesn't make any sense
yeah like that that was the most generic you could have seen that subplot on saved by the bell
and it probably would have been funnier to be honest it drags the movie to a whole i know john
was very unhappy john hughes with the great outdoors and career opportunities were two of his
scripts that he felt were not accurately represented on the screen and i think that's
one of the reasons why i think it's so important to be able to be able to be on screen yeah uh so i
don't know if that again that was like right before home alone so i i really i'm again i'm
fascinated by the man as the producer this mega kind of holly because i've i've even heard stories
where it's like he he would send scripts to people and he would go yeah just go to my office on the
on the fox lot no one's there but the script will be on the desk like he had offices he never visited
yeah he just i mean he really ruffled some feathers in the business because he didn't want to be on a
leave chicago and it's it's admirable in a lot of ways but when you look at what finally like
when he finally called it quits it was just that like they were really pushing back on that
that the system he had developed to film in his native chicago and yeah as what you talk about
after listening to my uncle buck commentary he liked to film in schools he would repurpose the
office space in schools to use his production offices and the gymnasiums would become sound
stages i mean very cost -efficient
very unique way to do movies but there's a certain point where i think they really pushed back on that
well and i think that answers the question we were all posing and entertaining earlier which is
why did he start writing these benign uh kids movies and it's like that's that's probably why
he's like well yeah i can't do it the way i want to do it so here you go i learned to keep the
checks coming in this this always fascinated me when i learned this that vince fawn uh who i do
love yeah yeah
even i just saw nonas i don't know if you guys are going to cover nonas but
i'm going to watch it we we should do nonas i want to see it and that's also the same producer
alex garcia as friendship and uh as as a restaurant you know restaurateur i think you'll
have some interesting things to say but how was it by the way do you want to tell us your
take on it before we watch it you know i i think it was advertised and marketed as kind of like
one of those book club movies but i i think it's quite a bit better than that like i think it's
i think it's yeah i i just like vince vaughn you know it's he's someone i've come to i heard you
guys on a long episode from a long time ago review freaky and you kind of echoed a lot of
what i feel about him but vince fawn from chicago apparently sought out john hughes
post his retirement and the two of them became really good friends and uh yeah he he i want to
say delivered one of the eulogies at john hughes's funeral uh but he really i would love to talk to
because he really got in there and got to know him right as the person and i just i'm like was
there no conversations there where vince was like dude just give me one of the scripts like let me
yeah let's do something it's such a problem to me how little there is about about candy and hughes
it's like there there's information but like it's not the stuff i want you know i want to know about
each movie and what they thought and what the experience was and i i guess just stuff wasn't
covered as in -depth at the time maybe i don't know
well i do know that they they they they planned far more movies than they made
yeah i think a big part of their collaborative nature was they would just
hang out real late at night chain smoke cigarettes and talk about scripts and movies and plan things
that never ended up happening and that's that's the sad part he had a stallone candy project going
right there were basically neighbors yeah bartholomew versus neff that
uh hughes later tried to do with schwarzenegger and stallone because hughes became one of those
planet hollywood investors later right in the 90s so yeah there was this reached the rock
hughes's last movie no you know what someone we have a po box for i'll have it somewhere
for the podcast and someone just sent me a vhs copy of it i was working at blockbuster when it
came out and my hands were shaking i was so excited it was like a john hughes like indie
shows about and it became of course his last you know uh sole writing credit it's it's a very very
bad movie very bad yeah he was so checked out by the end and i think a lot of those even like
drill bit taylor was a script that they right dug up of his that he wanted to be credited as edmund
dante's on and you know it's uh it's tough because the guy had such a great handle on
character and so many of those movies work because the
characters are so strong and the casting and i i'm also fascinated by the deleted scenes and
things like that and for years you know i'd heard about those as i'm sure you guys did those planes
trains deleted scenes this legendary cut and that's when i made my video about it i went
through this is like probably like november of 2020 i want to say yeah i put that video out
just that was sent to me at the time i remember that but that was like if i had to like look at
like the ones that really hit big that was one that for some reason really got but steve martin
had posted about it and paul hirsch the editor posted it was just it was getting a lot of
attention and as a result i was contacted by someone at paramount that was like you know we
want you to know we've we found some of the footage and apparently the hughes family has
archives and work print vhs tapes and i think for all of his movies they have that stuff i think
they're a little protective of it yeah but
did you consider reaching out to um the candies kids i don't know if hughes kids are alive and
well or what's going on there they are i have talked to john hughes's son i have had a couple
of interactions with the candy kids but they're very um involved in this ryan reynolds doc on
candy and so i think they're a little their lips are kind of tight on that and and they want to
which again it's people always ask me like what's going on with that i'm like i'm not i'm not
i don't i don't have any well my uh you know i i guess i would put him between an acquaintance and
a friend colin hanks who uh i i haven't talked to in a bit because he was working on that but i i
might shoot him a message today and be like when is this happening because he he and i must have
very similar taste too he was doing a queens of the stone age documentary he's one of my favorite
bands but they just never came out or else you know i don't think i missed it i would have i i
know it's so i know it's it's it's happening it's still happening i think it's in post right now
i know okay great i will also say that uh i have a friend paul myers uh mike's brother yeah has
written a john candy print biography that is coming out in october excellent it's there have
been a couple of like uh self -published john candy think this is the first like really in -depth
john candy biography our friend matt mccarthy gave me a or loaned me a biography on him that
just wasn't good yeah i mean there's there's a couple there's laughing on the outside which
was written many years ago
yeah it's and it was it's weirdly like harshly critical of him yeah yeah in what in in what in
what way just like like it shits on every decision he made in every movie he made but
it's like even the undisputed classics he's like very critical of it's weird and it's not in depth
and it's like heavy on canada stuff where you're like that's not really what i'm here for you know
it's just not a good book i sent pat a uh someone on youtube
finally uploaded this missing who's harry crumb scene uh that was used in cable edits of the movie
it's it's it's like man is that such it's poorly timed and and executed it's really strange
it's a bad scene yeah what what happens in the scene i want to see this joe it's a it's i'll
send it to you it's a four minute scene where they're in a wine cellar where there's thousands
of bottles of wine it's annie potts and john candy you know what's coming yeah it's like when you see
a seltzer bottle in the background of a three stooges short you're like that's that's getting
some point i'm on board already you watch you watch for four full minutes there's one funny
candy line i would say but the rest is just very dry boring conversation then at the end he's like
you know finally gonna open a bottle and you're like here we go finally and then all the wine
comes in but it's like this slow motion like the wine cascading down it looks kind of beautiful
but there's no comedic element to it at all like they don't even cut in candy going like
yeah like that would at least help
i will say that the final line it is pretty funny it's it's now the room has flooded so
that's how i knew about this scene is in the next shot in the movie you could see his pants are
stained like up to the knee and people are like what's that for so the wine is up to his knees
and he looks down just goes red wine that's not gonna come out like you know it's just that classic
it's like that whole scene was just to give candy that line and it was you know well it's like that
scene in plans trains where he shows he picks up uh steve martin in the truck and he's got a black
i think you know the movie should probably tell us how he got a black eye but they used to not care
at the time now they would just you know put some digital makeup on well and i think at the time
they didn't even realize yeah they were like we're i've heard the amazing thing about planes
trains and automobiles the ending do you know how that happened i would say at this point i know
everything okay maybe not as much as you but i feel like i've i've done all my research on
well so the amazing thing about the ending of planes trains and again i apologize if you know
originally as it ends when steve martin walks into that train station to discover dell sitting
there the what are you doing as filmed it was going to be that was his home train station and
he walks in and finds dell sitting there still following him and creepy almost yeah so that
outburst of dell what are you doing here it's not meant to be like i didn't know that yeah i had
this epiphany and came back what they did was paul hirsch
they
screened that ending people laughed at it yeah and they went back and paul hirsch the editor found
that footage of steve martin on the train just laughing and thinking to himself he didn't know
he was being filmed for that that was just them waiting in between shots paul takes that
restructures it to make it look like neil has this epiphany reverses the footage of the train
pulling out of the station and make it look it's pulling back in and then we get it making it look
like steve martin yeah i knew that
he was following him home which i agree it if it doesn't play as comedy it plays like single white
female they cut it split second what happens is steve martin opens the door he walks in he trips
over the trunk yeah so i also read so that but but the stuff was still in there of you you still
had him ultimately we're would have we're supposed to have empathy for candy right but you still had
Right. Like it was still my wife's dead and all that.
And he still brings him home. Right.
All that was still the same. It was just the I mean,
but honestly, like that completely changes the thesis of the film in a lot of ways
that Steve Martin realizes that on his own.
And yeah, that just it it does something in that character.
It makes it better. Yeah. Richer. Yeah.
And there's also a much more that whole scene was much longer as well, I believe.
Correct. Yeah. They involved monologue.
Yeah. And that Steve Martin documentary on Apple, he pulls out the script
and goes through it. And it was it was quite a bit longer.
And but again, did you did you guys see those deleted scenes from that they found?
Yes. The first the first 20 minutes were worthwhile.
Then it got kind of repetitive. Yeah.
You see that cab scene and the plane scene where they sit together
and the brownie scenes always a classic. I had seen that on TV.
That one, that one, the initial of them sitting there when he's talking about
about, you know, nobody wants a blabbermouth, you know, that whole thing.
That was great. And then the backseat of the cab,
there was a lot of stuff in the backseat of that, like punk rock.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's what that's what I realized once I started to see that footage.
I'm like, OK, these legendary John Hughes movies that are four hours long.
It's not necessarily a tight, good four hours.
It's just kind of I mean, it's it's a lot of what today is accepted as comedy,
which is that improv and riffing. Yeah. That he just encouraged them to do.
Today, a four hour movie, they'd edit it down to two.
You know, like he got it down to ninety one.
Like like I admire that about him is that there's very little fat on his movies usually until the end of his career, of course.
Yeah, I think Planes Trains, though, I mean, I love it again.
Favorite movie, but it does at a certain point, like it just takes off and it doesn't breathe.
It's it's very quick. I had never seen it theatrically till they did a big Thanksgiving night screening here.
They did it with Hannah and her sisters. It was kind of the most it was the night before Thanksgiving and it was so awesome.
But you feel it, you feel like that you feel that switch where the movie like that everyone's been enjoying this character comedy
and there's plenty of laughs and everybody's into it.
But right around the time they get in that car together, you know, that that the that leading into that like half hour
where Candy's in the devil outfit and they're going between you're going the wrong way and you're drinking all that.
It's it's relentless. It's just like a freight train.
Like did you ever hear the story?
Yeah.
About that devil costume.
We went on behind the scenes.
No.
So Planes Trains is going over budget behind schedule.
And one of the Paramount execs is like, all right, I guess I got to go out to the set and see what's going on.
The night before, Candy had had that idea.
Like, what if we cut to me as the devil?
And John Hughes is like, love it.
Let's get we'll get the wardrobe people to put together.
So this Paramount executive shows up and John Candy's dressed as a devil.
And he's like, what the fuck does this have to do with the Thanksgiving road trip movie?
What are you guys doing over here?
And I love that.
It's like an Amazon rising that moment.
It is so out of nowhere and brilliant.
It's an it's like a costume you'd get on Amazon.
It's the cheapest devil costume.
There's no, you know, there's just nothing to it.
And then the my buddy Scott and I always laughed about that sequence, too, because when they what you just said, Pat, it's out of nowhere when they turn to skeletons because they're so scared.
It's such an outrageous gag in the middle of a completely grounded film.
And you would almost.
Think that you would like someone would have been like, oh, you know what?
We're doing the skeletons gag.
The devil thing might be too much like in the same scene, but there's no, it's perfect.
It works.
I'll tell you from seeing it.
The actor in a sold out house.
The biggest laugh of that movie is him in the.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It's it's building, building, building.
And then the crowd goes insane when you see that.
You know, everybody in that audience has seen the movie before.
But it's the what's their reactions to it's it's candy.
Does that have the laugh?
I like that.
And then I have a I have a painted.
A poster framed poster of him in the mask doing that face.
Really?
Oh, that's great.
It's it's an all timer.
It's a it's a great film.
Well, Joe, this was.
Awesome.
It was really nice to sit here and talk with you.
Yeah.
You want to join our podcast?
Well, I was really natural.
I was telling Joe the next kind of step for me on the channel is I want to do interviews.
That's I've done some of these Blu -ray commentaries now, and I've interviewed enough people.
I'm like, you know what?
I just want to start.
I'm so tired of, like, watching these interview channels with people that aren't asking the right questions.
And so but I need to start, like, getting some content out there.
So I would love to have you guys on hats off.
Talk about the podcast, because I really I do mean it's become my my go to film podcast, and it's just delightful.
And I love that you guys bring this industry experience and perspective, but you do it with reverence.
And even if you have friends or connections involved in these movies, you just you handle it with.
With such charm and humor.
And it's great.
Thanks.
Thank you, Joe.
That means a lot to us, especially coming from somebody with your steep knowledge and a guy that we're also fans of.
And also somebody nobody's ever referred to us as delightful.
I've been referred to as delight less.
No delights.
Joe, plug away, please, for the.
Yeah, please tell us everything.
Well, I'll start.
And I talked about it last week.
I'll start by plugging Joe's excellent, very informative, very entertaining commentary on the new fantastic looking 4K of Uncle Buck, which I hate to quote Amazon as a price, but currently is on sale for like twenty two dollars on Amazon.
So scoop it up.
I've also done a summer rental.
If you guys like that John Candy film, I spoke to the film's co -writer for that commentary to get some information.
So I got a lot of great details about that movie.
There's a few coming.
I did the commentary track for a mouse hunt, which is coming up in 4K from Kino.
I haven't seen that since the theater.
That's so weird that we brought up mouse hunter.
Yeah, I know.
I'm not knowing that.
OK, well, there's that's another movie where there's I get into it on the commentary because I was able to speak to that film's writer, Adam Rifkin, who's great.
So that's coming out.
Yeah, that's coming out later.
I think June that comes out.
I've also done all of me, the Steve Martin, Carl Reiner, Blu -ray.
I did a commentary for.
I love all of me.
My mom and I watched that all the time when I was a kid.
Steve Martin's been nominated at least for that movie.
Lionsgate Limited is putting it out.
I guess they they own Vestron video now.
Right.
So they're putting that out.
I've bought every Lionsgate Limited release.
The Jackie Brown 4K, which is one of my top five.
It looked so incredible that I was like, I'll buy everything these guys put out.
Yeah, they're great.
And I recorded this commentary over a year ago.
Like, it's a long time ago.
I didn't think it was coming out.
And then just the other day I saw it posted.
I was like, oh, I guess.
It's out.
So I'm really excited about that.
And then, yes, I do have the YouTube channel, which is Hats Off Entertainment.
You can search there on socials at Joe Ramone.
And yeah, our podcast, Almost Cult Classics, the podcast.
You can find us on all the podcast platforms.
We have a YouTube channel as well for that podcast where we do some more video elements
and content.
And we've been watching Jerry Lewis interviews and reacting to them.
So that's that's been really fun.
Yeah.
If you want to see.
The greatest Jerry Lewis thing ever.
Watch his Dick Cavett interview.
OK.
From the 70s.
I mean, you have not seen arrogance personified.
And my favorite part in the whole interview is they're about to go to commercial.
And Jerry Lewis is talking about why he goes over to France so often.
And he goes, you know, sometimes you need that charge.
But over there, they appreciate the work.
They take it seriously.
And he's going on and on about his genius.
Whenever they cut to commercial, they cut back.
Jerry Lewis has an entire water glass in his mouth.
And he's going, oh, yeah, I start the lozenge days where he's clacking that lozenge in his
mouth.
It's the classic lozenge.
And then my favorite quote from the whole interview, he goes, Dick Cavett goes, why
do you choose to write, direct, produce and star?
And Jerry Lewis goes, it's not that you want to.
Because with every hat comes another eight hour workday.
It's that you can't find someone as good as or better than in the era of Scorsese breaking
the palm of Lucas Spielberg.
It is an unhinged interview.
We found one where he talks to the reporter and they they're asking him, why was he absent
from like American cinema in the 70s?
And he's like, he says, well, that was the start of the porno shit.
And I did not want to be a collaborator as if like.
The porn studios were knocking on his door, asking him that that is classic blaming something
that had nothing to do with.
It's like how every hair metal band from the 90s is like, well, then Nirvana came along
and ruined our career.
And it was like, no, you were fucking awful.
Yeah, that's great.
I love that.
So check that out.
We have all the all the stuff there.
But yeah, I mean, I again, I really appreciate you guys having me on.
And I want to return the favor because I want more people to discover your show.
And let's do it.
Let's do it, man.
And we'll hang when I'm up in when I'm up in Phoenixville.
We'll hang.
Yeah, I got a plug real quick.
Folks, please come out to the show at the SOPAC in South Orange, New Jersey.
That's Saturday, June 6th, I think, is the day after that.
I'll be in Nashville, Zanies.
And then in July, the 21st new special, it's coming out.
Finally, there's going to be a VOD period before that.
For early access details to come on all that.
And then in August, I will be at the Comedy Connection and then on to Denver for the comedy works.
All tickets, showtimes, details available at Joe to Rosa dot com.
If you're in New York City, swing by for a sandwich.
Joey Roses, Joey Roses dot com.
Thank you for listening, Pat.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
We are at see you in hell pot on Instagram.
We don't know what we're doing next month, but you can bet we'll be doing the new.
Mission Impossible at some point.
And then, of course, we're in the summer movie season.
So we'll be doing the big boys that aren't superhero based.
Thank you so much, Joe, for your time.
This was awesome.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
And don't forget.
Don't forget about Nona's guys.
You don't watch it today.
We're going to watch it.
Yeah.
All right, Joe.
Thanks, man.
All right.
Thank you, guys.
Talk to you later.