I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams you know I'll say
I'll see you in hell You know I will
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, the podcast where we talk about movies
And it's Christmas time so we're talking holiday flicks
My name is Joe DeRosa
And my name is Patrick Walsh
Happy Holidays to you
Whether it be Hanukkah, Christmas, Kwanzaa, whatever you celebrate
Today we're discussing a Christmas horror movie
Just because to my knowledge they haven't made any Kwanzaa horror that I'm familiar with
It's called The Apology
Starring Anna Gunn from Breaking Bad
It's really a three character chamber piece as they call them
We'll get to that later on
But Joe, what's happening in your neck of the woods?
I would like to point out that after my lackluster performance of the intro
I guess it was two episodes ago
That today, even with a head full of rage
And things I was complaining to you about before we started
I left it at the door
And I put on the face
And I delivered that intro with spunk
And energy
And I'm very proud of myself
I appreciate that
And Joe did have a lot of rage this morning
He was yelling about the situation with Israel and Palestine
He had very strong views
Which I guess I'll share now
I'm kidding folks
I thought you were
I swear to God I thought you were going to start talking about the situation
The guy, the situation
Would that be a thing?
Could you do that on late night?
The Israeli -Palestine situation with the situation
And then that's a bit where he comes out
That seems like a Conan kind of thing
I think you could do that and I know he'd be available
You could also do
I'd like to bring down the house a little bit
And talk about something a little more serious tonight
And obviously it's the situation
It's what's good
And you keep talking about the situation
Everybody thinks they know
But you're just talking about Mike
I was thinking
The other day
And I don't think I would ever do this on stage
But a perfect one of those
For Israel -Palestine
You walk out on stage
Ladies and gentlemen
I don't mean to get too serious here
Right as soon as I began
But I just feel like we
Desperately need to talk about
The affront
Against Israel
This horrible situation against the Israeli people
Of course, folks, I'm referring to SantaCon
That's great
Yeah
You can always get a laugh
When there's a situation that's like
Non -jokeable about
By taking it off into a harmless
Diversion at the end
People love that
Oh no, this is going to be horrible
And then you just give them something cute
They love that
I remember Dice did that with Batman vs. Superman
He was on the Tonight Show
He just did
This exact thing
He started to sit with
You know
I've never seen
A more disgusting
Display of competitiveness
It was when everybody was at a fervor
About Trump and Hillary
And then he's like
Of course I'm talking about Batman vs. Superman
And then does that whole bit
Have you seen these TikToks
Which generally have
Under a thousand likes on them
Of Andrew Dice Clay approaching people
In New York?
No, are they funny?
They're like
Performance art
Occasionally they're funny
It's of a piece with his
The day the laughter died
Kind of thing
He's got this weird Andy Kaufman
Streak in him
He approaches like some
Weirdo sitting on a bucket in New York
And he'll be like
Here I am sitting on my
Bucket
How would you
It sounds like a crazy man
Doing this but it's Dice
Sometimes he's got fans liking them
But for the most part I think nobody knows what to make
Of these videos, they're so weird
I've seen ones where
He'll be like
He'll walk into the Uber driver
And he'll be like
You didn't realize who you had
In here as your passenger
Did you?
That's hilarious to me
Because he was a big name
But he's humble enough to make himself the joke
He was doing something outside of
A Broadway theater
And it was a real nice security guy
But he can't be filming out here
You gotta take it along and he's like
What if I'm about to play this particular
Venue in about two weeks?
And he's like who are you?
Who am I?
They're great, they're great
And then he goes I'm Tyne Daly
I'm starring in Doubt
Yeah
I sent that to Joe
Tyne Daly in the Meryl Streep role
Or the Cherry Jones role if you're a Broadway fan
In Doubt
Two of the greatest actresses ever
And then Tyne Daly
No offense
Liv Shriver
Liv Shriver, yeah
With a big broad face on him
See then I was making fun of him to Joe
We were both talking about
How Liev had put on some weight
And I was like man Ray Donovan wrapped
You know he just went for Jersey Mikes
Whatever
But I thought he was still banging
Naomi Watts
Then I see a picture of her marrying Billy Crudup
Wait what?
I didn't know that
Crudup and Watts are together
It was a picture, tell you how disgusting celebrities are
It was Mark Ruffalo taking a picture
Of Billy Crudup crying
At his wedding
Holding his wife
And Ruffalo's like we love you so much guys
I don't know why
I hate celebrities so much
But it gets worse by the day
I know why
Of course you know why
Because of who they are
I saw a, while I was waiting
For a very tardy Joe
This morning
I saw a headline that enraged me
Even though it's about three people I love
And here it is, I think it'll enrage you too Joe
I think it was on like
Variety or something
How Jason Bateman, Will Arnett
And Sean Hayes proved
That podcasts
Can be big business
Now I love these men
They didn't prove jack shit
They came along
20 years into a massive trend
And continued
Making money
They're millionaires already
What are you talking about
They invented podcasts
Well that makes me mad
That's like saying how
Those three proved
That television was still
A financially
Pleasing
It's like
Guys, they're famous
Whatever they do, people will spend money on
Like if they
Jason Bateman and Will Arnett proved
Cookies can still make a buck
People will buy whatever they do
They're famous
That's why every celebrity is getting a tequila brand now
Because they're like
Just put whatever out there
And people will buy it
The number one tequila now is Clooney's tequila
The terrible tequila
I actually like Casamigos
But I don't love it the way some people do
I liked it
And then one day somebody, I forget who goes
I don't know man
It tastes like vanilla to me
And I was like
Oh my god
I only go blanco
I don't fuck with the brown stuff
No no, the blanco too
But then I was like
Then I noticed it
And then I couldn't not notice
I was like what the fuck
This does taste like
And then I was in a liquor store
And I was talking to the proprietor
And I said what kind of blanco tequila you have
And I made a joke
Because he had it all behind the counter
And I go
You can walk right by that Casamigos
Don't even recommend it
And he goes I'd never recommend that shit
And I was like
Yeah, I don't like it either
It tastes like vanilla
And he goes that's because they pump that shit into it
I was like
Oh really, okay
I mean I think
It's definitely not everyone saying
Oh this is clearly the best tasting tequila
Although I like it, fine
But I think that
Again, celebrity worship
It is
People saying if I drink
Tequila
That George Clooney quote made
Which he didn't
He tasted probably
Ten varieties
And said I like numbers
Six and ten
And then they found something in between them
But you're like I'm going to be like George Clooney
I'm going to drink the tequila George Clooney
Drinks
It's absurd
You could save $25 a bottle and probably get a
Higher quality tequila
What are you doing
It's dumb
It's really dumb
It's really really dumb
I respect
One of the
I respect George Clooney but one of the guys
I respected that went into the booze biz
Was Coppola
Because Coppola really went into it
He really
Was like no I'm going to get a vineyard
And I'm going to make wine
And he even says
There's a bonus feature on the outsiders DVD
Where they go to his
House to watch the movie
Yeah
And Diane Lane's like
Francis your home is so beautiful
Look at this and he goes
All of this is from the wine
None of this is from the movies
He like really like
Took a hard left out of entertainment
And just went into the wine business for a very long time
You know
Well I mean part of that was
He had several massive flops
In a row
He just announced that they're re -releasing
One from the heart which was kind of the last
Nail in the coffin of his movie studio
It cost a lot, made nothing
But like
Much in the
It's much less cool but much in the way Leno
Doesn't touch his tonight show money
I think that he basically uses this winery
To fund these movies I mean every time
He makes a movie it drives him into
Bankruptcy
That's a level of like
Being an artist that I do not have
In mind myself at all
Like never would I engage in something
That risked my entire
You know financial livelihood
Never and he's done it time
And time again with varying results
You know like this last gamble
That he's making as a very old man
If this thing comes out in bombs
As more than half of his movies do
He's just like alright well
I mean that's an artist that's like
I'm taking everything I've made
In my career throwing it in this
Final project because I'm dying what do I care
My family's taken care of
I respect it
How many kids does he have?
Just Sophia?
No I think he's got more than that there's a bunch of
Copulas running around
I mean I figure you know
Like if his one kid was Sophia
Let's put it that way
And I'm him
I'm going hey man
She's taken care of? Yeah she did well for herself
She's in good shape
She doesn't need my help financially
Fuck it man I can see
The light at the end of the tunnel here so
I'm gonna just I'm gonna go for it
And if it doesn't work then I have enough money
To live my final years at least
His kids are Sophia, Giancarlo
Who I'm less familiar with and then
Roman who is kinda like Wes Anderson's
Partner
Wow okay well then that's definitely
He's doing well too
Yeah I'm a fan I mean
I only love about
Three Copula movies but I'm just a fan
Of what he does
I am too Pat
And I'm also a fan
Of the movie corner
Oh
Would you like to take us there?
I'm just excited cause I have three this week
I love it
Let's do it
I soar
Well first off I finished Six Feet Under
Gonna recommend it one last time
Brilliant finale
But um
I watched
The Souvenir
And The Souvenir Part 2
And I guess I'll just combine them into one
Cause I don't have that much to say but
These movies are
Two of the most overrated
Films
In recent history
They are so highly reviewed
They are produced by Martin Scorsese
Scorsese talks about
This woman in her films
Every chance he gets
Joanna Hogg with two G's
Hogg with two G's
Sounds like the family that would come
Stay at faulty towers
The Hoggs
Big fat fat family that he
Spills some gazpacho on
Or something
The Souvenir is
A movie, it's British
It is a young woman who is a
Film student and she falls into
A relationship with a
Narcissistic
Young man
Who reveals himself to be
An addict, a heroin addict
And
She's in kind of these pretentious film worlds
She's got talent
But this relationship is like clouding
Her judgement and clouding her life
Interesting enough
It's got our boy
Richard Ioide in there
Which is a very hard last name for me to pronounce
As a pretentious film guy, he's very funny
Nothing else in it is funny
Tilda Swinton is in there
As the narcissist's mother
And she's pretty good
But that's basically it
It's like
How a young woman, and this happens to
Young men too, can fall head over
Heels with the wrong person
Early on before they get their
Receptors for what makes a bad
Or good person aligned
And you can lose years of your life
To someone like that, years of your career
And from what I read
This is a very personal story for this woman
She probably had something very similar to this happen
To her in film school
It's just not particularly interesting
You know, like, you hear about that
You're like, okay, alright, let's see where
They go with it, but
They don't really go anywhere with it
Then when I heard there was a sequel, it's almost like a joke
You're like, okay, what more could you
Have to tell? And they just
Pick her up a few years down the line in film school
Making her way, getting over
The relationship, still friends
With the kid's mom
There are 824
Releases
There
I don't know
They're well made, well acted
For sure, I just found it to be
A pretty boring version of the story
I think sometimes when people tell their own
Personal truth and story
They forget that like, you can change some details
To make it more entertaining
Or more interesting to people
That said, everyone else has raved
About this movie, maybe I'm wrong, but
Both of them I found average
Joe?
I watched
Headliners only
Per
Pat's sort of suggestion
To watch it
Well you texted me that you were watching
I told you, you gotta hate watch it, yeah
It was one of the most infuriating hours of my life
Watching this thing
Look, I'm friendly with Kevin Hart
It's a documentary about Kevin Hart
And Chris Rock
They did a series of shows together
Last year
I'm very friendly with Kevin Hart
We both started at the same
Club in Philly
About a year apart
But that's how I know him
And I don't know Chris Rock
I've met him a few times
I've had some conversations with him
But I am good friends with his brother Tony
That said, anything that's like
You know
These two famous guys are brilliant
Is something that's always gonna annoy me
So I went into it with a little bit of a chip
On my shoulder for that reason
But it's about comedy, it's about stand up
I gotta say, overall
I ended up enjoying it
Because
On a personal level
I enjoyed it, why?
Because there was a lot of interviewing
With my friend Keith Robinson
Who's one of my best friends in this business
They talked a lot about
A dear friend
Late, great Patrice O 'Neil
They talked a lot about the New York comedy scene
There was a lot of nostalgia
And stuff that was close to my heart in this thing
And it was cool to see
Two guys at that
High level of showbiz
Show this love
And respect
For people that
Are great
And brilliant
But are not at that level
You know, notoriety wise
At least, as them
And I
I enjoyed it
I enjoyed seeing the footage from the clubs
I enjoyed all that
I didn't really need
The aspect of
Which is the Netflix
Ball washing of
Isn't it amazing that these two people
Who are this famous did a thing together
You know, it's like the thing we were just talking about
With Smart List
There's certainly that element to it
I find that
I don't know, it's weird
I just read an article
Which was
Too
Angsty
Overall, but I did agree with the article's
Perspective, which was
It was talking about Felicity Huffman
Finally doing this
Interview after her
Short prison stint
With the Varsity Blues scandal
And it was just like
You know, she's kind of crying in it
You mean how she came out in that
Whip cream bikini
Yeah
Laid in the middle of the road
Yeah, that's the program
That's the other one
But the writer was just like
You know guys, we used to hate
Rich people
We used to resent their wealth
And we used to find any
Reason we could
To kind of take the piss out of them
And now we have sympathy for them
Like what happened? Now that overall
Take again
Is too angsty for me
But
It does speak to
Generally to something that
And I'm referring back to the documentary
Now that's going on
Where there is this
Obsessiveness in
Especially entertainment now
With the uber famous
Now you could say that
That's always been there
I don't agree
And here's why
If you look back to the 50s
Or the 60s
Or the 70s
Or the 40s
When Hollywood was Hollywood and all that bullshit
You know man
There was
One talk show
That some of the celebrities went on to
To discuss things
Nine times out of ten they weren't even
If you watch old Carson clips
They're not even talking about their latest movie
They're out there just having fun
And having a conversation
There were no
You know real tabloid
Shows on television
Tabloid magazines were certainly
In less circulation
But most importantly
The everyday common man aspect
Of entertainment
Didn't exist
And certainly wasn't populated by
Celebrities. Now we're in a world
Where
You have a Jason Bateman
Or a Kevin Hart
And they are uber famous and they are uber wealthy
And that person is also
Populating
Not just the movie screens
But your TV screens on TV shows
In commercials
To sell things
In podcasting that they
Can do out of their home or whatever
And
We've got this very blurred line now
Of
Like this uber rich
Are mixing in with all
Of us now
And there used to be a separation
And I'm sorry but I think that separation
Was a good thing. I think it was good
To turn on the Oscars
And for the only time
All year you saw
Frank Sinatra at a thing
And then he went back
To being mysterious elusive
Super famous Frank Sinatra
I think
There's a weird thing happening now
Or maybe Nicholson is a better example
Of that phenomenon
You just do not see him
In an interview
You see him at a basketball game
And you see him at the Oscars
And he smiles with his sunglasses on
He makes one quip and he leaves
That's all you know about him
After 70 years that's all you know about him
So yeah
And you know
So there's just this
Look I'm not that
There's an air in this is the one part
Of the documentary I really don't like
There's an air in this documentary
Of can you
Believe
And aren't you astounded
And don't you admire
The fact that
These two guys could have went out
By themselves and made
Millions
But instead chose to
Selflessly work together
To make even
More millions
It's like guys what the fuck are we talking
About here
It's nuts
I told Joe when it says headliners only
I was like okay so either I'm going to watch
These two legends do stand up
Or they're going to
Introduce me to some hilarious
New stand ups that I'm not familiar with
I hit play knowing nothing
But the first scene is
Kevin and Hart and Chris Rock
Enjoying a
$500 a plate meal in a nice
Restaurant and talking about
How
Great they've done
You know and
Sucking each other's dicks
And it's just like this big long dick suck
When it ended I was like
What even was this it's not really a
Documentary it's not like you watch it's not comedian
Where you watch their processes
Or them like create a set together
Or something it's really
Two rich people talking and that's
What a lot that's what smartless is that's what a lot
Of entertainment is and the
Thing too
Is that you're you're not seeing
Them that is a performance as
Well those three guys on that podcast
And especially
Rock and Hart and this movie are
Not showing you their true selves
They're showing you their fake selves
And then the cameras turn off
And they talk their actual shit
And treat everyone around them I have
To assume from all stories I've heard
Like shit so they get to
They like this pulling
The curtain back because
It makes it's like what the rock does
It makes people think they're seeing the
Real rock you're not you're seeing
A very carefully curated
Version of his life
You ever wonder who the paid
Man is recording these videos
Who the who the assistants
Are recording the rock having a
Christmas morning conversation with
His daughters they're
Sick they're sick
People yeah no well
I mean the thing now is
Because I have friends that
Do it now and
I don't know if I would do it if I had
The if I could afford to but I have
You know I have friends that you
Pay a guy and that's it like he's
With you all the time and he's
Shooting everything
You do in life not everything
I mean you know obviously you know
But like for instance if
You're going to go to do a day of podcasting
Or something with with on your friend
Shows that guy goes with you
And shoots everything now on the one hand
It's extraordinarily efficient
And very smart in this disgusting
Social media landscape we live in
It gets you immense amounts
Of content without having to do anything
Right but on the other hand
It becomes like that
What was that
Marry me movie
With JLo and Owen
Wilson where
You know at one point he has to tell her
Like you know if we're
Going to spend time together you can't have your
Social media person with us
Like there's
A real life happening under
Your nose and you're not recognizing
It because
You're giving so much to your public
I don't know man
I don't know what to do
It is truly
A real conundrum for me
I just had a meeting with my
And I'm no
Celebrity obviously but like
I'm rooted enough
In the entertainment business that I have to
Put this fucking shit out all the time on
Social media and I
I had a meeting with my reps yesterday
About all this where I was like you know I
Don't have a YouTube channel people are telling
Me I'm crazy that I don't have one but
I don't know if I want to start one because
Now it's another thing to commit to
I was like you know
I got the show I talked about this show
I said I got the show with Pat
You know we enjoy
Doing it and I do the show with Sal
We enjoy doing that and I put
Up stuff on the Instagram feed
To promote whatever I'm like
I don't know if I can start another
Thing
It's exhausting man it's exhausting
I don't know
If I left this business
I'd never post on social media
I'd never even look at it
I'd never look at it
You know especially
Let's say five years ago
More I was
When I was really like big on Twitter
And I was getting all these celebrities following
Me and I was tweeting twice a day
And I was always checking how many likes
And hearts I got and everything I was like this is
So fun I will never stop doing this
This is the best you know
Because you get all that dopamine from it
The day I cancelled Twitter like
Within ten minutes I was over it
Never thought about it again
Never wanted to go back this thing like
I wouldn't say it ruled my life I wasn't sick about it
But it was a part of my life
You know Twitter and
God it was empty and nothing and I
There hasn't been a single tweet posted
About what happened to
The Patrick Walsh nobody gives a shit
Nor should they
I devoted ten years of my life to writing jokes
For free
Yeah
I don't know
You know now there are other people
Though Pat that would say
And this is why it's so fucking sick
They would say well it wasn't foolish
Because
Doing that
Led to
You know not you
I'm saying but
Name a
It may have helped my career who knows
You never know what brings people to your writing
There are people absolutely who are like
No I wrote jokes for free on Twitter and it got me
Six writing jobs
I mean this is the problem
We've self -branded ourselves
Everybody's their own
Little
Institution or
Corporation now
And it's nuts
I remember interviewing
At Wet Hot American Summer
And he didn't
Use this in any way
For or against me but when I was
Doing the interview with Michael Showalter
He said he goes
What's going on with you on Twitter man
This Kumeya guy is really going
After you and I was like
Oh yeah we have a thing because I said a thing
On Rogan
And that sucks that should not be
Something your employer knows about you
And yet you did it to yourself
You know you put it up there
So yeah everyone's to blame
So
You know it's just
Part of our lives now you know
I had a bit about this with
When Obama
Was the first president on Twitter and I said
I should not
Be allowed to tweet at the president
Like there is no world
Where I should be able to write something
That the president of the United
States might see
It's not a letter about
I wish nuclear war would end
Or a threat of
Like what if he's about to do
Something and some comment he
Read gets to him you know
And it changes his mind I saw a comment
On our Patreon the other day that was like maybe
We could drop the music at the beginning
Of the episodes like the 15
Seconds of catchy intro music
That we have I don't know who said it
I moved on I've thought about it four
Times in the last week it is it is
Infected my week
I've been like how dare
You what you can't click the
Click the skip 15 seconds button
If you can't handle it people love that
And I'm talking to myself talking to
This guy in my mind crazy
So if I'm the president
And I read some shitty
Comments that can't be affecting
Whether or not you go to war you know
Yeah
Oh yeah
I watched the Netflix
Ridge
Reptile
A new film that like all
Netflix films is needlessly
Two hours and 20 minutes
It stars the great Benicio del Toro
Who I am happy to see
And just like in
The old 90s
2000s tradition of pairing a
Great actor with somebody who
Sucks Benicio del Toro
And Justin Timberlake duking it off
In a battle of acting but I'll
Say this
When Timberlake is cast
Well when he's cast according
To his strengths
Which are playing a pussy a
Coward a spineless piece
Of shit
As in black snake moan and a few other
Movies I think it can be really effective
And I liked him in this movie
I love del Toro in it we don't see him
Enough I feel like it's every three
Years he pops up he's great
He cast his ex girlfriend Alicia
Silverstone as his wife
She's great in it great to see her again
And speaking of people I haven't seen in ages
Michael Pitt
Who was on like
Boardwalk empire and a bunch of movies
And then just fell off the scene due to
A bunch of scandals he's actually added
A middle name to his name he's Michael
Something Pitt which is usually a sign that
You fucked up your career in some way
Would you change your name
Got Eric Boghossian
You know a great supporting cast too
The vibe of it is
Prisoners I think the movie
Seems very influenced and
Inspired by prisoners and
Sicario and those great early
Denis Villeneuve movies
It feels like them unfortunately
The script is not as good as either of those
Movies but it's a very solid
Thriller a whodunit
Timberlake's wife is found murdered
Del Toro is the investigator called in
To investigate
And little by little we learn
That neither of these men
Are what they appear on the surface everybody's got
Secrets
Del Toro is a dirty cop and there's a bunch
Of backstabbing and so forth
It's over long it's a little
Overstuffed with plot
Still I would rather a movie strive to be
Prisoners and come up short than a
Movie strive to be the Avengers
And come up short it's
Definitely
Entertaining and a better thriller
Than the
Master thriller maker's most recent movie
David Fincher's The Killer
It's definitely better than that I recommend
It
All right I have another
Docu thing here
I watched it was called
I gotta look up the damn name again
I thought I could remember it legendary
Timeless heroes Indiana Jones and
Harrison Ford
It's like a 90 maybe a little
Shorter than 90 minutes but it's
About a 90 minute
Documentary
That eventually focuses
On the conclusion
Of the character of Indiana Jones
And then the spine
Of the entire thing is
Harrison Ford's
Connection to that character
But of course
It gets a lot into
Just him in general his life and
You know it doesn't get too deep into his
Personal life he's fairly private it seems
I didn't even know this
They don't talk about this in the documentary
You know he's got a son that owns a restaurant
In L .A. I never knew that
No I had no idea
Anyway
Of course they talk about Star Wars
What is the restaurant
I honestly think it's called Ford's
He's a franchisee
Of Yoshinoya Beef
It's El Polio Loco
I think it's called Ford's
Honestly
Oh I know Ford's I haven't been there but I know the restaurant
There's a lot of great interviews with
And it's newer interviews with Spielberg
And Lucas
Lawrence Kasdan
Kathleen
Kennedy
Who's her husband
What's his name
The producer
Oh son of a bitch
Gary Marshall
Oh Karen Allen
Kate Capshaw
Lee
I'm blanking on his name now
Short round, what's his name again?
Kay Gui Kwan
Joe I missed the start, what is this again?
It's called Timeless Heroes
Indiana Jones and Harrison Ford
Was this like on the DVD or what?
No it's on the Disney, it's on Disney Plus
Oh I got it, I don't have Disney Plus, I gotcha
I regot Disney Plus
Because
Because they were offering
A deal, commercial free Hulu
And commercial free Disney Plus
For 20 bucks a month
I on Black Friday
By the way, I had none of the streamers
When Black Friday hit
I got every single
Streamer right down to your shitty Paramount
Plus, I got
All of them
For two to three dollars a piece
For like six months
Just cancel them all
Try to remember next year, cancel them all like on Thanksgiving
Then they, they're giving them away
On Black Friday
So, anyway, carry on Joe, sorry
So, um
That's okay
So anyway
It's a
It's an enjoyable documentary
Of course there's a ton of interview footage with Harrison Ford
Um
But it's just a talking heads thing
That kind of reflects on his career
Celebrates all aspects of it, talks about
All the different stuff he did
Um, you know
And there's really not much
More to it than that, it's a fluff piece
But it's an enjoyable one
Um
I didn't know this about him
I didn't, you know, and again
There's this, there's this
Element in it at times
It's a part that really annoyed me
Where Kathleen Kennedy is like
I called Phoebe Waller -Bridge
And I said, we would all
Just love it
If you played opposite Harrison Ford
In the next Indiana Jones movie
And then it cuts to
Phoebe Waller, you know, and she's like
Okay, I fell over in the
Booth
Screaming
And it's like
I just
Fucking hate that celebrity cool kid shit
You know, like
Oh, did you call
The uber cool
Famous lady
To star in the movie
With your hat in your hand
Oh, what if
She says no
Fuck off
We offered her five million dollars
And folks
She said yes
We couldn't believe it
You know what the worst part
About this celebrity worship is
I think, and it's a small thing
But it drives me crazier than anything else
It's a weird theme we have on this week's episode
When they'll say
And I just, it's because while I was waiting for you to log on
This morning, Joe, I read this little interview
With all the directors that are up for shit
This year for the Oscars
And they're talking about Michael Mann, who's part of the panel
And I fucking love Michael Mann as a director
But he's a notorious asshole
A notorious monster
A control freak
You know, he makes movies that
Look perfect and that comes at a cost
He's like James Cameron, he can ruffle some feathers
And
Ava DuVernay
A massive movie director
Is talking about how
I don't know how he got this reputation
He has been nothing but a teddy
Bear to me
And then Michael Mann's like, don't tell anybody sweetheart
And they share a little laugh
And it's like
He's not that way
To everyone
He's that way to other celebrities
I wish I was talking about anybody other than Michael Mann
But this whole thing of, oh weird
You had an issue with that actor?
He was always nice to me. You're an actor
Famous people
Are nice to other famous people
Because they assume that they can help them
Or
The other thing that gets me
A woman who's a 12 out of 10
On the beauty scale
Being like, I couldn't believe this guy
That everyone says is an asshole
Was nice to me
Like why would he be nice to me but mean to everybody else
People have so little
Self -awareness
Sorry John
Again
Anyway, watch
I'm not
Sighing at you, I'm sighing at
You know, I agree
Yeah, check out
Check out the legendary heroes
Thing if you want, it's a nice little
Send off to the Indiana Jones character
And it's, you know, it's good
Okay, okay
Did you get the 4K
Of the new movie?
It is sitting at my home
My house, I had it sent there
But it's sitting there
Alright, fair enough
I hear it looks spectacular, courtesy of our friend
Matt McCarthy, he said it looks amazing
Okay
Now Joe, are we gonna do
The
That apocalypse movie I told you about
The new one on Netflix?
Maybe
I gotta tell you, it does not look that
Intriguing to me, I mean
I'm not against doing it but
We'll see, leave the world behind
It's, you know, we'll
Maybe do it next time, if not I'll take it to the solo
Corner, I'll talk about it on here
But, alright, then I watched
Nyad, another Oscar hopeful
And, you know
There was something almost reassuring about how
Straightforward and kind of dull this movie
Was because it just felt like
Classic Oscar
Bait from like the late 90s
And that's how the holdovers
Felt to me too, almost like
We're trying to restart
That kind of shitty Miramax
Era where it's like, you make a
Movie just to earn an award
There's no other reason for it to exist, really
Nyad is fine
It's your classic sports underdog
Story, Rudy, whatever you wanna call it
Except the interesting thing about it
Is that Diana Nyad
Who is a real woman
Is narcissistic
A little annoying
A lot annoying, I would say
And just very
Self -obsessed, she also has kind of a checkered history
If you read about her, like she lied about a lot
Of her accomplishments, which is
You know, worth a look
If you wanna read that Wikipedia
But, the reason to watch it
The only reason to watch it is the amazing
Performances by
Annette Benning as Nyad
And Jodie Foster as her
Kind of coach, friend, partner
Nyad is lesbian
She
Is really weird
And off -putting
And I think that the movie does
Itself a great service by showing you
A lot of clips throughout of the real
Woman
And you see how weird and off -putting she is
And it makes you appreciate
Annette Benning all the more
Annette Benning is an amazing actress
I think one of our most underrated actresses
Like when you're listing off the best
Actresses working
She never comes up, or it's rare
Maybe for a little period
Maybe after American Beauty she did
But it's been a long time
Where you just don't hear people talking about her
She's always reliably excellent
This is a very different performance for her
I bet she will get nominated
It's always great to see Jodie Foster
Especially kind of weird to see her in like
The Mickey role, the sidekick role
Because Jodie Foster is such a big star in her own right
But
You know, the story itself is a woman
Who's 60, who decides before it's too late
She wants to swim like the longest
Distance in American history
Blah, blah, blah
It's real hard to make
Competitive swimming
Compelling
It really is hard
You're here for the acting
If you want to see a couple great performances
Otherwise there's no real reason to watch
Nyad
My final
Is
I did re -watch
Dial of Destiny, not on the 4K
But on Disney Plus
I'd seen it twice in the theater
And I wanted to re -watch it
In conjunction with this
Documentary
So third watch was at home
Folks, I gotta tell ya
Third watch, best watch
Of the three
It is getting progressively better to me
I am now prepared to say
I think it is one of the best Indiana Jones movies
I think
Temple, I'm sorry
I think Last Crusade, This, and Raiders
Are just about perfect
Indiana Jones movies
And I like Temple of Doom quite a bit
And Crystal Skull
You know, has its moments
But is flawed
But, you know, a lot of people would say
Well, even if you like this newest one
You couldn't possibly like it as much
As the other ones
Because it hinges on the other ones
And blah, blah, blah
And I would say that is in fact why it is so good
Just because it's a final chapter
Doesn't mean it's not good
Also too, if you didn't know who the fuck Indiana Jones was
You could a thousand percent
Watch this movie
And just be like, oh, okay
This is a guy that's, alright
Here's him when he's young and now he's old
And he's getting roped back into the whole thing
The story completely works
There's
Even with the
Marrian storyline
There's zero, if you had no idea what was going on
They established that he is getting
Divorced by showing you the papers
You see a picture of the woman
Even that works
I think
I'm just
Utterly
Confused
As how this is the
Lowest rated movie of the series
How it has a lower
Rating than Crystal Skull
I don't get it
I've said it before, I'll say it again
I feel like this was a movie that was easy
For people to take their frustrations out on
So they did
But
I think it's an excellent, excellent
Excellent
Indiana Jones movie
The adventure is awesome
The action is awesome
It feels like Indiana Jones
It's got emotional depth that
I would argue none of the other movies have
And it's just fucking great
You know, that's true
And I didn't like it, but as far as the emotional depth
I would hand it to that movie, I would agree with that
I really loved it
And I really scrutinized it this time
Because I was debating it with a friend of mine
And he was like, well, you know
I don't like that
Like
Phoebe Weller -Bridge gets to kick ass
And he doesn't get to kick any ass
And
They make him look stupid
Because he keeps outsmarting her
And I was like, well, wait a minute
Him being betrayed is nothing new
He gets betrayed by Mack
In Crystal Skull three times
And falls for it every time
Doctor
Whatever her name is
In Last Crusade
Tricks him
And seduces him
The people around him
Kick ass in all the movies
He gets the shit
Kicked out of him in all the movies
That's what's so great
You know, what makes Indiana Jones great
Isn't just the
You see when he swung with the whip
And then shot the guy, all that's fine
But what also makes him great is
When he has to like
Reluctantly fight the giant
German mechanic
And is like, this is gonna suck, I'm gonna get the shit beat out of me
And he does
So his shortcomings
And his flaws have always been a big part of the series
And
So I really scrutinized it this time
And I was like, wait a minute
He punches and shoots plenty of people
In this
And Phoebe Waller
Bridger
She only tricks him
Like one or two times
And then he's on to her
Like, and then he kind of takes the wheel
And starts to steer the ship
And then her character
Becoming redeemed and becoming
Human is also an amazing
Part of the story
And that's the whole point
She represents what he used to be
That was one of the interesting things in that doc
That I watched
They show some footage
Like of them shooting
That is not in the movie
And
There's a scene
I wish they would have put it in
Where she's yelling at him
And she's like, you're unbelievable
Your whole life you do
Whatever you want and think only about yourself
And then the second somebody needs to
Needs you to
Listen to them, you won't do it
And it was
Just a very simple piece of dialogue but I was like
That sums up the character
So perfectly
And sums up where he is
In his journey at this point of his life
So perfectly
Like he's stubborn
He's a rogue
He doesn't fucking listen
He usually is going for himself
In one way
Or another
And now he's in a position
Because he's old where he has to be a little more
Selfless and he has a hard time doing it
I love the movie
Is the de -aging
At the top a bit clumsy? Yeah
Of course, but I don't care
So is the footage
Of the
I don't know what you would call it
But it's not a tidal wave
In Temple of Doom when they're running from that
Rush of water
That looks completely fake too
You can see the line around their bodies
As they run, as they're on screen
Running from video
Of water
There's plenty of clumsy
Special effects
That when they're new
They don't look great
But you go, I get that that's fake but who cares
I remember watching Temple of Doom on cable
When I was like 10
With my friend Billy Morgan
Well Doom's got some tough effects
Especially as the picture
Gets clearer and clearer
Like some of that rope bridge stuff
Don't look so hot when they're falling to their deaths
Yeah, and even as a 10 year old
My friend Billy Morgan goes, oh man
That's totally on screen
He explained to me what that meant
I didn't know what it meant
So anyway
I think if you're gonna let
Some not
Amazing de -aging
But still pretty damn good
And
Age
And a character that you're
Supposed to not like at first
And then grow to like as she redeems herself
Ruin a movie for you
I think you're just looking for reasons
To not like a movie
And you know
That's what movies are a lot of the time
So I don't know
I just think it's awesome
It's not me doubling down
In the way I had to with Phantom Menace
Where I liked Phantom Menace
But I knew it had some big problems
And I would just yell at people
And be like, no it's great
I'm not doing that, I'm saying, no I think this movie is fucking great
So
With half a corona bottle
Lunging at somebody in a bar
Screaming about attack of the clones
We've seen it, it's not pretty
It's more accurate
Than you'd know
No I'll probably
Give it a second chance
But something that I have to
Just admit a lot of
The times is that
What you see
When you're in your formative years
Which I would say is
Five through college
That's going to be your favorite movies
You know
You'll never
Just the way you don't feel anywhere near
As good as you felt during that period of your life
You're not going to like the movies and music
Of today as much as you did then
Because I don't think you can
I just don't think the body is rigged that way
I try to remind myself
That yes things are getting worse
But also you've seen everything
When you hit a certain age
I think it's why critics get so cranky
Like Rex Reed is a perfect example
You get so grouchy
And you fucking hate everything
It's because you've seen everything a million times
So hard to say
I'll give it another shot and I didn't hate it the first time
And you forgive
Shit so much more when you're a kid
When I try to turn somebody on
To like even Planes Trains
This legendary movie
Everybody likes it when you show it to them for the first time now
But it's a movie with
Both the flaws too
Both the score
You know the horrible rap music
In the background
There's some logic things that don't quite add up
Whatever
You're just more forgiving when you're younger
I'm not going to be
Super forgiving of this one
The apology
It's a Shudder original
I intentionally didn't watch it
I was like great
A thriller like one location
In a house thriller
Set at Christmas time
Awesome I'm going to watch this
Around Christmas
And even though the reviews weren't great
I was just like I bet I'm going to love this fucking movie
And it starts out okay
The premise is intriguing
And then it just kind of keeps falling apart from there
Joe do you want to walk us through this
Convoluted plot
Well I didn't think it was convoluted
I thought it was pretty straightforward
You know
A woman is
I'll tell you real quick my issue with
When I say convoluted I mean
It is essentially a movie
Where
Your
Victim
Does not want to kill
The assailant
And the assailant wants to be killed
It's like immediately
All stakes are taken out of this movie
That's why
I was almost trying to figure out
People's motivations
You know it was clumsily written
And I don't mean convoluted like
There was a bunch of red herrings or it was hard to follow
I just mean sometimes
Their motivations weren't clear and in a
Two person
Movie
It's all about motivations
I thought they handled that really poorly
But go ahead tell us the plot of the movie please
Joe
Okay so
A woman
Is prepping for Christmas
Dinner
You know
Presumably the night before
Christmas or something
She and her neighbor
They were played by
The wonderful Janine
Garofalo, it was good to see Janine Garofalo
Back in the movie again, I hadn't seen her in a long time
Yeah
Are making
This dinner, the woman is stressed
That she's not
Going to be able to handle it
But it seems to be a normal amount
Of anxiety to have
When you're prepping for a holiday
Anyway
After the neighbor leaves
And the woman is alone
You start to
You learn through
A series of hints
That she's a recovering alcoholic
Her daughter
Has been missing
For 20 years
And is probably dead
But she's not sure
And she's on
The verge of relapsing
Just as that's about to happen
There's a knock at the door
She goes to the door, it's a man
Enter the third character of the film
The man
Turns out to be
Her
Sister's ex -husband
Who is coming to surprise
Everybody at Christmas
You also find out that she and this man
Had a very brief
Affair
Behind their sister's back
Her sister's back
And that this man skipped town
Very suddenly
After he and the sister split up
Which was coincidentally
Around the time that her daughter
Went missing
He starts having a
Challenging conversation with her
About the missing daughter
It gets more and more provocative
And leads to
His reveal that he is
The one that murdered the daughter
And potentially
Also had raped
The daughter
At least statutorily
But then you find out it wasn't even
Statutory, it was just forced
And he killed her
To
Obviously
She was screaming and whatever
You had to silence her
And then
The description of the film
Is that this launches
A sinister game of
Cat and mouse
As the two are trapped, snowed in
On this wintery night
And it goes from there
You can imagine, he gets the higher ground
She gets the higher ground
Once she gets the higher ground, what is she going to do?
Is she going to torture him?
Is she going to kill him?
It's all very emotional
And basically they're setting the stage
For like a hard candy
Kind of film
Yeah, it reminded me also
Have you ever seen Death and the Maiden?
Polanski's movie with Sigourney Weaver and Ben Kingsley?
Great fucking movie
With a similar set up and two characters
It's so fucking good, it's a filmed play
But it's really really good
Well when I realized this was going to
Go the route of, or I thought it was going to go the route
Of Hard Candy, I was disappointed
I hate the movie Hard Candy
I hate it for
For it's negative portrayal of pedophiles
Yes
No, I hate it because it takes on this
Extraordinarily
Extraordinarily challenging
Upsetting
And traumatic topic
And tries to turn it into a
Romp
By how?
By making the
Predators prey
Even more violent
And sinister than the
Predator himself
So you're now in a position
Where you're supposed to be
Rooting for somebody
Who's acting so
Despicably
You know, and this is
This is a pre
Hard Candy was a pre
To Catch a Predator world, but I think when
To Catch a Predator came out
There was a collective moment
Throughout the entire country where it's like
Guys, these guys
Are predators and they should be locked up
What is this gleeful dance
We're doing around it now
This is weird
You know, I met a guy
Over in Vegas
That like
That like does this
This YouTube thing where he finds
He sets up
Potential pedophiles and predators
And then like
Once he's in there
Once he has them like, you know
Once they come in and they realize
They're not meeting the kid, he does like a game
Show with them and he's like, I make them
Think if they can answer the questions right
I won't call the cops
But I'm always going to call the cops
Yeah, then he's like, and one guy killed himself
Isn't that great? And I'm like
What is this? This is disgusting
Like it's just gross
So anyway
This movie
It takes
Extraordinarily
I don't think heavy is a proper
Word, but it takes extraordinarily
Just for lack of a better word, heavy
Subject matter
Heavy, heavy subject matter
Traumatizing subject matter
And
I'm like, okay
You got to do one of two things here
You've either got to take this subject matter
Quite seriously
Yeah
Or you've got to make it so
Insane
That it's
That the viewer is sitting there going, I can't believe
I'm laughing right now, but this is nuts
Yeah
And it does neither
Instead
And it doesn't even do what Hard Candy does
Where it makes her
Such a monster towards him
That maybe you go, oh that's an interesting
Commentary sort of
Like a monster
You could be turned into the monster, whatever
They do none of that
It just becomes this thing
Where
And I'll reference another movie
That I hate, that is an all time classic
Argument on this podcast
Midsummer
Where I'm sitting there going, what am I watching
I'm watching a woman in pain
And that's the whole point of this
The whole point of this
Is to watch me have to watch
This woman learn the
Horrific truth
About what happened to her daughter
And that
Her life was wasted
Without any purpose
Or meaning or anything
And in the most depraved
Way possible
And then on top of it
She's not even going to get a real
Comeuppance on this guy
It's just
Her getting the confession out of him
After she
Tortures him and then he
Beats up her
It was just terrible
I haven't seen Hard Candy since the theater
Which is 20 years ago at this point
But like
I remember enjoying it to some degree
Because it gave you that
Catharsis, it's a revenge movie
Along the lines of a Death Wish or whatever else
And a lot of the times
Certainly with Death Wish
And all the movies that came after it
The big moral question
The thematic question is
Can you go too far in
Exacting revenge to where you become the monster
Prisoners is a great example
I know this Hugh Jackman torturing Paul Dano
That goes well beyond
Anything
That Dano has
Maybe done at that
We don't know what he's done at that point in the movie
But that's kind of the issue
Jackman goes completely insane
With torturing this guy and you're like
Well now I don't know whose side I'm on
This movie doesn't do that
You're not on the side of the
Kid raper
Obviously and murderer
But you don't really like
Either of them
Anna Gunn played Walter White's wife
In Breaking Bad
I think she was much like Carmela
One of the most unfairly hated characters
In TV history
Because you forget because of how much
You love Tony Soprano and how much
You love Walter White
That on the daily basis
They are doing horrific things
They are killing people, they are ripping people off
They're cheating, they're doing all kinds
Of crazy things and you hate the wife
In those shows even though she's right
She's the one saying hey stop killing
People and be a decent husband and father
Right
But I've never seen her in anything
Else and seeing her
In this I couldn't stand her
I got why people didn't like her in
Breaking Bad because she seemed so whiny
In this
Whiny is the wrong thing to say when your daughter
Has been assaulted and murdered but
I don't think she found
The notes within her performance
I feel like she was just at that level
Of like
And you're going to be pissed
No matter what, you can't pitch the performance
At the same level for 90 minutes
By the way
It's only an 83 minute movie or something
And I appreciate that
We always call out long movies, let's call out a short one
But to me
I didn't like either
Character
I didn't want to spend any time with them
And I certainly didn't want to spend any time in this situation
I didn't think Linus Roach
Was great at playing
Any aspect of that character
Be it the menace
The regret, anything, I did not find him to be
Particularly great
Nor did I find Anna Gunn to be particularly great
And if you're too
That's like if you're watching Misery where
The Kathy Bates character or the James
Conn character aren't good
And the story sucks
And it's not fun
And it feels like you're watching some like depressing
Holocaust drama
There is nothing
To recommend about this movie
I sort of can't believe Shudder picked it up
It stinks
Sorry
And they fucking wasted Garofalo too
I'm not
I am not surprised
That Shudder picked it up
I think that's a weird picker sometimes
But
You know, look man
I think it's one of these things
Where you're supposed
To be so swept away
By the ultimate
Liberation of this woman
Against this man
That she does
Rise above
The baser instincts
She doesn't sink to his level
She doesn't kill him
She doesn't give him the satisfaction
And instead she very
As a woman at the beginning of the
Thing who can't even handle Christmas dinner
She transforms into
A woman who is able to
Outwit somebody and have
The strength to manipulate him into
Confessing on tape what he did
So he will receive his just punishment
From the authorities
I appreciate
That concept and I think that that's
A great concept
They just don't do anything
With it
I would have rather
Seen something
I would have rather watched a play
Where the two of them
Sat at that kitchen table
And had a
Horrid
Exploratory discussion
About the ins and outs of the whole
Thing and then somehow in the end
You find out she tricked him into confessing
That to me would have been more
Interesting and
Carried more weight and depth
Why are you putting this
And this is what really bothered
Me about the movie
If you're going to approach
This sort of subject matter
Again if you're not going to make it
So wild and insane
Then you better take it seriously
And I don't think they
Took it very seriously
I think they thought they were taking it seriously
But
It kind of reminded me to
I don't know and look I don't mean to speak
I don't mean to speak out of turn
I have not experienced
Anything like this I can't even
Imagine I can't even begin to
Imagine
But it just
It just made me think of like
Like when like
Like sometimes you'll hear
Like black actors or performers
Or artists will say we are more
Than our pain why is
Every not every movie but why are
So many movies about the black experience about
The pain I felt like
That was this was a version
Of this with sexual
Assault where I was like
You're reducing this to just
The pain
And I don't think anybody that's
Experienced this would ever
Want to watch this movie
Like I don't think they would get
Anything from it I feel like it would just
Feel like this
This this
This a wallow
It's not a it's not a catharsis
It's a it's a wallow
It's a great way of putting it
In offensive or I don't want to say offensive
But in in
Touchy topics for no other
Reason than to like give this plot
Points it just feels kind of
Exploitative and
You never get the sort of release
You're waiting for
And yeah I just can't recommend
It it's a bad time
Yeah
Hog down
Hog way down
I didn't
Enjoy Janine's performance in it
I thought the cast
None of the cast bothered me
I thought they were all good
At what they were given to do
I just felt like what they were given to do wasn't
Good so
Yeah they're not like what
You said about them sitting down and talking at the table
It's like the movie doesn't know its characters
Well enough to have that conversation
It's like they don't
They don't really get into the specifics of how they're feeling
In the movie and that's a huge
Mistake for what this movie's
About I think too
That
You know there was
Just from a writing standpoint
None of it really
Made sense it was like it was
Like okay
So he takes he takes
The knives away from her
When he starts telling her
Which is actually a very good scene
When he goes I have news about your daughter
And she's about to cut the cake
And he takes the knife out of her hand
And there's that turn of like
Oh Jesus Christ
What is he about to tell her
That he's
Making sure she can't be armed
In any way
And then he takes the
The kitchen knife set
Like that butcher block set whatever you call it
And he puts it up on top of the fridge
And he starts slowly
And then he makes her
Take you know he has a gun
To make her sit down
So she will listen
And it's for his own protection he says
Why are you doing all that
If you want her to kill you
Once she gets him
In her grasp
I thought he brought the gun so she would kill him
I mean even that was not really clear to me
She ties him up
And then she's got him at gunpoint
And then she's like you want me to kill you
And it's like well wait does he want you to kill him
Because now you have the upper hand
Or did he always want you to kill him
Well at the end of the movie
They make it very clear
That he's always wanted her to kill him
Because he does not want to face
The responsibility
And punishment for what he did
So then why
Just kill yourself
Exactly
Don't take a road trip
To traumatize this woman further
And then
He shows up there
And she's like
When she's talking to him
I'm trying to remember exactly what she says
But she's basically like
All right carry on Joe
I've lost my point sorry
This is the last thing I'll say
How great would this have been
He takes the
Knives from her
He sits her at the table
He tells her what happened
He pulls out a gun
She goes
Oh I guess now that you told me the truth you're going to kill me
He goes this isn't for me
It's for you
He hands her the gun
The only reason I took the knives away
Are because I want it to be quick
And then
It's a movie
Where he's trying to convince him
To kill her
To kill him
He could say I took so much from you
I want to give you your revenge
I'm going to take one shot
At you and miss and I want you to shoot me in the head
At least I haven't seen that a billion times
That's interesting
And then it's her
Will she do it won't she do it
That's what I was going to say
She says to him
I don't I never wanted to
Revenge I never I would never torture
Somebody and it's like then what are
We watching like they
They keep raising these points just to kind
Of let them slide away
And then she says Pat and then she says
When she gets him tied up I lied
I've fantasized about this moment
For 20 years and then she doesn't
Do anything with it
Exactly it's just fucking wishy washy
You know and a movie about
This subject cannot be wishy washy
That sucked oh well
We will be back
With
A little picture
Called rare exports
A Christmas tale
Joseph
Do your plugs
I am at The Patrick Walsh
At Instagram
Joe DeRosa comedy for all
Tour dates people I am
Hitting the road pretty hard
In the new year and boy
Boy do I need to move some tickets
So folks I hope you can come
Out and see me
I will be hitting
The Gramercy Theater
In New York City
On January 13th
Austin Texas 19th and 20th
Of January comedy Mothership
Nashville February 8th
February 9th Charlotte
North Carolina February 10th
Charleston South Carolina
February 15th San Fran
February 16th Hollywood
At the Peppermint Club
San Diego on the 17th House of Blues
San Diego March 14th
Palmdale March 15th Portland
March 16th Seattle
All show info
And ticket links and all that stuff
Is at JoeDeRosa .com
And I hope you come on out to see me
Please also
Come to Joey Roses if you are in New York
JoeyRoses .com is the new
Website for all information
And good stuff
We'll see you next time folks
And we'll see you in hell