I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell
You know I will
Folks, here we are
The finale, the grand finale
Regrets
We've had a few
But then again
Yeah, folks
This is it
We have seen you in hell
We've been seeing you for the last ten years
But it's coming to a close
This show has survived
Different locations
Different
How many different networks were we on?
Let's count them up
Headgum
Well
What's his face?
Danny Harmon
Oh yeah, Starburns
Which I believe no longer exists
That's done
We were on Fangoria's podcast network
That's where it all began
Shoutouts to Ken Hanley
Ken's like
When we do the Netflix documentary of this
Ken will be the one sitting down in the chair
Adjusting his lapel mic
Before we start
Ready to go? Ready to go?
Yeah, so the Fangoria brass came to me
I don't think Ken even listens to
The show anymore
He may not
But yeah, he kind of
Put it together
I was reminded that in 2023
We already did sort of a oral history
Of the show, so we're not going that route again
But
I did see on Instagram a bunch of like
Memories on the See You in Hell
Pod page of people saying their favorite
Times of the show. Many I remembered
And brought a laugh to my heart
And many I was like, I don't know what the fuck this is
So we're gonna read through some of those
And see what we remember
But really ten years is a
It's a big deal
It's an accomplishment
And Joe and I were, you know, it was basically down to
Are we doubling down and doing another ten?
Or are we saying
This is a great accomplishment, let's move on with our life
And reading the comments
Right before we came on here, it just got posted
And announced on Instagram that we're ending it
I feel like you guys are not happy
You're not pleased
But I think you get it, you know
Ten years is a really long time to do anything
So, here we are
The Instagram now
And for whatever reason, I can't
Find it. Oh there it is, See You in Hell
I'm just pulling up so I can see
67 comments
The announcement just went out
Well, it's also this thing now
If you don't, like I post every year
Like one post a year
No one ever sees your posts anymore
Like you gotta get on the algorithm
And I don't think we're really on it
So people are probably still finding out
CKrab underscore runs
Right, does anyone have
Another podcast to recommend
Let the body get cold
Jesus
Yeah, it's like
Honey, I want a divorce
Okay, that's fine
Do you have any friends you could set me up with?
It's an odd transition
PJ Kiki
I guess it's pronounced
This just absolutely crushed me
Jesus, come on guys
Come on
Well, let's focus on the pause
Which is Emily asking
What are your favorite moments?
I'm gonna skip over like I'm devastated
We appreciate that
We do, it just makes me feel bad
Well, let me ask you before we turn to Instagram
Joseph, what
Do you have a favorite
Episode, a favorite story
I mean the one I saw in these comments
That made me go yeah, that was
When we were fired on all cylinders was
The Burt Young story
Yes
And Jesse Pop was in town this weekend
Which reminded me of that again
But just us going to see Burt Young
In a
A very bargain
Basement play
I tried to listen to that
Episode recently and I hated how
Broken up it was by ads
Which is a problem of being on all these different
Networks is that we have ads
We don't even know who's getting paid
Not us, I assure you
It's crazy though
Change, yeah
$12 every three months or something
Yeah
But that's one, I mean the one I see a lot is
Of course Joe's take on Jeepers Creepers
Which I think should find its way into
Your stand up at some point
Do you think it's well
Known enough to do it as a stand up
Routine? Yes
Alright
Con shitting on the floor
The second the episode began
Was a very memorable moment
What is yours
Joe, do you have any
I think the most fun was always
When we were in the same room having some drinks
It can't have that magic
Quality over Zoom, we try to capture it
And I think we do a good job
But knowing that we were going to go out and get wasted
After always gave the pot a lot more
Energy I think
It gives anything a lot more energy
It is true, it is something to truly
Look forward to
Yes
Well you know man
My favorite will always probably be
When you were wearing that
Whatever the hell that thing was
That sweater that you were going to give your dad
And I just couldn't wrap my head around
That you were wearing a gift that you were going to give to your dad
To be honest
I don't know what I was thinking at the time
That was great
My favorite line
From the entire podcast is
When you referred to Rex Reed as a mean old bitch
That's probably the hardest
I've laughed
And I still laugh at it
You've said a million things that make me laugh
But that was definitely my favorite line
That was one of those ones where I would like
Oh we were doing the pod today
And Pat said this
Like you know you brag to your friends
About what your funny friend said
Your friends go, who's Rex Reed?
Why is that funny? Why are you talking to us?
But you know man
It's been a journey man
It's been a journey
I've been very touched
By the fans
Obviously
By the people that have contributed over the years
Out of the kindness of their hearts
You know man Christ almighty
When we did that live show from New York
Not the first one where Krumholtz came on
And insulted me the entire time
But the second one
From the coffee shop
The Black Cat coffee shop
By the way rest in peace to Justin
The guy that owned that place died
Very sad, he was like 37
Died in his sleep
I don't think it was
I think it was just health or something
He wasn't sick
Or at least I don't think he was
But anyway
But when we did the show there at the Black Cat
You know I remember like Ken and Liz
And people showing up early for the show
Like helping us move chairs
Not because we said can you guys help us
Like you turn around
And Ken's moving chairs around
And you're like Ken
You don't have to do that
Thank you, Jesus
It's just been special
Those were probably
I would say our strongest
Live shows
Were those two at the Black Cat
And the party after was awesome
But the best live show ever
Obviously was fucking Lloyd Kaufman
In New York
I mean that was nuts
That was a blast, it really was
He's a legend
Chicago was a lot of fun too
Chicago was awesome
We had some great live shows, it was always really fun meeting you guys
LA, the first one ever
Was in LA, the first two ever
LA, for sure
And by the way
I'm not against and I'm sure Pat isn't either
Somewhere down the line
You know, just doing a live show
For the fun of it, man
Getting everybody together
And you know
Talking about some horror movies
Yeah, well we'll do an Eagles type thing
We'll play the Sphere
Probably around December
I think we'll announce that
But I would love to
Some favorite memories here
So every single on with the show
And on with the Joe
Says Christina Fuego
I forgot we even used to do that
But on
With the Joe
Yeah, an odd thing
We used to do, a bunch of different
Styles of that
I think for the 10 year anniversary
They should do a throwback to their Sam Elliott impression
But have him order from Joey Roses
We did used to do a lot of Sam Elliott, Gandolfini
We had a
Yes, and I forgot
I forget how to do the Sam Elliott
Impression
I think I'm going to talk about this
When we did
When we were at South by Southwest and I did the street food
Thing that I do there
James Adomian was on it
And I said, would you please do
Jesse Ventura
Reviewing Joey Roses
Yeah
And god damn man, it was like
He was like, they fed me turkey
I didn't believe it
It was a foreign meat
It was so fucking funny man
And then he did Elon Musk reviewing Joey Roses
Which was, it was both of them
Were so funny, anyway
I wish I could remember how to do the damn Sam Elliott
To meet that request
I literally don't even know where to start with it
I don't really have that either anymore
You guys drinking
Screwdrivers before that wedding
What would that have been? Pete's wedding
Or Jamie Lee's wedding
We were pounding screwdrivers and recording
Like wearing suits before we went to a wedding
That
I think Jamie's
And Dan's
Or was it Pete's?
Or was it Vincent
Georgia
No
Because we had to drive up
90 minutes to that wedding
That's why I don't think it was Pete's either
Pete's was out in
God damn sticks
No that was
No, Pete's was up in like wine country
But it was only like 45 minutes
That's it?
Yeah
You and I were staying at a hotel
I think we did
We didn't wind up staying at our hotel room
We left early
Was it your wedding?
No, I didn't drink before my wedding
I drank after my wedding, believe me
I drank through your entire
I remember being up in the room with you
With like Ian and everybody getting ready
And just was fucking hammered
At that point
Yeah, well I was like why did I remember
What wedding it is? And then I'm like oh right
He says right here in his question
You guys were pounding screwdrivers at 10 in the morning
That's why I don't remember it
I'll tell you
This is favorite memories
My favorite
Drinking memory with Pat
With this show
Is when we did the Mile High Horror
Festival in Denver
Yeah, people were mentioning that, the Maniac Cop
Yeah, and we had to do Maniac Cop 2
8 a .m. screening
Just madness
And drinking at
7 a .m.
We ordered so many drinks
And then still standing
At a strip club at
2 o 'clock in the morning I don't know how it was
Even humanly possible
Still drinking, no drugs
Just booze
I don't
And then sat through movies throughout the day
I still don't understand how we did that
I got back to my hotel room
At about 3 a .m.
And between 8 a .m. and 3 a .m.
We were at, remember we were at that
Bar where we were sitting in those
Wooden chairs that were close to the floor
It was like a ski lodge vibe
Yeah, and we met that woman who was like
She was being really nice
To us and she was like, she kind of took us in
And was showing us around
And then we were like, so do you come to the festival
Or what? She's like, what?
No, I'm just hanging out
She just was a random person
That for whatever reason just started
Hanging out, I still don't understand
What that was
Yeah, that was in Littleton, Colorado
Home of Columbine, and then we drove
To the airport in the back of a van
With the twins from The Shining
That was one of the cooler memories of my
Life
They were 60 years old whispering in each other's
Ears, but yeah
Still, every bit is creepy
Every bit is creepy
Jayrod
Paak says, I really like the story Pat
Told about the dude coming in to get his PlayStation
Set up and just fucking everything up
Yeah, that was the guy who I think was drunk
Setting up my home entertainment
System. Yes, another favorite Pat
Line
And then he placed his drink
Oh yeah
So close to the edge of the table I can
Only describe it as criminally insane
That's the good thing about not having any
Memory is that people tell you things you said
And it's like really funny to you
Because it's your sense of humor, obviously
Pat yelling at the kids at Bad
Santa too, that's maybe the
Darkest day of my life
Drinking at noon and yelling at children
I was Bad Santa
Swal J
has got a bunch
The Iron Giant
You fucking queef
You said who likes the Iron Giant
And I screamed, I like the Iron Giant
You fucking queef
I don't remember why that happened
Crane shots where we briefly had a segment
Devoted to 25 year old
Episodes of Frasier
Perfect Strangers reviews
Joe not watching Sopranos or Breaking Bad
Despite being a character in the Breaking Bad
Universe
Sam Elliott, Cami, Cami Diaz
Of course
Favorite review
That was
James Lipton, remember at Conan
He kept wanting to meet Cami
And then he wrote in lipstick
On her mirror and she was like
I've never met this man before
I was like oh he told me you guys
Were very close
Favorite review was Avengers Infinity War
Wow, interesting
That's the one where
That's the one where Ken Hanley publicly
Said I'm done with the podcast
And then he came back
Because that was the one where you didn't see it
And I just described the movie to you
And told you how much it sucked
I didn't see it and we reviewed it
And people were like
Guys, Jesus Christ
We were about to go on a break
And that was
Yet one of the other times
Where we were like we might just end this guys
Like we're kind of getting
And we just did this episode where I was like
I'll just describe Infinity War to you
You don't need to see it, it sucks
And people were not happy
Also because they loved Infinity War
People thought it was awesome
I honestly love how dismissive
That is of the whole Marvel experience
We were right
God damn it
The episodes that deserve more praise
And I agree are our
Season two
Seven Deadly Sins episodes
Where if you'll remember we were like let's do an
Entirely new format for season two
And then discussed
The seven sins which was a lot of fun
There's so many highlights but I love the ones
Where you're hanging with the boys, hearing about what they're doing
The love hate relationship with booze
Blah blah blah
Thank you much
There's a bunch here, Pat's outrageous story
About the Down syndrome girl when he
Was a teenager
Oh okay yeah
At the Special Olympics
The girl I was watching pulled her
Sweatpants and underwear down and rubbed her
Giant muff on my leg
On your leg?
Talking to my buddy Ryan Haynes and all of a sudden
His eyes get like dinner plates
He's looking down, he's like Pat, Pat, Pat
I go what? I look down and this girl is rubbing
Her pussy on my leg
The 14 year old girl with Down syndrome
And I threw both of my hands in the air
And was like help, someone help
Everyone see what's happening here
Please help me
I didn't want anyone to think I did it
I swear I don't like it
I swear
I'm getting harder and harder
Patting sweat off your brow
Boy I hate this
Yeah steam coming out of my ears
Also was it
Some weird dream or did Joe talk about
Pranking his mom once?
Like a toilet prank?
Yes, no that's not a weird dream
Oh I remember that
Yeah the two pranks I remember
Pulling on my mom when she got mad
One was I did the saran wrap
Over the toilet bowl
On April Fool's Day
I was at my friend Billy Morgan's house
And she called me and I was like hey mom
And she was like get your fucking ass home now
Like she was furious
That's not one for the moms
That kind of humor
Must have worked, she either pissed
Or shit and it went everywhere
And then the other one
Was I snuck
This still makes me laugh
Put a Freddy Krueger mask on
Snuck into her bedroom
This is a really
Nasty prank
Got nose to nose with her while she was sleeping
Turned a flashlight
Under my face
So it
You know the spooky ghost story flashlight
Yeah sure
And then gently woke her up
And my god dude
I gotta do that to somebody again
She really screamed
Jesus Christ like cartoon screamed
I'm crying from laughing
I fucking hate pranks
I always felt like if I spent one day on the jackass set
I would commit suicide
I would not be able to handle that
When I watch the super cuts on Instagram
Of people like
There's guys where their whole feed is like
Me scaring my mom
There's a guy in like Germany that like
Walk like
He walks into the room, his mom's never looking
And he goes
Every time
She does like the run
And falls to the ground
And then chases him
With a stick like you
In German you son of a bitch
God makes me laugh
Alright anyway sorry
No that's great
The one time I pranked my father was that salt shaker thing
Where he lectured me for days
About how wrong and bad
Pranks are because he got his feelings hurt
That's funny because
When you tell the
Bad Santa story
With the kids
I always picture
Even from the first time you told me
And I never said this
I always picture this episode of Frasier
Where Niles is in the coffee shop
And scolds these kids
And the reason he scolds them
Is because it's the salt shaker prank
And he goes
If you are not grown up enough to be in
To act like you belong here then you should not be in
Whatever and then it turns out two adult men
Did it to him
And that's the gag
But I always thought of that scene
When you would tell me about you yelling at the kids
And then
You actually also have a connection to the prank
In that scene that's weird
Yeah
Yeah I guess like father like son
That's not true I hate that I said that
Please strike that from the record
Every live show has been great
But Chicago was particularly raucous and fun
Happy tenth boys
Pat's post office and Amazon customer
Pat's stories always entertain
The fairly drunk maniac cop 2 live ep
Joe criticizing Pat's
Sweater and it getting very personal
The sperm donation chat
I forgot I told that story in the first
Hellraiser commentary
And every single poetic description
Of what their hogs are doing
Oh and Pat's claydoh story
I forgot I even told some of these tales
Back in the day we did used to drink a lot on the air
Claydoh was like the fake
Playdoh?
Yeah I got a fake Playdoh set
And that's how I found out
There was no Santa and that my family
Was poor
Because my mom started sobbing when I was like
I told Santa exactly what I wanted
I told him specifically
What I wanted why don't get this
And my mom starts crying I'm like what are you upset
About it's not like you bought it
And she was like I did I'm Santa
We're poor
What the hell could the dollar difference between
Playdoh and Claydoh be
Even as a kid
Even as a kid consoling
My sobbing mother I wanted to be like
But come on now we couldn't have sprung
An extra three bucks for the real thing
That's wild
We weren't doing great for a couple years
The episode that
Began with Khan shitting on the floor is one of my
Hardest laughs ever yeah that was amazing
What's a Khan update maybe
People would like that is he alive
He's alive and well man he lives with
My parents
All right you know whenever
I see him he still remembers me
And whenever I sleep there
Which is not very often but when I do
I'll always sleep with me it's very nice
We reminisce about
The old times it's kind of like
You see your ex wife at a wedding and
You end up banging and then you leave
That hasn't happened to me
Yet but we'll see
I mean you know what I mean
I'm talking like a George Clooney
Julia Roberts
Ticket to Paradise
Yeah but he's
Good he's very healthy
Good
Here's one maybe you'll remember because I don't know who this
Woman is Joe and Pat's back and forth
On Lindy West
Is one of the funniest rage moments
On the entire show
Feminist woman Lindy West
Yeah she's like the epitome
Of what's
That what's that what's the
Buzzfeed for feminists Delilah
Jezebel
She's like
She's like the personification
Of Jezebel and
Oh love actually right
She went off about love actually
She went after my buddy Sam Morel
For some jokes he did like she
She's yeah she's always
She said that
Because she was an overweight woman that
Something about like
She was
It was discriminatory to suggest
Or to have a workout room at work
That's not
What it was but it was something that crazy
Like she's always got some
It was probably that they described that woman
And love actually as fat when she's just
Not even remotely
Fat I know I always thought they should
Have said slob
Piggy
And Hugh Grant's voice no less
My friend Russ
What are you doing that love you looking for some truffles
Is that what you're looking for you pig
You fucking pig
Russ has a joke
You know I like chicks any
Size man I'm not discriminatory against a
Heavy set chick I mean not like that fat pig Tyra
Banks but you know within reason
That's a good joke
John Candy episode I forgot we did a whole
John Candy episode Liz Sheldon says I
Asked Pat on Twitter if they could do it and they did
And it's probably my favorite episode so there you go
We do love John Candy
And a little update because I know Colin
Hanks socially
That documentary is coming out in October
Which I am extremely
Excited about I might be able to get an
Advanced viewing of it
And there's a new John Candy biography
Written by Mike Myers brother Paul Myers
Who I'm sure would rather I not refer to him as
Mike Myers brother
Now do you think
The doc
Yeah do you think there's going to be
I'm excited to see it you know
But I've seen some shorter
Previous John Candy bio
Shows or whatever do you think
There's going to be stuff in there we don't know
Like some wild stories
Or some dark whatever
Or do you think it's really just going to be a
Kind of we kind of know there's nothing
To know you know like
I'd be surprised if there's any
Surprises in it you know
I think because of how heavily
His children and family are involved
It's not going to be a super warts and all
Is my guess
I think they'll talk about his appetites
For drinking food
Other things and probably
Just leave it at that but
I read a pretty mean biography
Of him that McCarthy gave me
Which was like
Just this guy who outside of
Planes, trains and automobiles he thought John Candy
Had never made a funny movie
So it's like why are you writing this book
But there was nothing
Scandalous what I have heard about
John Candy is that he was obsessed with
Marijuana and that's not the vibe he
Gives off and not something I ever
Would have thought but
I always heard this story of him like
Baking marijuana into the Thanksgiving
Turkey one year I'd love to hear that story
Christ
But I guess it was a pothead I find that
Kind of hard to believe but
Hopefully we'll find out about that
The Midsummer
Episode yeah I mean look
That episode
Was another turning point for the show it's like
Joe and I have always been
Mature enough to go
Hey let's not blow
Up the friendship over the podcast
And that's a big part of the show ending
Ultimately as well we don't
I'll tease it
You may never hear it
But there was
It has been recorded
A 10th anniversary episode that we have not
Released because we got
Into a fight on it
And looking back it was really minor
Especially compared to Midsummer but
It was just an accumulation
Of shit and
We recorded a updated
Commentary of the Children of the
Corn remake that was
On Shudder
And ultimately the movie is not great
It wasn't a particularly funny episode
Believe us when we say you're not missing
Much but that was kind
Of the pressure valve for the podcast we
Needed to kind of discuss
The you know what was happening and
I immediately
By the way and
It's something I would I want to say
To you and I have no
Issue saying in front of the audience
Immediately
As soon as we said we're
Going to end things and in these
Last few episodes we recorded
I immediately felt
And again guys it's not that this is a burden
Or anything it's just it's just kind of where you get
Eventually with something
You get to a point where it's time to move on and if you
Don't it's going to
Affect you personally and that's
All we're saying but I
Immediately felt a shift in the
Dynamic between you and me I just
Was like this okay like
You know there was there was a little bit of room to breathe
You know
You start building up just shitty
Resentments and then when you start it's like a marriage
Or anything else and when you start putting them out in the open
You're like you were completely
Wrong in your perception of that and
You were completely wrong in your perception of that
And you often find out there was
No real issue
At the core but we were
Just getting sick of it you know
That's that's all it is really it's
It's having to schedule an additional
Four or five hours a month
Plus an additional ten twelve hours
To watch the fucking movies I'm going to start
Doing new content
On my YouTube channel and
I am going to be very soon
Releasing a new YouTube show
I don't know I wouldn't call it a podcast
Necessarily it might be
Part podcast but the point is it's more
Geared for YouTube but I'm
Going to do it alone
Because
You know I was laughing with a
Friend of mine the other day and he
He's got a very popular long -running podcast
And he goes yeah you want to ever end
A friendship start a podcast with your
Buddy and there's something
Weird about it there's something weird
In the dynamic
That it forges between two people
Because
I don't know
It's monetizing your fun
It's monetizing what you and I have
Taken for granted as this very
Low
Pressure low
Problem
Friendship this great decade
Long friendship which has lasted
Roughly as long as the podcast maybe
A little more obviously a little more but
Yeah it's monetizing
And making a job out of
Your friendship and that became worse
When we separated
Locationally
Because as I said on the
Other episode you wind up only
Speaking to schedule a podcast
And then the friendship kind of becomes
This not important thing
It's secondary to the quote business
It's not great yeah
And that said
The
Location shift I think
On the other hand
And I owe this to
Pat I owe it to the show and I
Owe it to the supporters and
Listeners
It
Weirdly saved my ass during
Covid
Because it gave us something to do
A million percent
And also too
Strangely during Covid
Is when the show started to finally
Not monetize
Greatly but it but it started to monetize
And
Or maybe it was just post Covid or whatever
But the point is is during a struggling
Hard time
Both personally and professionally
The show
Was there so I could see
A friend talk to a friend
Hear from fans talk to fans I remember
Going in once or twice to the chat
You know the online hangs during Covid
Same yeah
And also too and it's never about the
Money but it was just the fact that it was
Starting to pick up and make some cash
You know that was
The generosity of people to pay for
Something like this at that period was
Was even after that period
Was extraordinary
And also too it was like
Holy shit like
Alright cool this obviously helps
Like we're all struggling right now
So yeah we were
And remain blown away by that
It's like we're asking people at a difficult
Time that's only gotten more difficult
In recent months financially for everybody
And we're asking for money to stay afloat
It winds up being uncomfortable
But I think we came
You know it required a lot of
Discussion but I think we came to a great price
Point I feel like a lot of our
You know you got
You guys kept the pod running you know that
I'm skipping all the comments that say
We love you guys you saved
My life you got me through this difficult time
And the DMs I've gotten things that made me
Tear up I always send them to Joe
We always see them even if we don't respond
We try to respond but as
Much as we helped you guys
Through that dark time Joe's making a great
Point there you guys helped us as well
Yeah it's like I
If you don't see anybody for three
Months which was the case
In those COVID
Times you start going
Nuts having four hours a month
Where you have to like force
Socialization even though it is with a friend
It really helped like it
Really helped and to go see these movies and
Talk and laugh and hear your guys
Feedback the comments even
Though of course we bitch we only focus on
The negative which is just how our brains
Are wired sadly
But the comments you guys give us
Are just they give us life so
Kind and funny and wonderful
There's one I keep seeing in the comments Joe
Maybe you remember this better than I do but
So this one says zombie shark
1980 Joe's story
About the child showing up at his house really
Made me laugh that's a very recent one that was very
Funny oh yeah
Also Pat's delivery of
I'm taking my calendar to Atlantic
City
I keep seeing that
I'm taking my flower calendar to Atlantic
City I don't know what that means
What is a flower calendar
I don't know
So somebody's gonna have to reach
Out on a comment and just explain to
Me what I was talking about because
I'm like well it sounds funny but
I don't know what that means yeah what the hell
Does that mean love
The boys shitting all over Veronica
Which was the Glenn Danzig
Vehicle oh
Yeah you know we never got to his
Second one I don't even know if it was ever released
But he had like that werewolf
Thing coming out or whatever I don't
Think that was released
Love Joe making fun of sopranos in the
Borat episode I guess that's Borat 2
I love sopranos
But Joe is hilarious as Tony
Obviously a tour would be great but I'd
Love if the boys did some commentaries like in the
Beginning we did we did but you're
Not gonna hear it and yeah we
Did and we ruined it
The recap are
Here we go oh the recaps of Kevin Spacey's
Bizarre Frank Underwood apology videos
Always make me laugh those are some
Whenever I'd see one of those that would be really
Exciting knowing that we were gonna be able to talk about
That on the show
The Elvis episode is gold
When Pat tells us the story of him watching
The Elvis concert from Blockbuster Video
Oh yeah when he used to pull his
Jumpsuit down to reveal his nipple
And then hit his nipple with the
Microphone like it was erotic
And this is during Fat Elvis
Favorite
Pat line I didn't realize you were
Scarface Joe comes to mind
Amongst the many sopranos kerfuffles
I don't know what that means either no idea
This one made me laugh I don't know if
You said it I said it or if this is just somebody
Being funny Christopher Lee to his
Agent after rejecting a part in
Monster Club hand on the
Doorknob as he's leaving and if you
Need me I'll be in golf sluts
Before
Do you know what that means
Wait say this again what
It's Christopher Lee
Did we ever talk about Monster
Club
Yes
What's the line at the end no no no
Wait yes Monster Club is the thing
With Vincent it's the anthology with
Vincent Price where he
He's at the Monster Club remember
Yeah Christopher Lee to his
Agent after rejecting a part in
Monster Club and if you need me
I'll be in golf sluts for
I guess
Christopher Lee was in a movie called golf
Sluts floor I guess so and said
But he said no to Monster Club
I'm seeing a lot
Of Jeepers Creepers and a lot of Burt Young
Play and I think those are some real highlights
For sure
Lloyd Kaufman of course
One of my favorite moments
Was from the Rogue One episode
Pat and Joe come in swinging at each other
About going out for drinks
Or hanging at Pat's palatial estate
I remember that fight
Pat has some real hard digs at Joe's
Failure to quote
Put it in anything
To which Joe replies you nasty
Bitch lol
Yeah that was like
I don't know we didn't go out for my
Birthday or something like that
I don't know some of these fights I'd probably
Listen to them and just laugh and think like
What were we even talking about
That and the story about the game
Oh yeah the game at Pete Holmes' house that we weren't
Paying attention to learning at a party
And the songs that we would listen to
While leaving the party while miming
Driving a huge steering wheel do you remember that?
I think so
A lot of these we were just drunk
I'll be honest with you
Okay every single folks
Joe was trying to describe
Some touring van thing
But he kept fumbling through trying to explain it
For about a minute then Pat says
Well Joe I couldn't have said it better myself
Some of these are just lines
I guess
The first two years of them being absolutely
Depressed is some of the best podcasting
Ever sure thank you for that
This is one of my
Favorites Joe calling Pat a person
That lives under a dock when he
Found out that Pat had bare naked ladies
Sticker on his car in high school
Every moment's been great but I just
Appreciate the growth of hearing two good pals
Hang out and their friendship has helped me through
Tough times
Pat's disgust watching Human Centipede
Is always a highlight for me
Yeah I can't believe
That's a good question like which are the two I wish
I had not seen
Human Centipede's one for sure
And then if you'll remember I couldn't finish
Hellraiser I've got a much better
Tolerance for shit now
Way better
Goodfellas is
The McRib
You know what that means?
No
No clue here either
Pat and Joe somehow not realizing that Furioso
Was a prequel I think that was just me
Wasn't it?
And that Anya Taylor Joe's character
And Charlize's character were one and the same
Yeah that was me
Loved Joe and Pat both realizing
They were fed up with Kehui Kwan
And Brendan Fraser during their Oscar circuit
Oh yeah that hasn't ended
No it's still there
And we're still pretending he's going to be famous
Again Kehui Kwan
Pat singing
The Drake medley in a recent solo
Corner Joe shitting on Elizabeth
Moss and how she
Looks like she smells bad
Joe's joke about Kermit the Frog
Having Brussels sprouts balls
You guys got a good memory I guess
That's also you listen to this stuff a lot more
But yeah
I mean for me I was never a horror
Guy when Joe called me and asked me to do
This it was like when you first meet like
Somebody you're really excited about or whatever
Like we were like newly
In love or something and Joe asked me to do the podcast
And I was like well I remember saying I
Don't really care about horror I don't watch a lot
Of horror I'm not even a fan
And that's definitely changed over this 10 years
I would consider myself sort of an expert
And it was a genre I barely
Paid much attention to I also
Can watch anything and not be bothered
Sure
How about yourself Joe how has your relationship
To horror changed
It's um
Well I will say that like
It's funny we were just talking about
This when I was on the road
My friend Matt Richards who's a very funny comic
His dad was out with us
And hanging out and his dad
Was talking about The Exorcist and he was like
I watched that movie
On TV edited with commercials
And it scared me so bad
That I will never watch it ever again
Like I don't like horror movies
And Matt
Who's a uh
You know he's kind of like he's like
A sort of clairvoyant
He's a comic but he does all this
Also magician clairvoyant
Thing that's very cool and uh
And he was like
He's like dude I don't go to
Haunted houses I don't fuck with stuff like that
Like whatever and it's interesting
Because
You know he's a guy
That
You know like I've seen him
Do stuff it's pretty impressive like
And you make I don't know I'm like if you
If you see him do these things you're like I guess
This is real like you know people
Have this gift uh this
Is certainly convincing display of it
But it's interesting that a guy that does that kind of
Stuff is like yeah I don't really fuck with horror
Um
But I was telling them is the point I'm getting
At sorry
That uh nothing scares me
At all anymore and it's the reason I will
Only watch The Exorcist every few years
Is because I never wanted to lose the fact
That it scares me
But that's my that's my relationship
Now I mean I'd be hard
Pressed
You could tell me this movie
That I just saw man is the scariest fucking
Thing that's ever been made whatever I
Yeah it's not
It's just not gonna freak me out I don't think
That's I love watching
It and I have fun watching it
But uh you know and it's
Not to say I can't
Jump or recoil
Right but a movie
Scaring me
Was a thing that would happen far
More frequently 10
Years ago than it than it ever does
Now I mean it doesn't
It doesn't get in my bones anymore you
Know no totally same
I uh I think it was when you were
Out here Joe there was a guy or we passed
This girl who was talking about how she loves
Jump scares
And you're like oh there are people out there
Yes like these bad things
That everyone thinks who keeps
Making these horror movies that's just jump scare
After jump scare yes and then just walking
Past a young woman she was saying the words
I love a good jump scare
So they're out there
Um and look we
Did three comedies this month I mean that
The podcast over time we were like
Can we do this can we talk about another
Type of movie and now we just kind of
Do whatever we want the appeal
Of the show I think has always been
Joe and myself
Um but I hope we brought you
Guys some new movies a lot of people were saying
You know we helped shape your taste and shit
Like that that's interesting
The podcast that I listen to you know
Always turned me on to new music and movies
And shit but yeah
You know it's great reading all these
Classic memories
Uh the new post that just went up
It seems like you guys are very sad
And I get it
We appreciate it yes
We're sad
Uh but
You know to go back to something you
Were saying earlier
Um
You know
It was when we were talking about
The you know during
Tough financial times the fact that people
Have and continue
To support the show
Uh really
Has meant more than we are able to put into words
Yeah
And that is the
Number one driving thing
You know in addition to
Pat and I wanting to just get back
To having a friendship
We never ever
Ever took that for granted
Or would ever want to deliver
You something that would
In turn
Be taking that for granted
You know we're very aware
Of what money means
To people these days
We're very aware of
Inflation and the economy
And the job market and
The struggles
The economic struggles presented
In modern day society
Uh that seem to keep worsening
Sadly
Yeah
We're very aware we don't take any of that for granted
Um and the last thing we ever
Would want to do is deliver you a product
Where we're kind of gritting our teeth
And
Not stepping up to the plate
Ready to hit as
At least give our best shot at hitting a
Home run that we can
Um so you know
That's important to me to uh
That everybody knows that and the fact that you're
Leaving these beautiful comments
And talking about how sad you are
Only reinforces that
Uh sentiment
Uh it only reinforces that it's the
Right thing to do sad as it is
To say let's
Let's uh take a breath here
Because it's
Your value
Of this show and
What you invest in it is far too
Meaningful for us to just trudge forward
Uh blindly
That's very true we have
The only time the comment really pissed
Me off genuinely
Would be any
Implication that Joe and I were like trying
To get your money or something like that
Because we stress
Over this shit I just saw a comment
Here where a woman was like I had to cancel my
My Patreon because I
Went on maternity leave and I wasn't able to
Afford it that stuff
Eats away at me you know like we
Were charging a little more than we probably
Than we wanted to
But that was because we had to do that to keep it
Going but the thought of somebody
Like
Stressing about can I afford the podcast
This month
I hate that you know it's sad to me
It sucks and I'll
I'll highlight a negative one
Why not
But this was only to me it wasn't on the main
Thing
Yeah some guy goes I just put out
I don't know one of the posts
I think it was the Kill Tony I'm on
Kill Tony it's out today whatever
And some guy wrote like
Hey man you gonna plan on doing your own
Podcast anytime soon you know the one
That we've all been paying twelve
Dollars a month for for all these years
What gives man it's like
What gives
We deliver four episodes
Every month that's what gives
You will get them before
The end of the month that's what gives
Like what oh
A comment like that chaps my ass
Yeah
Anytime it'll be like
Guys we'd really like this to be a
One episode a week structure it's like
Well then do your own podcast
You know and that's
That's the thing too it's like
We were putting the work and effort
In and then if any comment would be negative
It would be like you mother fuck even though these
Are our friends and fans and supporters
We were just it's like
Anything you know you get out of a bad
Relationship and you're like why was I
So impossible at the end there
And it's because the relationship becomes this
Other thing and a podcast
Becomes another thing
And that's
It I mean I'm sure you guys get it at this
Point you understand yeah what would
You say are your favorite five horror
Movies released since we started doing
The podcast or a five
You know we don't have to have it in order
Jesus
That's a tough one man
Off the top
My head I don't know
Comedy I think my number
One comedy in the last five years I
Probably gave a B plus two or something
You know because comedy is in such a bad place
There's been a lot of good horror in the last ten
Years well you know
Smile was a pleasant surprise
Sure
I mean I'm gonna I'm only gonna remember
Once recently but you know
The ugly step sister was fantastic
Um
What else did we get
We got the evil dead reboot
No was that before we did this show
That was good well oh no
Evil dead rise definitely
Yeah
I mean look I'm gonna throw
Hereditary on there sure
I don't know that
28 years makes the cut
Um
But
I liked
What are some earlier ones we did that we
Raved about
I mean yeah I wish
I had the episode list in front of me
I gotta be honest I don't even know where to go
To get the old episodes
Yeah um
I'm shocked that people
Know where they are I don't even know where they are
Well they're on itunes
And stuff for me the big
Uh annoying thing about
Our itunes is when you go to the page
The number one comment that not that it means
The most popular comment or anything but one of
Two comments that shows up says these guys
Should never discuss race
And it's like how
Is that anybody's take away from this podcast
That seems like somebody who hates joe
Or something who wrote that yeah probably
I have that effect on people
Uh but I'm scrolling
Through now dragged across concrete not
A horror movie but not horror but excellent
That I loved
Uh
It follows
It follows way
Up there
Uh not bird box
No
Men would be one of my least
Favorites
What the hell is cam
Cam remember what that was
Cam was a cam girl
I don't remember the movie but it was a cam girl
Vibe
Green room if that's ten years
That makes it for me
Apostle was that good
I don't remember it was cool I think
Yeah it was cool oh mandy
Mandy was excellent
You love mandy that's on my list
Get out is obviously on my list
Get out
Well solo
Came out
Which is not horror but
One of my favorite star wars
Movies uh solos
Is great solos great weapons makes my
Cut
I need to see it
That's a good that's a good bunch
Under the skin parasite
Which is not horror but oh yeah
Parasite
Uh I can
I'm seeing a few that I didn't like
Least favorite five
Quiet place
Annihilation
I like both of those to some degree
Uh
Mom and dad was on here which I actually
Thought was good
Winchester just a
Oh my god that sucked
We saw remember that Joe we saw
That in Vegas
God it blew
Joe had a show
I don't think I'd ever seen Joe do like a full
Standup set at a casino or on a
Like an hour long thing and I was sitting in the back
And Joe comes out
Tells a couple jokes
And this lady says something
I don't even know what Joe was like
What did you say you
Bitch it was like that kind of
I don't think I called her a bitch
It was a jaw
On the floor half the crowd was laughing half
Was shocked I thought it was awesome and the second
I think it was two shows one was just
Standard stand up and one you had some
Sort of bee in your bonnet there was something
Going on in the one uh
But then we saw Winchester because we stayed at a hotel
That had a movie theater and I think
That may be the only movie in ten
Years that we covered that you and I saw together
No that's not true we saw
Last Jedi together we saw
We used to see a lot of movies
Cheesecake Factory
Super Dark Times
One I forgot about
That's a good movie yeah
The Fury
That's an old De Palma movie
Brawl and Cell Block
1999 came out
Since we started this show
Not a bad flick
Not excellent
Gerald's Game
You know they're saying this long walk
Is
Some of the reviews are saying it's the best
Stephen King adaptation ever
No
I mean I'm excited to see it
These are the ones that are good
When they adapt his simple stories
Gerald's Game
Misery the mist
Things that are very just like
It's characters in a situation
This is the situation point A to point B
Let's see how it turns
That's always the best adaptations with him
Whenever they get into the
Heavy supernatural stuff
And whatever it's
You know
They change too much and it just doesn't work
I am reading currently
The Bachman books
Which will get me
Two upcoming movies
Running Man and
The Long Walk and I've never read either story
I think the Running Man
Trailer I'm very
Underwhelmed by it
This does not look
Interesting to me
I've liked each
Edgar Wright film half as much
As the one that preceded it
I think he's great but I like each one
A little bit less for sure
I think it's an obviously truer
I guess truer
Adaptation
That's usually the reason they go back
To the well on these things
I don't know man
That's one of the ones where the changes they did make
Worked for me
It's just cooler to see
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Stuck in this early
90s dystopian arena
Fighting
These lunatics
That are like
Villains from a Flash comic
Book or something
This new one
Unless they just aren't showing it to you
It's way more just like you're out in the city
And people are trying to kill you
And I'm like I don't know
Who cares
And then what is the plot of The Long Walk?
It's
You walk
Until there's only one person left alive
If you stop walking they shoot you
And I think it's they do it because
Everything
People are so desperate that
They do
They sign up for this thing to get money
It's kind of like a precursor to the Hunger Games or whatever I guess
It sounds like they shoot horses don't they
Where you gotta keep dancing or they kill you
They did an always Sonny spoofing that
But yeah it's good
It looks good
And Mark Hamill plays the villain
Which I think he'll be good at
He's usually good at that kind of stuff
Suspiria remake
Doctor Sleep
Don't Breathe
The Conjuring was fun
It's been a
Prisoners
It's been a great horror decade for sure
Yeah it's
It's been good man
It's been good and there's a lot more to come
And I'm sure
In our own ways
Pat and I will be
Finding out some way
To talk publicly about
Horror movies
Through our own devices
And you know
It's a conversation I hope to continue to have
With all of you out there
In some way shape or form
And you know
I don't know man
That's
I don't mean to say there's not much more to say
But there's not much more to say
It's been a beautiful run
It's been a great time
Never say never again
I do think that
We will see you live
Or in some capacity
Again at some point
But I just want to thank all of you
One last time
Pat I want to thank you
I'll be talking to you probably
In an hour you'll be texting me
To complain about something
Or vice versa
But I want to thank you in front of the audience
And I want to thank the audience
I want to thank Emily
I want to thank Will
I want to thank Ken
Liz and everybody else
Who has been involved
Who has shown support, who has shown love
Over the years
Big shout outs to everybody
Thank you
Yeah from
For everybody who's ever put pen to paper
And done a little bit of fan art
For us there's been so many like
Amazing pieces
To everybody who's ever
Left a comment
The amount of time somebody's been like hey I never left a comment
But I've heard every episode I'm a huge fan
We see it
We don't always acknowledge it, we've seen them all
It's all appreciated
The financial support is of course appreciated
We just can't say it enough
Emily has been our
Right hand woman
For the entirety of the show
Thank you, a million times thank you
We've said it before, we'll say it again
Will Podorf who's been really killing it on the
Instagram feed and with the fan art
Brandon Gash had a bunch of really cool
Fan art and 3D printer type stuff
The gifts you guys have given us at our shows
The stories about what we've meant to you
Meeting your partners
And your friends
You know
We love you guys, we've had a great time
Joe and I still exist as people
You can still follow us and hear
What we have to say and reach out to us whenever
You want
Yeah just thank you
That's it, thank you for everything
We will not see you next time
But Joe are we ready to
Wrap it up and say
We will see you
In hell