I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell, your favorite podcast where you want to know what's in the
middle about your favorite genre, sci -fi, horror, action, comedy, drama. It's just basically all
movies at this point because that's what happens when two men can't commit. I'm Joe DeRosa to my left,
because my man. Yes, it's me, Patrick Walsh. I can commit. I've been married over a year in a
relationship for about seven. So don't lump me in with you. She often when you're when we're out
together, you'll get up to go to the bathroom. She'll start using words like sham, far sickle,
cuck. Yeah. Yeah. So, you know, I wouldn't I wouldn't go patting yourself to patting yourself.
Patten on the back, general patten over here, general patten over here. Folks, since I
forgotten the last several shows, I'd like to get on with the show. And at the same time on with
the Joe, you fool. I love you. Come on, join the Joe ride. Rockset. Remember rock set.
Oh, yeah. What's the real song? Sort of an androgynous Swedish babes. She had like 10 huge hits
in the early 90s. She was like jump rope to her greatest hits. She was, yeah, she was real hot.
Yeah. Yeah. She was like, they took Annie Linux and they added a dash of Bridget Nielsen.
Yes. You know, Annie Linux, I would be too scared to sleep with. She falls into that category of like,
I can't bring you anything that you'll enjoy. I see. Yeah. She's so many like if a panel flipped open
on the back of her head while you were banging her in a circuit board, started to spark. Yeah.
You wouldn't be that surprised. No, not at all. I had this, my family had this very special Christmas,
two volumes and it was a, you know, vinyl, the big hit, the big pop stars of the day, meaning
the 80s, recorded all these songs and the albums were for charity. And they had U2's, the snows
coming down, which is a great version of that. Yeah, that's great. They had a sting doing some
bullshit. It was one of his first like loot songs. Right. And Annie Linux sang Winter Wonderland.
And to this day, I can't hear the song without being frightened.
She does this thing. It's like, it's like, Slaibels ring. You used to scare the shit out of me.
You know, are you familiar with Craig Wedrin from Shutter to think?
Well, I'm only familiar with him because he does music for like,
wet -hot American summer and movies of that nature. Yeah. He pops it up pretty hard
from the set. He does a lot of soundtrack stuff, but Shutter to think is a great
band, but it an odd, very dissonant band. For the most part, I just found on iTunes that he's got
two Christmas songs. Okay. And it's literally him being like, Santa can't make the snow come down.
Santa can't make the snow come down. You're like, why? Why is this? Yeah.
Make it about one of your weird topics. Why are you making this about Santa Claus?
One of my favorite things is when like an Aguilera will do a Christmas song and sing these
stupid lyrics. These songs everyone's heard a million times with so much passion.
Yeah. Like in the man, we can build a snowman. You're like, you're building a snowman.
Yeah, I know. It's just, you know, give yourself a hernia singing about putting some coal eyes
in a carrot nose and something. It's like when somebody dials up the national anthem too much.
You're like, how calm down? Whitney Houston is about the peak of that. She did it great.
She put her spin on it. She didn't go nuts. RIP Whitney. And RIP, if I may, it's a Bobby Forster.
I mentioned him on, you know, I, well, I'll get to it in a minute, but I've been doing a little
side project, but I don't think any movies have been mentioned more throughout the five -ish years
of this podcast than Robert Forster because of how much we talk, Jackie Brown. And I love the man.
Yeah, it'd be great to see him in the latest Breaking Bad joint El Camino. He had a little role.
That was his last thing, right? I don't know. Well, certainly last to be released. I mean,
it came out two days after he passed, but maybe he's got something else in the hopper.
I know he also was on last man's standing. Let's not talk about that, playing Tim Allen's dad,
but it shows, you know, I saw an interview with him and he was just like, you know, I'd get a call
and I say, yes, I'm a guy who says yes. I got a wife and three kids. They want me for something. I'll do
a wife and three kids. He's 90 years old. Well, I'm sure they're a vege. And this was an older
interview, but you know, just one of those character actors who loves to work. You could get him for
almost anything. And really, Jackie Brown didn't like put him on any sort of map. You know, he wasn't
in amazing movies following that. He got more work, certainly, but they gave like Pam Greer got some of
that like Travolta comeback. Very little though. But I felt like they gave Tarantino that they let him
cash that check once. Yeah. And then every other time he tried to do it, like, yeah, I mean, look,
it certainly brought Robert Forster back into the cycle of acting a lot more. But I mean, it was still
just in mostly supporting roles and stuff. But hey, that's a living. It's a little bit of the
parrot on or the tarot dactyl on the Flintstones used to say. I'm unaware. Unfamiliar, actually. It's a
living. I actually watched an episode of last man standing recently. Okay. Why? I was playing
something on Hulu and it just came on. Yeah. It was a Halloween episode. I didn't enjoy the show,
but I will say this. It was far better than I thought it would be. Okay. You know, but it's not
it's nothing I'd ever watched. I didn't laugh out loud. But I was like, this is much more well done
than I thought it would be. All right. But not enough to make me go. I want to watch last man standing.
But I hear good things about Tim Allen. Like I hear like, you know, around town that he's a good guy to
work for and stuff like that. I have heard it can't be true. I've heard that. Yeah.
Well, why would it not be true? I mean, I worked on the show that he was our lead -in on the Fox
lot and he was a notorious monster. Really? People told me, well, we're behind the paywall. People
told me he wasn't quite as rough as my cast, but one of the roughest casts or one of the roughest
stars in town. Really? Yeah. I heard the opposite. I heard he treats everybody really well and he's
easy to work for. Maybe he's changed. Maybe he's changed. I don't know. Who else is talking
out of school? Every, you know, this town. You know, people come up and be like, hey, I heard
such and such about such and such. Like it's not true at all. I just read some interview with Ruben
Fleischer's, a guy I know a little bit who directed Zombieland one and two and they asked him like,
so what about the internet rumors that Dan Acroid was in Zombieland two? Did his role get cut?
He was like, not only was he not ever in the movie, but no one ever mentioned his name.
She's like, I love Dan Acroid, but what are you talking about? It's just these things happen,
you know, they start up. Speaking of this town, Pat, I'm at the end of my tether here, buddy.
Well, you've been at the end of your tether for a long time. I'm fully off the meds at this point
and I'm starting to wonder if it was a mistake. Okay. But then I'm driving around today and I go,
it wasn't a mistake. This is the world. Yeah. Look at it. Right. See it for what it is.
You know, did you find getting off the meds difficult? I've heard it get me a struggle. Okay. Not at all.
It was, I stare step down off of them in the exact right way you're supposed to. Yes.
Getting off was fine. I'm just noticing that the little shit is setting me off more now. And I'm
like, that might be being off the meds. It also just might be, you know, I'm in a stressful,
stressful situation. I'm in between cities and my apartment, as you can see now, is
I'm big chaotic because I'm getting it ready for the move and I gotta get ready for shit,
get rid of shit. That's stressful. So that might have a lot to do with just the irritation of feeling
like I don't have a home. But my house is like things aren't put away and I go a little nuts. I don't
like it. It's unsettling. But I go to the doctor today. Nothing serious. But still I go to the doctor.
I call to make the appointment today. Yeah. Let me go. Yeah. We can squeeze you in. I go great. She
goes, what are you coming in for? Tell her in detail the whole reason I'm coming in.
Get to the office. Rash on the head of your day. Basically full coverage. Real bad burn when I pee. Yeah.
And no, it's not. It's none of that. I was gonna keep going. But I was like, that's gonna get
too way too gross. No. So I go in. I, you know, then I go into the little room, the office,
you know, the examination room, the fucking lady, the, and then another lady comes in.
So what's going on today? Reiterate every single thing I've already stated the first time.
Right. She looks at my chart. She's like, okay, I see. I see. I see. It's like, what do you worry
that some sort of subterfuge is going on between the chart? And when I'm saying, so then she leaves,
then the doctor comes in. So tell me about what's happening. I'm like, are you fucking kidding me
right now? And, you know, it speaks to, and I've complained at length on the podcast about this
onto you. There is a real efficiency issue in this world. And it is put under a magnifying glass
in this town. And I just, it sets me the fuck off. I can't deal with it, man. Like it's, I can't deal
with how goddamn out of fucking step everybody is with their job all the time. Do your fucking job.
Why is nobody efficient? Why does every single thing take so much longer than it needs to?
It's stupid. It's annoying. I'm driving home. This guy almost hits me in his car. I'm like, you
fucking, you know, it's myself. And then I'm like, you know what? Maybe I'm wrong. Maybe I was wrong.
And then sure enough, he like, like, zips up the road and cuts across three lanes. And I'm just like,
no, I'm not wrong. Everybody is this shitty. I'm kind of getting tired of this like,
hey, man, you never know what they're going through today. It's like, what are they all going
through something? Yeah. Is everybody have a, does everybody have a parent suffering from cancer?
And they're trying desperately get to the hospital? No. No. It's just people just suck. They fucking suck.
Oh my God. Maybe you go back to 10 milligrams. It does concern me because I was out with you in
your buddy, Mike, the other day at it. It was obvious that I was really on a tear, like just every
little thing. I was like, another thing. Well, yeah, I mean, he pointed out to me, you were like,
I don't want her to dry wine. It's not crisp at all. And then Mike was like, I didn't want to
tell him because he seemed so angry, but dry and crisp are not the same thing. Dry and crisp are the
same thing. Thank you, Mike. I mean, he was a bartender waiter. He said they're not dry.
Means dry dry. There's no like crisp and dry. What would the difference be? I don't know.
Crisp and dry mean dry meaning there's not an acidic tail on it. It doesn't have a lot of sweet to it.
Chris meaning there's not an acidic tail. It doesn't have a lot of sweet to it. I don't know one,
but you know, you return the glass. It was fine. I was very nice about it. It was fine. That was a
terrible waitress. Absolutely. She was awful. She didn't remember. There was three customers. She couldn't
remember anyone's orders every single time she came over. She had to reask what the drink order was
between taking the order and walking back with two drinks for two of us. She couldn't remember
who had the wine. Yeah. I mean, come on. It's like, you know, I'll take it up with Mike when I see him.
Please do. Yeah. Where was he a bartender by the way? St. Louis. All right. You know, I mean,
I feel like I could just go to St. Louis and be a bartender. Let's be frank. Well, you probably
could. I mean, you could do that anywhere. Also, what a establishment was he. You know,
you go with TGI Friday. It was something like that. I mean, you know, you know, it's not talk like
he was at Lebec Finn. I don't know what that is. It's a fancy restaurant. Okay. Good.
Well, shoot. I mean, should we... I guess there's a big one. We're talking about the Joker today,
which we're mentioning now several minutes into the show. But I think the biggest
scream and end story of the day and perfect for the movie we're discussing is all these big directors,
Scorsese, Coppola, talking shit on the Marvel movie. I love it. I knew I was on the right side of
history with this. I know it. Well, Joe, they're talking about DC -2. They're not strictly talking about
it. So they specifically keep saying Marvel. I think the people who write the article, but it's not
like... No, no, no. The quotes are specifically every... John Favreau just came out and defended their
statements. Look, Coppola isn't saying, listen, I love Batman versus Superman. I love suicide squad,
but these Marvel movies... But I'll tell you the difference. They mean superhero. They don't mean
superhero. Joe. Here's why. This is absurd. This is not absurd. This is not even a point to argue.
It's not an argument. Let me make my point and you'll see why I'm making it. They're saying
specifically Marvel movies because there has been a Marvel movie every single month for the last five
years and everyone is the same story and it is a complete fucking bombardment on the box office
and on movie going. That's why they mean specifically Marvel. DC has released four movies in the last
three years. They're saying this machine, this factory machine of Marvel is a problem and that's
what I've been saying. Sure, yes, but I think they're saying these big superhero special effect
finances. They keep literally saying Marvel in every quote every time. I don't know. They even know Marvel.
I think they're getting these questions. What do you think of all these Marvel movies and that's what
they mean? I think basically they're trapping them and asking questions. It's been in the news now for two
fucking weeks. Scorsese has been asked twice now and twice he has gone back and reiterated Marvel.
I'm telling you. I'm not just saying this because I hate Marvel. They're being very, it's a bigger
thing than just the movies themselves. Yes, but I don't think that these guys have enough of an
opinion on them even to be able to differentiate what I'm saying is, you know, Scorsese, I don't think
seen any of these movies probably, but they are constantly throwing these back up in the news.
They're getting another new filmmaker and we're reaching a point now where every one of our great
filmmakers are true artists in the decline of their lives and careers are going to be asked as
like the second or third question. What do you think of Marvel movies, superhero movies, whatever?
It's just such a stupid non -starter. They're trying to stir up more and more press out of this bullshit
story. And what I do like is somebody like Favreau who, by the way, I saw this weekend Mike Piednext
to him, said he had an odd peeing style, hunched over the urinal, but I like him saying they can say
whatever they want because of course they can and why is that in question? What's insane to me
is James Gunn or whoever the fuck taking to Instagram posting a picture of Groot and then doing
like a giant four paragraph thing about how these movies are art. They mean something to everyone.
James Gunn comparing Scorsese's minimal criticisms of Marvel films to the death threats of the last
temptation of Christ was enough to make me hate James Gunn again. I like James Gunn for a while.
I was on his side with the whole tweet thing. Yeah. I hate him again. He is a fucking moron. And who
was the other one that came out and bitched about it? There were several. It was Gunn, but it was Gunn
and somebody, oh, Sam Jackson saying they're Italian Americans. I think Marty Scorsese shouldn't make
the movies he make. It's like, are you comparing racial boundaries to fucking Iron Man right now?
Are you insane? It's all absurd to treat the conversation with any degree of seriousness. I find nuts.
People can like and watch whatever they want. And somebody, these days, somebody of any note saying
that kind of movie isn't my cup of tea. Be it any kind gangster or whatever else. That is a new story now.
I, well, Coppola came out and called them despicable. I love that. Coppola is like, he didn't go far enough.
I say they're despicable. Look, here's where I agree with you. I do think that the media
trying to get traction and blow over blow a story. I agree with all that. That's what they do when
they suck for it. And it's annoying whenever they do it with any kind of story. So I can't disagree with
that. What I will say is I fucking love that these filmmakers are coming out and saying this.
I think it's awesome. I think Marvel and this Disney machine are no fucking better than Trump.
It is capitalism at its fucking worst. It is grandstanding at its fucking worst. It is bling culture
and consumer culture at its fucking worst. And to say otherwise, it's one of the only funny jokes
in Jay and Silent Bob reboot, which we're going to do on another episode. But this is in the clip
they released. I'm not ruining anything. When Banks Banky or whatever Jason Lee's character says,
when he's like, you know, this reboot culture in Hollywood is just disgusting. And it's so greedy
in this and that. And then Jay goes, you like Marvel. Here's another Marvel movie. And then
Jason Lee goes, those movies are a fucking art of cinema. How dare you? You know what I mean?
For some reason, people, and I'm not trying to hammerhead a point. But this is what I mean about why I
think these people are referring specifically to Marvel. In that joke in the movie, they refer to
three other four, they're huge movie franchises. Yeah. And make fun of them. And then Marvel's the
past outside of some sort of obsessive childhood nostalgia, which look, I get it. I'm obsessed with
Star Wars from my childhood. But I was one of the fucking early Star Wars fans to say, hey man,
I really hope they don't make a movie every fucking year pleat. And I was fucking thrilled when
Kathleen Kennedy. And well, they stopped. After the second solo, after solo, she's like, we're not
going to do one every year anymore. It's too much. We're going to take our time. I was like, so happy
about that. When does that start? Because there's one coming out in two months. Well, that was that was
already scheduled in our track to come out. And then after that, it's a question mark right now. Yeah.
So my point is, is I don't get what it is about Marvel fans, where it's dude, you talk to them about
these movie, they, and they'll literally start arguing in defense of the movie. It made a billion,
that doesn't mean it's a good movie. It doesn't make it good. There's this sick fucking nostalgia
or obsession or whatever you want to call it, with Marvel. I think maybe they feel like it's finally
their time because Marvel never made a good movie until Iron Man. Yeah. DC was always the king,
like it would, you know, the Christopher Reeves, Superman franchise, and the Burton Batman,
and then the Nolan Batman, I think finally Marvel got a good one in, and they ran with the ball.
But it's at a point where it's like, I'm glad real filmmakers are coming out and being like,
this is fucking gross, man, like, right. And I'm sure Copa was pissed that when he, you know, he tries
to get $1 .5 million to do a passion project, nobody will give it to him. And these movies are basically
sucking up 25 % of Hollywood's money, minimum. But it really brought out the shit on Twitter,
which is like all these kids, and people who should know better, older than kids, being like,
Scorsese only makes one type of movie. What's he talking about? What? I saw that a bunch. All he
knows how to make is gangster movies. So they, they haven't seen last sensation of Christ. They don't,
guarantee they don't know what Alice doesn't live here anymore is. They haven't seen the Age of
Innocence. Coon Dune. I mean, it's, uh, it was nuts. This guy makes one type of movie and he's
gonna tell us this. What are they talking about? Then they're like, what didn't Francis Ford Coppola
make Jack? It's like, yeah, in a 40 year career, he's made a couple bad movies, you know, that it's
just everyone yelling at everyone. And why would you get so upset? You're, you've won. You're the
biggest thing in Hollywood. Shut up. I just, it's saddened. I agree with you that. And it saddens me
that the goal of cine files or the average outspoken cine file, I should say, is to be the biggest
thing in Hollywood. When the fuck was that ever the reward? Yeah. When was that ever the fucking crown with
movies? Because the biggest thing in Hollywood, even the Oscars every year as detesting as they are
reward sometimes a lot of the time lesser known things. Things that didn't make a shit load of money.
Because America is now only concerned about money. That's it. He with the most money wins,
including the presidency, end of conversation, not going further down that road. But like, well then I
also, but on a side point to that, I love how out of one side of everybody's mouth they're complaining
about the desperate, you know, a ailing state of our economy. And then they're out of the side
of the mouth. They're bragging about how great the latest Marvel movie was. Guys, these movies
are proof that, I think, I think capitalism is doing okay right now. Sure. It's making money for
everybody. It will be until we are whisked into a recession in a year, which will happen. Yeah.
But a fast will be dead and all that stuff. But nobody sees this as that. Nobody realizes when you
give the part of 7 -Eleven clerk to fucking in to to to Renee Zellwiger right in in Black Panther 4
that that's a that's a reflection of an ailing middle class that is disappearing. Yeah.
Anyway, sorry. Also, you got me all fucking worked. I mean, I came into this thing. Well,
they're pushing Avengers for best picture. And if you'll recall about a year ago, they were trying
to add a most popular, basically like the winner of this Oscar would be the most popular movie.
That's MTV awards shit. So like the Oscars have no, you know, gravitas anymore anyway. They're
not really what they once were. But to add a most popular movie, of course, people blocked at this.
And now, of course, Spielberg and others are barking about do Netflix movies count. And these these
battles are going to go on forever and ever. But what I did appreciate was Robert Downey Jr.
saying, take me out of this race for best actor. They're pushing him for Iron Man because that's a
man who who's got to know how fucking stupid that is. Yeah. He's playing himself. He makes wise cracks.
He wears a suit. He's in one 16th of each Marvel movie. Why would he be up for best actor? Yeah. No.
Because the movie was big. And he rightfully admits that he doesn't really look at the screen or he
doesn't really remember. None of them know which ones they're in. Yeah. I was like, I wasn't in that
movie. Yeah. You were. They don't know. Yeah. It's a, it's a, it's a, it's just, it's just insane.
This whole thing is nuts, dude. And you know, I'm driving to, and nothing against these actors.
Then I'm about to be offered me one. I'm there in five minutes. Nothing against the actors are about
to mention. Yeah. I'm driving down the street the other day. There's new Tina Fey shows coming out
on Amazon Prime. It's Tina Fey. It's Ann Hathaway. It's God knows who I'm sitting there. I'm going
for the love of fuck. Yeah. It's a streaming Amazon Prime show. You turn on ABC. It's Walton
Goggins has his own show now. I'm or CB. I'm like, what the fuck can anybody who's not already
killing it have a fucking chance? They won't take that chance anymore. There's no fucking Christ man.
You know, my, my old boss on broke girls talked about how, you know, Beth Bears is, you know,
the blonde broke girl. And now she's killing it on the neighborhood. But like she was always, I mean,
no, amazing with physical comedy and just a really, really great comedic actress. And she had been in
nothing. And Michael said they kept pushing him to hire Hailey Duff or Hillary Duff. And he was like,
no, we have cat dening. She's a big star. The other one I want to discover. And basically I had
to point out to them. TV is supposed to be about finding new stars who then become movie stars.
That's what TV is. You break it. You find somebody new. Like all the friends were new. All the
sign fell people were essentially new aside from bit parts here and there. And they just won't do it
anymore. They won't take that risk. And I think it's making things much more boring. But basically,
it's, it happened a Broadway. It happened everything. Even when I was in New York 15 years ago, I'd go,
hey, I'm going to go see this Broadway plate. And I'm really excited about who's in it. You know,
like there, there's no sense of discovery anymore. It's like, if you Jackman isn't doing the lead,
these musicals die immediately. Yeah, it's, it's literally, yeah, you walk into these things
anywhere. They got like Denzel Washington running the concession stand. So can anybody have a break?
Can anybody get a job? Please. Yeah. It's just fucking insane, dude. It's just
so nuts, man, like television. I mean, Jesus Christ, I turned on fucking, I tried to,
I tried to watch it and Hulu didn't work again today. But I tried to watch Hulu.
I mean, this is Hulu. I gotta be honest with you. I watch it with my pants off every day as
Hulu. That's right. You know what I'm saying? Uh, displaying your Hulu. You got Tim Robbins in
the, in the Newcastle rock. It's like, this isn't even that good of a show. Why is Tim Robbins in
this? I know. I know. For Christ sakes. You know what? I read this random roles, which is the only
thing I like these days on the Onion AV Club. The site has fallen to shit. They have the worst
writers in criticism. But uh, Tim Robbins was going through his roles and I got a big smile on my
face because they asked him about nothing to lose. And he was like, I love that movie. I think it's a
really fucking funny movie. I was like, thank you Tim Robbins. Now this is the one with Dan
Acroix playing dual roles, correct? Nothing but trouble. Okay. I'm sorry. Nothing to lose is Martin
Lawrence. Oh yeah. Because I remember thinking that movie was so funny. So few people know it.
It contains, uh, Martin Lawrence going, don't kill me, Freaky Jason. I said, don't kill me,
Freaky Jason, which my friends and I still do. Uh, great, great underrated movie. One thing I want to
say before we get to the movie corner is I wanted to make a quick, uh, about our last episode.
And I don't even remember which one it was, but I talked about how disgusted I was with busy Phillips
crying in the audience when Zellweger went on her big thing about how glad she was to be making
millions of dollars. Wait, not Zellweger. Michelle Williams. I'm sorry. Michelle Williams. Yeah.
Yeah. Renee Zellweger is playing Judy Garland. I hear she's great. I hear it's great.
I love Michelle Williams. But then I remembered, wait, Michelle Williams played this comedic role in the
Amy Schumer movie. Uh, I feel pretty. And Michelle Williams stole the movie. She was hilarious in it.
I couldn't believe how funny she was. Very good. But busy Phillips played one of the other girls.
And after doing very minimal research, I learned that these two are best friends. So while I was still
kind of thrown by the display, not, not the issue, I definitely think she should be equally paid.
And we said that a million times. But I get why busy Phillips was crying for her friend. I wanted to
make that because I just thought they were cutting to a random person sobbing. Well, I'll tell you
what I think, Pat. I think busy Phillips is as hollow headed as Michelle Williams. And Talon did
as either of them may be. I still think her little fucking speech was horseshit fair enough. Uh,
and was a was a was coming out of the mouth of the wrong fucking person. I, I texted you this
the other day. Never without good reason. Have I ever hated someone more than busy Phillips? I
don't know what it is. I see or I see red. I think it's the name. Uh, well, I, I, I have no real
feelings either way. I just wanted to clear that up. Ah, talk show something about her bugged me.
I understand that by the way, one last thing as we talk about the middle class disappearing. Yes.
When did the goal in Hollywood as an actor or comedian or performer to be on daytime game shows?
You see this array of people doing these fucking daytime game show?
Day, who's doing the daytime ones? Well, I'm just saying they're on all the, you know,
they're on during the day, they're on at night. But every time I turn one of these things on,
it's like hosted by Dex Shepard. And then the panel is on. Yes. The cast of Silicon Valley.
I'm like, what when did everybody want to be Charles Nelson Riley? When did that fucking happen?
I just saw Joel McCale is hosting like Duce's wild or some late night talk show.
Looks like he wants to blow his head off there. These are the dentist eyes in Hollywood.
He doesn't even joke around. Like somebody will say like, I don't know, Joel. What do you think I should
do? And he's like, do what you want to do? Like, he doesn't even do the minimal joking of a game show host.
He hates it. He doesn't want to be there. And they're giving him probably $5 million a year to do it.
This is the taste I get from that guy blows up on the soup. Yeah.
Is a young comic. Good looking guy. He's all excited. Like, hey, man, I got this dumb jerk off clip show
job. I'm having fun. Yeah. Sky's the limit, baby. I'm on my way. Get's on community.
Probably thinks not that great of a show. But hey, what am I going to be trapped on it?
Right. Get's trapped on it. Then it becomes a living hell with Chevy Chase.
Right. Thanks. I'm going to end the show, which was discussed about by critics who it was designed
expressly for critics as being the second coming of comedy. One of the best shows of all time
community is routinely featured on those lists. Just saying gets out of that. Thanks. Here we go.
Does one. Maybe two movies makes no noise. Get's to. Yeah. Get's his own Netflix show. He's like,
here we go. Yeah. Make zero noise. Nobody even knows it exists. And now he's hosting a game show.
And he's probably sitting there going, I was supposed to be the next fucking McConaughey. And what the
fuck is going on here? Yeah. He's his anger is palpable in a way I haven't seen on TV in a long
time. Usually people hide that shit. Well, the only person you'll find it from is lifers. Pat SayJack,
Alex Trebek. Those men still bring so much discussed every night that I love watching both shows.
Let me take you over, if I may, to Pat's movie corner. I'm going to start with a documentary I watched.
It was like a one night only theatrical event. So I'm sure it'll be on Hulu in a week called QT8,
the first eight. This is a brand new 2019 documentary about the films of Quentin Tarantino.
It's a little over two hours. Here's what I loved about it. They don't tell you shit about his life.
They don't do the whole. Quentin was born and you know, they don't do the whole believe it or not,
he was a video store clerk and the stories you've heard a million times. When Quentin was four,
he said, Mommy, why can't my view master make moving pictures? All right. All right.
I love that. I love that. It was just about the movies. In the same way,
Dupalma was just about the Dupalma movies. And that's an amazing documentary.
The Dupalma one is truly testament to how riveting the man's work is and the man himself is the whole
and even the ones you haven't seen, the scenes look so cool and they're shot so excitedly.
You get it. This Tarantino thing, they have great people interviewed. I'm talking Sam Jackson,
Tim Roth, you know, a lot of the bigs, Jennifer Jason Lee, etc. But no Tarantino. He said,
I want to be the first one in line to see it, but I don't want to be interviewed for it.
Great. That's cool, but also you're sort of missing the guy's point of view. Not that if you want
to hear him talk, you can't find it. You know, the man talks more than any one of the world.
Yeah. Kevin Smith is the all -time king of holy christ. The documentary is a quick, breezy watch.
It touches on everything except at the very end, it just feels kind of promotional for once upon a time.
They tell you it's coming, but nothing about it. But you know, all the stories, Jamie Foxx actually had
the most funny, interesting stories about shooting Django. He's great in it. And it's entertaining.
Bobby Forster in it, talking about Jackie Brown. My issue with it really was the lack of interviews,
by the way. No, Travolta. Oh, come on. I'm surprised they couldn't get it. Uma.
No, Uma. But they go into and they show you the footage of Uma crashing that car
right. But don't pass any judgment or say anything about it. They talk to Diane Vanora from
Englorious Bastards, Diane Krueger, excuse me. They talked to her about Tarantino choking her out to
get the reaction of from her about being killed believably. And she's laughing about it and they
don't get into that either. So like they they'll bring up these controversies but not really going
anywhere with them. Did the credits roll and did it was the first credit directed by Quentin
Tarantino? No, no. But there is also and this really bummed me out. And I guess I get it. It's the
world we're living in. 25 minutes of this thing are devoted to Harvey Weinstein. So when that starts,
you just felt this palpable groan from the audience. It was all these diehard Tarantino fans. And
you know, Pulp Fiction or whatever, they show Tarantino like hug Harvey Weinstein first
when he wins the Palm Door or whatever. And they zoom in on it ominously and they keep touching on
it throughout. And then they devote a big chunk of time. They talk about how Tarantino knew but didn't
say anything. But they don't really villainize him. So you're wondering why they even go into it.
Like the Woody Allen documentary, the big four hour PBS thing. An hour of that is talking about his
molestation allegations. And also Alan participated in it. Yeah. And answers questions about it.
This felt like really half -ass. And it's like, if you're going to do this, you have to get Tarantino's
opinion on camera or drop it and let us enjoy this fun ride through his movies that we were promised.
Don't in the 11th hour of the movie be like, now it's another Weinstein documentary of which I've
seen two in the last two months. Well, I'll tell you dude, speaking of Woody Allen and Tarantino and
Weinstein, Farrow is coming hard for everybody now. He just released that thing, that book catch and kill.
Yeah. And dude, he called out fucking Susan Sarandon. He called out a lot of Hollywood bleeding heart
blowhards. Yeah. Like you fucking knew she knew. Right. You know, Lena Dunham's on the list. He got
everybody. I mean, well, they aren't you know, of course, of course. Everyone knew and they didn't
want to shake anything up. Yeah. In their own career. And no one's ever going to face any judgment
for that or at least trial for that. The Ronan Farrow book, by the way, I've heard that it's like an
SNL audition where he does a thousand voices. Like he plays like a Russian gangster and is like,
oh, you know, like does voices it when he reads his audio book. Okay. Yeah. So I'm curious to hear
what the fuck he's thinking with that. But for a second, you're saying it's a talking book, Stevie,
Wonder Style, baby. Apparently it's a real embarrassment. I'm listening to the audio book of
she said, Jody Canter and Megan Tui, the, they were the female reporters who brought down
Weinstein. It's a fascinating book. I'm listening to the audio book of she's all that. And I got
to say it is better than the movie. The movie adaptation or the source material. It's a much darker
story. Yeah. Anyway, if you're a Tarantino fan, this is definitely going to be on streaming very soon.
Obviously it's worth watching. It just kind of bummed me out. And it's not as in depth as you
want it to be. But it's fun stories, actors talking shop. I enjoyed it. I just did a, or a moderated,
I was very, by the way, shouts out to the good people at SpectreVision, which is Elijah Woods
production company. Yes. They asked me to moderate their Comic Con panel. I guess at this point
was a week or two weeks ago. Had a great time talking to the crew from the company over there.
Everybody was extremely nice, extremely endearing. And the Comic Con crowd was awesome. It was a lot of
fun to do. So in preparation, oh, and I got a good joke off on wood during the panel. You know,
we did it. We, they saved the last five minutes for audience Q and A. And it's just a countdown before
a Lord of the Rings question comes up. Nothing to do with anything. Yeah.
First question. This kid's like, well, Elijah, will you sign my, my, uh, hobbit killed?
Whatever. Yeah. Uh, he goes, can you sign my Lord of the Rings thing? And I turn to Elijah and I go,
you were in Lord of the Rings. Good to bounce. Yeah. I got a good laugh. Yeah. And then a kid,
he goes, I'll sign it, but I don't have a sharpie. And a kid, another kid threw a sharpie up to him.
Uh -huh. And he goes, thanks. And I go, Elijah, if you could also shine, sign that sharpie before you.
Too, too nice laughs. I pitched Joe the joke. Uh, I tell you, these Lord of the Rings pictures were so boring.
Saramons was the only eye open in the house. Yes, folks. And I said, I want to, I want to, I
want to, I call those things Lord of the boring. Yes. For God's sake, both great options. Um, the, uh,
so wait, but what, but now I just went to beyond fest appear at the Egyptian and, uh, you know,
two week horror and sci -fi festival. I saw a lot of movies there. Elijah Wood had about five movies
in the fest. So did they have a screening or what was the theme of the, they had a, so the day before,
they didn't have a screen, but the day before they discussed their latest movie, which I have not seen,
because it's not out yet. Uh, the Nick Cage picture? No, the Nick Cage one, they weren't even able to show
the trailer for yet, but it has screened. It's some festival. Yeah, investor. They were talking
about their other new movie that has also screened at a bunch of festivals that actually comes out in
December called, and I'm blanking on the name right now. I'm so sorry. But it's about a, it's a very
dark movie about a kid who has, who had an imaginary best friend growing up and gets older. Some dark
shit starts happening. The imaginary friend shows up again. That would be honest. Yeah, it becomes
the psychological thriller about is this guy real or not. Um, anyway, sort of a horror drop dead
for it. That's exactly what I said on stage. Now they're nice laugh. Yeah. Uh, so anyway, um, but we,
but in preparation for the panel, I had seen a bunch of the specter vision films, but I went back and
rewatched some that I hadn't seen or rewatched some that I had seen and watched some that I hadn't seen,
but I will talk a greasy strangler. Never seen it. Wild film. People ever requested we do it.
So maybe I'll watch it. It is fucking wild. It's disgusting. It's disgusting. It's a revolting film
in, in the right ways revolting. I'm not saying it's bad. It's a, it's a great movie, but it's
essentially a really, really twisted like Napoleon Dynamite kind of thing. It's, it exists in this
weird hyper reality. Um, we can't really tell what year it is. Mm hmm. It's very Napoleon Dynamite.
The characters are very eccentric. They, they speak in weird affectations and stuff. But the drive of
the movie is that there's this killer going around called the greasy strangler. Right. Uh, I don't
want to give too much away in case we do cover it. But I will say that, uh, I, this movie had more
60 year old man cock in it. Oh, but then I have ever seen in my life anywhere. It's just an insane
fucking movie. And the fact that this company made it my hats off to them. I mean, look, they also,
they also got Mandy out there. Right. So these, by the way, I said in a moment of frustration here,
I didn't count it as a horror movie. It was a horror movie. The, uh, they're making great stuff.
This new one color out of space coming out with cage. That's the one that went huge at Beyond Fest.
It looks insane. Uh, I was allowed to see a trailer. It looks nuts from the director of Island of
Dr. Morale. Yes. So cool to see that guy back. And one of the reviews says the, I forget who said
this, but it said the greatest HP lovecraft adaptation to date, which is saying a lot. There have been a
lot of really great HP lovecraft adaptations. Sure. I love Castle Freak. Castle Freak's awesome
a reanimator. Stuart Gordon does amazing adaptations. I just watched the unnamable last night, which
is a lot of fun. Okay. Um, but the company is just doing excellent work. And uh, Greasy Strangler is
a hell of a watch. He's called the Greasy Strangler because he's covered in so much grease that it looks
like he's got a body deformity or something. Okay. Uh, it's, it's an upsetting film. And then weirdly
funny. And then weirdly frightening. It's, it's, it's really hard to kind of put your finger on it.
Yeah. I will check it out for sure. Uh, I did not see any of the, uh, the Elijah Wood pictures,
mostly because they were sold out. He produces them. But, um, I went to several movies at Beyond Fest,
including The Lodge, which is directed by Veronica Franz and Severin Fiala, who directed Good Night
Mommy, which was a horror picture. I think we discussed on here. And I thought a very good one. Yes,
we did. Um, so what the Lodge is is Riley Kio who portrayed, uh, the girlfriend on the star's show,
the girlfriend experience, meaning the prostitute who gives you the girlfriend experience. She is a,
a stunner. She's also in, uh, the Matt Dillon Lars von Trier movie I talked about on here,
which is, what can I remember that? The house of Jack Bill, which is on Amazon Prime, I think currently,
I'm excited to watch it. Riley Kio is a great actress. She is beautiful. She plays basically a new
stepmom. Two siblings go to this cabin in the snow with their new stepmother. Their actual mother
played by Alicia Silverstone has killed herself. Good to see Alicia getting a little bit of work.
And in this home, they are basically terrorized by something, a force, uh, they keep cutting back
to time of Riley Kio being in what appears to be a cult. And there's a lot of balls in the air
and you're just kind of, for the first half, this thing was super intense, very well shot.
And I love any thriller or horror movie in the snow. I just always have simple plan. The thing,
they're, they're my favorites. Uh, it's working. It's working. The audience is with it. And then things
start to fall apart as it goes and you're just like, maybe they'll pull this together. They got so
many things in the air and they don't. They botched the landing. And I think everybody walked out saying,
boy, that was a let down because the first half is so strong. Uh, it got a theatrical release,
but a very brief one. It's worth your time, but it's definitely an average horror film. The
lodge. Uh, baby, the synergy is here today because my next movie stars the star of the movie,
the girlfriend experience. Sasha Gray. Sasha Gray. She's in. Talk about a pornographic. No, no, no,
she's in a specter, specter, specter, specter vision movie called open windows. Okay. And also stars
Elijah Wood. They're the two leads. All right. Psychological thriller about he plays a kid who runs
the number one fan site in the world for this famous movie actress played by Sasha Gray. Yes. Uh,
he's in an event because he's won a contest to have a private dinner with her and interview her
for this fan site. Okay. Uh, his computer is immediately hacked as he's waiting to go to the event.
Uh, and it's seemingly being, uh, uh, at first it doesn't seem it's being hacked. It seems
he's just being messaged by somebody from the production company of the movie. Yeah. And then
very quickly realized this is not a guy that works for the company. This is a guy who's insane
and has hacked into Elijah Wood's computer and is manipulating a thriller situation of like,
you need to do this. Then you need to go do that kind of like that movie with Johnny Depp,
where he has to like assassinate the guy. Nick of time. Yeah. Like that kind of vibe real time movie.
Yeah. Um, and, uh, you know, as it, as it begins, you kind of think Elijah Wood is going to be the
creep because he seems so obsessed with this actress. And then you realize he's not the creep. He's
actually the good guy and he's trying to help her. And it unfolds from there. Uh, very fast paced.
Again, not again, but another cool thing about this company is man, they know how to shoot on a
budget. It's, you know, so much of this movie takes place in one room. Yeah. And then it gets out of
the room and but it doesn't get too big production wise. Right. Uh, and it's just whether you like the
film or not, it's another great example of what this company is good at doing, which is making these
low budget these days, meaning 10 million or less. Yeah. Uh, thriller, horror movie, psychological
pieces. And they're, they clearly don't care about does this thing reach a wide audience. Like,
they care that it reaches the people who were fans of this thing. And, uh, and they do a great
job at it. So, uh, check out open windows that book. All three movies I'm talking about today are
Spectra Vision movies and all three are on Amazon Prime. Oh, all right. So you can see all three if
you have a membership. We'll do. Uh, I saw also at Beyond Fest. And this by the time you listen to it,
we'll be on Netflix. Uh, I recommend seeing it in a theater because it was so fun. Dolomite is my name.
Can't wait. Uh, I have seen Dolomite. My friends in high school were obsessed for whatever reason.
We watched it as kind of a so bad. It's good, but also it's got a lot of real enjoyment out of it.
So I was familiar with Rudy Ray Moore and Dolomite. But, um, you know, this, the screenwriters Larry
Karajuski and Scott Alexander gave a talk after where they said Eddie Murphy came to them right after
Ed Wood came out. He was reciting the whole movie to them new every line of Ed Wood, which I thought
was such a cool story. That's awesome. And was like, I want to do the, uh, Rudy Ray Moore's story. They
were obsessed. They love kind of so bad. It's good cinema. They go out with this as a package in
1995. We've got Eddie Murphy attached. We wrote Ed Wood. We want to do this for Dolomite. And it was
passed on by everyone in town. So now some 20 years later, the movie comes to the screen. I'm glad it
did. It's Eddie Murphy. I mean, best in years is easy as pie to say. But, uh, you know, he also
just seems on fire and engaged and connected in a way he hasn't in a long time here. It's like
funny. Eddie Murphy again. It's like him being R rated funny again. He's so fucking funny. I think
probably Bo finger was his like, all right. I like Ed Wood. This is kind of in that ballpark. But
weirdly, he's like perfect in it as like, you know, this guy who he steals, uh, you know,
street jokes. Your mama jokes from a bunch of bums. And he like interviews neighborhood bums
to get jokes because his own stand -up career isn't really taking off. And they make a low -budget movie.
That's basically what it is. You watch the movie get made. Wesley Snipes. Best he's been in, you know,
say 30 years, probably best since blade. He should be nominated for best sporting actor. He is
incredibly funny in it. Everybody kills in it. And you should see it in a theater, even though it's
on Netflix, not because it's a big wide screen movie. But because these big laughs, you know, it's
very rare that a comedy like that opens up. It's hilarious. It's sweet. It's entertaining. It's
one of my favorite movies of the year. Check it out. Yeah. From what I could tell from the clips I've
seen, it looks like Eddie Murphy is playing a very funny, comical variation of his dream girl's
character. Sure. Yeah. Wesley Snipes is playing a very funny, comical variation of Nino Brown from
New Jack City. It looks like almost like it. What if these? I think that's fair. Two guys were funny.
I mean, I know they're, I'm not saying it's derivative. I'm just saying like it reminded me of
that. Snipes is definitely doing something I have never seen him do before. He's playing like a true
character. You don't see Wesley Snipes in it at all partially because he just looks different over time.
But they talked about other director and people were like, is this okay? Like, should we let this
performance in the movie? It's that biggest swing and it just kills. He's hilarious.
Um, my last is another specter vision movie. You've talked about this film, I believe,
Toad Road. Never heard of it. Okay. I thought we, I thought you had brought it up. Toad Road is the
first movie they ever released. Is the Frogger adaptation? It is the Frogger. By the way, we don't
think that the Lord of the Rings movies suck. They were just funny jokes. I didn't like them.
Not my thing. They're, they're a little too involved for me, but I think that they're good movies.
Yeah. I just, you know, uh, the, uh, uh, Toad Road was the first movie they ever released that
the story was that Elijah Wood came across us at a festival and said, I want to put this out or help
get it released. Um, it is, I mean, it's shot on, I mean, shot on video. It's like it, it almost plays
like a found footage movie, but it's not a found footage movie. Uh -huh. The director and writer
of the movie was making, uh, apparently a documentary. I think about drug culture at the time
and realized his footage had no like real thread to it and was like, this is boring. This is just
people sitting around doing drugs. So what if I did something like this but actually added a story
to it and dramatized it and he, but he still kind of shoots at docu style. So there are several scenes in
this movie where there are a bunch of kids hanging out together. He said he found the actors on my space
because he wanted like a real natural like connection between all these kids. He didn't want it
to feel like actors and it doesn't. There's footage in this where I'm like, I think these kids really
did just get all fucked up in a house. Right. Um, the sad part is the main storyline. It's about a
girl falling head first into drug culture and becoming more and more obsessed with it. And then
eventually meeting what seems to be her doom in real life. The actress that played this character
died of a heroin overdose like months after the release of the film or something. Um, it's a
documentary. It's a narrative. No, no, it's a narrative. But they didn't get her started on drugs.
I don't think so. I just think she, I think that's probably why she played the role so well.
Oh, she knew the world. I don't know. But uh, anyway, no, there, there, there is nothing. I read
up on it. There was nothing like she never tried to drug till this move. Like, right, right. And I
don't even know if people were actually doing drugs when they shot the thing. Yeah. I'm just saying
it's a pretty convincing portrayal of what it's all about. And you know, I think it takes place in
Maryland or no, takes place in Pennsylvania and they do really capture. It just took me back to when I
was in college, just getting out of college, you got all those pod head friends that live in one house
together. The kitchen is a fucking disaster. The house smells, but you go there and you have a keger
and everybody eats mushrooms and takes acid and smokes pot and gets completely fucking out of their
heads. Right. And you act crazy and it's hilarious. Right. Um, it took me back to all that. But
there is a dark storyline of the movie. It's called Toad Road because Toad Road is an urban legend
from Pennsylvania that there is supposedly a road called Toad Road. And there are seven gates along
the road, which are the seven gates to hell. And if you can get through all seven gates, you will reach
hell. Uh, and it's about this girl becoming more and more obsessed with this legend and wanting to
try this. And things unfold from there. Uh, there are points in the movie where you were, where you'll
probably hit a place that I hit where I was like, well, where is this going exactly in one of my
watching, but it ties together very nicely at the end. And it has some cool, very weird haunting
elements to it. It's worth watching. And with that being said, at 55 minutes and 59 seconds,
let us get to our review of the movie at hand, Joker. Joker, starring Joaquin Phoenix directed by Todd
Phillips written by Scott Silver and Todd Phillips. This, uh, real quick before we get into it.
You know, an important thing to keep in mind when you watch this movie is this is a one -off movie.
This is not meant to tie into any of the other DC cinematic universe films. They've said that.
And because of that, it plays very much like if you bought a one -off Joker graphic novel
you know, that was, and they released those. They'll release a graphic novel where it's like,
this is a one shot. It's not going to be a series. What if this happened instead? What if this was
the way it all went down? Right. And that was clearly very much the approach to this origin story
of the character of the Joker. And that's what it is. That's what it is. Um, you almost have to discuss
two things with this movie. A, the movie, and B, the absolutely insane press about the movie.
That's been going on for three months leading up to the release. It started with reports of, you
know, eight minute standing ovation and having seen the movie, it's like, I don't believe it. Was
this their first movie? The people in the audience? Why would it, why would any movie cause people to
stand up and applaud for eight minutes? It's insane. Well, if it's like a con or something like that,
it's not, I don't think those standing o's are literally meaning like, we loved it so much we stood
for it. It's like a thing that you do in the audience to be like, we're gauging how much we like
this versus everything else we saw. Therefore, people stood for three minutes over there. So now we stand
for five here. Sure. I think they got to stop doing it. I think that's what it is. I don't know. It just
completely inflates expectations and gets everyone nuts. And honestly, the reviews of it, when they
started the actual reviews, I saw largely negative. And I thought, I bet that's in reaction to these
reports of eight minute con standing ovation because it makes you hate the movie unseen. But
critical reactions have been all over the damn place. Audience reactions have been all over the damn
place. And basically the bigger issue with it became, are you worried about getting shot? I had
somebody say to me, you're going to see Joker. It was like a Wednesday night. Are you worried about
getting shot? No, I'm not. You know, like I wouldn't be surprised if Warner Brothers drummed that
controversy up. Well, I'll tell you this. I saw it on opening day. Yeah, I was on the road up in
Vermont. Was there security in shit? They had a they had a no well, no. The theater that I was in there
wasn't security. But the people that worked at the theater were definitely coming in and checking
on things more so than I've ever seen happen in a theater. Yeah. I got to be honest at the time.
I was grateful. You get a little spooked or the shit gets in your head. There was a guy in the theater
who was very shaggy looking and reeked of weed and cigarettes. Yeah. And looked shady. He had his
cat pulled way down and he kept walking in and out of the theater. And I got to a point where I
got up and went and sat in the back row because I was like, I'm getting freaked out every time the
fucking door opens. Right. And it was really annoying. But, you know, all in all, obviously,
there was no shooting. But I was saying like variety would have a report and it would be like
suspicious character ejected from Joker screening in Maryland for smoking. And it would be like a
news story. I don't know what happened with this movie. I don't know why it got so blown out
of proportion. And there is not a stitch of mass shooting anything in this thing. There's not. I get
thematically why people said this is dangerous at this time. But it's like, it's not your fucking
decision to make. And I can't imagine the big universal movie, The Hunt, which we may never see
because Trump and the right wing decided that it was too dangerous. I can't imagine it was
any more or less inflammatory than Joker. We're just deciding things at random. And depending on
what the news is that week, movies can just be completely stripped from the multiplex. And it's a
dark and scary time. hats off to Phoenix and to the crew of Joker for refusing to entertain any of it
with the press. They banned press interviews from the red carpet agreed. Good for them. Now overall,
I thought it was a great flick. I thought it told a great story. I thought Joaquin's performance was
exceptional. I thought it was very well directed. I thought it was very well written. And I actually
thought at the end of the day, like I said earlier, this being a sort of one shot origin story,
you could take the Joker element out of it. And it was still would have been a riveting performance
about a guy just coming unglued. I liked it a lot. I did not. I saw the I saw a certain homage to
taxi driver in this thing. I saw a certain homage to King of Comedy. But these reviews were people
going, it's just King of Comedy with Joe. No, it's not. Right. It's not. And it wasn't taxi driver either.
No. I thought it told a really interesting story. I thought, and I won't give away the very end,
but I thought the sort of Coda or button or whatever you want to call it, the sting. I think you
know, the tag. Yeah. I thought the tag on this whole movie was a great, fully realized nod to the
Joker and who the Joker is and all that stuff. And I thought it was a slow burn to get to it,
but it was a burn I enjoyed watching. I thought it was a lot of fun. The fun is the wrong word,
but I thought I found it to be a very, very enjoyable film. Yeah. I mean, I think I liked it a little
bit less than you. I did enjoy it. In terms of my opinion of superhero movies, which has been
well documented on here, I liked it more than most. I liked it more than almost all the marvels and
certainly the DCs. Just, you know, I didn't love it. I liked it. And I think that my issue with it
was, and I think a lot of this, I can freely admit, was the amount of passionate arguments and
discussion about this movie. When you see it, I'm not sure it warranted it. There wasn't,
there wasn't quite the grasp of theme or grasp of what it was trying to say to make it this big
lightning rod of controversy. I don't know that Todd Phillips is deep enough for that. That said,
he's always been a good director. The hangover movies, even though they got worse quality -wise,
got increasingly beautifully shot, you know, some really incredible camera work. And this continues
that. He's a good filmmaker. Joaquin, I think, ties it together in a big way. I think if they had
brought on Jared Lido, who was apparently pissed that he wasn't asked to do it, I'm not sure this
movie, I don't know if I would have gave a shit at all. Joaquin goes a very long way to making this work
and making a largely unsympathetic character sympathetic. I think a superhero movie being influenced
by Scorsese, he's a taxi driver and can't comedy is a great thing. I don't know why anybody would be
upset about that. Would you rather they be influenced by the other superhero movies? You know,
it was a different take. I liked it. I can't believe they showed us Bruce Wayne's parents getting
killed outside the theater for like the 18th time. That's been on camera. My issues with it.
Let me say, I was surprised they showed that. But by the time I realized they were going to show it,
I thought it was a brilliant way to... I loved the way they connected Joker directly to that.
And I was almost like, oh, this could almost play like a prequel to the Burton Batman.
You know, Joaquin, though, reportedly was against putting any of the Wayne stuff in it. He really
wanted this to be completely separate. But I thought that was smart. I was glad it was still Gotham and
not like New York. I liked that they played Thomas Wayne in the books and the previous movies
has always been a very like a philanthropist and a very generous man and endearing man and a man
who was out to save Gotham in quotes. I liked that they tilted this in a different direction where they
said, well, look, we're familiar now with men of power saying they want to save the poor and they
can have completely underhanded motives. And I liked that they played Thomas Wayne that way,
especially when you knew that Bruce Wayne was going to grow up to be the favorite son of Gotham.
Right. And Joaquin Phoenix was going to be the sort of disregarded son of Gotham. I was like,
oh, that's very clever to me, that Gotham sees this guy in one way, Joker sees him in another,
the kid sees him in one way, Joker sees him in another, they are kind of linked. I thought that was
pretty cool. Did you think that Thomas Wayne was the father of Joaquin? Because it was a big discussion
on the way home for the movie. And we didn't come to any agreement. I think that it was left
purposefully ambiguous. And I thought it was another interesting commentary on money and power
where every time Joaquin Phoenix found proof or clue or lead to his father being Thomas Wayne,
there was always a counterargument of, no, your mom was fucking crazy. Right. And all that shit was
doctored and it's all fake. None of this was real. That's why I would hope thematically they
were intending us to believe that his mom, Patricia Clarkson, was telling the truth. That wasn't
Patricia Clarkson. Patricia, what? I don't know, the lady from she was in an American horror story.
It's all and six feet under, right? Wasn't it the six feet under, lady? What's her name? I don't know.
All right. I'll find it. I get that. I get the mixed up. I think that's what it should have been
because this very rich, powerful man is just flat out denying it. And that's what keeps happening
is Trump and others are just like, that didn't happen. That didn't happen. So that's how I took it was
that she was telling the truth. And she was made to look crazy by these rich and powerful men.
Well, and I think that that's what I'm sorry. I think that's one interpretation of it. And I thought
that that's why it was so great. They never gave you definitive answer. Sure. Because so often these
these cases come down to one person's word against the other. And the rich person gets the
final say so I like that they that they just depicted it as, hey, man, this very well could be true.
But if it's not, this is something that would set a guy like this over the fucking edge.
Yeah. You know, um, and it was also a classic theme with the Joker is in the comics is all it
takes is one bad day to put you over the over the limit. Right. And I thought this movie did a good
job of that. Like, hey, the state is cut funding. Your clinic is gone. Your therapy is gone. Your
meds are gone. Uh, this guy that you thought was going to be the savior for your life and who you
thought as your father is is saying no to you and saying get out of my life and your mom is crazy
and this woman you trusted might be a lunatic and all this shit. It just as that on folded. It was
there. I was like, I, I liked it. I liked that that kind of experience sends one guy to be the
Joker and the other guy to be Batman. Yeah. So, uh, I thought that was pretty cool. My, the, the real
kind of inciting incident was it, my nitpicky mind really, it did, it did really bother me.
This movie, the, it's kind of doing the seven thing of you don't know what time period or where it
takes play. I got them city. Obviously. But on a billboard, there are on a marquee, they're showing
blowout, Brian DePalma's blowout and Zorro the gay blade. That to me says this movie came out in 1981.
Or, you know, it's set in 1981. So, and also Danero's talk show set looks exactly like Johnny Carson's.
Right. Who is filming Joaquin Phoenix doing his stand up at an open mic? Are they there with a
what kind of camera? Cause it's not a phone. And why are they filming him? Why are they filming him?
Because it wasn't memorably bad or crazy. Also, then why would they send it to Danero? And why
would he show it on television? That for it, for it to be such an important part of the plot
was wildly unbelievable to me. I was like, couldn't they have found an easier, better way to do this?
Because Johnny Carson never in a million years would be showing a fan submitted grainy video of
someone doing an open mic night of stand up comedy that wasn't particularly funny or interesting.
Well, I will say that back then talking to the guys that were that I know in the business of
stand up that were around back then, I know VHS recordings of your sets were not that rare because
you had to do it because it was the only, they were like, that used to be the only way you could get
booked in another club. There was no internet. So you had to literally VHS record everything and
send out the tapes and whatever. So it wasn't that far of a stretch for me to go, maybe the club
is just shooting the open mic or whatever. I will say though, it would have been, it probably would
have been a two time consuming way. It would have made more sense though, if they invited him on,
if there was a scout in the audience and then the scout brought him on the show and then he made a
fool of himself on the show. And then they kept making fun of that and then they brought him back
to make amends and then he was like, fuck you. Or even if Joaquin himself submitted the tape.
It just seemed like 30 seconds more devoted to that subplot and I wouldn't have spent a half hour
of the movie going, what? That said, you know, by and large, I thought it was a good film. I certainly
wasn't bored by it. The stuff with what's your name? Zozy Beats, that's probably not everyone.
Zozy Beats as his love interest. I won't spoil that for you, but basically what I thought was
unbelievable about that wound up, you know, proving to be true. And I liked that aspect of the story.
Yes, I thought that was cool. Shout outs, by the way, I had many comedian friends in this movie.
They mentioned Samaril, Samaril, Gary Goldman, Chris Red and Greer Barnes, who was my favorite of
my friend cameos in it because he plays one of the other clowns. And just getting to see my friend
Greer say to Joaquin Phoenix, what the fuck made you think that was a good idea? It really lit me up.
It made me laugh. And it was fun seeing Greer the next day or two days later and saying that to him
and making him laugh. One thing I couldn't believe and maybe some reviews have mentioned this, but it
just goes to show how narrow -minded, even film critics can be and that they don't see everything.
Really, what I found most jarring was that it followed very closely a Joaquin Phoenix movie that
came out one year ago that I saw in theaters and I believe mentioned on here called You Were Never
Really Here. Right. And in that movie he plays a mentally disturbed vigilante who takes care of his
sick mother and bathes her and so forth and then goes after a bunch of pedophiles with a hammer.
It felt so similar thematically in the way it was shot and everything to Joker. I don't understand
how nobody made that connection or how really how Joaquin didn't say I just played this basic part.
But if you're looking for a great double feature you know that's a great look at it. It's a more
indie look but a great look at a similar subject matter. And I think they're both good films. My
my hog is not fully erect but it's out there. My hog's up for this one and I will say this to
me the most challenging part of the whole thing for Joaquin Phoenix and he pulls it off.
Finding yet another way to do Joker. Yeah. Jesus Christ man. What's crazy is that this role has
become like our 10th or the 5th you know but like the Joker is something that draws our biggest
and best and and so bit. Yeah the way he does that sort of like that sort of a feminine
like sort of child clown like oh did I say like I was like man I've never seen that take with this.
Right. It's like that's that was that was very impressive to me that he found another way in
with the face paint on. To me he is the movie he's very good in the movie and I think it's what
puts it over the over the edge. So that's our show our next episode will probably be Jay and
Silent Bob strike back and reboot and then after that we're going to do creep show but it wouldn't
hold it wouldn't hurt us to there's a new episode of creep show this week. You know the more we know
about the series as a whole the better. Yeah I'd like to see a couple more apparently I mean I feel
like getting better and stronger as it goes creep show the shutter series not the move. Yeah so catch us
next time with Jay and Silent Bob. Parts one and two. Jotaro is a comedy on Instagram and on
Twitter. Jotaro is a comedian on Facebook. Subscribe to the Facebook page please. Follow me on Twitter
follow me on Instagram more importantly. And then we're ways off I will be at Skankfest in
Houston Texas the first ever outside of New York Skankfest and that's in like March I think
and I'll have other dates coming up before that we just don't know when exactly this releases I just
know that's far enough off to plug it. So come and come and say hello if you can. Oh also I'll be at
I can't announce that when you're all right that's it. I am the Patrick Walsh a Twitter and Instagram.
Follow me on Letterbox. It's a very fun app where you can see what your friends are watching and
what they think of it. And that is a great companion piece to my new Patreon solo joint which is a solo
Pat's movie corner where I sort of talk a little more in depth about four or five movies. I'm going
to post at least one of those a month as a bonus bonus probably more than that. So check that out
our Patreon listeners and if you're listening to this you are one and we thank you again for making
that journey with us. It has been not just a smooth transition but easily are our best and most
successful incarnation of this podcast. So thank you for coming along. Yeah we it gives us new hope to
maybe we maybe we can keep this thing going a lot longer than we had initially thought at the
beginning of this season. So that's good stuff. Oh one more plug I'm sorry I'm touring in January
in February February I'm going around the Chicago area dates are not posted yet January I'm also
Pittsburgh I'll be in Lancaster PA and surrounding areas look on joderosa info .com for tour dates.