I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell. It's time to review, review, review the movies we view.
This week it's Five Nights at Freddy's, which god it felt like fifteen folks.
Yeah, uh, we'll get there. This was new to me, I was not even, never even heard of the video game.
Um, can't say it made a new fan out of me, but we'll get there.
Well, it's uh, you know nothing, well whatever, we'll get to it.
What's going on with you, Pat? You, you hinted, well you said you wanted to talk about New York
on this episode, but then you also hinted that you had a date, which I'm assuming was not good
if you want to talk about it. Well, it was, I can't, I won't really talk about it. It was just,
I went on a date with this person, had a nice time. Um, as I told you, we went to the roost,
our old stopping ground, and um, then I got home and looked up her Instagram and she follows us,
the podcast, everything. Oh, okay. We talked for three hours. I'm like,
I think you need to mention that. It's like, you know, she knew, she probably knows everything
about me. Anyone who listens to the podcast would have a vast backlog of information about me.
So anyway, she just didn't bring it up. Maybe she didn't want to seem like she was
stalking or something. I don't know. Well, she's going to hear this.
That's what I was thinking. Yeah. That's why I didn't want to mention it, but here we are.
Um, well that's, that's, hey, thank you for being a fan, miss.
No, thank you. Of course. Thank you for being a fan. This is the person, uh,
Joe, I, I mentioned to you was talking a lot about, uh, bringing down society,
yes, which is not usually first date conversation, but look, it's 2023, baby.
Things are getting wild in these streets. It sounds like fun. I think, yeah, she was talking
about, uh, a lot of talk about the joker and how the joker is sort of how she wants to live her life.
All right. There you go. To each their own.
Each their own. Nice girl. Lovely. Um, might be a second date. I don't know. Uh,
I'm also about to go to Atlanta for the Miss Pat program. Finally starting back to work on Friday,
the writer's room for a couple of weeks over zoom, and then I'll be going.
Um, and yeah, New York was a lot of fun. I met, uh, Brian from impractical jokers. Yes. Q, uh,
the citizenry of New York treats as though he's a disciple of Jesus, you know, like any policeman.
I feel like if a policeman were to watch when shoot a homeless person in the head,
they'd be like, get out of here. We love the jokers. Can you take a picture for my daughter?
Like there's all these cops, like get a picture for my daughter and loves the jokers. I mean,
everybody loves, but yeah, really, you really see it in New York. Yeah. It's like when the
Ghostbusters are walking through the city, when they become celebrities and he was dressed as a
Ghostbuster, which added to it, but because it was Halloween, you should point out. It wasn't. Yes.
Yes. Uh, it was fun. We marched in the Halloween parade with a tequila company. Yeah. Shout out to
a super bird and my buddy, Tommy Mariello, uh, who's working with them. They're great tequila
and a super bird. Love the name. Love the tequila. Yeah. It was good to kill. We had a good time.
I got real fucked up at that parade. And then I got
COVID or something the next day, man. I was real sick for about eight days. Yeah. I was very
worried something was going to hit, but it never did. The one time I got COVID was the last New
York show. I got it right when I got back to town. I feel like all the diseases of the world
travel to New York and grow stronger. Yes, yeah, I got Jesus.
I'm pretty sure though, I got sick from the, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, Arlene's thing, the live
show. It was also windfall thing. I feel like that's probably where I picked it up because
everybody got Pinkstone's, uh, wife got sick and Brian eventually got sick and I, uh, it was all
A lot of people at that event got sick.
And yeah, why wouldn't we have?
We were in a windowless music venue for hours and hours and hours.
And then went to a windowless bar for an additional four hours.
Yeah.
So, and I got real wasted.
So anyway, that was, yeah, that was a fun time though.
It was a great, it was a great little Halloween week.
It was, it was great seeing everybody.
And the parade was cool.
It was a lot of fun.
Other than that, there's not much going on here.
What are you doing for Thanksgiving?
You go home?
I was thinking of having just my parents over to my new house and just the three of us
doing a little something.
But then my cousins invited us over, so we might go there.
OK.
But, you know, man, I feel like I got to I feel like I got to run right back to New York.
Thanksgiving isn't much of a holiday these days because I usually have stuff to tend
to over that weekend in New York.
But so, you know, I'm not really thinking too much about it.
I'm on the road on either end of it, which is stressful.
And I've got a lot of recording to do on the days that I'm not on the road.
So I'm really trying to look at December hitting.
My road work for the rest of the year ends December 3rd.
Flying home, desperately trying to not get sick and and then really enjoy Christmas.
That that whole stretch and the New Year starts and then it's all back out onto the road again.
You know what I mean?
So, you know, you know, what about you?
What are you going to do?
Roost?
No, God, no.
My plan was to travel.
I was like, I'm going to book a trip and just go somewhere.
And then we had to start work.
We start work on Friday and we work through Wednesday.
Then we're off Thursday, Friday.
So it's like there's no point in me traveling.
And I only have myself to blame.
I've been out of work now for months and should have done it if I was going to.
But I don't know.
A few friends have asked me over for dinner and stuff.
I have this weird like shame, you know, like two of my best friends are a married couple
and they have two adorable little daughters and they're like, come over.
We're going to watch plans, trains and have dinner or whatever.
But there's a part of me that's like, even though I was invited, I feel like I would
be imposing on their family Thanksgiving.
And then you flip it.
If I was them, I'd be like, come by, of course I don't get, but I can't, I can't
shake the feeling that I'm not wanted in a situation like that.
So I just don't go.
Well, perhaps it's not.
Perhaps you're misinterpreting it as not being wanted.
Perhaps what it is, is you, you, you feel a little just out of step in that scenario
or like a fifth wheel.
And it's not that you don't feel wanted.
It's that you're just like, I can't relax.
I don't know, man.
That's how I would feel.
Yeah, it's both.
I mean, you start to pick up on things like, you know, you, when you always got an invite
from certain for certain married friends.
And then now that you're not married, you see them on Instagram.
That's like four married couples out on the town.
That's always a bit of a jab, but you know, I just got to find my, uh, my bye -bye love
crew, uh, my Paul riser, my Dan Stern and my Randy Quaid, if you remember that film,
which was a full length advertisement for a McDonald's in addition to being a movie
about three divorced men out on the town.
But I would like, uh, like a divorced entourage.
It would be nice to have men I could talk to about that.
I think I've told you this, but my favorite Craig Kilborn, when he hosted the Daily Show,
uh, joke was he, he, he, he was doing like the, you know, the, the, the opening thing
where he's just, what's in the news segment.
And he goes, uh, he goes, uh, Helen Hunt announced this week that she will, that Matt,
Matt about you will be coming to an end because Helen Hunt has announced she wants to leave
the show in order to pursue her movie career after the success of as good as it gets.
Paul riser said he will do the same pursuing his movie career by sitting home and making
VHS copies of bye -bye love.
Yeah, I don't remember it being a terrible film.
No, but it, they just, they showed the poster of it and the, and the title of it just was
like, it really, I'm approving of the joke.
Just have you noticed now, like, if you watch SNL now, Che and Colin Jost, like this week
in particular, it was Chamele.
So there wasn't a laugh to be had, you know, the kids, the kids, complete void of talent
and charisma, but that kid, dead eyes.
God, that wonka looks fucking terrible, but they're doing this, uh,
show where not, I'm sorry, they're doing the weekend update and the audience is groaning
and booing every joke and Che, uh, in particular, you know, always kind of goes for the jugular.
I, the best part of, uh, the show these days, it used to be the most boring part, but the
best part of the show is weekend update.
Uh, the jokes are good.
They pull no punches usually, but even the most mild, innocuous things.
Everyone is groaning.
Everyone is like, Ooh, if you dare take a shot like that, like with Paul Reiser, no
audience would laugh at that now.
Like they look at everything as cruelty.
They look at jokes as cruelty now.
It's like somehow the entire world has changed in five years, but they wound up like Johnny
Carson style.
They had to make a comment after each joke because it's like, they all get this response
of like, Oh, guys, you're at, you're at the nation's longest running comedy show at 1130
PM on a Saturday night.
Loosen the fuck up.
Is it because are the groans though, because they, they did the thing where they would
make each other say terrible jokes.
And now the audience is trying to have fun with like, Ooh, Ooh, you know, I always enjoy
when they do that.
Those are funny, but no, it's like if they make a joke, that's, um, mean to like, uh,
they had made a joke calling Joe Biden old and clumsy, you know, that they used to have
Chevy chase playing Gerald Ford and he would fall off a ladder and crash into a desk or
whatever.
Now they make the mildest joke about an 80 year old man, maybe not being the strongest
Walker and everybody's like, Ooh, it's like, come on now.
You know, uh, these are jokes like the way we're not, we're not, they're not making jokes
about, uh, Hamas, you know, for Christ's sake, Nate's episode.
I didn't see the whole thing, but the, the sketch with George Washington was really funny,
man.
Yeah.
Metric system and everything that was, I was like, wow, that's really funny.
They, they have a couple of good ones all the time.
Now a couple of good sketches on there.
Um, and I still watch always.
I'm a big fan.
Here we go.
What's that?
Uh, you're not a fan of the show.
I don't dislike it.
I just don't watch it.
Um, but you know, I got friends on it and stuff, so, you know, it's, it's, I'm, I'm
when I see it, when it's funny and stuff, that's good.
Uh, I get a kick out of it.
Uh, but, um, uh, good news, psycho, because you were saying Wonka looked bad.
Uh, the trailer for Ghostbusters, frozen kingdom came out.
So frozen empire, whatever the hell it's called.
I thought it looked, I think it was awesome.
I love the plot.
Sorry.
I agree.
I agree that you had the ice thing.
I was like, right, you're doing the Ghostbusters two thing, not a perfect movie, but it's like,
you're coming up with a new crazy ghost story.
I like that.
Yeah, I like that.
It's a, a universal threat, you know, or large scale threat.
I like that.
There's clearly some bad guy that they hint at.
Uh, and I thought that Patton Oswalt was pretty perfectly cast as that, like, you know, the
nerd, the bookwormy nerd explaining what was going on.
And I was like, all right, that works.
And I love that you see Murray, Ernie, and Ackroyd in the, in the trailer.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm like, all right, man, this feels like it's going to be Ghostbusters.
Let's go, you know?
So I'm up for it for sure.
Yeah.
I like the first one as we, as we know, the first, uh, ghost afterlife, whatever it was.
Um, shall we movie corn?
Yes.
Uh, I have started watching the for my consideration movies for 2023.
A lot of them are in theaters and they start sending them to the house, which is always fun.
My first of these was a screening of the Holdovers, the reunion of Alexander Payne
and Paul Giamatti.
It also stars Dominic Sessa, who I was kind of unfamiliar with.
Probably now that I look, because he's only been in this one movie, um, Paul
Giamatti plays a curmudgeonly, believe it or not, uh, professor at a snowy New England prep school.
Dominic Sessa plays a kid whose parents kind of abandoned him for the holidays.
And divine joy Randolph from the high fidelity show who I love.
She's very, very funny.
She's great.
She plays a cook at the school.
And these three are sort of left behind for Christmas break.
They hang back to kind of Giamatti volunteers because he has no family and no friends.
He's kind of the Scrooge character and these three form friendships, a camaraderie,
you know, the ice thaws between the three of them.
It's pretty predictable.
It's kind of exactly what you'd expect.
It's over two hours for no reason.
Um, as we mentioned, uh, sideways, one of the greats, certainly one of the great Giamattis.
And I wanted more.
I just got to be honest.
I was so excited to see Giamatti freed from billions and trying again, like in a great
new part, and especially the reunion of pain pain didn't write this though.
It was another writer.
Um, and I think it really lacked Alexander Payne's mean, dark, satirical edge that,
you know, like that's what keeps about Schmidt such a perfect movie.
And what makes it so shocking when you start crying at the end of that movie is it's like,
it's nasty.
It's kind of a mean comedy and then reveals this like heart at the end.
The Holdovers is much more of like a generic, uh, feel good kind of Christmas movie.
It feels like something Miramax would have come out with in 1999,
like cider house rules or something like that.
So there's an appeal to it, a charm.
Um, there's at least 20 minutes of the movie is, is Giamatti walking around a snowy campus
while like Nick Drake songs play.
And for a movie that's 20 minutes too long, I, you know, we could have lost that Alex.
Uh, I think Alexander Payne made three perfect movies, election Schmidt and sideways.
And since then it's been pretty average.
Unfortunately, he's all this game, man.
Since the descendants and I did not like the descendants.
So, uh, well, and also too, they keep my friend Phoebe saw the movie and she was,
she was very excited and she was like, dude, it's bad.
She's like, it's just not a good movie.
Uh, now I don't know if I'd go, I haven't seen it yet, so I don't know.
But I said to her, I go, since the descendants, they've been,
they've been shucking his stuff out there to people.
Like it's these like knee slapping comedies, like election.
And they're not, they're like the soul searching melodramas.
Everybody's miserable.
Like it's, it's not funny.
Like, and then these reviews, it's achingly hilarious.
And you're like, what are you talking about, man?
Like, you know, so I had a feeling that this
was going to be another one of those, uh, it's a shame, uh, to hear that it might be,
but it's very well received critically.
For fit for 15 minutes of this thing, it's Giamatti being a dick to his students.
And that's great.
Like when that started, I thought I was watching like a new,
like a dead poet society meets bad Santa kind of thing or something.
And, um, that's super funny.
He's the first, when we first meet him, actually, they cut from a close -up of preparation H
to Paul Giamatti is how he is introduced in the films.
Like this guy is an asshole.
Um, and then his interactions with these snobby kids are hilarious, but that, that bite goes
away so quickly and you're just left with this kind of generic schmaltz fest.
But, uh, I wouldn't say skip it.
It's pleasant enough.
It would be fun with your parents.
There's nothing offensive in it, but it's not a great movie.
Uh, I have three Woody Allen's.
Uh, I rewatched Small Time Crooks.
Okay.
It's such a great movie, man.
It's so funny.
I'll try it again.
I have, I remember it being bad, but I don't, I don't remember much about it.
I think it's great.
He's great.
Tracy Ullman is great.
Uh, Michael Rappaport's funny in it.
Um, Lovitz, I want to say.
Lovitz is in it.
Uh, um, um, uh, Elaine May.
It's a great movie.
It's just great.
It's really funny.
Uh, you know, the, the dynamic between Tracy Ullman and Woody Allen is great.
They're a good pair.
They're a believable pair.
Yeah.
You know, he does like this honeymooners thing throughout it where she constantly
calls him stupid and he'll be like, oh, I'd like to punch your face right off.
You know, like they're always very combative, but they love each other.
It's very funny.
Yeah.
And, uh, you know, the plot is, is they're going to rent out this pizzeria that they're
going to make a cookie store so they can tunnel under it into a bank and rob the bank.
And lo and behold, the cookies take off and, uh, they become very rich, uh, as,
as, as the moguls of a cookie empire.
Um, it's just a fun, fun, fun, Hugh Grant's in it.
I really, really like it.
I think it is a very unsung, uh, Woody Allen movie.
And I think just as far as comedies go, it's just a great, fun, lighthearted
caper comedy.
Uh, it's very enjoyable.
I'll give it another go.
You ever, uh, I watched the new David Fincher picture, the killer
starring Michael Fassbender.
It is, uh, in theaters and also on Netflix.
Okay.
David Fincher, as far as I am concerned, had not made a bad movie, uh, until Mank.
And I was excited about Mank.
I know a lot about the back history of Citizen Kane and et cetera, et cetera.
And I just thought that movie was a fucking drag and was surprised because Fincher makes
such entertaining movies every time out of the box.
The killer, unfortunately is another step in the wrong direction.
Uh, I did not like this movie and I was so surprised by that.
I'm like, all right, he's getting back to his roots.
It's a hit man movie from Andrew Kevin Walker, the writer of seven, which is
arguably Fincher's best Zodiac, another prime candidate, but the killer for a half an
hour is Michael Fassbender in a high rise looking across the way through a window at
the person he's going to assassinate.
We've all seen scenes like this in thrillers before he's in there and there's a narration
going on and the narration is so boring and so generic.
He's like, you know, it's the kind of thing where everything is a quote.
So it's Fassbender just like sitting in a chair and then it's like, I think it was
Nietzsche who said, you know, like that kind of shit, the most generic voiceover.
And I text my buddy, uh, who had asked me if I had seen it yet.
I'm like, Hey, did this movie suck or am I crazy?
And he goes, well, a little teensy spoiler.
And it's really not, he goes, he's not as smart or as good at the job as you're
supposed to think he is.
That's kind of the, the fun of the movie.
Okay.
So Jesus Christ, it's hard to even explain it.
The movie is a, is a guy, he's a hit man, but he's bad at it.
So he's supposed to kill this guy and he's talking for a half an hour about what an
It's not a, it's not a comedy.
That's the thing.
It's a bumbling assassin, but it's not a comedy, Joe.
It's not like the man who wasn't there or something.
So he, he eventually shoots at the half hour Mark missing his target and shooting
the hooker that the, the Mark is with this lady in the back.
And then all of a sudden I'm like, Oh, this is a comedy.
We've been watching this guy talk about what a genius master assassin he is.
And then after a half hour of him talking about how amazing he is, he shoots the
wrong person in a room with two people.
I'm like, that's kind of fun.
It's not played funny, but I was like, I sort of get what this movie is trying
to do now.
And that's kind of interesting from there.
He gets in trouble from his superior, obviously, because he shot the wrong
person and they beat, they rough up Fassbender's girlfriend as punishment.
And then he tries to get revenge on them.
Then it becomes a standard hit man getting revenge on the people who sent
him out to do the job thing.
But there's nothing funny in it.
And when you look online, you'll see, and it's about half the critics.
The other half don't even mention that it's allegedly a comedy.
Half the critics are like a hilarious, self -deprecating look at Fincher
by the man himself.
It's a movie showing you how Fincher views himself as a director.
I'm like, I don't fucking think so guys.
That's not why David Fincher doesn't go into Netflix and say, give me a hundred
million dollars to make a movie.
That's a metaphor for my career as a director.
You're reaching because there's nothing there.
The movie is not good.
And critics have lost the ability.
Just like I was talking about with SNL, you don't make mean jokes at people
anymore because everybody screams at you.
And critics also just don't say things are bad anymore.
It's like this movie is bad.
It's boring as hell.
Everyone I've talked to thinks the movie is boring as hell.
I don't get it.
Maybe people will see it and like it.
If you do, I think if you didn't know it was directed by David Fincher, I don't
even know if you would finish this movie.
There's nothing interesting about it from a directorial standpoint.
There are no great shots.
There's no great dialogue.
There's very little suspense.
There's one great Bourne ultimatum style fight scene, but in a John Wick world,
it just seems generic and boring.
So yeah, the killer and the holdovers.
I know it sounds like I hated them both.
I actually think they're both fine, but to be like we're entering Oscar season.
It's the end of the year.
Like these are the great movies of the year coming out.
It's not looking good.
It's not looking too good.
Well, I watched a delightful film that I'd never seen called Alice.
It's one of the Woody Allen's I'd never seen.
It's about Mia Farrow plays a kept socialite wealthy housewife who has never fulfilled
any of her dreams or pursuits because she is married to a domineering condescending
prick played by William Hurt.
She falls in love with a tall dark stranger played by Joe Montaigne.
She begins an affair with him while she also sees an Asian sort of medicine man
who gives her these potions and herbs and things that give her magical abilities
that are akin to some of the things from Alice in Wonderland.
Eventually, Joe Montaigne is going to go back to his wife
leaving Alice, Mia Farrow's character Alice in the lurch, and she also at the same time
figures out that her husband is having an affair.
She's then tasked with a choice and she's given an herb that if she gives it to one of these men,
they will love her for the rest of her life.
She needs to decide, it culminates with a very funny scene where she's at a party and every man
in the party is hitting on her and she finds out that the cook thought the herb was nutmeg
and put it into the eggnog and it's very funny and she has to leave the party.
Anyway, it ends with her actually going overseas to help the poor
and becoming a single mother with her children and starting a life of true independence and
becoming the truly fulfilled and complete person that she was always meant to be.
It's a very, very quaint and charming film. It's funny
and that's it. It's just a really enjoyable film. Judy Davis is in it.
I think that might be everybody of note, but I liked it quite a bit. I'd never seen it and
I really enjoyed it. I saw that one. I find fantasy is not really Woody's
specialty. I like Purple Rosa Cairo, but I never like magical comedies. It's nothing to do with
Woody Allen, but that's just how I felt about it. After watching and enjoying Arnold, the Netflix
three -part documentary, I was excited to watch Sly about Sly Stallone.
I heard it's rough.
It is. It's real rough. There's so little quality control over there sometimes.
The Schwarzenegger movie was three hours long. First hour is his childhood through the weight
lifting. Second is his film career. Third is his political career. I wanted way more of the film
career, but it's a well -done documentary. Sly is like 90 minutes long. It doesn't mention
easily three -fourths of his films. They talk about like Stop My Mom Will Shoot and Oscar
and his bad years, but like they missed several huge hits. There's scenes of like a few scenes
of like Stallone talking to his daughters and stuff, but like not enough really. You don't
really get a sense of him as a man or what makes him tick or anything. When Copland comes up,
it's discussed as a failure. Stallone talks about how there's one great anecdote
where he talks about how he felt the scene where De Niro is eating the sandwich.
He was so excited to be doing the scene with him and he was like, I just felt like
De Niro was not giving me the classic De Niro. I could tell he was annoyed with me, but like I
wanted him to yell at me, so I just kept playing it like dumber and dumber and stuttering and then
finally he explodes and does that. I go blow away. You blow it. Of course, that's the best part of
the movie. So that was kind of cool to hear that that was like an improvised moment. That's very
cool. Where Stallone was like, I just wanted to wind him up and have him yell at me because what
a thrill. But yeah, his movie career is almost like 30 minutes of this thing. Like we're spending
a lot of time on the set of like Paradise Alley. They miss what people want to know about
Stallone. It's just a weird big miss. And when you're done with it, what I felt like was watching
a good Stallone documentary. I was like, oh yeah, that felt like I watched the bad version now. I'd
love to actually know something about him. So swinging a miss for Sly. Arnold, you know,
but the film section is great. Lastly, I rewatched Crisis in Six Scenes, which was the
Woody Allen TV show that he did for Amazon. I didn't like it the first time I saw it.
I rewatched it because I was just in the mood. I was just on a kick watching his stuff and I
wanted to watch something with him in it that I hadn't seen a million times already.
So I rewatched that. I really actually did enjoy it on the second watch.
Once I was able to step, he's denounced it. He thinks it's terrible. So, you know,
nobody's in the minority for thinking it's bad. But yeah, I actually enjoyed it on the second
watch. I was like, this plays a lot more like a play. It's not really a TV show. Or it's like a
movie that's just split up into six pieces. I find that once Miley Cyrus's character shows up
as a fugitive during the 60s, it takes place in the 60s, as the fugitive who they're going to
harbor at their home. And then he gets to start being the paranoid Woody Allen. I was like,
this is funny. I'm enjoying this. There's a really funny scene with him and Bobby Slayton
at a diner and Bobby Slayton is his manager and they're coming from a pitch meeting because
Woody Allen's a writer and he thinks the guys at the counter are in the CIA and he's like,
do they look like agents? Do they look like agents? And Bobby Slayton's being like,
I think I know them from William Morris. I'm not sure. It's just funny. It just made me laugh.
It's not great, but it's enjoyable enough. And I wouldn't say, hey, go watch it again,
whatever. But if you're in the mood, you want to give it a second chance, I would say, sure,
give it a second chance. It's got some very funny lines. It's quite charming. It also came out at a
terribly inopportune time. It was hard to kind of watch it without all the noise that was
surrounding it. But I don't know. I enjoyed it more or less. I'm a simple man these days. I like
things that don't challenge me too much. That show was fucking horrible. So did I at the time.
We were also locked inside. Was that Pandemic Times? It was right about to be. It was just
smooth sound. All right. We got our big movie of the week here.
We sure do. So, Joe, maybe you could tell us a little bit about the game. I'm unfamiliar with
the game. Well, the game started as a, you know, I think it was first on the iPhone, you know,
an iPad and stuff. I mean, maybe it was on the console. It's on the consoles now, but I don't
know. It's a very simple game. You're a security guard. You never see your character. It's all
first person. And you have a very simple task. You have to switch between these monitors,
these security monitors. And there's a rhythm you establish in switching back and forth between
the monitors. And then slowly but surely, of course, you start to see that things are moving,
meaning these animatronic characters or whatever. And you have to stay alive. It's a survival game
before these things get to you and kill you. And there's different ways you can
thwart them or halt their progress or whatever from the room you're in, blah, blah, blah. That's
the basic idea. So when now they've made nine of these, which they've evolved over time, but
it's not a terribly complex game. And the mythology comes out that this place, I guess,
is Freddy's. Freddy's is short for Freddy Fazbear's, which was Chuck E. Cheese, basically.
And these animatronic animals are the things that you used to see at the Chuck E. Cheese.
Now, I guess it comes out in the game through newspaper clippings and little tidbits and clues
and things that the place in some way is haunted by or being manipulated from beyond the grave by
this guy who was a child murderer. Mm hmm. Played in the film by Matthew Lillard.
We'll get to that. But so anyway, when they said we're going to make a movie five nights,
this is one of these again, dude, this is one of these fucking things.
This these games came out so long ago. Remember how long it took them to make the Angry Birds
movie? Yeah. Jesus Christ, guys, make the fucking thing. There's been like four knockoffs of Five
Nights at Freddy's. Right. One of them starring Nicolas Cage. Yeah. What was that? Willie's
Wally's Wonderland? Yeah. You know, so just came out to there's been knockoffs. It's like
because they couldn't get to whatever. It's just such a simple thing.
A guy's a security guard. He's got to survive the night. These things are coming alive. Some other
people come into the mix so you can have some people get killed. He's got to outsmart them.
How does he do it? You know, and OK, well, it's five nights. OK, so do it over five nights. Fine.
OK, but we want to bring in the mythology of this guy that killed kids and whatever. OK, fine. So do
it. Even even the amount of layers I just said that actually are related directly to the game
almost sound like too much for a movie. This fucking movie.
Now, I've not played all nine games. I played the first one and I read up on the games today.
I don't know how far into the mythology that they build in this movie the games get into.
My assumption is none, because everything I've read about the games is saying,
you know, through little hints and things, you learn about the backstory of what's going on here.
Right. It's fucking movie.
It starts with it starts with a guy, the main character. He's got a little girl living with him
and you assume it's his daughter. It's not. It's his kid's sister.
Already we're off to a confusing start. Yeah. Then he's having flashbacks from when he was a kid
of his brother getting abducted. OK, now it's getting more convoluted. Then we're showing him
in meetings with a woman who appears to be roughly his age trying to get custody of the little girl.
You think it's his ex -wife. It's not. It's his aunt.
His aunt. Well, now she's 25 years older than him. That's Mary Stuart Masterson from
Some Kind of Wonderful, Fried Green Tomatoes, et cetera.
She was tremendous. I thought she was like 40 years old.
I was excited to see her. I had not seen her in a movie in so long.
But yeah, when I realized and Joe texted me today, he was like a lot more custody battle
in this movie than I was expecting. It's about 15, 20 minutes into the movie. There's some scene
at a diner where they meet up. Mary Stuart Masterson is walking around with a lawyer,
a fat lawyer for comedic relief and trying to get custody of the girl. But then the flashbacks
and everything, it's constructed so confusingly. It's his aunt. So it's his mother's sister.
So now his parents are dead too. Everybody's dead.
And then, like you said - Coincidentally, unrelated to the monsters,
everybody's dead. And then she's walking around with this
lawyer, like you said, for comedic relief. By the way, the way her character is written,
she would never work with this lawyer, ever. She's a manipulative, conniving, scheming woman.
Then let's add another fucking subplot. She's secretly hiring his babysitter, you find out,
to be spying on him. The one rock this guy has in his life that he thinks is the girl he can
trust and rely on to watch his kid's sister while he goes to work every night is technically employed
in secret by the aunt. So he takes this job doing security at Freddy's, but Freddy's is shut down.
Yeah. It's almost like they come up with the subplot with the aunt and the custody
to give him a reason to need to take a job. It's like, guys, we didn't need that. Everyone
needs money. Everyone needs a job. That's how the world works.
It's so crazy. So he gets employed to watch a place that has been shut down since the 80s.
Why is it shut down? Well, a bunch of kids disappeared. So now there's another subplot.
They keep adding layer after layer after layer to this fucking thing. Guys, all you had to do
was make a movie about a guy that was hard up for work. He takes a security job at this place.
Once he's in there, weird shit happens and he starts to realize something is not right and
put your thing in about the kids disappeared and whatever, fine. But my God, man, then it turns out
then they bring a cop character into this who, for reasons that are inexplicable until the very end,
likes coming around to the abandoned Freddy Fazbear's establishment to check on the security
guards. Of course, she's super hot. It's absurd. Then you find out she's like a hot 27 -year -old
blonde cop. Have you ever in your life seen that ever? Then you find out that her dad,
as this all unfolds, her dad is the guy from the games and in the movie that killed these kids
and hid their kids' bodies. Oh, Jesus Christ. You find out that the kids that disappeared
were murdered by this guy that owned the place. He hid their bodies in the animatronic animals
because no one will ever look there. Then the kids' souls possess the animals and then the kids
are haunting the guy in his dreams that he has about his younger brother getting abducted. Then
you find out that the guy behind all this killed his brother too. Then you find out that guy is her
dad, the cop's dad. Then you find out that that guy is the guy that hired him for the job,
Matthew Lillard. Then you don't even know why Matthew Lillard hired him. At the beginning
of the movie, this guy's a security guard at a mall. He gets fired from the job because he beats
up a guy that he thinks is abducting a child, so he gets fired. Then Matthew Lillard is like,
I don't even understand what he is. I thought he was the manager of the mall and he just kept
giving this guy different jobs in the mall. It wasn't that.
He's like, you're fired, get out of here. Then he's calling him in the next scene like,
hey, you want to take this job I got for you? Everything about it is so weird and convoluted.
It's Josh Hutcherson from The Hunger Games, just a zero charisma on that kid, nothing.
I thought it was Pedro Pascal for the first like 30 minutes of this thing.
Really? Yeah, it's just like, so I read a little on the production of it and it started 10 years
ago, like 2015. They were going to do it. This is what I mean. It's ridiculous.
Gil Keenan, who's this guy who did like Monster House and stuff and he was going to do it and he
was all excited about it and then they fired him. Then they bring in Chris Columbus, who did Home
Alone and Harry Potter and all that. Columbus does a new script. He loves it. He's excited to
direct and then he gets so bogged down and frustrated with studio notes that he walks.
Then the guy who created the game takes over and writes the script, having had no script writing
experience at all. He throws out Chris Columbus's script. This is the guy who wrote some of the
biggest movies ever made. So we're left with this and what it really feels like is a slightly
elevated Shudder movie. It feels like it's from that same assembly line of like the Zac Efron
Firestarter. Just these really bad generic horror movies that look cheap. Then I just looked it up.
I was like, who's even watching this? It's on Peacock and blah, blah, blah. It's made like
$300 million globally in a week. So these games must be way bigger than we thought.
No, the games are huge. So they've got a built -in audience and all they had to do was not fuck this
up. Now we're going to get more. We're going to get more with this stupid fucking mythology
because the movies made money and that's all that matters. The audience score is at an 88 %
on Rotten Tomatoes. It's got to just be uber fans of the game franchise. It's got to be.
But I mean, like all video game movie adaptations, this sucks. This almost never works
and it's the same story every time it takes them. They've been talking about making a fucking
Bioshock movie since the Xbox 360 was still the current system. That is two full Xboxes ago
and they still don't have this thing off the fucking ground. Guillermo del Toro was attached
to do it and they couldn't get it done. These fucking idiots, they just can't do anything right
and it's because they've got a rotating cast of fucking staff members that don't understand
what any of this even is and they bounce from boardroom to boardroom sprinkling notes without
having any concept of what is going on and then going into the next room and doing the same thing.
It's just so fucking stupid. I wouldn't have been excited about this movie
even if I was a massive fan of the game franchise and I wouldn't have been excited about it even
if I wasn't because I just don't give a shit about animatronic bears coming to life and
killing people primarily because also too in the games, unless it happens in the later games,
there's no like the bear's face doesn't come off and turn into a saw contraption.
I don't even understand. There are like these weird saw torture scenes in it and it's also
a movie that's in theory for kids. My friends have taken their little kids to see it and they say
their little kids love it but it's also pretty violent. If it had been a splatter movie because
they cut away from each impact shot, they cut away from all the violence. Because that's the
13 fucking horror movies. They're being proven smart again and again. I was so shocked by the
box office on this thing because you know it cost five million tops and it's bad and we're
going to get more of them. I don't know what else to say. I'm sorry but at the end of this thing,
when this girl goes, he's my dad and then you realize it's Matthew Lillard, you're like,
what is Matthew Lillard, 10 years older than you? What is this?
He's older than you think. We're older than we think and he's older than we think.
That's fine but for Christ sakes, guys, your brain recognizes certain things and your brain
is not going to recognize Matthew Lillard as a guy that abducted a little boy 30 years ago.
As being like the appropriate age that man would be now. It's just crazy.
That's true. Also why, and it may have been explained, but why
were these sweet innocent kids, why do they become demons when they're placed in the...
They don't explain it. The thing at the end where the little girl, his little sister,
draws a picture and that turns the kids good all of a sudden.
This stupid cliffhanger ending where the cop is in a coma and you're supposed to give a shit if
she wakes up for the next fucking romp with these stupid fucking robots. By the way, if the kids are
turned good, okay, what are you going to do now? Also, I hate it that the animals are out of the
building. When they kill Mary Stuart Masterson, they're not in the venue anymore,
they're just in her house. God, this movie fucking sucked. It fucking sucked. I hate it.
Really sucked and it needed to escalate into something where they leave the
restaurant. They go out into the mall. Maybe that's the sequel or something, but...
No, I don't like that the animals leave the place. That whole game is in the place.
Oh, you're saying when they just left. I got you. I see what you're saying.
Yeah, that bothered me when it was in her house, when the bear was in her house. It's like,
the whole thing is Five Nights at Freddy's. It's not Five Nights at Freddy's and at Mary Master,
whatever the fuck her name is. Well, they can't have more dead kids show up for the sequel,
so I assume that these kids are just going to get turned evil again by some sort of curse.
The guy comes back, I guess he haunts in the game. That thing he says at the end where he goes,
I always come back. That's like a famous line he says in the game, I guess.
There's a bunch of Easter eggs for the fans of the game or something, but that didn't help me.
This game came out amidst the iPad entertainment craze. They started making games for the iPad
or that you could play on the iPad. The room was one of these games where
you went into different puzzle rooms and you had to figure it out. There was a loose
story of what was going on and who was controlling the situation, whatever.
They did the Telltale series, Wolf Among Us. They did the Batman Telltale games,
which are basically just pointing. You watch a scene and then you're given some choices and
you pick it and then whatever you pick, then that happens and you watch a scene. They're iPad games.
Five Nights at Freddy's was an iPad game. It was meant so you could sit
and have the perspective that you were looking at a control panel of monitors
and you could touch the screen and go from that monitor to that monitor to that monitor.
Yes, it was a huge craze, as was Angry Birds, another iPad, iPhone game, but Jesus Christ,
guys, this ain't a movie, man. This ain't a movie. If it is, this kills me. Have these people seen
open water? Have they seen hostile? Have they seen movie after fucking horror movie where they
put people in an insane situation, trapped or buried, whatever it is, with Ryan Reynolds?
The whole thing is him in the coffin. Have these people seen any of these movies and maybe
researched them and said, OK, well, here's how you make it interesting with with one scenario.
Watch Cube. Watch any one of these fucking things.
And that's all you had to do. That's all you had to do.
They just over plotted it. You know that that's all there is to it. If they were trying to like
and it sounds like when I read up on the Wikipedia that he just had a story that he came up with,
that he liked a new story. I don't think this stuff all comes from the games.
Um, it's just sort of needlessly convoluted and you couldn't make it as simple as that as just
a guy walking around killing people in a in a thing. You know, you can't a first person
shooter thing is never going to translate into a movie. But Joe was right. Really, all you need
is some generic reason why this guy needs money that maybe isn't some big child custody battle
with an aunt. And then he's working there. Then that's it. Yeah. Here's your prototype. Don't
breathe. Boom. Yeah. You know, it like, you know, my God, the thing with the ski lift, that movie,
fucking paranormal activity, literally what the move with the game is. Yeah. You're seeing shit
on security cam hogs way down on five nights at Freddy's hogs way down. They keep blowing it.
I mean, it is, I think since the eighties, I don't know that we've ever had such a fruitful time for
horror, maybe the, the post scream era, but we are just getting a lot of shit and streaming horror,
uh, is probably the worst other than comedy. It's probably the worst genre. Uh, they're just,
they just miss it on these direct, uh, like I thought sick. The Kevin Williamson thing was
extremely better than this. I know you didn't like it much job, but compared to this, it was great.
Yeah. That seemed like water in the desert from what we've been saying. Like we've had some good
ones smile and, uh, talk to me and et cetera, but by and large, these, these shutter or peacock
peacocks weirdly decided that they're a special, they're going to specialize in horror, but they're
great. The Hulu Ween ones are not great. It's like, it's taken over the direct to DVD
business. Basically you're watching like just low grade ripoffs of better movies all the time.
Folks, we will be back with the live episode from New York and also I believe we'll be doing where,
where evil lurks or when evil lurks, whatever the hell it's called. Um, second half of this month,
uh, just some plugs. Uh, I'm in Buffalo. I'm in Pittsburgh this Friday, but it's sold out. Thank
you for that. Uh, Buffalo, New York on Saturday, the 18th theater at Seneca one low tickets,
only a few left for that one. So please come on out. And then for the rest of this year, Denver,
Colorado on November 30th at the same summit, Phoenix, Arizona, December 1st at Crescent ballroom
and December 3rd, Salt Lake city at the sound. Well, uh, if you want to get tickets for these
events and the info for these events and all of the dates I have in the new year, which are a
shitload, New York, Nashville, Charlotte, Sanford, West Hollywood, San Diego, Palmdale, Portland,
Seattle, uh, go to Joe de Rosa .com. Also, please come on down to Joey roses. If you're in New York,
we're open seven days a week, food and drink. Always a good time. Joey roses, NYC .com. Come see
us. I am the Patrick Walsh on Instagram. Watch them as Pat show, if you like to on BET plus.
Uh, and we will see you next time for when evil lurks, when evil speaks, whatever that's called,
the new one. Everybody's chatting about on shutter. Uh, we will see you next time and
we will see you in hell.