Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, the podcast bringing you all the latest and greatest and
greatest about the genre films that you like to watch so much, horror movies, sci -fi movies,
action picks, sometimes a little bit of drama. My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh and this is a very special episode of the show. I believe our
second episode, maybe third, was a commentary on the film Nightmare on Elm Street. Please go back
and listen if you want sort of an in -depth look at that film as well as a look at the early days
of this show and my and Joe's relationship. Today, we are going big picture and we are
going to discuss the entire franchise. I'm talking Nightmare on Elm Street 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
New Nightmare. I'm going to be discussing, and Joe, I'm sure you'll join me, the four -hour,
three -hour documentary Never Sleep Again, which I rewatched this week.
The remake, the Michael Bay -produced remake, we might even get to Freddy's Nightmares,
folks. That's how in -depth we're going. Walsh, I own Freddy's Nightmares, the complete series,
bootleg, of course, because it's not available ever. It has never been released,
the abomination that it is. But I will take us on a walk through Freddy's Nightmares. We're
going to skip the segments today because we've got a lot to cover. Yeah, we've got our work cut
out for us. We're going to go, you know, we haven't really discussed, but we're going to
go chronologically and then at the end probably lay out what our ranking of these pictures would
be. And by the way, I just forgot, as I think a lot of people forget, Freddy versus Jason,
we will address as well. FVJ. Actually, I'm lying a little bit. We have to do a quick new psycho
because I said in the last episode that I was excited about this news story. And it does kind
of pertain to what we're doing here today. It's about, you know, it's franchise news. It's big
franchise news. Michael Keaton set to return in the bat suit in the new Flash movie starring
Ezra Miller. Now, he's not just an older Bruce Wayne. He's going to be putting on the suit.
I guess he's still in good shape. Well, they're doing it. They're doing. I couldn't be more
excited about this. DC has pulled the trigger on the Flashpoint storyline and the crisis
on Infinite Earth's storyline. And I won't bore you with the details, Pat, because I know you
don't give a shit. But basically, what takes place in both of these storylines is events that allow
the different versions of reality to start intersecting and crossing over. So suddenly
you have there's this version of Batman. There's that version of Batman. There's that version of
Superman. There's that version of Superman. You start getting multiple versions of characters.
They started doing it on the TV show already, The Flash. They brought in
Bert Ward came back, did a cameo as a former Robin. Robert Wolp.
How old is Bert Ward? He wasn't dressed as Robin. It was supposed to be that he used to be Robin.
My point is Ezra Miller showed up on the show as another Flash. They go into the Tim Burton Gotham
at one point and there's a Robert Wolp cameo. He's reading the newspaper. How did they get
Wolp? They pass a newspaper. You see Keaton's face on it. Brandon Routh comes in as Superman.
The kid from Smallville comes in as Superman. It's a brilliant, brilliant move on DC's part
cinematically because they just figured out a way to make every single thing they have ever done
in movies or TV count as the same universe and they can tap into it however they want. So now
they can go make a Robert Pattinson Batman and just go, well, that's that Batman and maybe he'll
slide over here or maybe this one's just Affleck or whatever. So they're bringing Keaton in as
Batman and as one of the, I'm sure many versions of Batman and the rumor is that he's going to be
the sort of Tony Stark of the DC universe, the older superhero with a lot of money that's able
to sort of orchestrate the team and get shit done because he's got the resources. So I could
not be more excited. Now I'm amazed that this is happening because, and you can see it online,
although, you know, trigger warning, there is a video that I watched of a fan approaching Ezra
Miller. Ezra Miller appears to maybe be on something or drunk. I don't know. I don't know
else would make somebody do this, but he chokes this woman. Right. And that was never proven to
be a hoax. It is Ezra Miller choking a fan who approaches him. They're letting him still be the
flash. That video came out and then just kind of went away. I just looked it up. There's no like
that video was a hoax story. So it looks like he did it. Yeah, that's I've heard. I've heard.
I've heard. All right. Well, then I guess it seems pretty stupid to wait until the movie comes out
to address it because people will address it. They've addressed. No, it's been addressed. It's
certainly been addressed. I don't know. I don't know that they're getting rid of them. But yeah,
it's so wild. Yeah, I don't know with all this shit, man. You know, yeah, you shouldn't choke
people. It's bad. Well, everyone was really pissed. They're always pissed with Tarantino,
but they were pissed because Emile Hirsch from Into the Wild is in the new Once Upon a Time in
Hollywood. Or, you know, you all saw the movie. Four seconds, by the way. Yeah, he's got a minor
role, but not three, four years ago, he also choked a woman and dragged her across the floor
at a crowded party. Right. Yeah. So I guess maybe choking is a gray spot for Hollywood. They're
out. Yeah. But yeah, that's it is. Oh, these times we live in. Yeah.
Everyone's Sinatra would just get mad because like a reporter would be like,
I think he's a bum. And Sinatra would be like, how dare you write bad press about me, you punk.
Like, it's like, my God Almighty, it was not incidents of choking. Now we're just choking
left and right. Anyway, speaking of men who are horrific, who do horrific things, the man of the
hour. Yes. The man, Fred Krueger. And you want to talk about times changing. I used to dress up as
Freddy Krueger as a child for Halloween. It was adorable. He was a child murderer. And yes,
many Halloweens on the first Halloween that I did it, my dad had to make me the glove because it
wasn't a toy you could buy yet. And what did you use as the actual knives? No, he found like some
sort of very thin metal that he could cut like, like very, you know, they weren't sharp or anything,
but like, and he made me the glove. He made me the fucking Freddy glove. That's nice. Yeah. That's
love. Yeah. That's love, baby. So yeah, we're going to go through the franchise film by film.
Bobby England portrays Freddy Krueger. And it all started, by the way, after watching that documentary
and then several other special features about these movies, I don't ever need to hear Robert
England speak again, as long as I live. When he is not in the Freddy gear, he is the most pretentious,
annoying fuck. I guess he's never done anything wrong, more power to him. But when you hear him
talking about like the deeper meaning of some of these movies, it's like, shut up, dude. He gets,
he gets real deep into that. I thought we were doing some real wild stuff, man. You know,
yeah, he's talking about, you know, Freddy's dead, but you know, yeah, I mean, I loved it. They said,
let's go all the way with this. I said, let's do it, baby. Let's hit the jets. Like, yeah, he's kind
of a cornball. That's why when they have him in the ponytail and then New Nightmare, you're like,
I don't think this is a parody. I think this is Robert England. Yeah. He's painting in one scene.
Yeah. My favorite part of that is the voicemail message where he's like,
I'm not home. He's like, you can leave a message, I suppose, but we're going to be gone for quite
some time. Could you have overacted that anymore, Robert? It's your going away message. Yeah,
you can tell that Robert England believes there are no small parts, just small actors.
Yes. And he takes that, that answer machine, outgoing message riff as far as he can take it.
So look, I don't, I mean, I don't think many people are going to argue with you that the
classic of this franchise is the original. A Nightmare on Elm Street, written and directed
by Wes Craven, launched, you know, an extremely profitable multimedia dynasty.
Which he didn't want, which is incredible. He did not want a franchise.
He didn't want it. In order to get New Nightmare, Bob Shay, the head of New Line had to give him
some back payments for all these. So Craven never got paid for all these sequels. And then finally,
Bob Shay, who comes off as notoriously cheap in the documentary, was like, yeah, we made amends
on certain things. He probably wrote him a huge check. Right. But the original is the classic.
We discussed at length in the commentary, but the original, to me, is the only one that still
really has the power to terrify. There are scary moments in all these films or most of these films,
but the original is still genuinely shocking, genuinely scary. Stars a young Johnny Depp.
As they discussed in the documentary, they wanted a more buff blonde jock type. They got Johnny Depp,
who was the right move. The great Heather Langenkamp, who comes back for New Nightmare.
And also the guy that plays the salsa dancer and along came Polly as Rod Lane.
Yes, exactly. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah. It's the same actor. It's the gay dancer, salsa dancer
that teaches Ben Affleck how to salsa dance. Ben Affleck? Or Ben Stiller, sorry. Along came Polly.
Yes. And of course, John Saxon, who also comes back for various cameo roles throughout the
franchise. Just a home run from Saxon. Saxon's great. The lady who plays the mom, I'm blanking
her name. She's a country singer. Really? Yeah. And she's wonderful as the alcoholic deadbeat mom.
She's really fantastic in it. Yeah. I mean, the Nightmare on Elm Street, the original really,
it goes into dreams. It feels like your dreams are becoming real. The highlight of all the
sequels is how crazy they can get with these dreams and how outlandish these fantasy sequences
can get. The original really captures what it's like to actually be in a nightmare, which I think
what makes it so scary. They do a lot of the universal things of sinking into stairs and
you can't move and the hallway gets longer and that sort of stuff. But at the end of the day,
this is based on real incidents, which Wes Craven talks about, about a guy who would not sleep in
his nightmares. It is such an amazing premise for a horror movie executed about as well as it
possibly could have been. I agree wholeheartedly, wholeheartedly, which is a phrase I think we should
start using on this show. But I totally agree. I actually think too that Nightmare on Elm Street
embodies the device that makes all great horror great, which is you cannot escape.
When you watch a horror movie and there is a threat, I think you're in a lot of trouble the
second an audience member can go, but why wouldn't you just drive away? Why wouldn't you just go over
there? Right. And the best horror movies to me all have a hook of you cannot escape. Nightmare on
Street, when you fall asleep, this man will kill you in your dreams. You're going to have to sleep
eventually. Texas Chainsaw Massacre, this crazy family runs this town secretly that you're in
and they're tied into everywhere and you're not going to get out. The Exorcist, my daughter who's
12 years old is possessed upstairs in the house we own. You can't leave. So Nightmare on Elm Street
does that tremendously, obviously. And just in a way that I've never seen
prior or since, the idea that they're going to make the monster a monster because he's horribly
burned, it makes it worse. It makes it more frightening. When there's the element of this
to you and you see the suffering of the bad guy, it's not just, oh, he's a demon and he's got a
crazy face and it's spooky looking. It's like, no, you're looking at a man that was literally
burned alive. It's so upsetting. And the way they incorporate that into his look, obviously, and then
incorporating him into these nightmares in the setting of the boiler room and that being a
representation of heat and fire, but that's also where he would take the children. The fact that
he's a, and this was a last minute change, that he was a child murderer, not a child molester.
Yeah, it's interesting that they, you know, in some of the later movies, they hint at it,
kind of, and it's more explicit in the remake. But yeah, he is just referred to time and time
as a child murderer. That was an absolute decision they made in the remake was they said we went with
Wes Craven's original premise, which was he was a molester. Right. He's a murderer in the original
films because Craven changed it. Also, another very interesting thing, it's a deleted scene
that you may or may not have seen, but a lot of people haven't seen it, but
there's a deleted scene from the first movie that explains when the mother is showing Nancy the
glove of Freddy and telling her we killed this guy that you think is haunting you in your dreams.
We murdered him. Right. They cut it out of the movie. There's an extended version of that scene
where she says you had a sibling and you find out that all of the kids on Elm Street had siblings
that were murdered by Freddy, which is why the parents murdered him. And it is kind of a head
scratch. You're like, oh yeah, why would the parents have murdered him otherwise? You know
what I mean? Like because he killed some of their kids. So that's a good detail. They probably
should have left him. Yeah. I don't quite understand why it was cut out, but it was. But anyway,
I'm sure they were just like, look, you see this guy, you're going to hate him. You don't need a
whole lot of backstory. Yeah. So the movie works on all fronts except for, and this is the one
criticism I would give it, and it's Craven's criticism as well. Craven hated the button on
the movie. He hated that Nancy figures out how to destroy Freddy and it's by no longer fearing
the concept of him, which is very mythic and mythical rather and interesting. And it's also
very Stephen King -esque. It's it. It's all that stuff. But Craven hated the button. He said the
studio made him put that button on, like, you know, where you're talking about where they see
the lid of the convertible looks like Freddy's sweater. And then the hand comes out and yanks
your mother back into the house. Yeah. Craven didn't want that. He didn't want this cliffhanger
thing of, you know, he insisted on that. Yeah. And Craven didn't want a sequel either. Right.
But the, you know, you can't do much better than Nightmare on Elm Street part one. It is,
I've said this on many podcasts, it is my gateway horror movie. It's the horror movie my mom showed
me that made me fall in love with horror movies. I was obsessed with Freddy Krueger as a kid.
Talk about different times again. I mean, it's just strange. Like he was like Bozo the Clown
to us or something like. Yeah, he became very cartoony near the end for sure. But I mean,
aside from cartoony, I just mean like from the get go, he was a pop culture icon. It wasn't like
this is a creepy guy in a movie and it's a bad example. It was like it was Superman or Batman
or Freddy Krueger or Jason. Like it was. Yeah. It was very iconic. Well, Friday the 13th franchise,
I think I haven't seen all of them, but it's an unquestionably worst franchise. I agree.
The Halloween franchise is an unquestionably worst franchise. There's just a whole lot of visual
invention and cool shit, even in the worst of these Sniper and Elves movies.
But the original has so much iconic imagery in it. It kicks right off with that little
sort of picture in a picture of him fashioning the glove in the boiler room. It sets the tone
right off the bat. And then some of those scenes they had to do in the remake, the glove coming up
between her legs in the bathtub. I would cite that final moment. I know Wes Craven didn't want
to do it, but it's that end of Carrie or end of Friday the 13th final scare. And honestly,
Bob Shape probably was right. It probably added another 10 million to it. It probably added the
sequels. But I remember that dummy being sucked back into the house. It looks good enough.
Sure. The effects are all really good. The blood, Johnny Depp collapsing into the bed and the blood
flying up. Almost every 15 minutes has a scene that sticks with you that you remember even after
only seeing it once. Right. And that's what a horror movie should really strive for, I think,
is just these amazing visuals. Another deleted scene is Johnny Depp's bloody body coming out
of the hole in the bed and falling on that one. It's an excellent film. I agree with you. I am
glad Bob Shape pushed for that button because it gave us a legacy. It would be a shame if this
movie was one and done. I know they don't hit the mark every time, but I am a proud owner of
Nightmare on Elm Street films on Blu -ray. And there are films I revisit, even the bad ones.
And then the last thing I'll say about the first one, the inventiveness of the weapon as well.
It's so crazy. He's going to have this glove with razor fingers on it. It's so interesting. It's
like a super hero -y version of a horror movie monster. He's got his weapon. He's got secret
powers or superpowers. He's got his costume. They talk about in the documentary about how
just like an action movie or a horror movie is only as good as its villain,
these movies, Freddy became the hero in an odd way, very odd considering he was child molester,
but they were talking about how the best of these movies are only as good as their hero.
Horror movie heroes and heroines can be super generic and the Nightmare on Elm Street franchise
really comes to life when you have a good hero or heroine like Lang and Kim who is excellent.
I had a massive crush on her from just the 10 of us, which was her TGIF sitcom. That was how
England played the role. They talked about how David Warner, the guy from Time After Time,
a really good British actor, was cast as Freddy and dropped out at the last minute.
Of course, it wouldn't have been the same movie, but that is a guy who doesn't seem to have really
a comedic bone in his body. I don't know where the franchise would have gone with him.
But England, outside of that phantom of the opera that he did and a few other things,
he's basically done Freddy and that's it, but he is an all -time legend of horror. There's a reason
that every few years they're like, let's get a new Jason, let's get a new Michael Myers,
because it doesn't matter, but they realized pretty quick you've got to have Freddy. They
started to shoot part two with an extra as Freddy Krueger because, of course, England naturally
wanted more money for the sequel. They realized immediately, okay, this does not work without him.
He's just an actor who found the perfect role. He is great in it. He's annoying in real life,
but he is great in these movies. He is great. That brings us to two.
And I, unlike a large portion of the free world, like part two. I understand why Craven didn't
like it. I understand why he said it broke all the rules of the first movie, because it does.
He particularly hated Freddy coming out of the dream world.
That's a big part of part two as well, but coming out of the dream world and just being in the real
world, and also the fact that Freddy chooses to return at a pool party. I think, you know,
Wes Craven just appears to be disgusted with every movie he didn't do, but two, he kind of
reserves his most bitter words for it. I love the pool party scene. I think it's one of the
most awesome scenes ever in horror movie history. I know it doesn't follow the rules of Nightmare
on Elm Street, but watching Freddy get, you're dropping him into a playpen. I mean, this is a
dance in yard filled with teenagers and he's running around doing crazy shit and slashing
everybody. It's a really fun horror movie scene. If I had directed it, I would have done maybe a
five minute montage of him popping rafts. Him just reaching in, popping it, and the person goes,
you know, falling into the water. Yeah, I would have liked a few like a hot dog on the blades,
gags. Sure. Yeah, yeah, I get it. They didn't do every all they could have. Yeah. Somebody's
like, I can't get this beer open. Let me with the knives. Yeah, yeah. So, two is infamous now
because of all the commentary about it that's come out over the recent years that was started
basically with the Never Sleep Again documentary and continued on with the Scream Queen
documentary, which we talked about on the show already. It's infamous for its homosexual
undertones, overtones at this point. I mean, it's painfully obvious. But I will say this,
I like that they make those commentaries in the movie. I like those undertones and overtones.
And I would say that as far as the entire franchise is concerned, part two is the only one
texturally that feels similar to the first one. It's grainy film. It's a lot of dark corridors.
It's a lot of it. They're in the house from the first one again.
Freddie, it's my hands down favorite version of Freddie. Visually, he looks really fucking
scary. And if you never sleep again, they talk about how the designer wanted to make him more
witch like, which is scared the shit out of me. Like real witches, not like, you know,
like not CW witches, like witch witches. But I like the movie, man. And it's still Freddie
in creepy one liner land. They're not jokes yet, you know, he's got his little quips,
but they're not funny. They're disturbing when he rips his, you got the body, I've got the brains
and he rips his head off and his brain is pulsating and you can almost see it like squirting.
That's great. That's great stuff. You know, so I'm a big fan of two. I realize it's not perfect,
but I think as a sequel, it works. And I think it was interesting that they took it to,
to at the time, the next level, which what else were they going to do? You know,
wouldn't have worked for me if it just retread what the first film already did.
I like to, I like it kind of for the camp value of the homosexual subtext. But I do wonder what a
very serious treatment of a closeted teenager dealing with Freddy Krueger would have been,
you know, they wouldn't have made that movie back then, but I think that would have been
fascinating. What we're left with is this movie that even the writer can't stick to a story on
whether he intended it to be gay subtext or not. The director and everybody involved in the
documentary seems to genuinely not have noticed the gay stuff. And they all laugh about it now,
but I mean, they're, they're whipping the gym teachers bare ass with a towel and, you know,
they go to a gay club in it. And I mean, look, they all don't, they all say we didn't notice.
I watched the movie for 20 years and didn't notice. Right. Yeah. I can't blame. And also too,
that's the big, that's the big example that people use is they go, they go to a gay bar.
It's like, here's the, every movie went to a gay bar back then there was police academy, every,
every, every movie went to the, what was that? The gay bar called the Swedish fish or something.
Yeah. The, the, the greasy pearl, something like that. You know, like, and it was, but like,
that was like a trope in the eighties was like a guy ends up with like a leather bar.
Right. You know, so it just didn't seem, it didn't seem to have any significance. It just seemed to
be like, Oh, this is like the part in the movie where they do this. So, uh, I didn't notice it
for years and years and years. Oyster bar. Mike is telling us that. Yeah. Okay. I didn't notice
it for after watching this movie as a kid for, you know, and into my thirties. Uh, then again,
I also wasn't a movie mogul, uh, create that film. I was a child just watching it. Um, but I like
the, I like the movie. I love the nightmare, uh, sequence at the top with the bus where it ends up
on the pillars and the earth is falling. And it's like that apocalyptic realm. And they, I think
they never sleep again. It's kind of like, they imagine that's where Freddie lives. Like it was
just cool, man. It was a lot of really fun stuff. Uh, and some very funny moments in the movie too.
Um, I would love to see though, as you just said, a real serious treatment with the approach, uh,
or take on this story. I would love to see that. I would, I think they could do that now. I think
if you, Hey, they're, they, they're still talking about rebooting it. I wish they'd done that or
more interesting than, than the reboot we got. I think, uh, now's the time. Now's the, for sure.
Reboot it now, bring back Heather Langenkamp, uh, Jamie Lee Curtis style, right? And make the
main character a gay kid who's struggling with sexuality and stuff and get back in all these
themes. I think that'd be fantastic. I couldn't agree more. The, uh, the documentary, which came
out, you know, not even 10 years ago, you can just see how much things have changed in that too,
because they do 20 minutes of talking heads of people like, Whoa, I didn't know it was gay.
And they cut to clue Gallagher, who was a fantastic character actor. And he's like, look,
did we know? No. Did somebody, uh, suck my dick so I could get the role or maybe, you know,
like they're all making these gay jokes and laughing about it. And you can watch even Mark
Patton, uh, kind of talk about it as this like funny blip on his career, which is why I found
the screen queen thing so disgenuous, you know, to act like it's destroyed his life. I already
talked about my issues with that documentary, but, um, yeah, two, two is not a bad movie.
I think Joe likes it a bit more than I do, but not a bad movie. And I think, uh, if anybody
says that one of these movies is better than the original, they're talking about part three,
the dream warriors. And I would say this as we slide into third, third,
which is what I did a lot in high school. When you slide into third and you feel the juicy turd.
Yeah, that's it. Um, were it not for two and taking the sidesteps that it took with the,
the mythology of everything three would not have been a thing when it would not have been
the triumphant return that it was to form with Wes Craven returning to the series, uh, and things
kind of getting back to basics and Heather Lang and cow coming back. And I, it, what a,
what a great payoff. What a great payoff. Yes. And I run up street three dream warriors, uh,
was written by Frank Darabont, uh, one of the very best adapters of Stephen King. Now,
well, he was the share runner of walking dead for many years. Now he's mostly in the news for
trying to get hundreds of billions of dollars out of the AMC network that I'm sure he's owed.
Um, but Darabont, of course, road directed the Shawshank redemption and the green mile.
Uh, he left after year one of, of, yeah, he was, I, and I believe he was let, I was not an amicable.
Correct. But you know, that's the only season of the show. I, I loved, but, uh,
Darabont and directed Britain and directed by Chuck Russell, who we just talked about with the blob.
The blob came the year after nine brown Elm street three, but Russell also did the mask. Jim
Craven co -wrote the story. Yeah, they, they took a crack at it. Actually,
Wes Craven had written a script and they kind of brought in Darabont and Russell to rewrite it.
And it became sort of more their thing. And even Craven admits, yeah, they did a great fucking job.
Uh, and he speaks very critically of every movie in the franchise, except this one.
So nightmare three is Patricia Arquette. Um, they talk about everyone in the film at a massive
crush on her, which of course you understand she's great in this. She's in my opinion,
arguably better than lying in camp as the heroin. Um, you sort of root for her more,
maybe it's just that she became a big star. Who knows? But, um, also Laurence Fishburne,
this is like a decade after apocalypse now. And Laurence Fishburne is like an extra,
he's got 10 lines. This is when he's doing like cowboy Curtis on Pee Wee's playhouse.
Yeah. What a career the guy had. I mean, now of course he's, he's huge, but, um,
Fishburne, uh, uh, who's the actor that plays the doctor in it? He's in a bunch of stuff.
I like that guy. He's a doctor is, is very good. Yeah. Craig Watson, who was in body double,
Palma's movie, body double. He was the star of that. And he stars in one of my favorite
tales from the dark side episodes called the geese and stacks, very creepy dollhouse episode
of tales from the dark side. Yeah. I got to get back into those, but, uh, it is a stacked cast.
I had seen half of this movie. I had seen one, two, half of three and new nightmare and the
remake is all I had seen. So a lot of these were new to me, but dream warriors is almost as good
as one. The, the drawback of it structurally is that there are 10 different times in the movie
where they're like, and usually it's the, uh, the overweight black guy. I can't find his name
in the cast list. My favorite of all nightmare and all three characters of all time.
He is absolutely fantastic and funny and funny in a real way, not in a jokey Avengers kind of way,
but 10 different times in this movie, he's like, it's time for us to go get Freddy. I mean,
they do that scene over and over and it's like, yeah, you know, you're fighting Freddy. We know
you're doing it, but they do the like Ash cock in the shotgun. Now it's time scene over and over
but the effects are amazing. The Freddy worm that eats Patricia Arquette is still, even when you
watch it being done, it's still kind of amazing and looks sort of scary and dangerous. Um, the
movie did extremely well. It got the franchise back on track. The visuals are incredible at the
end. They do sort of a Harryhausen homage with the skeleton coming at them. It's really a, uh,
kitchen sink kind of affair. There's an awesome movie. The kills in it are second to none. My
favorite kill of all time is in three, the TV, welcome to prime time, bitch. And he shoves her
head into the TV. I was actually standing smoking in front of the Glendale Galleria when I lived in
LA. I don't remember if I was with you or not. Um, but a woman came up to me and said, do you have
a light or cigarette or something? And I said, uh, I didn't, I think she asked me, I had a light.
I don't remember. And I go, uh, yeah. And, uh, and then, uh, I look at her and I go, wait a minute.
I know you. I go, wait, you're a nightmare on street three. And she goes, yeah. And I go,
use your TV, use the TV kill. And she goes, yeah. And I go, you're the best kill in the entire
franchise. And she's, she was very touched. And she said, God bless you. It was very nice meeting
her. Um, but that the kills are just awesome. The return of Heather Lang and cap coming back,
telling the kids inside the mental asylum that are suffering from these nightmares,
as she did in the first one, that they're the last of the Elm street children. What a chilling line
in the movie. Of course, it's not true because they make like eight more, but when she says that
she's basically trying to, they're, they're all on an asylum. You know, some of them have tried to
commit suicide. They're all very troubled teens. Um, and she's basically wants to test out a drug
that will keep them awake, you know, because she knows what this is.
Prevents dreaming. It's not, doesn't keep them awake. Prevents dreaming. Suppresses dreams,
but it's, it's got potentially dangerous side effects. Right. Uh, the, you know,
and then the classic power struggle, the supervising doctor is against it.
Thanks. These kids just need some good old, uh, fashion therapy. The newer doctor, the younger
hipper guy is, uh, wants to give it a shot. He sort of is falling in love with Nancy.
Uh, they get into the lineage of Freddie, which is great. The bastard son of a hundred maniacs and
all that stuff. My buddy Brian told me he saw, uh, three at the, at the Vista here with Darabont
and that line that Freddie is the bastard son of a hundred maniacs got a standing ovation.
Uh, it is an amazing line and you watch all these movies, especially sequels and nine times out of
you're like, why did they make these choices? That's so stupid. That's so wrong. And this is
just a sequel where every choice is correct. The backstory of Freddie, that it was a nun who was
trapped with, with a hundred insane criminals and they all raped her, um, is you, you couldn't come
up with a crazier, better, more horrific backstory. And it's better than the Freddie backstory,
you know, that they do everything right. What do you mean? You said it's better than the
Freddie backstory. You know what I mean? They, the burning, the burning alive. Oh yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It complements it. And in a way it's even more kind of sick and depraved and
it also fits like they're not inventing shit to get out of plot holes or whatever. They're giving
you more about Freddie's backstory and it's more disturbing and, uh, just really, really well done
from a script standpoint. And that his own mother is saying, he's a piece of garbage. You need to
kill him. There is no, yeah, there is no sympathy. There is no empathy. He's horrible. He came from
bad stock. Uh, he's damaged goods and that's it. Uh, John Saxon returning as Freddie's, uh,
Nancy's father. That's a great reveal. It's like that classic sort of Bogart scene where she goes,
I know the man that can help us and they go to the bar and he's like a drunk now who's not on
the force anymore because, you know, his wife is dead and his daughter's crazy and all that.
Just so good, man. They go back and they dig up the skeleton. The skeleton comes to life, as you
said, in the, in the, you know, that sort of Harry, Harry, uh, what's his name? Harry House. Ray Harry
House. Ray Harry House. Um, it's just great stuff. The original script, which is a lot of fun to go
back and read, is really dark. I mean, even compared to the first film standards, uh, it's
really dark and really crass. Like it's, it's vicious. Like I remember there's a scene where
he calls Nancy cunt. Freddie does. They actually show that in the documentary, a couple of pages
of the script. I would love if they did an adaptation of that version too. There's a lot of
untouched Nightmare in Elm Street material that I would love to see come to life. Like I, I,
it's just so interesting. Uh, four is a much brighter, I mean, they only can get so bright,
obviously, but four is when, uh, Freddie starts to become funny. Now, when I was 12 years old,
I saw part four and it blew my mind. I mean, I, I loved this thing. I can't even, I mean,
four came out around the time of Tim Burton's Batman, I believe. Um, it would have been a,
about a year prior, August 19th, 88. Uh, I'm just giving you the basics real quick. It's called
the Nightmare in Elm Street for the dream master. Uh, and it was directed by first time director,
although, you know, on the scale anyway, Rennie Harlan, who was a director who did some of the
best and most visually exciting action movies of the eighties and nineties and now is combined to
like direct to video stuff for some reason. Maybe he's got a personality issue, but Rennie Harlan
did, uh, he did the Adventures of Fort Fairland. He did Die Hard 2, which is awesome. The scene
where Bruce Willis hits the ejector seat and flies up into the camera is one of the coolest
things in movie history in my opinion. He also did Cliffhanger, which is awesome. The Long Kiss
Good Night, which is awesome. Uh, Deep Blue Sea, which is ridiculous fun. And then I see where,
where they, uh, pulled the plug on him was Cutthroat Island. One of the biggest flops of all time.
Yeah, that's up there with Waterworld. Yeah. I like both those movies actually, but
Rennie Harlan comes off as pretty charming in the, uh, in the documentary and they just said he was
like living in a rundown apartment with a roommate. He stunk, like he was wearing the same clothes
every time they saw him and he just basically begged to do it and they let him. And, uh,
they talk about how Bob Shea, the head of New Line hated him and didn't want him to do it and
wouldn't talk to him on the set. But then opening night, he gets a call from Bob Shea and he's like,
let's go, uh, drive around and check out all the, uh, the theaters because he saw what kind of hit
it was going to be. Um, but yeah, Rennie Harlan, I think gives it a great visual flair and also a
lot more comedy. I was blown away that Freddie comes back from being peed out of a dog's penis
as fire. That was a surprise to me. I will say, but yeah, take it away, Joe. I just wanted to make
sure we got the credits. Yeah, no, Rennie Harlan clearly was like, and I mean, look, he didn't write
it, but, uh, the writer and, you know, and director and, and producers, sorry, you know, who did write
it, Brian Helgeland, who wrote and was nominated for LA confidential, one of the greatest screenplays
ever written. That's so weird. That's so weird. This was clearly the, the Freddie had been established
at this point. This was clearly a big money franchise at this point. Part four is when they
clear, clearly said, let's do it. Like, let's pull out all the stops. Let's make the big blockbuster
popcorn summer nightmare on Elm street movie. And that's what they did. It's a, it's a lot of fun.
It's absurd, but it's a lot of fun. I never was crazy about the fact that they killed Joey
Kristen and Kincaid right off the bat. Uh, but they were hell bent for some reason on turning the
story over to a new heroine in a new set of characters. I don't know why they wouldn't
stick with the old ones, but they didn't want to, uh, I like Alice as a, as a heroine in this film,
uh, but in my opinion, Alice and her crew can't compare to the dream warriors.
Well, the girl's playing the same role that Patricia Arquette played in three and they
couldn't get her. And that to me is nuts. Uh, it's not nuts that they couldn't get Patricia
Arquette. Apparently she wanted a very nominal raise and Bob Shea wouldn't give it to her.
But yeah, the fact that this girl is playing Patricia Arquette's role, I,
I only knew that by looking at the Wikipedia page. I don't know why they just didn't make her a new
character. They look nothing alike at all. And also it doesn't work that suddenly everybody from
part three is entirely adjusted and normal, right? You know, you got Joey who in part three
hasn't spoken in 18 years or whatever the fuck it is. And this one, he's like skateboarding down
the hallway of a high school, like, Hey baby, he's getting, you know, he's getting chicks and
whatever. It's kind of ridiculous, but, um, but it's still a fun flick. The one thing you said
that is, is not entirely true. This is the one sequel that Craven said he really liked. He said
he really liked part four. He thought it was fun and he enjoyed it. He says that in the,
in the never sleeping game. Um, you know, some fun kills, but, uh, uh, our buddy Pinkstone, uh,
who we discussed often on the show, uh, discussed often, discuss often, not discussed, uh,
yeah, he and I have often agreed that the, the jump the shark moment of Freddy Krueger is in
nightmare on street four. And it's when he says, Rick, my little meatball and eats the meatball
that's Rick's face. That's crying. Yeah, that's pretty bad. Um, well for like England says his
favorite moment in all of the franchise is, uh, the, the moment where the Patricia Arquette stand
is coming out of the diner and they replay her doing that like three, four times. Um,
that's Alice does that. That's Alice. Okay. It is a very cool moment. Uh, and,
and something I wish the franchise did more of in that recreating that dream feeling. Um,
I remember seeing that in the theater with my parents and my mom looking at me and my mom
looking at one another, thinking a mistake had happened in the real, like it was so confusing.
And then it was like, oh, wow, that's really cool. They just, they got me. They tricked me.
Yeah. The, the, the guy who, and I can't believe we got out of three without mentioning the nurse
scene. I remember Ebert even spending most of his review talking about that nurse scene,
but if I had seen that when I was 10 or something, it would have just pushed me directly into
puberty. I mean that they did such a great job of casting what the ideal woman for a
10 year old boy would be. I mean, she, she's unbelievable. And then in four, the actor who
played that part is like, you know, of course, uh, my weakness is a beautiful naked woman always
has been whatever. He says it so many times that you're like, we got it, dude. You're straight.
Yeah. But, um, in four, they have the woman in his waterbed come up nude. Uh, and, um,
I appreciate those moments. And I feel like all eighties horror should have some nudity.
It's why you're there. It's a big party. I'm not against a little Wang flopping around.
Not at all. They couldn't do it back then. And a cool kill. The waterbed kill is pretty cool.
And it's sort of a nod back to the Johnny Depp kill in the first movie. Um, you know,
Kincaid's kill is not anything, uh, grand, but at least Kincaid gets to die at the scene of the
crime. When the, when, when Freddie comes back to life, the, the rebirth of Freddie, that whole
sequence is pretty cool. It always reminded me of the hellraiser scene when Frank comes back from
the attic boards. Right. Um, and you know, it's a pretty fun movie. Like I said, it's, it, it is
the Star Trek four of this franchise. It is the one where they were like, we're going to do
something from out of left field fingers crossed. It works. It did work grossed an insane amount of
money, uh, solidified Freddie Krueger as an absolute household name, uh, and, and pop culture
phenomenon. Uh, and so much so that they rushed to make arguably the worst entry in the series
next to six, uh, Nightmare on the Street, part five, the dream child. Dream child,
which you see a significant drop off in budget in, in the writing, in the directing,
in the acting, in the cat, every part of this thing is a drop off. This is a movie that works
for approximately seven minutes, the entire opening sequence of this horrid birth that's
happening in this disgusting hospital. And you realize it's Freddie's mom and she's, you know,
she's about to give birth to him and you're going to see Freddie be born. And then he comes out as
this like burned rat and then like scurry. It's so disgusting and fun. And then, you know, the
classic line he comes to life and he grow and he puts the hat on and he goes, it's a, it's a boy.
Like that whole sequence works really well. And then from there on out, this fucking thing plays
like a made for sci -fi. It's terrible. That it's a boy. There's these writers that talk about how
they, they brought in a lot of people who were doing horror novels at the time to pitch their
take on Nightmare on the Street five. And they had pitched this dark, amazing version, although any
writer would say their version was amazing. Maybe it wasn't, but they said the only line that carried
over into the new version was it's a boy. And they, they clearly hate what, what was done,
but that's a writer. You know, they turn in the draft. It was rejected. They're going to hate
whatever gets made, of course. Sure. But Nightmare on the Street five, the dream child is bad. It
does seem cheaper. There is a lot of discussion about Bob Shay's cheapness, which is odd because
eventually a new line would be the studio that made the Lord of the Rings trilogy or at least
co -financed it. It is directed by Stephen Hopkins, who his Wikipedia page is hilarious to me. So
he said, when I look back, I think I'm the luckiest guy in the world because I don't understand how
it all happened. He's clearly not a fan of it. He made Predator two. He said, I'm pretty immature
really. So it was kind of just a laugh. He talks about how much it sucks. He followed it with
judgment night, which he says is a real absolute total bomb, even though that's kind of a cool
movie blown away with Tommy Lee Jones and Jeff Bridges. He says, I made a lot of mistakes.
That's not a terrible movie. I like that movie too. And The Ghost in the Darkness with Kilmer
and Douglas and the Lions. And he says, it was a mess. I haven't been able to watch it.
So how does this man keep directing it? He hates everything he's ever done. He's another Josh
Trank or whatever his name, you know, Josh Trank, Josh Trank make terrible movies until the cows
fucking, you know, for sure. And some of those movies are pretty good. This movie is just not.
And this is one where the stuff they invent in terms of Freddie's backstory, you know,
they're continuing earlier stuff, but it just feels wrong. It does not work in my opinion.
The most memorable sequence is to me, something that I know would have deeply traumatized me as
a kid, oddly enough, because I just hate, I hate stuff like this, but the Greta scene, the,
anorexic ish model who was forced to in the unrated cut to eat herself, Freddie is serving
her herself. Apparently that was way more graphic and very disturbing, but, you know,
he's feeding her herself and her face keeps blowing up and she looks like the kids in the
Garbage Pail Kids movie, you know, that like same kind of facial style of makeup. I don't know why
it was so unsettling to me. It's the only nightmare in it that really works, even though I hate
it, but I acknowledge that it's scary and it does work. Yeah, that's a decent nightmare sequence.
This is also in the documentary around when England says, we were shooting at this point,
two buttons for every scene, one funny and one not funny. And then of course they use a funny one
every time. Right. It's just no pun intended, an abortion of a film. It's horrible. It sucks.
I've watched it a million times. I never enjoy it. I never will enjoy it. Even as a kid, I remember
seeing, I remember going to see a movie with my friend, Scott, my best friend, Scott, that I
grew up with. And before the preach, before the trailers came on, when they're showing just like
the still pics on the movie screen, they showed us still for Nightmare on street five, the dream
and we freaked out because it was like so soon after four, we couldn't believe it was happening
already. And then I remember seeing this thing in the movie and just the movies and just being like,
God damn it. Like something's not right. I'm not enjoying this.
It's got what I consider to be the second most offensive of all Freddy kills.
Uh, first of which is in the, is in six, which we'll get to a super Freddy in this,
my God, I'll fucking mighty. I mean, they put Freddy on a skateboard and then he turns into
a superhero. It's super Freddy. He exclaim, it's just so fucking bad. Like it's, it's terrible.
It's fucking terrible. I mean, the, the scene that is especially for a diehard fan, like yourself
the franchise is, is I assume a slap in the face, but it is kind of cool is the comic book
sequence. No, that's the one I'm talking about. That's in six. Oh, okay. No, no, no, no. This,
that's in five. Six is a, we'll get to six. Six is the video game one, which is okay. Yes. To me,
that scene while being stupid and while not being, you know, anywhere near what you want to see Freddy
do. I thought it's the reason I like the franchise more than others is because it,
it takes those visual chances. It does kind of cool visual things, even though it doesn't even
look great. And it's incredibly stupid. I admire that they went for it, but, uh,
well, here's what bothers me about it. You're taking the kids love for comic books. He's a comic
book artist and then that's his nightmare. It doesn't make any sense to me anymore at this
point. This is what, this is what five and six start doing. They start taking like,
like the bulimia scene is great because the woman is obsessed with her figure. She's terrified of
being fat. Right. Uh, the asthma kill is pretty good because she's, you know, she's got a condition
that is scary to her, you know, that frightens her. But when you take it, it's, it's like,
if, if somebody says, you know, my God, I love, I'm an accountant and I love crunching numbers.
And then he's like, he's, you know, he's stuck in a calculator with Freddie. I'm like, well,
this is stupid. You wouldn't be scared. Let's just say I've been batting it around while I'm
out here in Montauk. Okay. Um, sorry, excuse the noise. I'm, I got to plug in my laptop,
but, uh, well that's fine. Let's, let's slide into six, which is even worse somehow than five. Uh,
it's crazy how bad six is agreed. Um, this was, you know, what, what we didn't go into with
the dream child is that this one, this one, and then new nightmare have the two most notorious,
uh, creepy kids from, from 80s films. So this one has the kid with the big giant eyes who looks
like he's a corpse. He plays, you know, sort of Freddie's son and that kid appears in like
everything. He's in Jurassic park. If you'll remember, he's like the little annoying kid who
like bothers our heroes. And then in new nightmare, you got the kid, uh, Nico from a pet
cemetery, the kid who says boys have a penis, girls have a vagina from kindergarten comp.
Yeah. But, um, that also, by the way, is the kid that they tell, uh, they needed him to cry in
and, uh, somebody whispered in his ear, your dad died. Your, your mom that, well, yeah, the dad
says, he told the director like, look, I know I've got, uh, if you need him to cry, I got something
I don't like to do, but, uh, but I'm happy to do it. And he was, yeah, we're going to need it.
And he goes over and tells him that his mother died. Um, child actors, man. Oh, it was a different
Hollywood back then, wasn't it? It was anyway. So yeah, part six is Freddy's dead.
The final nightmare, the final nightmare, which is the only nightmare on Elm street to feature
Roseanne and Tom Arnold. And this was on the coattails of, uh, Jason goes to hell. The final
Friday. This was the thing. This was a big thing that they did where they were going to, where they
Mike, can you tell me final Friday or new night or, uh, Freddy's dead, which came out first?
Cause I believe final Friday came out first because I remember when I, when they announced
this one and I saw the title, I said, Oh, they're doing what they did with Friday the 13th. They're
doing like the big send -off to Freddy finally. Right. Um, this movie makes me sick. This is the
only one that I won't even put on. Uh, I see it in theaters with the 3d. I saw it in theaters with
the 3d where they told 3d look better. I hope it was good enough. I mean, you know, it was that
old school 3d where it was literally like the blue and red images, right? Whatever. But, uh,
I saw this with my cousin, Denise in the theater and, uh, Oh no, Freddy. Sorry. I'm wrong. Freddy's
dead was first. And then Jason goes to hell with second. Okay. Thank you, Mike. Um, and which was
the home alone where the wet bandits killed Kevin McAllister off? What year was that one?
Uh, that's Kevin's dead. Kevin McAllister goes to hell. Yeah. Uh, but I mean, this thing,
I mean, you want to talk about jumping the fucking shark in every way. I mean, they,
this is the, this could be the prototype for everything wrong to do in a sequel. They give
Freddy a daughter. They turn a spring, Springwood or Springfield, whatever the town's called
into this like post -apocalyptic, uh, you know, wasteland where no children exist anymore.
And now all the adults have gone crazy. Um, they make every killing that Freddy does just an absurd
set piece. That's, I mean, they've got him riding a fucking broom and talking like the wicked witch
at one point. They have him wheel out one point that is two minutes into the movie. They have
him wheel out a card of spikes. Like they're doing like Wile E coyote shit in this thing.
It's got the most egregious of all kills in any nightmare in Elm street. When he puts the kid
into the video game again, a kid that likes video games, why would his nightmare be a video game?
And then Freddy is playing with the power gloves and he actually says, now I'm playing with power.
He says the Nintendo catchphrase, this fucking thing, they do a not, this is your brain on drugs
parody in the middle of the movie with, with Johnny Depp, who comes back, uh, the lady that directed
this movie should be sent to the wolves. I mean, she's like a, she was like a producer at new line
cinema. They let her direct this thing and she says it in the goddamn documentary.
Her whole take was we're just going to go nuts. We're just going to do everything crazy. It's
like, no, don't do that. Especially when you guys start talking about the other versions of this
movie that was submitted, one of which by Guillermo dealt or was it Peter Jackson or Guillermo?
Peter Jackson, you know, that would have been amazing. Amazing. Some of the version that went
with was written by Michael DeLuca, who was the head of production at new line cinema.
So you can kind of see why they chose his draft. No executives writing anything. That's insane.
Shea was trying to do everything in -house at this point. He's letting like, yeah, the lady was,
I forget what she said she did before this, but it was like, it was crazy.
Like John Waters. I mean, her name is Rachel Talalay and she went on the new tank girl.
Robert England's like, you know, she came up with John Waters and she kind of wanted to bring some
of that spirit to the Freddie franchise. And it's like, look, I absolutely love John Waters. What?
Why would that be the spirit you're bringing to the Nightmare on Elm Street? It's insane.
It's fucking nuts. It is fucking nuts. It's a terrible, terrible movie.
Freddie deserves so much more of a send out. Oh, oh, oh. They give him a daughter and then they
show the new backstory of Freddie, which is he was married and like had a bunch of different
gloves that he used. And then his wife found out that he was killing kids. And then he kills his
wife and the daughter witnesses that. And then she suppresses it because it was too dramatic.
And then she has to, Oh my God. And then this fucking 3d thing they tacked onto it where the
last 15 minutes were going to be in 3d. That was the big gimmick of the whole thing. And the girl
in real life or in the movie, the character puts on 3d glasses. So we're just saying fuck any sort
of realism. I mean, I know it's Nightmare on Elm Street, but that was nuts to me, her putting
on 3d glasses. I was like, they didn't even try to explain why she wouldn't be doing that. Not
that there's any sort of reasonable explanation I would have bought. Right. And then finally,
finally, the only almost redeeming part of the film is when she goes through Freddie's head,
she gets into Freddie's dream. And you see the memories that he has from growing up,
which none of which make any sense. One point he's with his father who hits him a lot. And you're
like, what? His dad, he didn't know the dad. That's the point. Yeah, they never show the
nun mom again. I guess it's supposed to be these in foster care or something.
And then the big kick in the nuts when he's burning alive by the parents that kill him.
And what could have been this awesome fucking sequence where you finally got to see that go
down. These like three demon heads from hell that look like Henson Muppets fly around him and say,
like, we'll give you everlasting. It's like, guys, you're this is like worse than when they
went into the town in the second matrix or whatever. You know what I mean? Like nobody
needed to see this. You're showing way too much and explaining way too much. This sucks.
Oh, it sucks. It definitely sucked. It didn't do that well. Nobody liked it. Critics audiences
didn't like it. Before we get to the reboot. Now, the DVD set has two episodes of Freddy's
Nightmares on it. The one I was most excited to see was the pilot directed by Tobey Hooper,
which everyone says is great. The only good episode not included to start it. I was amazed
to see that it had it start John Cameron Mitchell, who is now the director of a bunch of movies like
Short Bus. He's on the show Shrill. But I got through two minutes of this thing and I was like,
this is this is sub USA up all night. You know, it looked like it was made on for no money at all.
They talk about on the documentary how they got away with a lot more stuff because it was syndicated.
And the guy also is to tell you, I'm sure he regrets doing this now, but he's chuckling,
talking about how they would have actresses get naked, knowing full well that they couldn't use
it. And he's like laughing. And if you see it in a flash of his eyes, like I shouldn't have said
that out. Right, right, right, right. I got through five minutes and I was like, joke and handle the
Freddy's Nightmare portion. I'm not going to believe it was an hour. They actually show the
origin of Freddy in the first the first episode is called No More Mr. Nice Guy. They show the
origin of Freddy and then completely fuck it up by having him linked to a different family with
a different cop father. When you're going you're going out of your way to be confusing now.
It's not Nancy. It's not her dad. So just don't make it another cop with a daughter. Make it an
accountant with a son or something. It's confusing. But you at least get to see a sort of proper
depiction of the origin of Freddy. It's good enough compared to the rest of the series. It's
excellent. It is a terrible show. My friend John Watt gave me copies of the episodes years ago.
So I think just out of the kindness of his heart, he just was like, you know, he's a fan and a friend
and he comes to a lot of my shows and he just brought me these ones and he said, you can't get
these anywhere. And I tried watching them and I've tried watching them as a kid. And as a kid,
we were like, these suck, man. And you just sit there and wait for the wraparounds with Freddy,
just so you could see Freddy. Because every episode wouldn't be, there would be no Freddy.
It would just be night. Like they did the thing by episode four, they'd already done three episodes
of he doesn't know when he's awake or he's asleep. He can't tell what's real. It was like that was
every episode. There was no other plot to it. It was a terrible show. The one good thing that came
out of it was, and they talk about this in the doc, was that that crew was also the Tales from
the Crypt crew. So when they did Tales from the Crypt, I think they said when they actually had
a little bit of money they could work with, they really knew how to stretch a budget and they made
it work. Yeah, apparently, according to England, yeah, that crew went over to Tales from the Crypt
and if they hadn't have been able to keep the budget down on Tales from the Crypt, that show
would have been canceled after season one or two because it was too expensive. So they just showed
them how to do it cheaper. But yeah, I definitely had no interest to keep watching it. Now,
yeah, sorry. The franchise was dead for not that long. In the case with all these things after,
okay, this is the last one and they interviewed Talalay at the time and she's like, absolutely
not. It'll never come back. They waited three years. But they did it right. They reached out
to Craven and before, I would have said New Nightmare is an awesome movie on a par with the
original, a great return to form, blah, blah, blah. Watching it now, I thought it kind of sucked
and I was surprised by that. The appeal of New Nightmare is that it does something that
most horror movies at the time, almost all horror movies at the time, were not doing.
And it's kind of a precursor for what would be done to perfection in Scream and the Scream movies
where it's very sort of the real world is blending with the dream world, but also
the real world where Heather Langenkamp is Heather Langenkamp and Freddie is Robert England.
All that stuff's very cool. I just found the movie dull and not even remotely scary.
This movie, when it was announced, I, again, Pinkstone and I, we couldn't have been more
excited. I mean, this to me was like when they said, we're going to make three more Star Wars
movies with Harrison Ford and Mark Hamill and Carrie Fisher. I was like, what? So when they
announced that they were going to do this, that Craven was part of it, that they were going to
sort of right the wrongs of the franchise, that they were going to make Freddie scary again,
I couldn't have been more excited. I saw it on opening night. I was elated. I was walking on
there. I loved the movie. I still like it a lot. It's not perfect, but Wes Craven's not perfect.
Wes Craven is a classic case of a director, much like Carpenter in many ways, much like John
Waters. The limitations always made him better, I felt like. Sure. Yeah. I mean, this is only
five years out of shocker. Shocker is an abortion. Yeah. Which he made is
an attempt to create a new franchise because of the money he didn't get from the Nightmare on
Elm Street franchise. But look, for what it is, New Nightmare was a gift. I was thrilled that
the franchise ended, pretty much ended here with Craven and Langenkapp and England returning
and just kind of putting a nice period on the entire thing. I love the depiction of Freddie
in it. I like that he's sort of this like trench coat gangster -y kind of look to him. It's very
slick. It looks very cool to me. I like that they make the glove part of his hand now and the blades
are just kind of coming out of his fingers. I liked it. I thought it was really, really cool.
And I actually thought the explanation worked of there's an evil that gets trapped in something
it likes and it manifests through that. I thought it was all cool. Was it scary? I wouldn't say
scary, but I did find Freddie to be very threatening or menacing. Yeah. In the doctor's
office when he drags the babysitter around and up the ceiling is kind of cool. But basically,
for me, this is an ingenious idea for where to take the franchise, not done particularly well.
But I love that it paved the groundwork for Scream and more kind of movies that could be
both genuinely scary and also sort of like a commentary on horror as a whole. There are cool
moments. I mean, Wes Craven writing himself five scenes in this movie was an insane choice. But
I mean, he can't really act. It's a cool moment though when Langenkamp realizes that he has been
writing in his laptop the conversation they're having. Yeah, it's great. And the moments like
that in the movie that are cool and exciting just make you wish that there had been more to them or
that they had been expanded on or done a little better. And really all it amounts to is this kind
of final hell scene with a ridiculous matte painting of hell that they cut to for like one
embarrassing shot. And then a lot of Freddie wrapping Langenkamp up with his big tongue.
And he gets a little fucking with the kid, you know, trying to eat him. And to me,
it was almost the least scary of the entire franchise. So I love what it's trying to do.
I wish it had been done better. But certainly, that late in the game, they needed a big shake
up that wasn't 3D. And that was about as good an idea as anyone could have had.
Right, I agree. Solid entry doesn't always hit the mark, but worthwhile,
which kills me that then they go to Freddie versus Jason, and it finally happens this big
monster clash that people have waited their entire lives for. And is it entertaining? Sure. Is it fun?
Yeah. But it just kills me that England just goes right back to the worst version of Freddie again.
Yeah, like, like when New Nightmare was kind of a bomb, you know, so I think New Line just
really tracked what the previous one had done and tried to either emulate it or go away from it.
England absolutely had power at that point to go, I'm not doing it if you make it campy.
100%. Yeah. And just like Harrison Ford said, we're not doing Indiana Jones five till the script
is right. Like there is no other Indiana. I'm Indiana Jones. So that's it. England could have
done that with this. And I wish that he would have because this one not only brings it so
Freddie versus Jason starts with a cool again, like sort of like little peek into the origins
of Freddie. You see him before he's burned up and it's creepy and it's skin crawly and it's dark.
And I was like, okay, they're going to get dark with this. This is pretty cool. And then by three
minutes into his voiceover, he's like, and then they forgot about me and that's a bitch. And you're
like, oh, come on, man. Like, what are we doing here? And it's just right back to the, you know,
he cuts a girl's nose off at one point and says, got your nose and you know, it's all that stupid
shit. There's some good sequences in the movie. The cornfield scene with Jason is great.
Jason's got some really solid kills in this, uh, Freddie, uh, cutting the nozzles off of the,
the, the, the tanks and shooting them out is kind of cool. Yeah. I mean, it's just,
it's just, it's can't be goofy as Freddie. Uh, you know, the director I forget is his Japanese
director Ronnie you. Yeah. He said he wanted to ride a Chucky and that kind of stuff. Yeah.
Which Brian Chucky is another one where it's like, what are you, what are you guys doing, man?
Right. Um, he's, he's into that campy, you know, he wanted a big universal sort of monster movie
exploited exploitative clash, you know, and it's like, well, that's what it is. And if you like
that sort of thing, then sure. Um, yeah, it's, it's Wolfman versus Frankenstein or whatever.
I mean, to me, especially seeing it in theaters and not having a real emotional tie to either
franchise, I thought it was pretty fun. Um, and the final sort of not letting either one win by
having him beat head Freddie, but Freddie also winks indicating he's still alive. I'm sort of
baffled with what a massive hit that was that we never got another Freddie versus Jason. That,
that makes no sense to me unless you know why there was no, I, I, I have no idea why there was
heavy talk that it was going to be Ash versus Freddie versus Jason. Yes. Or a pinhead. Yeah.
Pinhead was supposed to show up at the end of Freddie versus Jason. Right. And it didn't, uh,
they couldn't get the rights or some shit. I don't know. And then they said they were going
to potentially do Ash, you know, and then I think they did a comical book version of the Ash sequel,
I think. Um, well, that would have been even more comedic, I would imagine. But for me,
Freddie versus Jason was really fun trash. I had a good time trash. Don't get me wrong, but I think,
it was about as good a version of that fun jokiness, uh, as you can get certainly more
on the right track as opposed to like Freddie's death. Sure. Which brings us finally. Yes. To
the Nightmare in Elm Street remake from 2010, I believe it came out.
Freddie versus Jason versus Ash was the comic, uh, Mike is telling us, oh, and they had the fake,
uh, the fake Jay from Jay and Silent Bob, the fake Jason Muse. I remember as well,
the stoner guy, they didn't get Muse. Oh, they wanted Muse for that. Well, if they didn't,
they just completely ripped him off, but I'm sure they offered it to him. I'll tell you one,
one cool thing that the movie does do. They do very nice references to the, to the franchise.
Yeah. And two of the things I really did like were when the friend breaks the other friend out of the
asylum. It is the asylum from Nightmare three. Right. And the medicine the kids are on is the
pill, the dream suppressant pill from Nightmare three, which is what they use that in Freddie
versus Jason as the device to why Freddie has lost power because they, they suppress their dreams.
Nobody dreams about them anymore. So I thought like, you know, little things like that are very
cool. Um, could have been a much better film. I think so, but it had its moments. That girl that
was in it, you know, was on her way to, to stardom and became quite a mess. She dated Edward Furlong
and Monica Kena. Yeah. Oh my gosh. You can see some, some tabloid shots of them. You know,
they look like they've lived quite hard. Yeah. Uh, anyway, well, you know, if you're, if you're a
parent and your daughter brings so many fur along, you might as well just stick your head in the
oven. Well, I think she got fur along when he was still like fur long. And then like he went,
it was a Bobby Brown Whitney situation. He started going down and that was it, you know.
Right. Uh, anyway, uh, the remake, you know, uh, I was very excited for this because as you all
can tell, I'm a huge fan of the franchise. I thought Jackie Earl Haley was an exciting choice
to take the, take the reins over. Uh, I liked that it was going to be based, uh, you know,
on the first film with a lot of nods to the franchise. Uh, I liked early on that I was
hearing the director saying our Freddie is not funny. He's not a nice guy. He's not likable.
This is a bad person. I was all in for this thing. Uh, when people saw it and started saying it
sucked, uh, and I'd say, no, I liked it. And people would say, how could you like that?
My response was always the same. Did you see four, five, six and Freddie versus Jason?
This to me was a gift. It was a gift to get a scary Freddie again. It was a gift to get
a menacing Freddie again. It's not a fantastic movie. It's not a bad movie. It's a little boring.
It's a little flat. Um, it's, it's the twists and turns aren't riveting enough to keep you
totally invested mentally, but it's a scary Freddie again. And I was happy to get that.
Did I like the look of Freddie? Not entirely. Uh, they did say that they turned, they toned down
the look of him quite a bit. They said they looked at actual burn victims. They wanted to make him
look like a real burn victim. And they said that the pictures were so disturbing, right? They had
toned it down because they didn't want you to look away from the screen when you saw him. Um,
but you know, Jackie O 'Reilly, obviously a very, very capable actor. Uh,
he, during his, uh, pedophile Renaissance, he played pedophiles for a few years. Yeah. Uh,
you know, uh, but it just doesn't, it doesn't have the weight of the first film at all. It,
you don't see the crafting of the glove. They kind of focus on parts of the backstory that
you don't really care about. Um, but again, you, you, you throw it next to five, six, uh,
and Freddie versus Jason. Uh, I'm, I'm a happy guy with this movie. Uh, yeah. It's from Samuel
Bayer who never directed another movie. He did the smells like teen spirit music video and a bunch
of other very famous videos. Um, he had to be convinced to do this. Yeah. He kept saying,
Michael Bay sent him an email, like almost begging him and he's like, all right, fine. I'll do it.
Yeah. I think, you know, the, the visually and the way it's shot is probably the,
the biggest thing to recommend, but I actually rewatched it this week. I saw it in theaters,
didn't like it. And in rewatching it this week, I definitely agree with all your criticisms,
but I would take them all much further. I think it is insanely boring. It does absolutely nothing
new with the characters of the franchise, aside from leaning a little in a little more to the
mullah station, which is not really something I needed or wanted. I think Jackie O 'Haley is
horrible. I think the makeup is horrible. I love Jackie O 'Haley, but I think his performance is
dead in the water. Uh, I don't think it's scary or funny or anything. I don't think it's interesting
or good. I think Mara plays the, the Langen camp role and I like Rudy Mara. She's nothing in this
Kyle Gullner as an actor. She's very, uh, she's very flat throughout this entire movie. Uh,
I think everybody's flat throughout, um, to me. And I think this will be sacrilege to you, but
this is, this is my least favorite of the whole shebang. I think it is, I think it is, uh, it
just doesn't have a pulse. So like six is bad, very bad, but in this sort of, I can't believe what I'm
watching way that keeps you watching minute to minute. I couldn't even keep my eyes on this
remake. I thought it was so dull and such a missed opportunity. And especially if you're going to
come back after all this time and remake it to do nothing new, nothing interesting, nothing fun,
nothing exciting, no good scares. This is all jump scares. The ones that are there and not very
good jump scares. Uh, to me, it, this was a D minus. I thought it absolutely sucked and is my
favorite of the whole thing. You know what? You convinced me. You convinced me. You're right.
At least five, six and, uh, eight are, uh, fun in a way that you go, this is absurd, but like,
you know, you're still kind of laughing and you're just like, this sucks, but whatever,
I'm going to just see where this goes. You are right. I rewatched the remake this week too.
Uh, I did find it very, very hard to stay invested in. Uh, it is very boring. I did
notice that there were tons of jump scares. Uh, it's not surprising to me that you say the guy
didn't want to direct it. It seems like a movie that was directed by a guy who didn't want to do
it. And the other ones with all their massive flaws were clearly done by people who were pumped
and excited and wanted to try new things. Were they successful? Absolutely not. But there's more of
a spirit of like, we're trying, we're having fun. We're, we're, we want it to entertain you. They
say like, you know, the new star wars movies to them were, were, were they just, they, they were
indifferent. They didn't care. They said it was dead. And they said, despite the fact that they
felt Lucas misfired with the prequels, at least there was, there was the heart of a man trying
something there. Uh, so I could, I, you know, I don't agree with that criticism of star wars,
but I can, I can, uh, I can agree with you. I, I, I hear you. It is a very boring. Look, it's
something I've said many times on the show. It's music director shit or music video director shit.
It's visually stunning. The editing is great. You know, it's very, very well put together,
but there's no life to it, you know? And that's how I feel about a lot of these movies we review,
where it's like, just go direct music videos, man. You want to make music videos. You don't want to,
you're not tapping into characters. You're not bringing emotion out of people. You're not raising
my stakes. Even Clancy Brown in this is, is passable, you know, even, even Clancy Brown and
even, uh, by her name escapes me at the moment, but the mom for Friday night lights, who was an
amazing actress. Uh, I mean, they're just, she's there, they're, they're given nothing to do.
She's given even less than Clancy Brown is to do. Yeah. Uh, Connie Britton. Yeah. Thank you, Mike.
And from the writer of, uh, you know, Wesley Strick wrote Cape Fear for God's sake. He's
written some bad movies too, but I mean, Cape Fear is my favorite thriller whole time, really,
that and misery. So I don't know what happened here. I wish that the documentary extended to
this because if anything ever seemed like just something went wrong, I'd love to hear what it
was, but man, it did not work for me at all. I would have liked to, I think if they had
England in it, it could have worked. I don't think Jackie's bad. It's just, it's, it's very,
it's the performance does shave close to his Rorschach character in Watchmen. And I think that
that's sort of a thing that's hard to do. The beauty of England is, and as mad as I get at him
for leaning into the humor and whatever, the beauty of England is, is you can't see anybody else
when you see him as Freddie. That's it. That's what he does. You know, when you see Mark Hamill
as Luke Skywalker, you go, this man was now he'd done tremendous other things in voice work,
and he's a, he's one of the best jokers of all time on the cartoon. But you look at him in that
role, you go, this man was put here to be Luke Skywalker. This was his job. And with Jackie or
O 'Haley, you couldn't say that because he was a guy we already knew. We saw him play characters
similar to this in two other movies, taking aspects from both of those movies and children.
Watchmen.
Yeah. And then you kind of go, well, it's still in the Watchmen voice. And he's kind of got the
Watchmen attitude, but he's also molesters. Yeah. It's like little children. It's hard to sort of
separate that stuff. So it's weird. The choices are weird. I feel like the director didn't know
how to direct actors. There are line deliveries where I go, there's, I don't understand what your,
there should have been a different emotional push behind that line. Like I don't.
Agreed. And then we don't need to go into it, but if you have Shudder,
I would say easily the best horror documentary I've ever seen is Never Sleep Again. And so much
more fascinating and honest than like Crystal Lake Memories, which is okay, the Friday the 13th one.
But I love a movie documentary. I could watch it if it was 20 hours long, but I particularly love
when people are honest. If it's the documentary on a DVD where everybody's like, you know, we all
just knew we had a great cast and you know, I love when people are open and honest and admit when
they've made mistakes and admit what didn't work and what sucked. And the best example of that is
Never Sleep Again. It's fantastic. And it's on Shudder. Is HBO Max streaming all the?
HBO Max is streaming all the Freddy movies, including the remake. So you can watch this
all streaming very easily, but Never Sleep Again, if you've never seen it, especially watching it
right after the franchise, as I just did is such a treat. The only one that I think might give it
a run for its money is this In Search of Darkness, which is this four hour eighties horror documentary.
I had tickets at the Egyptian here in LA. I was so pumped and my dad came to visit and I was
devastated because the only way to get it was on Kickstarter. So my plan this week was to
offer a hundred dollars to anyone who would get me a copy of it because I missed the window.
And what do I see in my inbox this morning? But that documentary is coming to Shudder on July
30th. So I'm pumped about In Search of Darkness. We'll see how it stacks up. But as for right now,
if you're a horror fan, if you're a Freddy fan, you got to watch that documentary. It's awesome.
All right, gang, that is a massive episode covering a massive franchise.
Nightmare on Elm Street, our favorite and your favorite, who knows, but we covered it.
Jodorosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter, Jodorosa Comedian on Facebook and TikTok.
Without a Country, the news podcast with Corinne Fisher and myself on Gas Digital. Go over,
put in that code WAC for your free 30 day trial. Thank you for joining us. Thank you for subscribing.
Thank you for all your support on Patreon, especially through these dark times we are
living in. We love you all. We do indeed. I'm the Patrick Walsh of Twitter and Instagram.
I do monthly hour long run throughs of the movies I've been watching over quarantine,
which is a lot of movies. Pat's Solo Movie Corner. Thank you all very much.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.