Welcome to We'll See You in Hell. This is the podcast you turn to for all information
you need ever concerning a fantasy film, a sci -fi film, a horror film, maybe a drama,
maybe a comedy, perhaps some action where you're all movie whores.
Pre -code nudies, you know, pre the Hayes production code when they'd have like a lady frolicking
in a lake in black and white with sepia tone. We cover those sometimes.
That was nice. I cover myself when I watch those. Yes.
To hide the. You get what I mean.
Yeah, I went to. We're still in New York, folks.
And thanks for a fantastic couple of shows the other night.
Very fun live shows. Very fun.
Thanks to our special guest, David Krumholz, who upped the tension in the room to a thrilling degree.
Everybody was like, what was going on up there?
I was like, just good radio, baby.
But now it was awesome of him to come in.
Everybody got a big kick out of seeing him, I know.
And yeah, I'm still in New York. Went to the Museum of Modern Art today.
So a lot of tasteful nudes there as well.
There is some shit there. Like, you know how whenever they're doing it,
like the movie Velvet buzzsaw with Gyllenhaal, absolute piece of shit.
So it was a Netflix. Yeah, I remember that.
From the guy who did Nightcrawler, which was awesome with Gyllenhaal.
But it just didn't work.
It was a satire of the art world mixed with a horror movie, and it didn't work.
But whenever they do it, there's always the bit like Art School Confidential,
which is a good satire of the art world.
But it'll be like just like a pencil sitting on a chair.
And they're like, like everyone's gasping about how amazing it is.
You know, right, right.
MoMA, you know, like we go in and see like Picasso's shit,
like the wall length murals of Picasso did.
You're like, no, this is fucking hard. I get it.
But they do have shit, especially in the modern art world,
where like there was something today that was like a piece of plastic
and it's fully on display and like don't.
They had to put don't touch signs all around it because you'd think,
oh, who left this trash here?
It's not art, you know.
But then again, that's the old age old discussion.
What makes art art?
There was some great stuff.
They have, you know, the other Andy Warhol soup cans and stuff.
A lot of people said that's not art.
I think that shit's kind of cool.
It certainly makes a statement of some kind.
You know, I do think
I think initially that stuff was that pop art thing was pretty interesting.
I think it then got away from itself right where I was just like,
you know, tea, you know, like some teenage kid splicing together
magazine pick looks like a ransom note.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, putting it on a wall and people saying it's genius.
But some of the Warhol stuff is pretty is pretty cool.
And some of it's a little masturbatory.
I mean, but that's where you get in a modern art museum
from any modern artist.
There's a lot of interesting stuff and then a lot of stuff for you.
I don't know.
But it's kind of like going to a TV museum and you're going,
you know, some people are complaining that Three's Company is in there.
Sure. You know, whatever.
Exactly right. That's a good comparison.
Yeah. But then that's not a knock at three.
I love Three's Company.
Right. I went to the which I would recommend to anyone
listening in the New York area or if you're visiting
Museum of the Moving Image in the Story of Queens
or not, not quite a story, but out in Queens.
And it was my favorite place when I lived here.
I used to see double features there all the time.
They would do like every film of a director.
So if you get a director you love, it's like great double features all the time.
They got a cool 2001 exhibit.
They have a permanent Jim Henson exhibit that is just fucking awesome.
We're going to be talking about the Dark Crystal in an upcoming episode as well.
But they had a lot of shit from Dark Crystal,
surprisingly little stuff from Labyrinth, which I prefer.
And then they had a lot of Muppet show Muppet movies.
That's cool.
But it's great.
My favorite exhibit they ever had there was all of the suits worn by
Pacino, I'm sorry, Pesci, De Niro and Sharon Stone in Casino.
It was a full wing of like the most expensive 70s clothes you've ever seen.
That's cool.
It was great.
Check them out.
Especially if you live here, check out what exhibits they have coming up.
Why have I never gone there?
I don't do any of this stuff.
You're in the cultural center of America.
I do none of it.
You know, I take this city like a character from an old
Bogosian play or whatever.
You know, I'm just kind of wandering the streets, smoking, staggering around,
drinking coffee, you know, trying to make sense of it all.
You know, I got to get out there a little more
like a Woody Allen character and, you know, delve in, you know?
Well, speaking of, you know, there's the famous line in Annie Hall
where he goes, the only cultural advantage L .A. has over New York
is you can make a right turn on a red light.
And is that true?
Can you not make a right on a red here in New York City?
You can't know.
Interesting.
Yeah. So that's that was a funny joke.
But it's also a joke.
Not a great one.
But it's also a joke only for people from New York and L .A.
Correct.
It's not you know what I mean?
Like there's like there's so many people.
That's that I believe is from Annie Hall, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. And if you just said that, sorry, I didn't hear it.
But it's all right.
You know, you may have to listen in all the time.
I know.
The I sense it.
But I mean, Annie Hall, arguably the man's biggest film.
Yeah.
It was seen by far more people than just folks in New York.
And well, maybe it wasn't.
Maybe that was sort of the like the parasite of 1977 or whatever,
where, you know, if there weren't DVDs and stuff,
a lot of people wouldn't have seen Paris or, you know,
I think in those days, like my parents in Missouri going to see Annie Hall
work the same way as us going to see Parasite in that it's a foreign culture to them.
And I think that a lot of them liked New York.
Because Woody Allen's doing these things that to like to him,
they're not meant as jokes.
Like I went and saw my analyst and, you know, whatever it is to people in Missouri.
They think he's doing a satire, but it's just his life and his rich old white problems.
Right.
Look, I love a lot of the man's stuff, but, you know,
I had to kind of stop seeing them in theaters when they're not going to play anymore.
But Midnight in Paris, I went and saw that at the Los Feliz Theater
and the performative laughter at like the jokes about, you know,
an inside joke about Ernest Hemingway or whatever, liking to drink,
as if only smart people would know that you get to get people in the theater who are like,
it's like, shut the.
Yeah, it's a little too, but it's not laugh out loud.
Funny.
It's a little much.
Would always end with me in the lobby after screaming, I'm smart, too,
and everybody and then fake laughing at them.
Yeah, I would.
I would go out to the lobby and drink and then wait and say,
you think you're better than me, right?
As they came out, take swings at them and fall into a standee or something.
Yeah.
You fall into the latest Transformers cardboard cut out and they go,
that's the kind of movie that's meant for you.
You fucking drug.
I once saw my buddy Ian and I had no plans on Christmas Day.
It was the one time I stayed in L .A. at Christmas.
We were real down in the dumps.
And we went out to the Magic Johnson 16 Theater in Crenshaw in L .A.,
where they have 10 reserved spots for police cars.
But it's the most fun place to see a movie, as you can imagine.
I mean, the stereotype embraced in the beginning of scary movie, too,
where people like to talk a lot at the theaters in those communities.
Which kind of people?
But I don't see it as a negative stereotype.
I mean, if you're watching a horror movie or a comedy or especially a bad movie,
there's no more fun place to be.
And, you know, it was a very rowdy screening.
I used to go down there when I used to review movies.
So like Saw 5, I'd go down and they'd be like, you stupid bitch.
Yeah, hilarious.
But my buddy Ian and I are out getting popcorn or whatever.
And there was this mother daughter who got in a fistfight
and were throwing each other into the dream girl standee by their weaves,
just like throwing each other around.
And it was everyone's kind of standing around watching and enjoying it.
You know, two women, even the ushers, just watching it.
But then through their screaming at each other,
we realized that they were mother and daughter.
And when the daughter started to scream at her mom,
she started crying because she was just so ashamed.
She was fistfighting her mom in public.
And then the thing got so bleak, we couldn't keep watching.
That's rough stuff.
Anyway, I talked to Ian today.
By the way, on the phone, Pat, you called him up?
Well, he lives in L .A.
I didn't know you guys were that close.
We once in a while we poaching my friends.
We do text and talk.
You know, I'm the reason he's in comedy.
He's told me that he's told you that.
Yes, no, but we I called him in a little while back
and then he called me back today and he goes, hey, man,
you know, just just hitting you back, whatever.
So at the end of the call, I said, hey, man, well, it's good talking to you.
Good catching up. Hope to see you soon.
Right. And he goes, yeah, you know, I just I just want to call you back.
You know, you had called me, so I just want to call you.
And I go, yeah, and I called you a month ago.
And he goes, all right. Yeah, it took me a little while.
And I go, you know, Ian, these are the types of relationships.
It was so hard for me to tear myself from when I left L .A.
Sure. Sure. The intimacy of a month long. Right. Call back.
Ah, boy. So that that that's that that reiterated by my move.
Ian is from New York.
So there's kind of putting a little hole in your theory.
No, no, no. I have a theory.
People that like L .A. are either from L .A.
or were meant to be there eventually.
That could be right. I mean, I'll say when I was back
the first couple of days, I was like, yep, you know, just whatever I feel
whenever I come back after a few years. So glad I left.
So glad I don't live here now.
I'm still glad I don't live here, but I do love to visit.
And the truth is, I love the theater.
Yeah, I love, you know, I like a lavish musical.
I like seeing the hot shows.
Yeah, it's great. All that stuff's great.
Yeah. I mean, look, this city.
But when it when it was the last time you went to a Broadway show,
was it Glengarry?
I see Glengarry with Tambor and Leo Schreiber here.
I saw it was great.
No, I saw the following one twice with Pacino and Pacino did it here.
Pacino did it. He played Levine, Pacino, Cannavale.
I should have come back.
What's his face? The guy that plays.
Oh, man, what's his name?
He's the guy from office space.
It's like Mike, my Gary Cole, not Gary Cole, the other guy.
I've heard of my money. There's no one better. Michael Bolton.
Oh, John C. McGinley.
Yes. John C. McGinley played Moss from Scrubs.
Yes. Yes. I forgot he was on that.
And then the guy that played Aaron now is also somebody you would 110 percent know.
Yeah. I'm just blanking on his name.
How was Pacino as Levine?
Great. Great.
It seems like not his wheelhouse.
Well, I mean, this was a much older Pacino, so it made it made a lot of sense.
You know, like any played it very.
Pacino is good at playing a very desperate beaten man.
Yeah, he's also good at playing like a hothead, whatever.
So this was not hothead Pacino. This was very much, you know,
but except for the scene where he dresses him down.
Yeah. Finally, like the big thing at the end
where Levine dresses my ass for the record.
Yeah, that was like full on Pacino. Yeah.
But it was great. I saw that twice.
But that was probably the record and shit.
You know, I could see coming twice a year and seeing some shows recording.
We can keep this thing alive, people.
Yeah. And I'm going to have to come to L .A. at least twice a year.
Kicking and screaming. But I'll be there.
You're in the sequel to kicking. It's Will Ferrell's kick.
Yes. Play his son.
Now, is my wing prepared at your house? Have you?
Heather's always like, you tell Joe he can stay here.
And I'm like, we'll just wait and see if I feel like.
Listen, I don't say this to start any sort of quarrel.
I feel like you don't want me to stay with you.
Oh, that's not true at all. It's never come up.
But you would like me to stay. We have a room.
Now, I don't mean because of me personally.
I just mean you seem like the kind of guy to me that's like,
we'll see if there's a hotel.
I am the kind of guy who has a little anxiety around a houseguest,
but it's if they're staying a long time or if they're family friends.
I don't mind at all.
I come in, babe, you don't even know I'm there.
That's how I like. Yeah.
No, it'll be fun. Three of us hanging out.
I would be a blast. Yeah.
I've grown to I've always liked Heather,
but I've grown to really like her quite a bit.
I mean, me too. Yeah.
Yes. I've always been very fond of her.
You know, I've always thought she was very lovely and fun and everything.
But like, I feel like these last few hangs, I've really gotten to know her a bit.
She's really asked me a lot about myself with this transition.
And I've asked her nothing about herself because you should.
That's the part of L .A. I held on to her.
Right. No, she's the best.
Yeah, she's great.
You know, with her her being around helps me.
A, everyone just asks where she is when I show up,
especially other women and wives and so forth.
But it just helps me when you engage with the two of us,
you walk away feeling like we've asked you a lot about yourself and your life
and your career and everything, because 100 percent of Heather, you engage with me.
You know, I don't even who knows what I'm talking about half the time.
Shoot, you know, you know, she helps me appear more compassionate.
Sure, sure. Yes.
Yeah, it's a it's a tough thing.
It's a tough thing asking other people.
I really tried it.
I really tried to do it and be present.
Yeah, it's very hard.
I don't I'm fine with that.
I always start with a how's your life?
And I, you know, I try to press into some.
I bet I better and better all the time.
But with me, it's not a narcissism thing at all.
It's a I'm in my own head all times of the day.
I always ask.
I'm always, you know, I attend to it.
Yeah.
But I do notice I have a bad habit of like if somebody says to me first,
how are you doing?
I will dump all my shit out.
Sure.
And then after seven minutes go like, huh, gee, I'm sorry.
I'm real.
How are you doing?
And I'm like, I don't like that I do that.
You know, when I really because my dad has that issue.
But when I really noticed that I was having a problem with it
was around the time I was doing the last show.
And I'd go to meet you guys for my last tell of it.
Cool kids.
OK, yeah.
They want to name it.
But when I meet you guys at a million times,
when I meet you guys out at the bar, you'd be like, how are you doing?
And I'd be like, you know, just vomit all over the floor for 10 minutes.
I was at an event with you once.
It was somebody's event.
It was somebody's birthday or something.
And yeah, yeah, it was a ball.
It was.
Yeah, no, I and I'm not kidding.
We walked into the book.
We rode in an Uber together.
Yeah.
Talked to me about everything going on the entire Uber ride.
Got to the bar.
We walked into the bar.
You were talking to me about it.
I went got a drink full lap.
Came back around a good thirty five minutes later.
Came up behind you and heard you still kind of talking about it.
Yeah, I was unable to.
And that's why now I won't talk about it.
I have to shut down any conversation.
The one of the stars of cool kids, let's leave it at that,
who gave me the most trouble, is appearing on Broadway.
And I was walking into the Harry Potter show and saw his face above me.
And I immediately had to take my coat, my scarf off.
I was like, I need a minute.
I needed to be away for a minute and just sit and kind of breathe deeply.
Shit.
How was the Harry Potter show?
Now, guys, on the live show, which might come out before this,
Pat talked about how he was going to see the Harry Potter show.
It was three hours, then a dinner intermission, then another three hours.
How was it?
The Harry Potter show was very cool.
My issue was, and it's my issue with at least half of Broadway,
is it had Broadway acting.
So the kids are Harry Potter's son, whose name is Albus Severus.
Doesn't name him Dumbledore.
Albus Dumbledore.
Oh, Albus was Dumbledore's first name.
And Severus was Snape's first name.
So it's Albus Severus.
Okay, all right.
There we go.
But the guy who played Harry Potter looked like him and was fine.
The kid who played him was doing the whole like,
We're going back to Hogwarts.
You know, and he's like 16 or something.
But it's like the second he spoke, I was like, I can't do this for five hours.
So there's flashbacks with the young kids in it.
There are flashbacks throughout.
But the bulk of the story is Harry Potter as a 40 year old man.
Right.
And he's married to Ginny Weasley, Ron's sister.
Ron is in it.
And Ron's kind of like a fun stoner.
And that's cool without actually smoking weed.
But you get the vibe.
Hermione is in it.
And now, and Joe, I'm interested to hear what you have to say about this.
But Hermione is black.
Okay.
I don't listen.
I will explain my whole take on all that.
Sure.
But I'll wait till you finish.
Well, it took me a minute.
And I guess what's cool about it is that this little kid next to me was cracking me up
because the play is very boring in parts, as you can imagine.
And when you're six, who knows, you know, it's a six hour play.
So this kid sit next to me and like 10 minutes into like a real exposition heavy
part at the beginning, this kid leans back in his chair next to me and goes,
which I thought was hilarious because I was doing the same thing in my mind.
But yeah, Hermione is black and married to Ron.
And that's not explained.
So a lot of the kids are like, how is that Hermione?
Which is cool.
It opens up a discussion.
Sure.
But then there's a young their kid.
So there's a young Hermione.
There is Ron's kid.
But the people you're focusing on the most are Harry's son, Albus,
who appears to be on the spectrum or something.
Maybe the actor was.
I don't know.
And then the other kid who also appeared to be on the spectrum who was Malfoy's son.
Okay.
But he's son bad.
He's not evil and hates the fact that Malfoy is his dad because everyone thinks that he's bad.
And people also suspect that Malfoy couldn't perform sexually or was impotent, let's say.
And that Voldemort, which they pronounced Voldemort throughout the play with no T,
Voldemort fathered this kid with Malfoy's mom.
That's what the rumor is.
So everybody's like, this kid's nice.
But what if he's Voldemort's son?
That's a good little plot.
J .K. Rowling did the whole story for it.
Haggard in it or Haggard?
Haggard's in it.
Also black.
Okay.
And Haggard's barely in it.
They had a guy who played Snape and Voldemort who was really good.
But wait, Voldemort comes back?
Yep.
All right.
Don't tell me.
I'm not actually.
I don't care.
But when the Snape guy starts talking and he's not doing Rickman, it's exactly like
when the guy didn't do Fred Gwyn in Pet Sematary.
You're like, you have to do it.
Does Voldemort have the same makeup as in the movie?
Very similar.
And he talks the same.
Okay.
But basically what it is, folks, is it's a whole lot of story.
It should have been a three hour play with two intermissions or something.
The six hours is is imposing to say the least.
But the special effects and the magic are the coolest I've probably ever seen in a stage
production.
They do a lot of like just on stage stuff that you can't figure out how it was done.
We had a lot of fun.
There's a lot of cool like, you know, lighting effects and all kinds of stuff like that.
But the kids acting drove me nuts.
Both kids.
So, okay.
So to answer your question, and by the way, for anybody tensing up at home, I'm not mad
about I was saying, Joe, you're going to hate this.
I was wondering what your take my take on it is.
But I do have thoughts on it.
My take is this.
Number one, I don't have a problem with it.
Right.
But then that means I don't have a problem with it from all sides.
Sure.
So I get annoyed at the people that take issue with people taking issue with it.
Unless it's a white character.
And then they go, oh, just deal with it.
It's like, no, no, no, no, no.
If we're going to protect the racial integrity of all these other characters, that goes.
What's right is right.
Right.
So either we do it or we don't do it.
So I'm fine with doing it.
Yeah.
I just think we should do it in all shapes and forms.
The one thing that does confuse me when they do it sometimes is in a play like this, where
they're clearly basing major parts of it visually on the movies.
Yes, for sure.
Then it's like, well, now this is just confusing.
If you're going to do it, just do it.
And do it for kids.
So the massive pro is that a kid goes, well, mommy, I thought Hermione is white.
And she goes, well, what does it matter?
Oh, I guess it doesn't.
That's great.
And colorblind casting is what it's called.
And they're trying to do it more and more.
What I imagine happened is they're putting this thing together.
It's called Harry Potter and the Cursed Child or Cursed Child.
And they were probably like, it's the same thing I just thought when I watched these movies.
There's like two non -speaking black kids that are wizards.
Right.
So they probably thought, boy, are we going to get away with this in this day and age
and having this all white British cast, whatever.
What if we mix it up?
And you don't think about it after five seconds.
But you also definitely at the beginning are like, that's not Hermione.
Same as if they did the Idris Elba as James Bond.
I just I just I'm all for it.
But it's going to take a lot, especially your old school James Bond fans
who are going to take a minute and go, OK, all right, let me work with this.
Never understand why it's like make make like if you're trying to make this
look like the grownup versions of the kids from the movies,
just make them then make other characters in it.
Make Harry have an adopted black son.
I don't fucking know for sure.
There's a million ways to do it.
But anyway, so but obviously I don't have a problem with it.
The only time I take issue with it is when Hollywood and they do this often,
do it in the most racist fuck you way possible.
And I have a bit about this in my act right now.
When they remade a Christmas Carol for FX, they gave Bob Cratchit a black wife.
And the movie takes place in 1876.
And the joke is I go and I'm sitting there watching like,
is anybody going to mention?
Yeah, people would have been talking about this in 1976.
And like this presentation of like, what are you a racist?
What's wrong?
It's like, no, I remember history.
This is this is now distracting.
So if you want to do this, right, because here's what they won't do.
And this is the greater point.
God forbid you just do a black Christmas Carol.
Right.
You fucking racists.
They did a Mickey Mouse Christmas.
Yeah, but they won't do that.
They won't do that.
Instead, they'll change one character's ethnicity.
And that's always the way they do it, by the way.
They did it on it with A Christmas Story, the NBC musical version.
They made Maya Root off the wife.
It's like, guys, this takes place in the 40s.
Right.
But it's always for some reason, it's the wife.
And it's always it always has to be some.
We're going to throw in an interracial marriage here in a time period
where of history where this would be an issue.
It'd be an interesting thing to deal with if you're going to bring it up.
Bring it up.
It's like when an interracial couple would walk into all in the family in the 70s,
there'd be comments made about it, you know?
Yeah.
And you get into the discussion and everything else.
If it's a modern day thing, of course, no one's going to comment on it
unless you're doing like, you know, Spike Lee's movie Jungle Fever,
where that's the plot of the movie or something.
But so that's the only time I'm kind of like it because it feels flippant to me.
It feels very like, you know, well, will you deal with the confusion here?
No, I don't need to do do it.
Do this properly.
Making it all black or for Christ sakes, make Bob Cratchit black
and he can have a black wife.
You don't want to put two black people in there.
There's certainly no reason that Bob Cratchit couldn't have been a black guy.
And talk about a commentary on this guy getting treated horribly by a rich white man.
Yeah, it's like, come on.
Sure.
How was that Christmas Carol Who Fucks?
Did you watch the whole thing?
It completely sucked.
It's just like when you read the book Wicked,
they don't do this in the play.
But when you read the book Wicked, like suddenly there's like fuck scenes
and they're cursing and stuff.
You're like, I don't want my Wizard of Oz stanky.
I'm sorry.
I don't like.
So I felt like when the Muppets came back to TV, I was like, fuck this.
The Muppets always had some real edge to them,
but it was never like Kermit walking out and being like, I can't get my.
By the way, you ready for this?
Yeah.
Cratchit's black wife, she's like into like voodoo and shit.
Oh, and that's like why the ghosts come because she like sends them.
She like conjures up some it's not great.
That's not great, folks.
I think we should head over to Pat's movie corner.
Yeah, I have a really fast news psycho.
Sure.
Really fast.
I implore you people.
I implore you.
I only know of this because I Googled the man's name and found several
articles that were written about how funny his Instagram was.
But I Googled Craig Kilburn last night to see what he's up to.
I was always a huge Craig Kilburn fan.
He's hilarious.
That's smug for me.
I liked him in old school.
Found multiple articles like Craig Kilburn happily left show business.
He spends his days restoring his home with his longtime living girlfriend
and has the funniest Instagram of all time.
And I went and started watching videos and I.
I implore all of you to follow.
He only has twenty five thousand followers.
What does he do?
Complete arrogance, complete, but like absurd, lots of posts
with him in different expensive scarves.
OK, he talks about how expensive the scarf is.
One of them is him.
It's like a slow montage of him napping with smiles on his face.
And it's like the three ingredients to old Craigers, beautiful maps.
And then one of them, it's it just says charcuterie board.
They're ridiculous.
One, he's bragging about his shoe collection because he goes,
when I hosted late night television, I received an obscene amount of free footwear.
Right.
And he goes, I'd like to showcase today.
And he pulls out these shoes from like, you know, sacks for some shit.
And and he goes, he goes, I've never worn them, but I will wear them on Saturday.
To the beach cabana.
And he goes, I know you're thinking, Craig, they don't look very beachy.
And then pushes into the camera and he goes, I'll tell you this.
I have never and I mean never had white wine in sneakers.
OK, so he's in touch with his fans.
They're really funny.
That sounds funny.
I'll check it out.
Talks about going to one last one.
They're going to Home Depot.
He goes, because I do like to rub elbows with the common man, the salt of the earth.
He goes, of course, later none of them realize
I will be making an entrance into a French restaurant for dinner
where those people will not be.
And he goes, and if you see me there, don't talk to me.
And then he goes, of course, people, I'm kidding.
If you see me there, come over, say hi, buy me a drink.
I think most people, you know, certainly anyone below my age
does not know Craig Kilburn.
And if they do, it's as the boyfriend in old school.
I honestly never watched him on television.
He was the original host of The Daily Show, but I never saw it.
And the original daily.
Look, The Daily Show is a great show through and through.
But the original Daily Show was it was a parody of a news show.
Yeah.
So all of the story, you know, when Stuart came in, it became,
you know, an almost like a worthy news source that happened to be funny.
Yeah.
Or it was a worthy news source.
That would be funny.
Kilburn's version of it was there was no worthy news in any of it, baby.
You know, like it was him just making fun of how seriously news shows take themselves.
Yeah.
There was a lot of absurdity.
He was moment of Zen was him like originally.
Right.
That's right.
He would do five questions with all the guests.
Every interview, he'd just be shitting on the celebrity the entire time.
All the field pieces were completely absurd.
It was like, you know, we found a man that that collects,
you know, pig dick skins or whatever.
It was always something crazy like that.
Right.
And it was fucking hilarious.
Apparently, Colbert was on there before Stuart.
It always makes it seem like Stuart discovered him.
But Colbert came in and I believe replaced Brian Unger, who plays the lawyer on It's
Always Sunny, who was the funniest correspondent on the show.
That's I don't know if he's a stand up.
He's a great comedic actor.
But Kilburn had a thing where he would every Thursday, he would go like,
you know, people, it's Thursday.
And when it's Thursday, I just want to dance, dance, dance.
And he would just get up and dance for 35 seconds on TV.
Appreciate that.
And he tried to do it on The Late Show.
And it just didn't.
It was funny, but it didn't translate as well.
That audience is way too broad.
I was when he I always said I was like, no, Stuart should have went to The Late Show
and Kilburn should have just stayed on.
But then Stuart did a whole new thing with The Daily Show and it really worked.
Folks, I saw a movie I've never seen.
And I had I had pride myself in having seen pretty much every comedy made in the 80s and 90s.
It's called Guess Who?
Based on the board game.
No, unfortunately not.
And how they not made that.
Guess Who came out in 2005.
I guess that explains why I miss it.
I would have been living here in New York and very busy.
Guess Who is a remake of Guess Who's Coming to Dinner.
Oh, it stars.
Bernie Mac and Ashton Kutcher.
The plot is Kutcher is the white boyfriend.
Zoe Saldana in an early early role brings him home to meet the parents.
Of course, it came right after Meet the Parents did not capture the same success.
But my thoughts are this.
That's a fantastic idea for a movie to update it.
Yeah, you're going to do the dad switch the races.
There could not be a better choice than Bernie Mac.
Yeah, that's perfection.
And they they missed the mark again and again and again and again.
Bernie Mac is the highlight of the movie.
He gets some laughs out of you just out of just some insane line deliveries
that you can tell were just like maybe him being bored on the day or whatever.
Does he get into the whole like, oh, yeah.
OK, good.
So he's got a lot of really funny moments.
Ashton Kutcher, I guess I haven't seen much of his film work or TV work, whatever.
This guy is the most mugging, shameful like he's Jimmy Fallon, you know,
like just desperate for your laughs.
And he's trying to do like Steve Martin physical comedy, but he's not gifted.
So, you know, that really doesn't work.
There's one incredible scene that kind of shows what the movie could have been.
And it probably got noted to death.
But he's like, yeah, you know, my grandma is really racist.
You know, she used to tell these kind of jokes or whatever.
And Bernie Mac goes, let's hear the joke.
He's like, no, no, no, it tells the joke.
I like the joke.
So Kutcher's hemming and hawing.
And then finally, he tells this black joke that his grandma used to tell.
And the whole table, including Bernie Mac's dad and all these people,
they're all laughing really hard.
They come around, they laugh the joke, they get it, they like it.
So he's like, you got another one?
So he tells another one and he keeps going with it.
And his daughter's like, stop, stop, stop.
And you're just waiting for him to do the one that the table all gasps that he goes too far.
That's a beautiful scene.
Very well written, very well acted.
It's like how you never know where the line is, you know, in this kind of situation.
And the whole rest of the movie is just lazy shit.
So I don't recommend it.
By the way, that's one of my favorite.
We talk a lot about our favorite comedy devices.
That one always gets me.
It's like the round robin of joke telling.
And then it gets to the guy that's like, I got one, I got one.
Two Puerto Ricans.
Jukebox cuts out.
I'm doing all TV this week.
I watched in its completion, Afterlife, the Ricky Gervais program.
I liked it.
I enjoyed it very much.
It starts.
I'm a big Ricky Gervais fan.
After his Golden Globes appearance and the shots he was taking during the monologue this year,
I kind of recharged my battery on him.
And I really, really wanted to see what he was up to lately, but also revisit some old stuff.
So I revisited old stuff.
And then I was like, I'm going to watch Afterlife front to back.
I originally had no real interest in it
because I was just kind of like, you know, I've seen Gervais do this.
He's the guy that hates everything.
He's going to be saying crazy shit you'd never say to people and whatever.
And then when it started, I was like, you know what?
This is much darker than I thought it was going to be.
It's not that outlandish at all.
There's a couple of outlandish moments and they use those to sell you on it in the trailer.
And I was I was pulled in.
I wanted to see where it was going.
I felt that the first half of the season was got pretty trite at times.
Yeah, with like these soliloquies about like nothing means anything
and people are worse than animals and whatever.
But that is sort of the setup for where the series eventually turns
the direction it turns and goes to.
And I was like, OK, I can deal with that overall.
Liked it.
And spoiler alert, I mean, I won't do the whole bit,
but he's got a friend who eats constantly, who he's always making fun of.
And there is a scene where a woman is selling pudding made out of her breast milk.
And it is a seven episode setup for this joke they do in that scene with the with his fat friend.
I was like almost crying laughing that it was so funny.
I'm not sure I remember the joke, but I like the show.
I'll just do the bit.
The guy's eating constantly in every episode.
Your race is like, oh, look at him.
Oh, look at the neck fat, you know, and all this shit.
Yeah, because Gervais is so fit.
Yeah.
Well, he does apologize to him eventually.
But they go to cover a news story for the paper.
They work for a woman who makes rice pudding out of her breast milk.
And she's like, God, it's the two of them.
And it's and she's like, God, try it.
It cuts to a single of Ricky Gervais.
And he goes, I can't.
I can't.
I don't know who would eat this.
I don't know.
And then off camera, you hear I do remember that.
Yes.
It's just one of the it was it was an amazing.
Yeah, it was just an amazing joke for that character.
I still like Gervais as well.
And I could not and still have not done Derek because I just would see him doing that character
and be like, nope, not not happening.
That's a bit schmaltzy.
But it does have there are characters in it that are make it worth watching for.
All right.
But this to me stayed on the good side of schmaltzy for the most part.
And it's weird that he goes that way because he's that's his whole persona is he's not
an emotional person.
But he does go schmaltzy.
I like the afterlife.
And I think the second season is about to start.
I saw come to daddy.
I heard this is great.
Now, my question is, is do you want to is this one we should save?
Fair enough.
I'll save it because it's an interesting thriller.
Horror is a pretty generous description.
But yes.
All right.
Or is it going to be too hard for me to see?
No, I'll hang on to it.
If we remember, great.
If not, you know, I'll tell you.
That's one on my list to see with color out of shape.
Yes.
OK.
Color out of space.
Then I will do the cook, the thief, his wife and her lover.
Wonderful film.
Yeah, I guess.
You know, when I was a kid, whenever my dad had run an R rated movie and leave,
I would fast forward it looking for nudity.
And I remember that one.
I started fast forwarding through it.
And there is plenty of nudity, a lot of it from Dame Helen Mirren,
who I sat next to at the film Uncut Jams.
But I'm watching this thing as a kid and just sensed that it was too adult for me.
I was like, no, like there was an evil coming off of the movie.
So I realized I had never actually watched it.
And I sat Criterion Channel, which is, I think, the best streaming service.
They had a bunch of Peter Greenaway movies who did The Pillow Book with Ewan McGregor
and a bunch of stuff I had never seen.
So Cook, the thief, his wife and a lover, his best known movie,
his best that I've seen by a million percent.
He tends to be a very boring director.
But yeah, it's it opens with Michael Gambon, who eventually plays Dumbledore.
Right.
When Richard Harris died.
But opens with him shoveling dog shit into a man's mouth.
It's rough stuff.
Yeah. And kind of gets darker from there.
It's a lot of people cheating.
There's cannibalism.
There's double crossing.
And if you've never seen it, it counts as horror.
It's a pretty rough fucking movie.
But also, I think great.
And then if you read about what every favorite movie that makes sense.
Yeah.
Or it's either him or the guy that did Mandy.
One of those two, they're like, that's the you know, my the best movie.
Ari Aster.
That makes sense.
Especially in like Ari Aster.
You can have a lot of fun reading what it all represents.
So reading what those four characters cook, the wife, love or represent online.
You get a lot of interesting theories and it's a dark, dark ride.
But I loved it.
Check it out.
I watched my good buddy, Craig Ferguson's docu series, Hobo Fabulous.
He did a standup tour called Hobo Fabulous, and I was assuming that he was building up
to a special that he was going to call that.
And instead, he did a docu series that showcased basically most of the material from whatever
this new hour was that he was touring with and then also got into the behind the scenes
of not just the road, but his take on comedy and touring, leaving Hollywood, and then
to live in Scotland again and whether or not ultimately he's ever going to do standup again.
And he none of it is down.
None of it is sad.
But he really talks a lot about like, you know, I don't know if I want to tour anymore.
I don't like leaving my family.
I've done this for a long time.
I had a great time.
I'm having fun on this tour, but the the leaving of my family for these long stretches
and like living on a bus and it just doesn't mean as much as it used to to me.
And I thought it was just as a comedian, especially, I really thought it was enjoyable.
My buddy Joe Bolter directed it, who used to co -host Craig's radio show with him
and worked on the Ferguson late night show.
Well, actually, Ferguson took over for Kilburn.
How about that?
It's just a nice watch.
It's one of those really nice, endearing things to watch.
And Craig's a really, really charismatic guy.
And he's funny and he's charming and he's a fun guy to watch.
So I enjoyed it.
All right. Check it out.
Didn't even know I was out there.
And it was more interesting than watching just a straight front to back 62 minute standup special.
Right.
You know, it was it broke it up and it put things more in context.
So I like that.
All right.
Uh, I saw villains, which is new to like, you know, streaming services and stuff.
It was probably got a brief theatrical run, but a buddy of mine produced it.
The same buddy that did Ingrid Goes West, which was maybe my favorite movie of that year.
This was not as good.
I don't think my buddy's a Patreon subscriber, so I'll speak freely.
You're still allowed to have an opinion.
I am.
Uh, it was interesting, I guess.
But it's Bill Skarsgard, who is in today's show.
Straight, uh, what's that?
Stranger things.
Castle Rock.
Maika Monroe, who's a very good young actress.
They are a young, you know, your standard young Bonnie and Clyde true romance.
I love you so much, baby.
And they're on like a little crime spree.
Their car breaks down.
And they go into a house looking for help.
They find a girl chained up in the basement.
The girl's parents are played by Kira Sedgwick and Jeffrey Donovan, who's the guy from Suits.
And then these people are even sicker than your Bonnie and Clyde young couple that are on the run.
That's a cool concept.
Yeah.
You know, and it's kind of stylishly done.
Weirdly, it keeps getting more and more kind of stylishly directed.
And there's like an end credits sequence that's very, uh, visual, you know, in a strange way.
Like that wasn't the tone throughout, but it becomes this very like visual cool movie.
I liked that.
They had some fun with the premise.
The characters, I wouldn't say it was their fault performance wise, but the, the quote
insane couple, uh, Sedgwick and Suits are, I don't know, the characters are drawn a little too
cartoonish for me.
So it took the suspense out, but it plays half the time as a dark comedy.
So that might've been intentional for me.
I wish it had decided.
I wish it had gone full horror or full comedy, but the way it was working at this point,
neither really was strong in my opinion, but it was an interesting premise.
Well -directed fun cast.
You wouldn't hate it if you, if you watch it on Netflix or something.
All right.
My final is just, I finished the complete first season of high fidelity.
I talked about the first few episodes briefly on a previous episode, finished out the season,
absolutely loved it.
Can't wait for season two to come out.
It was completely 100 % attached to the characters by the end of the season.
I just, I just thought it was great.
I thought it captured New York and the essence and spirit of New York so well.
I thought it was funny.
I thought it was, it was emotionally daring.
They, the, the characters are flawed.
They make some really bad decisions, but it, but you don't hate them for it.
You know, it's, it's, it's like watching real people, I guess is the best way to put it.
And somehow, you know, although it's a little cheeky at times,
they do pull off the addressing camera thing, which, you know,
at this point is a very nineties kind of a trope, right?
But, but, you know, Zoe Kravitz is really, really good, man.
Everybody in the show is.
I'm going to watch it on the plane.
I'm excited to see it.
I'm really excited for season two because everything, you know, the expect,
the expectations that I thought initially the show was going to kind of let me down on.
It didn't.
And it, and it really delivered.
And, oh, this is the best compliment I can give it.
And if I were a critic, I would say this.
I think this is finally the answer to Sex in the City
that everybody has sort of been waiting for, you know, Sex in the City in the first three
seasons or so really, really tackled dating and being single as you get older.
And the trials and tribulations of that and blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I think we've all kind of been waiting for another show that gets the grasp on that
and makes it feel the way it actually feels.
And this show does like it really gets in there.
And I thought it was great.
I'm going to watch any nudity.
You see Zoe Kravitz is tits a couple of times.
Really?
Like briefly, but like there's a scene in a bathtub where
she's like it's a comical scene kind of because she's her mom skypes her.
And she means to decline it.
But then her mom, she hits answer by accident.
Does Lisa Bonet play her mom?
No, no.
Her mom's played by a white lady, actually.
OK.
But so she's like shuffling around.
And at the end of that scene, she starts talking and you see her tits
and she covers them, but she clearly doesn't give a shit.
Yeah.
Well, that's Bonet passed it on.
Yeah, yeah.
And there are one or two shots in it where she's wearing sunglasses,
where she looks freakishly like Lenny Kravitz, but still like hot, like a hot woman.
Lenny Kravitz dated one of my fellow pages.
We know we were all like 22 or something and just very bizarre.
Like go out to a bar and sitting in your group of like 20 year olds, there's Lenny Kravitz.
But whatever.
The thing that's funny to me is, and I said to my buddy who was on a couple of episodes,
I go, you know what's funny?
I go, her character would hate Lenny Kravitz.
Right. Yes.
Oh, I, I find there to be almost no worse musician.
I hate his music so much.
The if you took the first three albums, I've only heard the singles.
The self -titled mama said, and then are you going to go my way?
You could concoct a pretty solid 10 song playlist.
Okay.
That you would go, okay, this is cool.
I don't know that you'd always want to jam out to it, but you'd be you wouldn't you'd be fine with it.
Yeah.
After that comes fly away and then it is off the fly away is the worst song ever.
Oh my God.
I want to get away.
I want to fly.
That is the worst melody ever.
It sucks.
Sick.
All right.
Today's episode, we're covering Castle Rock.
I think we're going to focus probably a little more on season two.
Yes.
We've already reviewed what we did the first half of season one as it was airing.
This will be spoiler heavy.
Yeah.
I mean, my experience with the show was I was watching season one to do for the podcast.
I immediately was like, everything about this is wrong.
I was so excited about this and they have fucked it up in every imaginable way.
I am bored.
I don't care.
And I stopped at episode five and Joe starts telling me this season two, baby,
it's back in a big way.
You got to check this out.
I'm like, yeah, but then can I just start or do I got to watch the season one?
Joe's like, you got to watch the season one.
So I wrapped it up.
I felt that season one, to be honest, did not really improve that much.
It had a couple of good moments, but overall was just a completely disjointed mess that
was never scary.
Stories didn't click.
Sissy Space, it was good.
Beyond that, nothing really made any impression on me at all.
And it also didn't feel like Stephen King, if I'm being honest with you.
So I didn't even know why they use that juicy dangle of like, this is going to be a story
in the Stephen King verse and then didn't really use it, at least to my satisfaction.
Season two starts and suddenly two is a massive step.
Yeah, right.
Immediately.
It's a it's a sort of alternate universe.
Annie Wilkes from Misery Prequel mixed with Salem's Lot, which they kept very quiet.
But also now you say prequel, but it's a present day.
So I was thrown by that for a little bit at first that this wasn't taking place in like 1980
because it is a young Annie Wilkes, but it's taking place in 2020, which is confusing at
first.
That's why I say it's sort of more like an alternate universe kind of, you know, in this
reality.
She lived during these years and this, you know what I mean?
Right.
But anyway, she they kept the Salem's Lot elements very quiet.
They didn't promote that at all.
Yeah.
So that was a nice surprise.
And I would say plays a much bigger role in this than, you know, Annie Wilkes is certainly
the main character, but the Salem Lot stuff, Salem's Lot stuff plays a much bigger part
in the story itself.
And I think obviously, to me, at least, I felt that this was this was the explanation
for that was what they tried to do initially with this was we're going to do an anthology
thing that takes place in Castle Rock and we're going to make up our own creepy stories
and in this weird little town or whatever, they realized, I think quickly, like, OK,
people watched, but that approach wasn't really working.
We better get back to the basics here.
And they did.
And they did it in a very interesting way.
This thing moves plot twists galore, more King alumni with Tim Robbins coming back,
and then suddenly midway through the season.
And again, this is spoiler heavy.
They start going back to shit that happened in the first season.
And I was like, holy shit, they're going back to Shawshank.
Are they going to tie this into the first season?
Right.
And that's when it really got interesting because I was like,
if they pull off somehow tying these two seasons together,
now we really got now we're cooking with gas here.
I completely admired that they didn't just dump it because my instinct,
if I had done that season of television, would have been let's pretend this never
happened and start start over.
So the fact that they had faith in season one, even when no one else did and kind of
kept it in the mix was cool.
And it sort of makes in retrospect season one seem better because
it's easy to get invested in two.
Right.
But it starts with like an amazing montage of Annie Wilkes and her daughter who was played by
who was the other girl from eighth grade.
I don't remember her name, but the amazing young actress from eighth grade.
And it's a montage to let the river run the Carly Simon song from working girl.
And it's like Annie Wilkes and her daughter growing up basically beautifully done montage
that tells you so much about the characters in the first five minutes.
Lizzie Kaplan is awesome.
She's doing a Kathy Bates impression.
It's not like she did her own take with the character,
but she was really awesome in it.
I thought that whole storyline to me beginning to end was great.
And when she kills somebody with this ice cream scoop very early on and I was like,
oh, right, there's finally something in this that is fun.
They must have gotten that note, right?
Season two.
Remember, this is supposed to be fun.
Season one was miserable.
There was like no no joy in it.
It was just a sad drama.
And even the violence wasn't cool or fun.
Yeah, even like even like the one big Stephen King thing in season one was was
Sheriff Pangborn.
Yeah.
And even that character suddenly was this just brooding miserable fucking asshole the whole time.
It was like nothing fun about him.
Tim Robbins sort of steps into that role in this one.
Yeah.
But he's they they electrified the character so much more.
They made him so much more of a fun prick.
Yeah, everything, including the violence and the kills,
seem to have taken that note in a big way.
Just have fun with it because it's more you wouldn't go so far as to say campy,
but there's like laughs in the violence.
And, you know, there's I think dark humor throughout that really worked.
Did you know that the okay.
So Tim Robbins older son.
Yeah.
The one who's the real asshole.
Yes.
Did you know that that's the character from Stand By Me?
The key for Sutherland.
I did, but only because I looked it up.
That's how I knew too.
Yeah.
But that's pretty cool.
Yeah, they did a lot of that kind of stuff.
A lot of more I thought fun, well done nods to King.
There's two other really stories that you're focusing on.
One is the Salem's Lot stuff, which to me wasn't great,
but that's also maybe because I never read it.
I only saw the miniseries.
And then there's the immigrants.
Were they Nigerian?
No, Somalian.
I'm sorry, Somalian.
Yes.
And apparently that's a real thing.
I looked that up as well, but that's happening in Maine
is there's like a big, big Somali population there,
which is really interesting to me.
But it's a nice juxtaposition to this old cult
that are basically the people responsible for the Salem lot.
Yes.
Or whatever.
You got the guy from Captain Phillips.
I'm the Captain Now guy who's great in this.
But the evil beings are trying to take over the town again.
And then there's also on the surface,
that's sort of happening literally beneath the surface.
And then above the surface, there's all this xenophobia
going on about the Somalian people taking over
and stuff like that.
So all these were well done.
Yeah, I thought.
Yeah, I really liked it.
I'm curious to see where season three goes.
My one gripe with this.
Are they doing it?
I think so.
I think the guy said we loved what Lizzie Kaplan did
in season two, but we've yet to make a decision.
Like singling her out is like the one thing he liked
is not a good sign.
The one thing I was bummed they didn't do.
And maybe they tried and just couldn't get it done.
I really I would have leapt out of my seat
if at the very last scene in this thing
is her Annie Wilkes at a book signing
for whatever the author's name is.
Paul Sheldon.
Paul Sheldon of misery.
And you're excited because you're like,
oh, this is how the obsession with this starts
because she's she murders her daughter at one point.
Yes, I was actually very surprised
there was nothing with with Paul Sheldon.
There was some reading stuff.
Actually, all the backstory stuff they gave her.
I was like, what perfect.
That Stephen King himself would not have written
a better misery prequel.
Yeah, no, I thought it all.
I thought it all led to the set up very well.
Her daughter gets really sick
and that's when she becomes obsessed with the books
because she's reading them as her daughter is in bed
and whatever.
And then she ends up murdering her daughter
and in a psychotic fit because she thinks her daughter
is possessed by a demon and the kid isn't.
And then now Annie Wilkes is walking around
with an imaginary daughter with her all the time.
So they do a good job of showing how bad shit
she really does go and what she's capable of.
And then the last scene is her at a Paul Sheldon book signing
and she's so excited.
And the one thing I really wanted to see
was I wanted to see James Khan like walk out
and kind of smile at her or whatever.
But, you know, who knows, maybe they asked him
and maybe it was like, get out of here.
I'm not doing that.
Well, it also wouldn't have made sense
because she's younger and then he'd be 90 coming out.
That is true. That is true.
Well, they could have de -aged him, right?
They could have got Scott Khan.
Yeah, that's a good call. That's a good call.
I mean, he's free, right?
Is Hawaii Five -O still on?
It is still on, but he is free, I guarantee.
Anyway, folks, check out Castle Rock.
It's worth your time.
It's worth your effort,
especially if you're a Stephen King fan.
You know, it's the ultimate gets better as it goes show.
I know everyone hates to hear like,
where do you get to episode 11?
But that's the truth here.
And unfortunately, you have to watch the first season.
And it is a bit of a slog.
They're long episodes,
but I do think it's worth it ultimately, as Pat said.
And I'll say this, too.
Everything that King has heaped his praise onto,
these adaptations of his work,
and so many of them have sucked.
I mean, the man has gone full,
from one side of the pendulum to the other,
with hating a masterwork like The Shining by Kubrick,
to now saying anything they make
that was adapted from his work is fantastic.
This is the one thing where I was like,
that was really great.
And Stephen King has not said positive things about it.
He doesn't shit on it,
but I saw him the other day on Twitter being like,
no matter what you think of the show,
you gotta like the set design or something like that.
Was he back on Twitter?
Cause he left.
He left after he said that he didn't think diversity.
I saw it, yeah.
I witnessed that.
Go down.
But anyway, that's our show.
Real quick, though.
I just read The Outsider,
and I'm gonna watch the HBO version.
I hear it's awesome.
I hear it's awesome, too.
But the book is a bit of a slog at times.
He overwrites everything to an absurd degree,
but he takes a swipe at The Shining in that,
at Kubrick's version of The Shining.
All right.
It's like he still needs to do it.
Like the Pet Sematary remake.
Christ, Christ.
Yeah.
Kubrick did nothing.
There's something else going on there.
The Kubrick Shining adaptation is more faithful to the book
than the Pet Sematary adaptation is to the...
What is...
I don't get it.
I think it was so personal to him.
It was about his alcoholism and all that,
that maybe the movie version hit too close to home or something.
Who knows?
All right.
But he said at the time,
I think Kubrick really wants to make a movie
that will hurt people.
And I don't understand that.
Well, anyway, that's our show, folks.
Jodorosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Tour dates at jodorosainfo .com.
Jodorosa Comedian on Facebook.
Thank you, as always, for your support.
We appreciate it.
And thank you again to everybody
that came out for the live shows.
We appreciate it.
I second that in a big way.
And thank you, Emily Florence,
for helping us out on that show, as always.
Great to see Ken Hanley,
who got this podcast kind of off the ground
back in the early days.
Will Podorf.
Will Podorf does the artwork for the show
or some of the artwork for the show,
some of the amazing artwork we've gotten for the show.
Folks, I'm on Twitter and Instagram
at the Patrick Walsh.
I'm going to be on two podcasts coming up.
Other than this one,
my friend Miel's called Punch Up the Jam
and my friend Bridger's called I Said No Gifts.
Thank you very much.
We will see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.