I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's Will See You In Hell.
Here we are to talk about the movies that you love, the movies that you don't like
the movies that you feel medium about.
My name is Joe DeRosa and mine is Patrick Walsh.
How are you, everybody?
It's good to see you.
It feels like it's been a while, Joe.
It has.
I think we recorded the tilt your mic just a bit down in front of the mouth.
No, no, no, tilt.
Tilt.
There you go.
Thank you.
That's better.
Patrick, Pat, I had some audio issues in the beginning of the, well, it's the same audio
issue I have every week.
I simply forget to turn on the microphone.
And since you can't see him, he's in a, he looks as, he's dressed as a man that might have
shuffled in off of the street randomly, so he got a p -code on, yeah, it's cold enough.
Yeah, it's cold in the house, the chilly these days out of the way.
It is.
It's always cold up till like noon.
It's, you know, it's like 55 degrees in the house, or I'd kill for 55.
Well, in the houses is too cold, but outside I'd kill for 55 right now.
It's too cold and they sent out this email from the gas company that's like, hey, your gas
bill is going to be outrageous for a while.
Sorry.
Jesus Christ.
So, you know, it's not like I'm, I'm scared to turn it on and spend the money, but they
don't say what it's going to be.
You know, I'd rather not turn it on for a week and have it be 10 grand or something.
So I, it doesn't bother me to put on a p -code, even though I know I look like a homeless
Oscar wild at this moment and I got to get my hair cut.
Yeah, it looks good.
You look good.
You look fit.
Oh, thank you.
You just, you just look like you just go and out of the wind or something.
Yeah, but other than that, the, I, yeah, it's, it's a horrible time.
I, I, with that we're living and I woke up to two days in a row of a fraud act, a fraud
activity on my Venmo.
I mean, it's just you open your eyes and that's how the day starts.
I mean, it's just, yeah, Jesus Christ, man.
Can I get a bolus cereal first?
Yeah, no, I, I had a wild evening last night, but not wild really.
I was supposed to meet up with our friend, Jamie for dinner.
I did.
Jamie Lee?
Correct.
Yeah.
Okay.
We had a nice dinner.
We discussed our lives.
We caught up and you know, we're going to be done with this dinner.
It was an early meeting, 630.
And I've had this date for like a month with this girl from Tinder or ginger, whatever,
very, very attractive.
And we've talked a lot, had a good rapport.
So we were supposed to meet up around Christmas, didn't, hey, I got busy, I got busy, you
know, that kind of ship.
And then here in the new year, she wrote and was like, Hey, I hope you weren't trying to
shake me off or something.
You want to try to meet up again?
I go, yeah, that'd be great.
Sounds fun.
So we set last night as our hangout time.
I go, I'll be done with dinner about 830 is 9 okay.
She goes, no, that's perfect.
That's perfect.
Let's go out.
We'll get a drink.
How's this place?
Good.
Texting back and forth.
So I text her before I go into dinner.
I go, Hey, just want to make sure we're still on for tonight.
After.
After the two hour hang, I tell Jamie great to see you and I flip open my phone, no response.
So now here I am dressed and ready for a date.
It's scheduled.
I know it's supposed to happen.
I get no answer.
So then I'm immediately in this mode of, by the way, I'm at the same restaurant where I
got stood up when I first started this dating post divorce, same exact restaurant.
Reach out, call this girl, no answer, no text.
Finally, I give up, I'm standing on a street corner like a fucking loser.
Go home, go to bed, wake up, two in the morning in a complete panic, having no idea what
I'm panicking about.
I felt like Sam Kinnison screaming in my brain, right, walking around the house like quickly,
looking for what?
I don't know.
And I stopped myself.
I was just like, what are you doing?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Uh, then I realized I had two glasses of wine at dinner.
I hadn't had a drink in a while.
Maybe that was doing it.
But what woke me up in this state of like the house is on fire, it was awful.
And then I get into bed and I'm like, check my phone, this girl never even texted back, didn't
even have the courtesy to go, hey, I'm sorry, I dozed off or whatever.
What's wrong with people?
This is two months in the making for us to go get a drink.
Well, couldn't pull it off.
Yeah.
Look, there's still the hope that something horrible happened to her.
And that was why she didn't text, but, but yeah, no, that's, uh, that sounds pretty,
uh, LA -ish.
I, I saw an, I saw an article today, uh, Pinkstone sent me a really great article, uh,
the writer of which is escaping me, but it was about the problem with binary thinking
and the way that we're all thinking in binary terms these days, where everybody is either a
hero or the worst human being that's ever lived and how bad that is.
And at one point in the article, he, he makes an analogy to a dating app and he goes, which
by the way, as I've mentioned, these are very bad for you and there's a link.
And then I found a whole article about why dating apps are so bad to you, uh, gave
myself a quick pat on the back for Trashing Tinder all those years ago when it first premiered
on my Comedy Central special, but I was going to send it to you.
And then I was like, I was like, I don't know if he's in the mindset to see something like
this. And I, I didn't want to be like, I didn't want it to come off like I was being
like, look, see, I just was like, he might be interested in reading this.
I don't know.
I, you know, I might have read it.
I've read a few things, but send it over.
I don't care.
It's, you know, you hate to be one of these people like, it's the worst because I'm
probably going to wind up meeting my next girlfriend on them.
It's just kind of like, what is the worst is people, at least half of people are nightmares.
And that's going to be reflected when you're dating.
Obviously.
Yeah.
You can only you, it's, it's no matter what the device or innovation is, yeah.
We will use it to do the worst thing possible.
Yeah.
That's all there is to it.
So I'm sorry that happened to you.
That sucks.
I, I, I was, I just was sitting here last night, quite a quiet evening.
I haven't had to drink in a week.
Yeah.
I'm over a week.
Tuesday will be two weeks and Tuesday is the night that we take out our staff from Joey
Roses for a very late holiday.
So, you know, appreciation hang.
I was like, all right, if I have a few drinks, I'll have it that night.
But I got to tell you that I hate to admit it on record.
You feel a thousand percent better, not having alcohol in my system.
Yeah.
When you go away from it, you wonder how you ever did it.
But then it comes a point where you got to get back in there.
And when you get back in, you wonder how you ever did that.
It's true.
It's almost as if we never should have started.
I, uh, the statistic that I've heard about dating that, that rings true is apparently
that women are significantly pickier than men, which is not a big surprise.
But that men are, their women are only targeting the top 20 % of men on the apps.
All women are going after the same 20 % of men, which leaves the other 80 with zero
attention.
And it leaves these 20 % feeling like gods who never want to settle down because they're
getting the pick of the most beautiful women on earth throwing themselves at.
So they wind up fucking all them and then women are like, guys are shit.
And it's like, that's true to some degree.
But what about the other 80 % who you're not giving any play to, you know, I don't mean play.
Like, was Siso, I got, I got my tinder set to the, I'll do anything filter.
It's, uh, it's, uh, Albert Brooks and Nick Nolte telling you who your matches are.
That's the, do you ever see I'll do anything?
No, wait, what are you saying?
I don't do anything as a James Albrook's picture with Albert Oh, oh, oh, no, is it funny?
It's kind of funny.
Uh, it's, it was a musical with songs by Prince and they wound up cutting all the music from it.
So it's with a little misshapen.
It's a little odd, but I always thought the movie was pretty funny.
It's like a Hollywood satire.
James Albrook's despite the singing sensations of, yeah, you know, Albert Brooks, it's rare.
You get Nolte in a film and don't have him belt out a couple show stoppers, but, uh, I, uh, speaking
of Nolte by funny Valentines, I realized last night and I have a story for you, but I realized
last night, I've never seen Cape Fear, I've never seen it.
It's amazing.
I've heard, yeah, I just, I don't know, I've just never seen it and I was watching all kinds of clips
of it last night with, uh, you know, on YouTube and I was like, why have I never watched this?
Like it's, yeah, but then I did think it was we, it's funny.
In my head, William, uh, God, who's the guy that died?
Oh, boy, blonde hair, glasses, accidental tourist.
This is name, hurt William hurt.
In my head William hurt was the lawyer and then I was like, no, it's Nick Nolte.
Nolte's maybe best work, you know, it's weird because I was like, I couldn't, I was having a hard time
picture yet.
I was like, Nick Nolte's playing like the vulnerable guy, like that's weird.
Well, this was at the time when Nick Nolte was voted the sexiest man in America by people magazine.
Wow, which is absolutely insane to me.
And he's the start of the drink and try not long after.
So I'm at least, you know, it became public knowledge.
I'm looking up, I see we got a jolly Richardson.
I'm always a fan of her in, in this picture you're talking about.
I'll do anything.
Yeah.
Uh, I woke up two days ago to repeated phone calls from Venmo saying somebody is trying to
authorize your account.
If this is not you, please type in this code.
I typed the code in turns out I got scammed.
Person sends two grand to somebody I know, you know, luckily it was a friend.
Uh, I guess the scam is as they immediately then message the person they sent the money to
and say send it back to me, that person sends it back.
They take it out and whatever.
I managed to not lose the money.
It's stuck in a Venmo account that I can't access, but at least I didn't lose it.
But here's the most amazing part.
I call Venmo to deal with the fraud.
Yeah.
Venmo's audit, I have been trashed in Venmo from day,
fucking one at the casual nature of a money exchange app like this, the fact that it's
public, the fact that you're writing emojis and and cute little things.
So everybody can see who you're giving your money.
It's a fucking childish baby app that people use because they can't grow up.
Use PayPal, use Zell, use a fucking grown up set.
But whatever I'm a private on Venmo, you don't have to do the emoji shit.
I don't understand how why people do do that.
But because for all the reasons I just said, uh, and here's the thing.
I, I am, I'm a, I'm a victim of this disgusting decrepit rotting society we live in.
So I have to use Venmo.
I have no choice.
So whatever this happens, I call Venmo.
Pat, I am not lying to you.
I get the automated system.
You know, with the prompts, press this if you want this or whatever, right?
Yeah.
Seven prompts, seven, not one of them pertains to did somebody.
It was fraud part of your, you know what I mean, uh -huh, which is insane.
It's insane.
It's not even an option.
Claims department, nothing.
Okay.
I hate, I hit zero.
We're sorry.
We don't recognize that response.
It's ridiculous.
So eventually I just hit whatever to try to talk to somebody.
I, I get a guy, he says to me, here's what I want you to do.
Here's what I recommend you do.
You call your buddy Dan that the $2 ,000 was sent to.
Uh -huh.
You asked him to send it back to you.
By the way, which is what the fraud people did, right?
That was their thing.
That's part of the scam, right?
At no point in this conversation, does the customer service rep say immediately change
your password, immediately disconnect your bank account?
None of these things.
This is what he recommends.
I do.
I love that the guy at Venmo is also like, he's what you're going to want to do.
You know, you're like, you're in an alley or something.
Uh, he said, call your friend.
Have him send the money back then call your bank and have them block any
transactions with Venmo.
Then call back Venmo, I go, I'm going to stop you there.
Why am I doing all of this, right?
This wasn't my fault.
Venmo should be doing all these things.
The guy goes, well, sir, I'm just trying to tell you the easiest way to do this.
I go, this isn't the easiest way to do this.
You just recommended three phone calls that I have to make two of them to
the institutions where I'll be put on hold for extended periods of time.
And I can't get to anybody directly.
How is this the easiest thing for me to do?
And he goes, okay, then move it on.
How about you do this and he starts going and I go, hold on a second.
Isn't the easiest thing to do for me to just have my friend pay me back the money?
And he goes recommended that you didn't want to do it.
I go, no, that's not what you recommended.
You recommended two other steps on top of that that I don't understand.
And he goes, well, it doesn't matter.
I went ahead and froze your accounts since you refused to pursue the thing I recommended.
Now we're going to take, I go, I didn't tell you to freeze the account.
He goes, well, I did it because you, I go, why are you acting like this is my fault?
And he goes, it is your fault.
You took the fraud call and you, you complied with there.
And dude, I lost my mind.
What does he mean?
You took the fraud call.
It was my fault for falling for the fraud scam, where they said type in this code.
If this isn't you, and he goes, okay, Venmo would never call you, sir.
And I, I just, I go, well, then fucking Venmo should make that clear to the customer.
How the fuck am I supposed to know?
Venmo's never going to call me.
You're sitting here blaming me right now for, did I fell for a fraud scam that seemed legitimately,
like Venmo was calling me.
I was walking up to five phone calls in a row of an automated message saying,
then this is Venmo, if this is not you, immediately type this code in that we're texting you.
It was so insane.
So now I'm in a situation where I disconnected my bank account from the Venmo thing.
Because I put the hold on Venmo transaction or block on Venmo transactions on my account.
I've got $2 ,000 sitting in a Venmo account.
I can't reconnect the account because now Venmo won't let me reconnect the account.
I can't get the money out of the Venmo account into my banking account to do an instant transfer.
If I can get it out, whenever that is allowed to do an instant transfer of the money back into my account,
it's a $25 fee.
It's insane, dude.
I just emailed this, you know, some representative named me a message to me and said, Hey,
you know, your accounts on frozen, you can use it again, we're sorry about the inconvenience.
And I just wrote back, look, I appreciate your help.
Here's the deal.
The account never should have been frozen to begin with.
I can't reconnect my bank account for whatever reason.
It's an error on Venmo's end.
My bank is allowing it to happen.
You guys aren't.
I need it fixed.
I also need the $25 fee waived since none of this was my fault, including the fact that I fell for fraud,
which your representative told me was my fault.
Please advise.
I'll wait patiently.
I still haven't heard back from Old Mia.
But this is what we're living in.
I mean, it's a horror show.
This is how the day you read your response and hung herself in shame.
She has a commitment to customer service that is that great.
Yeah, she said she goes, well, I can't, I'm not meeting this tender date tonight.
I could be able to respond to that.
Yeah, it's a lot anymore.
I'm in a loss.
I will say I get PayPal emails that I almost fall for a couple times a week.
So, you know, these scams anywhere that money is exchanging hands.
There are scammers waiting to take it.
Sure.
I don't know, ma 'am.
I mean, I went out yesterday and I get that people are struggling and it's only going to get worse.
But I looked out the window yesterday to see a guy.
There's always people rummaging through the trash cans and they're always taking cans and whatever else.
And it's kind of like, okay, I get it today.
There's a guy who has my trash can on the floor, like completely tipped over.
And I'm seeing like the back half of his body rummaging around.
And when he comes out, he's got paperwork.
Now, I try to tear everything up and I've got a paper shredder.
But he comes out and is standing in front of my home reading something, not a script.
It's just like, you know, paper.
And I open the garage door.
He looks all flustered and I'm like, it's okay, man.
I go, if you want to take cans or whatever, I go, I don't, I just don't think you need to be rummaging through it like this.
And he's like already walking off and let it go.
You know, what am I supposed to do?
But you're supposed to do is say, and I'm sorry.
And I know you might not agree and I might be whatever.
Get the fuck off of my property.
This is private property.
I understand that everybody needs a helping hand.
And I understand that we should be altruistic and help people.
But this concept that it's a fucking free for all.
Yeah, it's a free, you know, this, I just saw a video online.
This fucking lady walks, it's security cam footage.
It's real.
This lady walks into a convenience store holding an axe.
An axe and this, and she walks right up to a guy in line and starts talking to him.
This dipshit doesn't back away from her because God forbid we pass any judgment on any individual at any time.
She hits him in the face with the fucking axe and splits his face open.
It's like, it's like guys, yeah, there's got to be some boundaries here.
This is, this is insanity.
A guy does not have the right to come on to your private property and go through your personal trash cans.
It's not a fucking store.
It's not an alleyway.
It's nuts.
It could be a lunatic for all you know, I agree, I agree.
And in watching like families walk along the street and have these like drugged out guys come at them and yell at them and brought daylight.
You know, we're clearly entering into a road like world.
And then there's the added thing the back in the corner of the car through road.
But the other thing is why you know, you feel everyone is a monster or you're immediately attacked.
If you say anything along the lines of, we're going to stop this or we're going to do something here.
A lot of Twitter is like, can you believe this fucking ass?
Now I've seen here, I've seen the extremes.
The one extreme is the storefront guy spraying down a almost woman with his own.
Right. Yeah, you don't, yeah, that's terrible.
Saw that video.
I was like, okay, mistake there.
But then you see stuff where a guy like takes a picture.
And I'm talking about like Matt Gaetz or something.
I'm talking about just like some guys like, is this what we want for our neighborhoods?
And it looks like, you know, a goddamn disaster area.
And then people are like, shut the fuck up.
What's your problem?
It's like, no, there is something to be said about not wanting your neighborhood to look like a disaster area.
No, can we not agree with that?
But people can't.
It's like, well, you did, you did this and that's why people are home.
No, I didn't do it.
And the person who posted this picture didn't do it.
It's our disgusting capitalistic society.
But we can at least make places for these guys to live or else they're going to be in the street.
I get that.
But also, I don't see what the end game is.
Also to, you know, I can say this very confidently as a business owner.
This concept that homeless only means the old lady with cans and a shopping cart is crazy.
It's bullshit.
Yeah, there are the people we've we've had an issue with and I'm using heavy quotes homeless people.
Sometimes at the bar in our outdoor space and whatever where we've had to tell people to move on and they get threatening.
Now if I just tell you that, if I say that sentence to you, yeah, your head immediately goes to it's some sweet person who's in a, no, it's not that's not what I'm talking about.
And I would never not be accommodated to somebody like that.
It is a guy who has a place to sleep every night, but has no residence.
That's a very different thing.
It's a guy who does a lot of fucking drugs.
And because of the drugs he does, he is spending all of his money on drugs.
And he couchserves with his friends that allow him to spend all his money on drugs.
That is that's a version of homeless and you know what?
When you say to that guy, sir, you can't just sit here.
You got to order something or whatever.
Why?
Because he's a man in new clean clothing who is just sitting in your thing, smoking weed or whatever or cigarettes or whatever.
When you say to him, sir, you need to move on.
He threatens you.
There's there's there are different colors to this spectrum people like, you know, like come on, man.
Yeah, there's these people that are like, you know, homeless or unhoused doesn't immediately mean drug addict or whatever.
And it's like, no, of course not.
But they're, let's not pretend there isn't a large subsection of these people that are on drugs and dangerous in LA.
I mean, it's, it's, I don't know, there's no upside to us even saying this.
But it is like you go to a Meba and it's like scary at noon.
You know, and I've lived in horrific cities, you know, horrible.
I lived in Williamsburg when it seemed like the most dangerous place on Earth.
It was horrible.
It was not Lena Dunham's paradise.
And you know, walking home at four in the morning and I've seen some horrific shit.
But never at like noon in a, in a sort of major area with policemen just sort of driving past it, like it's not happening.
Well, I know you're, I can say this for both of us before we, we just, I don't think we've said anything off base, but I just in case anybody thinks we sound monsters.
I can say this for both of us.
I live in New York City.
I obviously have no problem with homeless people.
I obviously have no problem with different economic classes.
I obviously have no problem with somebody asking you on the street for a bit of help.
I have no problem with any of that.
What I have a problem with is people that abuse a social construct and a social contract.
That's what I have a problem with.
I mean, plenty of people in New York who that, that it's, they've written articles about it.
I'm not saying anything crazy.
They have homes.
Yeah, they have homes that are like, yeah, dude, I, I panhandle and that's how I paid.
There, there was an article once in the village voice about like I put my kid through college pan handling.
It's like, I'm just saying sometimes you got a, you know, you got a, I used to have a joke in my eye.
I go to New York is the only place on earth that can make you window shop homeless people.
We're like, I don't know, bad.
Yeah.
You may or may not pass, you know, you know, this guy seems worthy of the dollar.
This guy seems like he's scamming this guy, whatever, you know, it's a, it's just a fucking horrible.
And then we're saying this because of why?
Because I started this conversation with I got scammed by something that seemed to be concerned about my own safety and financial security.
Right.
You get a call where somebody is saying we're trying to help you because somebody is trying to hurt you and you trust them.
And unfortunately now that's just trickling down into every aspect of life.
It's this, it's so disheartening, man.
It's just so disheartening and all the older people that say there was a time where this wasn't a problem and we didn't lock our doors at night.
I mean, I don't know if I fucking buy that anymore, man.
I feel like this is always a problem.
The problem just continually snowballs, you know.
Well, the seniors are the easiest people to target because they believe that everything on the internet is legit and real.
So that's how they get into big, big trouble.
My grandma was telling me about she almost went up and met with some guy who was like, she was claiming he was her grandson.
And she was like, I knew it wasn't your voice, but I just kept saying, why would this guy be pretending to be my grandson?
So I was going to meet him at this bank.
I'm like, Grandma, Jesus Christ, she didn't do it, but it's, I think what is happening is people see what you can do with no consequences in politics.
Let's say, for example, and they're like, well, I'm not going to pay my fucking taxes and be Mr. Good American Joe citizen anymore.
I'm done. I'm going to find some other way to make a living because that's all these monsters are doing and they're not wrong.
But once, once that starts getting noticed by the general public, that's when the world is in jeopardy of just its whole structure falling apart.
Maybe we're due for that. I don't know.
So folks, if you're going to vote in this next presidential election, vote Trump.
Make America great again.
I guess is he running again?
There's rumbles of it. Who knows what the hell is going to I got to be honest with the state of everything over the last, what is it?
Six years now, two years of Biden, four years of Trump.
I wouldn't be surprised if they called off the presidential elections.
It's time that we're going dark this year.
It's time for us to just reevaluate and look at some new candidates.
It's, you know, they got to lower the age, I think, you know, this is wild, dude.
It's wild.
Yeah. Leno, here's a new psycho.
I didn't even know this recovering from multiple broken bones after recent motorcycle accident.
He just got over the burns and he got to know a motorcycle accident.
He wants to die.
Jesus Christ. What is this guy doing?
Maybe he's drinking or something because they finally just pulled his, they pulled the plug on his CNBC show.
The car is one.
Yeah. So that's like the final thing for him.
Like that was his last connection to television.
Oh, he's got to cancel and I've never been in a dad's home where he wasn't watching that show.
He's hosted a game show on like regular NBC like a daytime game show or something.
Yeah, but I mean, this is this is all he had.
He was, and he's been on TV for seemingly a hundred years at this.
No, no, I'm saying he, he currently has a game hosting a game show.
Well, then, Mosel, I didn't know that.
Yeah, I caught it.
I made fun of it on the thing here, not made fun of the show, but made fun of how cheap the set was.
Yeah.
And as, you know, as a, you know, meaning like the TV television is continually deteriorating, which I'm going to Christ.
I saw a clip this morning from how I met your father.
You bet your life he is doing.
If you can find on Instagram, this clip, it was just an ad of the very first thing I saw this morning of how I met your father.
And it's Hillary Duff talking to Josh Peck.
And he's got this fake tan on.
You'll know it when you see it. He looks diseased.
And it is the least funny clip, including like show of the nine hour Holocaust documentary.
It's the least funny clip I've ever seen in my entire life.
And I was reminded that not even a year ago, I was devastated to not get a job on how I met your father.
And I watched this clip and was just like, you know what?
Fuck you.
Fuck you and your awful fucking show.
It's, well, let's go to the movie corner because my whole movie corner is television.
Okay.
Yeah, let's do it. Let's do it.
I saw I would love to recommend a picture that I know you love, Joseph.
And I had never seen it called Flash Gordon.
Oh, yeah. Good time.
I always, I feel like I rented every non -arrated movie in the video store by the time I graduated high school.
I don't know how I missed Flash Gordon.
I guess I just didn't care.
I think I've even seen Flash Gordon, the adult version.
But flat, have you seen Flash Gordon?
It's an actual movie.
No, I've heard of it.
That's, that's, I don't think I ever saw, but that's one of those famous.
That's like one of those classic corner titles.
My favorite, my favorite porno parody title ever is bright lights, big titties.
I mean, to me, nothing will ever top that one.
But, but Flash Gordon is very good.
That's very, very well done.
Why not bright tights, big titties or something?
You need something with that lights.
Don't, I don't think you push it.
I think you just let it lie there.
Like, let it, let, let it take you all the way to the last word where you're like,
when's it going to become a porno title?
Then you also, you like the suspense of it too.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it's just a great, and they might have worked lights into the plot.
It might have been about, you know, I don't know.
I always thought shaving Ryan's privates was pretty good.
That's very good.
Yeah.
I also like the careless, specific fetish if you like watching men get shaved,
but it's, you can't have a better title than that.
Right.
I also like the carelessness of Edward penis hands.
How they were just like, I fucking, yeah, yeah, I've seen clips of that one.
Actually, I had never seen Flash Gordon.
I thought it was incredibly fun.
I had, I had somehow already seen the making of documentary of Flash Gordon.
So I knew about a lot of the drama that went on.
It's a movie unlike any other.
It's very, very campy, but it's also not joky.
You know, it doesn't like Marvel is significantly joke here.
This is a movie that seems like they were just obsessed with making it cool.
All the costumes, the world, the sets, everything's great.
The only actor who wasn't good is Flash Gordon himself, and it winds up kind of working for the movie.
They got this great director who just passed away.
Mike Hodges, who directed it.
He did Croupier with Clive Owen, which is an excellent gambling movie.
He did the original get Carter with Mike Kane.
He's a really good director.
This is the only movie like this in his catalog.
And this is back when Hollywood allowed a great director to take a property like this and run with it.
You know, Marvel and DC.
Well, I shouldn't DC.
It's still yet to be seen since they still haven't landed their cinematic universe yet.
But Marvel, you know, the routine, they go out, they find some young kid that
that they can direct the movie for basically, you know, and that's kind of it.
And, you know, it's, it's, this is back when, you know, they would, they would let a guy that knew what the fuck he was doing.
Take on something like this and then you get a great product like Flash Gordon, where it's just wild vision, you know.
Yeah, you can tell that it was made by somebody with some vision.
His other movies are all like somber character studies and this was him, you know, taking a big swing.
And to me, it really worked.
I loved it. I had a lot of fun with it.
But the main reason I loved it is the 4K.
I know I'm becoming Mr. 4K.
But Drew McQueenie, who started out on Ainut Cools, a film writer.
I've read his stuff through the years and he just commented like this is the coolest 4K disc ever.
I started seeing that from a few people on Letterbox and it just is.
I mean, it's like you gasp with each new scene that starts costumes, the sets, the visuals, everything just looks so great in the 4K.
I've never seen it the original way.
I have to imagine this is a vast, vast improvement.
But what I'm learning about the 4K is that the best discs are the movies that are super colorful.
It does the most with color.
I highly recommend if you got a 4K player picking up Flash Gordon, the arrow special version with all these features is only like 20 bucks.
Well worth it.
I have the 4K. I upgraded to it. I haven't watched it yet, but the blue ray looked spectacular.
So I can only imagine what I'm in for with the 4K.
I've got three TV shows here. Do you want me to go from worst to best or best to worst?
Let's go. Let's go worse to best.
All right. Nightcourt.
Yeah.
Dear God.
Folks, nobody loved Nightcourt more than I did as a kid.
I was so excited when IMDB added it to a streaming catalog.
It was a show that for years I tried to find on DVD.
The entire season, you know, each season hadn't been released.
I still think to this day you can't get a full set of nightcourt.
And the seasons themselves are still priced like old school TV seasons used to be priced.
They're like 40 bucks a pop or whatever.
Are they put it on peacock?
No, it's just an IMDB streaming.
I mean, maybe they will eventually, but I don't know.
But I was excited when they announced the new nightcourt.
I was excited to even with the fact that, you know,
very heartbreaking to me that Harry Anderson is not around anymore.
Markey Post is gone.
Even as they passed amidst the announcement of this show, I think Harry Anderson had already died.
Markey Post was still alive.
I still had hopes, high hopes for this mainly because John Lara Kett was coming back.
I was waiting with baited breath for a trailer, anything.
I was googling consistently, you know, every week, there's a trailer, whatever.
When the trailers and promos for this finally dropped, I was like, oh, we might be in trouble here.
You know, and then I watched the first two episodes.
It's terrible. It's just a terrible show.
It's, it's, it's ballless.
Yeah, it's just got no soul to it. It's got nothing.
It is a paint by numbers sitcom with a bunch of dumb gags.
The characters are, it's just, it's just so paper thin.
And the original show had a lot of gags in it.
But the characters were so, you know what?
And this is the thing too.
I've been like revisiting King of Queens late at night to go to bed to again.
And I've, I've already done Queen, King, Queens in the show.
I'm like, I think it's just a, it's just a lack of ability.
It's like these actors just don't bring the charisma.
They don't carve the characters out.
Yeah, you know, there's a lot of stuff on King of Queens where you could go, well, on paper, that's not really much.
But look at what the actor did with it.
You know, totally friends is the same way for you know, I don't even love friends.
But those six people, when you really look at what's being written, what is on the page
and the laughs they're getting out of it, like that's a gift.
And it's, and it's not a skill that people have anymore.
It just isn't big bang everything about being as naturalistic as possible,
as grounded and real as possible.
And that's not what multi -chem is.
So you wind up with these DOA shows big bang theory was another good example.
Two and a half men was another good example.
You can sit on those shows all you want when you watch those shows.
You knew who every character was.
The best example I can think of is not even a sitcom.
Liam Neeson and Phantom Menace.
He took some really wooden dialogue that didn't have much to it.
And you watch it and you walked away going, I know who that character is.
I get it.
There was subtext. He brought a lot into it.
And that's just not happening on this show.
But that's just the surface issue.
Let's go a little deeper here.
Why?
And these are my two biggest issues.
Number one, I know why Richard Moles not on the show.
There's a TMZ interview where they said, would you do a night court reading?
And he said, I would run in the other direction.
I love entertainment. I hate the people and then he left it at that.
I then also he say and he hates the makers of night court.
He didn't specify, but I then saw an interview with Harry Anderson
during the run of the show where he said, we're lucky to have such an amazing cast.
And he named everybody except Richard Moles.
And I'm like, okay, there's that's a hint.
Anyway.
So that made sense that he wasn't part of this.
Why is Marsha Warfield not on the show?
Why? She's still working.
She was just on the on the gay comedy Netflix special that was all the gay comedian.
She was on that.
She's still working. She's not on it.
Instead, they found another black woman who has
like is reminiscent of Marsha Warfield, not just in her attitude and stuff,
but she's got the same vibe as Marsha Warfield.
To me, I'm like, okay, so one of two things, you're either ageist
where you didn't want to bring back Marsha Warfield because you thought she was too old.
Or you're racist.
And Marsha Warfield said, no, I don't want to do it.
And you said then we'll cast somebody that reminds people of you.
It's fucking weird, man.
It is fucking weird.
It's a weird, complete, fucking red flag in the casting.
I don't understand it.
It's odd to me.
So there's no Pete Holmes is playing a love interest of Melissa Rouch for a few episodes.
I know he's on a few episodes.
So you can ask him about his experience on set.
It's not my story to tell, but yeah.
And then on top of it, you don't even make her the daughter of more, make it her daughter.
Yeah.
Make this show has such little common sense writing in it.
Am I wrong that the plot is she inherits her dad's courtroom?
No, that's not what it is.
Okay. She takes over.
She becomes the new judge in the same court as her father, who is dead.
Gotcha.
Which brings me when I just said about the surface area writing and the lazy writing
and the lack of pursuing obvious writing.
And what you just said, it all brings me to the greatest problem with the show.
John Larrichette's character, Dan Fielding.
Dan Fielding was a lethario.
He groped women.
Yes.
He fucked anything that walked.
That was the whole gag of the character.
Now, I understand that you can't do that on television now.
I understand why it would be inappropriate.
I understand why it was inappropriate then.
And we didn't have clear enough glasses on to maybe understand that.
I understand all of that.
But to bring this character back and not reference it in any way,
shape or form to in fact pretend that he never was that person
and go in the opposite direction that he was just sort of a misanthrope
or is just a misanthrope that's dropped out of society now.
Why?
Because his wife died to go in the opposite direction that he
was a man that was happily married and never addressed them.
Maybe they'll address it later on.
I don't understand why you to address this later on and not off the bat.
It's so bizarre.
It's like you you definitely wouldn't go in now and pitch a show
about a guy who had like decades of me too and now we're supposed to love him.
I get that.
But you've got this beautiful comedy set up built in to this show.
It's a guy who we've seen for 10 years on television be a monster
to ignore that and not have fun with it.
Criminal.
It's classic.
That's the hook of the sitcom.
That's that's the show.
It's classic Hollywood bullshit.
It's we're going to go in the other direction and virtue signal with this
character and then if we get called out on it, we'll address it.
Right.
And act like they were sorry all along.
They just didn't realize it's such fucking nonsense, man.
It's it's poorly written.
It's poorly executed.
They they get one like eight Emmys for the show.
He won every year.
People don't didn't forget the character and they're giving him nothing
funny to do.
They pay zero tribute to the original characters.
They glaze over the fact that Harry Anderson's character and the real
Harry Anderson are dead.
They they pay no tribute to it whatsoever.
They don't make it in any way a motivation for Lara Ket to come back.
Right.
The idea that he has to come back now as a defense attorney when he was the
prosecutor is brilliant and it's fucking poorly done.
And there's nothing to it.
There's he's not indebted in any way.
And then on top of all of it, the final episode of night court
was that he his character ran off to pursue marquee post because he was secretly
in love with her for all these years and he finally had redeemed himself.
And then in this fucking show when he talks about his dead wife,
is it marquee post character?
No, it's a different character.
And she's died in real life and on the show, she can't come back because
the actress is dead.
What the fuck, man?
I know I literally don't understand why things are so stupidly fucking
written like this.
It drives me crazy.
The the the sheer tonnage of things that sound
wrong and and insane to me makes this feel strongly of network interference.
Yes, but you can't always blend the network in these situations.
But it sounds like they just didn't let them do anything.
And it suffers, of course.
I think it probably started in the direction of doing all these things
that I'm talking about.
And oh, Dan's going to come back and redeem himself.
And and then these fucking network people put their fingers in
and it gets softer and softer.
And then somebody on the writer's room complains that this joke is too much.
And then they then it's softer and so and the whole fucking thing because
everybody is fucking pissing and moaning and afraid of everything.
You end up with this solo show.
And and these reviews that are on the previews for it now.
It's yeah, 10 out of 10.
And this is this is people payola is in full effect.
It's in full shit because they'll do you can see it.
They'll do a review when when a pilot is clearly shit and everyone knows it's
shit, then the critic will say, you know, this is just dead and arrival.
Don't waste your time.
Then there's these shows where the pilot is shit.
Everyone knows it's shit like night court and the critics are like,
there's enough here to keep you sticking around.
The pilot doesn't work at all.
The first five episodes don't work at all.
But we feel like they're probably going to work out those kinks as time goes by.
Like what what what are you talking about?
They play favorites, you know, now with Twitter, the critics can all talk to the
showrunners.
It's absurd and the night court series is doing very well, which is crazy too
because it means we're going to get more of this shit and they'll take the wrong
lessons from it.
Are they still doing the big surreal gags?
Yeah, that's the one that's the one thing that like made
its way and is like the jokes, the courtroom gags.
And I was like, that's cool.
Like that's that's part of it.
There's a funny joke in the second episode where she tells the staff,
I want you to make the courtroom your own, like make some changes.
And the guy has a mural painted is getting a mural painted on the wall.
And he's like, you know, it's going to be great.
It's it's, you know, this guy's an excellent artist and he's going to paint a mural
of judges or whatever.
And then at the last scene she walks in and it's the golden girls.
And she's like, and he's like turns out he was all he can paint as the golden.
It's like kind of a funny gag, you know what I mean?
Like there's there's moments like that.
There's like
it's just it's just it's like for for this character of Danfielding to come back
and be the opposite of who he was with zero motivation outside of
Harry's daughter asked God damn it.
Trump up that he finds out that Harry died and he feels bad because they had a falling out.
I mean, this is fucking writing 101.
I don't understand.
I just don't fucking understand.
Have them say I want to I want to write all the wrongs that of my past
because my wife would have wanted that and I want to be a better man in her on anything.
You know what a real funny a real funny premise for the show would be off top of my head
is that he let's say he was devastated by a marquee post death went and lived in an
island somewhere then he can just be like, yeah, I'll come back.
You know, I've been meeting I've been wanting to practice law again.
And it can be that Austin powers line of like as long as, you know, you can still grab a lady's
shapely behind. I'll be sound as a pound or whatever.
Yes, you just comes back and he walks into like Stan alive or whatever, you know,
kisses a picture of Trump in his wallet, whatever the gags are.
Yeah, and then realizes that that's not going to be what this is, you know,
and that's the thing, dude.
They won't have him kiss a picture of Trump because they're so fucking scared.
Well, they're rooting for shut the fuck up.
It's right.
Some characters God damn it, man.
We want we weren't rooting for John Lerichette to to finger
typist clerks in the original night court.
We were shocked by the behavior, but shock leads to laughter.
That's what happens.
So or have him come back now as a widow and he's like, he's like the attic.
He's like the food addict in the in the in the cookie store.
Yeah.
And he can't act on any of these whims anymore.
I just, and he's desperately trying to not hit on women at work.
Even if you reeled it back and made it like he just can't flirt with women.
Yeah, that's funny.
Like that's something.
There's a conf, anything, anything.
Yeah, it's terrible.
All right.
I'm going to refill my coffee while you do your next one.
Fair enough.
I need those other cup of coffee.
I saw a picture called the, you know what, I got a shout out for Joe here.
13 lives.
We got the screener.
We made fun of it for its reviews.
We said, why are they treating this like some sort of Oscar candidate?
The reason they're doing so is because it's a good movie.
It's the kind of movie that used to routinely get nominated for Oscars and win Oscars.
It's a story about human bravery and triumph in the face of extreme danger and adversity.
I like to quite a bit.
And Joe, the cave sets were unnervingly realistic.
They really were.
But it's a true story and I have heard the documentary about it is amazing.
I have not seen it, but it is the story about the group of, I believe the documentary is called the rescue.
And I'm going to watch that too, but it's 12.
I don't know about 12, but a group of Thai boys, a soccer team that goes down to explore a cave and get stuck with their coach.
It was big nationwide news.
If you heard about it, it's probably because Elon Musk preferred to one of the rescuers as a pedophile.
Because he didn't want to use Elon Musk's submarine that he had made to rescue the boys.
He thought that might be stupid.
So he said, well, we know why you're looking for these boys in the Thai cave.
Really, not Elon Musk's finest moment, although there aren't many at this point.
The kids are stuck.
They call in to British guys who are known for their cave diving skills played by Colin Farrell and Visual Mortensen.
Of course, I love those actors, Farrell.
I think is one of the most interesting actors working today.
But when they are together, like they have just this great camaraderie.
And that's what Ron Howard does really well.
He gets no credit because he is a truly a faceless, almost anonymous director.
He has no style to speak of, but he knows how to make you care about situations.
He knows how to get you to immediately believe that a group of people are friends working for a common goal.
Apollo 13 comes to mind or back draft or you know, he's good with actors because he's an actor himself.
I loved all the performances in this movie.
I really cared about it.
I didn't know how it ended to be honest.
That's just me not paying attention to the news, I guess, but I found it very suspenseful.
I'm excited to watch the documentary.
And it's worth a watch. It's on Amazon Prime.
So you've got it, whether you know it or not, I thought it was a really exciting kind of true life drama and I enjoyed it.
All right.
Second on my list is a show that I don't love, but that I liked.
Yes.
So we go hate to like and to love.
That 90s show, you know, I wasn't the biggest that 70s show fan in the world, but I like the show and I enjoyed it.
Never seen an episode, oddly enough.
It was funny. It's a funny show.
Like, you know, you go back and you watch it like there's a reason so many stars were spawned out of it, but like particularly.
Kutcher, Kutcher is excellent on it. He's fucking great.
Kuhner is awesome on it.
And then the two, the main kid, what's his name and the main girl, the redhead from orange is the new black prep palm.
Yeah.
More prep palm, Wilmer Val Dorena.
He's really good on it.
And what's his name, the main kid?
I want to say ho for great.
Oh, yeah, to for great.
Yeah.
And then the parents are awesome.
And then the entire cast would Smith the entire cast they were the parents are awesome.
The entire cast the original shows it's it's an it's an everybody loves Raymond style cast where you're like, man, everybody really brings their A game and they do.
They do their job like and they get it done.
And they and and again, very carved out characters.
That 90 show did not sound interesting to me a reboot centering on the grandparents.
I was like, what? I don't get it.
But I watched the first episode.
Tofer and Laura come back in the first episode with their daughter to visit their grandparents.
The daughter is sort of a square kid.
She meets the next door neighbor who's very cool and takes a liking to her.
She wants her chance to finally have a great summer and make the friends that she'll have for a lifetime like her parents did.
So she ends up staying at her grandparents house for the rest of the summer.
And that's the setup for the show.
And then we see the others and cameos.
Coach, Kunis and all the first episode grace tofer and prep on are in a lot of it.
Yeah.
And then to put your and Kunis show up at the end.
And it's awesome. Like when there's a kid in the whole first episode,
who's like the good looking kid in the group.
And he's funny. Like he's, you know, he does this thing where he's like,
he's like, I forget he does this thing where he looks into a woman's eyes and he's like,
hey there, whatever, I forget what the what the gag was.
But it was funny. And like he does it to the grandmom at one point.
And she said, what is wrong with you?
And at the end, Kurtwood Smith is like, who the hell are you?
And the kids like, I'm so and so, so and so Kelso and the audience cheers because they're like,
oh my God, it's Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis's kid.
Right.
Through the backdoor Kutcher comes in and he's like, what's up?
And like the place goes crazy and you're like, it's like a really fun cameo.
And then Kunis comes in and yells at him. It was funny.
Apparently prep on comes back for like three more episodes.
Grace is only in the one.
Masterson is obviously
and Fezes in it. Fezes and in the first episode.
But he's in this series because he owns a hair salon in the neighborhood now.
Oh, and Tommy Chong comes back.
Was this character gay, Wilmer Valderama?
Now, he dated Mila Kunis at one point, but it was always sort of
ambiguous, I guess.
Yeah, you know, it was like Warren Beatty and shampoo where he seems gay,
but he actually is fucking everybody.
Yeah, so anyway,
is it an awesome show?
No, but it does all the things a sitcom is supposed to do.
It carves our characters.
It has a storyline that makes sense.
It creates tension and drama amongst the comedy.
So you give a shit.
And most importantly, it feels like a continuation of the original show.
It looks like the original show.
It's shot like the original show.
And it has the edge and humor of the original show.
One at the plot point of the kids in the first episode is them trying to get a
keg as underage kids.
It's like, thank you.
Right.
Do something that is real, that is edgy, that people can relate to.
Like so I think it was a really, really solid effort.
You know, I'll eventually watch the rest of the season, but
surprising, I thought it was going to suck.
And I actually enjoyed it.
And I was like, this is this is what this should be.
So my hat's off to them.
I saw Bullworth, which I had not seen since the theater.
You want to talk about a different time.
Holy Lord, this movie, I remember being deeply controversial,
even when it came out in 1998, when anything goes or anything went.
This was controversial then.
It would simply not be released now.
It is Warren Beatty.
He's a senator.
He is depressed, miserable.
He starts off the movie, you know, clearly just kind of unhinged and depressed.
This is the best I've ever seen, Warren Beatty.
And I just never like him as an actor. I don't find him compelling.
Right.
I do think Nicholson should have played this part
and you have an all -time comedy classic.
But I like it supposed to be Nicholson.
No, but he always conceived it for himself.
But I would always take anyone over Beatty.
I mean, he's just not a charismatic enough guy for me personally.
So save that thought and make a note of it.
Yes, because we want to do this episode where we recast iconic roles.
Yes, we will do so.
Then that's a good one for it.
Anyway, it is.
That said, I think Beatty is really good in this.
The premise is he hires a man to kill him so that his daughter will get the insurance policy.
It's the same set up as short time with Devnie Coleman.
He knows that a suicide would void the policy.
So he wants to kill himself, but he just hires somebody to assassinate him.
He gets completely fucked up drunk, goes to this campaign event,
and just starts...
He's talking to a group of people at a black church
and they're like, why do you make us these empty promises?
This is what the trailer was, too.
We don't understand the politicians promise us.
And he's like, no, because you're black.
We don't give a shit.
We come down here. We take a few pictures.
We don't give a shit about black people you're getting.
And just starts answering all the questions very honestly.
And with the amount of lies we're subjected to now in politics currently,
it does seem like we're at an all time high.
But wow, it's shocking.
I can't call it refreshing, per se.
But it just felt like a movie that is alive, it's got a pulse to it.
Then he starts rapping.
Yeah, the rappers.
That's where things get problematic to say at least.
I mean, he's rapping.
He's not as terrible at it as you'd think.
But he's rapping about political issues.
It's sometimes lying to line.
It'll be funny and crazy.
And the next line will be so corny.
It makes you want to rip your ears off.
But it all kind of works.
He starts dressing like a rapper.
The soundtrack is like, it's like Warren Beatty running down the street with NWA blasting.
It's just, it's an insane movie.
It's truly insane.
The supporting cast is exactly who you'd want for a movie like this.
You got Jack Warden as the right hand man running around.
I texted Joe Jack Warden has never walked into a movie and not said,
Joe Dorosa, you old son of a bitch, how the hell are you?
He says it to everyone in every movie.
It's Paul Servino.
It's Oliver Platte.
It's Don Cheetle.
It's Halle Berry so hot that I thought I was going to have to take a break at some point.
All right, take it easy.
Unbelievable.
I'm not allowed to say Halle Berry is a beautiful woman.
Take it easy.
Well, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you can say that.
I didn't want to hear the details of what the break would entail.
Joe, you're so grossed out by my sexuality and I don't understand.
It's beautiful.
It's passionate.
It's powerful.
I got to say it's so far from a perfect movie that you can't like rave about it.
But man, when it's working, there's nothing else like this movie.
It's crazy.
I think it might be one of Warren Beatty's finest hours.
And then when I read up on Wikipedia about it, Obama apparently used to say all the time,
God, damn it.
I would just love to go bullworth on these mother.
Yeah.
I saw that too.
He dreamed about it.
And you can sense that when you watch Obama, he wants to tell you the truth.
Even when he's just doing his best version of it, at least he wants to.
And that's what I really, really loved about this movie is that if politicians did this,
they would be tremendously successful.
They just can't.
And that's sort of the beauty of the movie.
Trump is sort of the evil version of going bullworth and it worked.
Anything different from the status quo will work.
But people just don't try it because of how conservative most of the country is.
But I don't know.
It's to me, it was really funny, really surprising, really interesting.
And it's definitely the only movie that ends with Halle Berry telling Warren Beatty that he is her N word.
That is the final line of bullworth.
She kisses him.
He's 65 years older than her.
She kisses him and says, you're my N word credits.
Rent that you can't find it.
It's honestly not on Blu -ray, which for a movie to not be on Blu -ray,
that this was nominated for multiple Oscars, screenplay and other awards.
The funniest thing I learned was that Beatty showed it to this legendary dude.
Who's the fuck?
Joe, why are we, why do we forget things now?
Anyway, it's this legendary black guy you would know his name.
I'm going to find him and get back to you when Joe's talking about his next thing.
But Beatty showed it.
No, no, no, not an actor.
I'll find, I feel bad. I don't know his name, but I'll find it.
He showed, Beatty showed him the movie because he said, I think I'm just going to take the financial hit and not release this thing.
Beatty was such so scared to release it because he's like, I just think that this is too fucked up.
Cornell West, sorry.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Famous professor. He's in the Matrix sequel.
Anyway, he was like, I don't think I can release this and he asked Cornell West and he said,
look, this thing's wild, but it needs to be seen.
I think this is really impressive and you should bring it out.
But imagine a movie now where people were that scared to even release it.
Like, there's something exciting about it.
You can rent it on Amazon Prime. It looks like dog shit, but it's the only way to see it.
I recommended highly.
My final entry.
That was your third, right? Yes.
Yeah, my final is a TV show that I loved.
And again, surprised, thought it was going to be kind of a mild, I roll or were passable at best.
I don't know why I thought that because I'm a big fan of the franchise.
But for some reason, I just didn't think it was going to be good.
I was 100 % wrong.
I finally started watching Chuckie.
It is awesome. Man, it is awesome.
It is a great, great, great horror show picks up and way to watch.
Yeah, picks up shortly after Cult of Chuckie.
And God, man, I got to hand it to
Is it Don Mancini? Right?
Yeah, that's done. Yeah, right.
I got to hand it to that guy as this goes.
Because at first you're just like, oh, is it going to just be like a new Chuckie story?
As it goes, it's like, no, no, we're going to tie in the entire franchise.
Everybody's going to come back and like, and the fucking plates this guy is spinning with these story lines
That started going sideways in the fourth movie with with bride of Chuckie where no in the fifth movie
See of Chuckie where the Tiffany doll spirit wants to go literally into Jennifer Tilly's body.
I forgot about that.
Yeah, and the reason Jennifer Tilly is the human form of Tiffany is because
She literally possessed Jennifer Tilly's body.
Dude, he does not miss one detail of anything that was set up in any previous Chuckie movie.
He brings in footage from the old movies to to to let you know what the fuck is going on.
And yet this still works as its own entity.
Even if you never saw any of that, you would be like, okay, that's weird.
I get it though. That's what's going on.
The new characters are great.
The kids are great.
The main character is a gay teenager who is bullied by his father for being gay.
And is bullied by his high school mates, not necessarily for being gay, but for what some of them it is for that.
And then others, it's just because they think he's weird.
And he's the kid that gets Chuckie.
And when Chuckie finally springs to life and kills the first person, you're, you're excited.
You're rooting for Chuckie because it's on, it's in the honor and defense of this kid that's getting shit for no reason.
And then, and then as it goes, it starts to turn and the kid realizes like Chuckie's not an ally.
This is bad.
The characters are written real.
The high school students are written real.
It's edgy as hell.
Sci -fi did bleep out a moment where Chuckie calls a high school girl a cunt.
I guess they thought that was too far.
What's on shutter, isn't it?
It's on sci -fi originally and now it's on peacock.
I think it's, I think it's also on shutter.
It may be.
It's just a, it was weird that that was, they were like, well, that's too much.
I mean, there's so much worse in this thing.
But, um, but, uh, it's awesome, man.
It's just fucking awesome.
Fiona Dorif in it, playing not just the character she played in Colt and Curse of Chuckie,
playing in prosthetics, the young version of Charles Lee Ray.
They, they made her look like her dad and she plays in the flashbacks.
The human version of Charles Lee Ray when he's like in his 20s.
It's fucking nuts, dude, till he's back.
Everybody comes back.
The original fucking kid from the first movie comes back like as Andy Barclay.
It's awesome.
It is fucking awesome.
The kills are insane.
They're over the top, but they're, they're great.
And I got to tell you, man, there is almost no humor in this thing.
Like I thought it was going to be like a comedic kind of romp.
It's not funny at all.
It is a dark show.
It's great.
Watch it.
It's so worth watching.
And I'm curious to see how I've seen some stills from later seasons.
And I'm like, clearly this gets fucking bonkers.
I can't wait to know idea what happens.
So anyway, watch Chuckie.
So get let's get to the movie though.
We're we're chugging along here.
Let's do it.
The movie is the menu, a black comedy, you know, horror is sort of pushing it.
There's not really like horrific elements to it, but sort of if it's got
the feeling kind of of a a tales from the dark side kind of thing to me,
that kind of a tongue in cheek sort of satiric dark comedy that gets a little
gory, a little bloody, a little weird.
But the plot is this a bunch of very snobby foodies.
Some of them like douchey finance bros, one guy who's basically just a foodie
himself, Nicholas Holt, who's like, you know, it's sort of the food seems to
almost awaken a demon in him.
Judith light from who's the boss.
You know, there's there's people who you you realize throughout the movie all
have secrets, all have bad things that they have done.
They are brought to an island by a very wealthy chef.
They sign up, well, they sign up for it.
It's an exclusive dinner, right, played by Ray Fiennes, who was great in the movie.
Ray finds, excuse me, even though I know his name, I still say a rock.
And that's basically it.
He's giving them all this, this very fancy meal.
And then you learn as it goes on that he actually has sort of ulterior motives.
You got John like wasamo, who's in everything nowadays.
He's great.
He's playing like an Adam Sandler type, basically, who that was the funniest scene of the movie
to me is when Ray Fiennes explains why he brought him there because he saw his movie, Mr.
Sunshine and he did not find it.
Haging Mr.
Docter Sunshine.
Yeah, it's clearly like patch atoms is what the movie's supposed to I did not find the antics
of Dr. Sunshine amusing thought that was very funny.
But yeah, so that you find out they're all there because of well, you find that they're all there because they want to be there.
But then you find out that they're all there and being subjected to something very sinister because of their past deeds.
And it's clear that Ray Fiennes is playing to kill all of them.
The first twist comes when he brings one of his chefs out in front of them.
His sous chef out in front of him and his and he says for our next course, our sous chef so and so is going to present.
A dish he's been working on and he berates the sous chef and says you will never be as good as me will you and the guy goes no and whatever and he goes.
And you accept that you're just not as good and he goes and the sous chef accepts all this and starts crying.
And then Ray Fiennes says I present to you his dish.
This course is called the mess because every course has a name and the guy blows his brains out and you're like OK, something terrible is happening here obviously.
The people are trapped for various reasons they can't really get off of the island once they're there.
And there's one character played by the oh my god Anna, Anna, Anna Taylor joy.
Yeah.
Who Ray Fiennes repeatedly corners and says you don't belong here, you're messing everything up and you don't really understand why until the plot unravels and things are revealed.
But she also is the only person there that's not impressed with any of the food she's like this is all pretentious bullshit this sucks.
I'm not into it blah blah blah blah blah blah yeah.
And and and eventually becomes apparent that Ray Fiennes plans on killing everybody there including himself and his staff.
But why?
Well, why?
My takeaway was that this was a big very, very well done and executed.
No pun intended commentary on internet culture.
And this is what it is.
It's about the it's about hero worship.
It's about the sick of fans.
It's about people doing things for status instead of quality.
People doing people choosing to be next to other people they don't care about.
Or have any real connection to it's just about what it means to for them to put themselves on display and say look at me.
I thought it was really, really well done and what you eventually learn is that Anna Taylor joy's character is not.
It's in the beginning you think she's Nicholas Holtz girlfriend.
And then you realize she's not she's actually an escort.
Who's there in the last minute because his girlfriend didn't want to go dumped him and then he brought her.
They were knowing full well that she would die.
Well, yeah, Nicholas, well, Nicholas helps the only character.
That knows it's eventually revealed that this that there's a plan for him to die that for all of them to die.
Because Nicholas Holtz character sort of represents the you know the parasite fan right now who will do anything to be basking in the glory of this person he's obsessed with.
Including dying for them because you know it means he's the best and he's part of the scene and all this stuff when he's got no real talent or ability to do it himself.
But anyway, Ray finds says to her you realize she's not she's screwing up the night because she's not supposed to be there.
And she's not there out of any self indulgent for any self indulgent reasons.
She's there just by chance.
And then she's also a member of the service industry.
And Ray finds is like the you're fucking this up which eventually sort of leads to her dismissal from the she doesn't die everybody else does.
But you know it's kind of hard to to to regurgitate every detail of this movie and why the commentary is so scathing and so sharp and so funny.
But it's all there when you watch it.
It's all there and it's very well done.
It's airtight in my opinion it's a 90 minute script that was film.
Yeah.
There's not a stone unturned in the script.
There's not one thing where you could go back and go yeah, but this didn't make any sense.
Anything that was a little puzzling to you.
If you think about it for a few minutes, you're like, oh wait, oh that's that's why she died too.
Yeah, it's almost entirely done.
They shot it like a play with all these actors just having to sit in the background of other people scenes, you know, which I think really is effective.
I think this would be an awesome play.
And maybe they'll do it as such, but it's it's all about the script and the acting, you know, it's not a real show we film making exercise.
It's just basically a really good story really well told.
It's a little ludicrous when you sit and think about it like them, you know, printing out pictures of people's affairs on tortillas and stuff like that.
It's a little goofy at times.
The smore necklaces he makes them wear when he's going to set them on fire or whatever, but it all just works.
It's like the tone is a little left the center at times, but it never goes too big and broad and crazy.
It's a very like just a really controlled well written well acted script.
The fact that it's getting Oscar attention, I think it's just because we're in this place now where movies are absolute shit.
I don't think it's like an Oscar movie per se, but it's really entertaining.
It's on HBO Max.
I haven't talked to anybody who was like this movie sucks.
It's a cool movie for sure.
I liked it a lot.
Yeah, I, I thought it was, I didn't know it was getting Oscar attention.
I think it's, I don't know if I agree or disagree with that.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I think in a, I think in a different climate, this probably would not have had the star power.
It doesn't it.
I don't think, you know, yeah.
I was in a stone originally in the, and the Taylor joy role.
And it was originally Alexander pain directing it.
Oh, wow.
But I think everything worked out for the best.
I mean, it's, it's just a well made solid picture.
I actually saw it twice.
I saw it way too late at the theater.
And then I watched it again in HBO Max.
And, you know, I'm with Joe.
It's the kind of thing where there's no loose ends hanging out.
It's, it's, it's, if you're going to have the story be front and center, you got to make the story work.
And they really did.
They went above and beyond.
Yeah, I thought.
And again, I love anything that's a scathing commentary on people like this.
Yeah, it's becoming a big subgenre of horror is eat the rich horror.
You know, there's a lot of that going on right now.
Well, it's eat the rich, but then it's also just sick of fans.
Yeah.
And I personally took way more, I took way more from it than than the rich commentary.
I took way more from it where it was just like, no, the rich are just an easy.
It's a easy demographic to, to, to represent all of these awful personality types.
We see online every day.
Yeah.
Because in my opinion, the chef is the entertainer or the brand or the whatever.
And then all of these people are different types of people on Instagram.
Like that's kind of how I took it.
And, and you know, I think that's in there, whether that's supposed to be what it is or not, it manages to do that.
But I, but that also is a thing.
You know, in our next movie, we're going to talk about we're going to do sick on the next episode.
That's a, that's a whole thing about, you know, the wild COVID argument personalities and everything.
All of this is sort of going back to what we see on the internet every day, which I guess is just reality and what we live in.
But, yeah, it's cool.
You know, like there's all these documentaries and essays written about how the horror of the 70s was a reaction to Vietnam.
And, and, you know, Texas Chainsaws, a reaction to Vietnam and stuff.
I think 10, 20 years from now, people are going to look at the horror of this time and just talk about how it's going after these targets.
But also, you know, in the case of sick, it's one of the only movies about COVID.
That's not a documentary.
It's like horror is usually the first to tackle these difficult subjects because they can they can just kind of have some fun with it and make it crazy.
And point out how insane the world has become.
So I'm enjoying this, this time of horror where it's actually got targets and is hitting them really effectively, I think.
And we'll be back with sick folks.
Two hogs up for the menu.
And we'll be back with sick.
Joe, Rosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Check out Joey Roses in New York open seven days a week 11 30 a .m.
Joey Roses NYC .com.
And I am on tour like a motherfucker.
We got the residency here in New York at the Crane Theater once a month doing I never promised you a Rose Garden.
Come check that out.
Next one is February 14th Valentine's Day.
We also have dates in March after that.
And then I'm on the road like crazy.
One more New York show to plug in evening with kooge and friends kooge the great Instagram food influencer and my friend.
Me him and Michael rap report doing a roundtable discussion about food.
And then.
That'll be at city winery February I think it's eighth and then and then the road is just nonstop coming up.
Jota Rosa info .com to see me in a city near you.
Boy, it makes me sound like I have nothing going on.
I am the Patrick wall at Twitter and Instagram and the miss patch show season three scheduled for an April release.
I'm sorry season four scheduled for an April release.
Thank you all very much.
We'll be back with sick, which is available on the peacock talk soon.