I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
This is the pod where you get the bod.
And by the bod I mean patty walsh in myself bringing you the hard muscles, the tight curves and the juicy buns.
Oh wow.
Would you agree?
I wouldn't disagree.
I don't blame you baby.
We bring a lot of juicy buns to the table.
So butter them up and have a bite.
How are you Pat?
I'm alright.
Today's film is Annabelle Crayachone.
No, no, comes home.
Cajun man used to say.
Really?
It's Annabelle comes home as the newer.
Annabelle comes home as Cajun man used to say.
Yep.
Yeah, so I haven't seen any of the Annabels except this one.
I have seen the conjuring in the conjuring too.
I have not seen the nun or the nun too.
The nun, the nun too is not out yet.
It will be.
The nun is terrible.
Okay.
And then are there any other films in the conjuring averse?
I personally like to fold in all of the Patrick Wilson films.
Okay.
It's just a little fun game I play with myself.
So I'll pretend that little children is basically a fan fiction conjuring film.
Hard candy.
Hard candy I put in there.
Watch the girls episode where she fucks Lena Dunham.
Yeah, the show where he's the doctor on TV.
I pretend that he ran away from the conjuring universe to become a doctor.
What show is that?
I think it was called the doctor or the good doctor or something like that.
Now let me ask.
I guess it's only two.
Hard candy and little children.
But this guy does a lot of pedophilia movies.
Yeah.
Well, he's not a pedophile and little children.
Right. It's Jack Erohaling.
Yeah.
So no, not really, I guess.
And tense picture.
He does a lot of movies with little children in them.
Yeah.
And he fucked Lena Dunham, who was 25 years his junior in that picture.
That show.
No, he's not that much older than Lena Dunham.
Is he?
I bet.
Well, who knows.
But at the time, I think she was 22 and he was a 40 -something -year -old man.
Which is legal, I guess, folks.
It's 100 % legal.
I didn't say it wasn't.
There's no I guess.
It's legal.
You're allowed to do that.
I didn't say it wasn't.
And you're getting out of the defensive.
I think the authorities should give him credit for banging Lena Dunham.
Patrick Wilson is probably older than we think.
He just is blessed with great genes.
I find him a fairly dull actor.
I like him all right.
But I think he's another one.
I'm like, he's another Tom Arnold to me.
I'm like, who did this guy catch doing what?
Yeah.
How was he getting this past and this fucking Jesus?
Because you got?
He's adequate.
You know.
You got next to him.
I always want to call her Fomka Johnson, but that's not her name.
He's nearly 50 years old.
Okay.
What's the tells her name?
God damn it.
The girl from this movie?
Yeah.
The way of Farminga.
Vera Farminga.
I always want to call her one of my favorite horror films of recent years.
Orphan, which I thought was incredible.
Vera Farminga is in this thing.
And as far as I'm concerned, connect circles around this guy.
Farminga is a strange thing.
I mean, she blasted onto the scene with departed.
She had a good little indie career going.
And then she was just like, all right.
I'll do these horror movies forever.
It's strange.
Well, that's kind of what Wilson did too.
Because he was doing the indie flicks.
Yeah.
And he got a lot of stage or FaceTime rather from watchmen, I guess.
Right.
And the good doctor.
Or whatever the hell.
I think you're making that up.
I don't know.
He was in a show where he played a doctor.
Farminga was down to the bone.
Was her big critically acclaimed performance.
And I guess she's gone back and forth.
She's been running scared, which is a great Paul Walker picture.
Really entertaining.
Incredible movie.
I thought the movie was a blast.
What?
Speaking of pedophiles.
That scene where they go into the pedophiles house is such an amazing sequence.
The one where he looks like Freddie within the shadow.
Oh, God.
I thought the movie was really fun.
That's a true B movie that they don't make anymore.
I loved it.
I hated it.
All right.
And I hate you right now.
I don't mean I was got a lot of affection.
I mean, I think a lot of people like that movie.
I take it back.
I enjoyed it.
About hating you.
I mean, not the movie.
And she was the star of Bates Motel.
Let's not forget.
Yes.
Which was a decent show.
I dropped out at some point, but it was decent.
I mean, I got to tell you.
What I always thought the Hitchcock psycho classic was missing was a B storyline about pot dealers
in the small town.
Yeah.
That's about where I dropped out.
Now, Joe, I'm not seeing anything about a doctor.
He played the good wife.
Maybe it was called a gifted man.
That's it.
Dr. Michael Holt.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right.
Fair enough.
Thank you.
Was that CBS?
The good doctor was about a boy doctor.
Yes.
People love shows about a boy doctor.
I don't get watching any shows.
But I've never seen any show about doctors, except Grey's Anatomy, which I love the first few seasons of.
I guess I get it.
It's a case of the week.
You know, you get a new guy with a pot cut sticking out of his head or whatever.
For a while, I was pitching an hour drama about Dr. Teath from the Muppets.
I'd watch that.
It was about his private practice off the set of the Muppet Show.
Yeah.
They said nobody would buy it.
I would have bought it.
Yeah.
Dr. House MD, of course.
I've never seen that show either.
I kind of wanted to do like, remember how I got Asner?
Did the dramatic spin off a Mary Tyler Moore?
Yeah.
I wanted to do that with Dr. Teath.
Okay.
And they wouldn't.
They wouldn't buy it.
Dr. Teath, not the most fully fleshed out of the Muppets.
So you've got a lot of room to work with his backstory.
Yeah.
How did he get into the Muppets?
Why did he leave private practice to do the Muppets?
What's the story that before?
Did you know?
I think he was the inspiration for Dr. John, who just passed away.
One of my least favorite musicians of all time.
I'm not a fan of Dr. John.
The audacity of the name.
He's saying the blossom theme.
In my opinion, nation.
The sun is gonna show.
I hate that style.
Also, you're white.
Like I hate that shit.
Yeah, I hate it.
Like you're essentially doing black voice.
And I find that gross.
A lot of young white women do that.
And I hate it as well.
Dr. John is the original Iggy Azalea.
Exactly.
My story line.
Just so you know, my storyline with Dr. Teath is he lost a young child
on the operating table.
And he decided he couldn't do it anymore.
Okay.
And then he started a band and joined the Muppets.
All right.
Could he have...
That would be your series finale.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, and you can have cameos from the...
So like, they're like, hey, do you work on animals at all?
And he's like, no, I'm a human doctor.
And they're like, what if it's...
Your old friend, Ralph.
And they bring in the dog, Ralph, to work on.
And he's got a heart attack.
Right.
He...
Ralph is what brings him into the Muppets.
Yeah.
Because they have a falling out.
Right.
Early in the series.
And then the amends is him joining the Muppets.
By the end of the pilot, it's just like the Blues Brothers,
where they're trying to find...
Put the old band back together.
And you've completely abandoned the hospital.
And it's just the Muppet band going on the road again.
Animals behind the drums.
Animal ODs in the season finale.
Yeah.
You have a young, straight -laced animal as an orderly.
Animals like...
You learn what goes wrong with him, you know?
They're like, oh, we got someone else for you to meet.
And he's like, oh, it's not that crazy son of a bitch.
Animal, is it?
And then he comes out and he's like wearing a nice button up.
And his hair is parted neatly.
Exactly.
And it's like, holy shit, you got your stuff together.
And he's like, you know, I'm doing okay.
But by the end he relapses.
Yeah.
That's...
This is a good show.
I gotta be honest, I think I'm on to something to hear me.
No, I agree.
I mean, they made that Melissa McCarthy movie.
Why wouldn't they make this?
We need to watch that, by the way.
I...
Not with a gun to my fucking head.
There's nothing I hate more than dirty puppet movies.
I hated the Peter Jackson one.
That's one of my least favorite movies ever.
Meet the Feebles.
It almost made me vomit.
I think we've talked about it on the show.
I actually almost vomit it when I watched it.
The one that the Spider -Man guy did about the cops and you look stupid as shit.
What's that one?
I don't know.
It's one of the movies that guy did before cop car.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It's not a genre of people need to see.
I didn't like the new Muppets.
I mean, I liked having the Muppets back.
But I was just like, the thrill is gone.
Did you know the head writer of the new Muppets was the guy that wrote
anger management, the Charlie Sheen show or something?
And it was like, they're doing like gay and sex jokes in these...
Yeah.
It's like, what are you guys doing?
I know.
My favorite gift that I like to send out now is instead of a folks,
if I do a bad joke, I send out this gift that always makes me laugh.
But it's Fuzzy Bear.
It tells a joke into a microphone and goes like, eh?
Like, looks around.
And the microphone walks away.
I think I've sent it to you.
And if I haven't, you can expect it soon.
But he's like, you guys like that one of the microphones sneaks away from Fuzzy.
That's a great joke.
And that's a great Muppets joke.
I think the great Muppet Caper is one of the funniest movies of the 80s.
I think it's better than Muppet movie.
I think it's better than Takes Manhattan and Christmas.
I love it.
I don't remember it at all.
I don't remember this one.
Charles Groden for Christ's sake.
And he wants to fuck Miss Piggy.
Like, if you're not laughing already, I can't help you.
I don't, I saw that movie with my granddad in the theater.
That's my last recollection of the film.
The great Muppet Caper is start to finish hilarious.
And the songs are good.
And I love it.
I remember hating the Muppets take Manhattan as a kid because they do the whole
Kermit loses Gets Amnesia.
I'm like, I'm not here to watch this fucking frog think he's somebody else for two hours.
Yeah, I remember that.
I remember that.
Yeah.
Man, that drove me crazy.
I remember hating Superman 3 for that reason.
Well, Takes Manhattan gives you the amazing sequence at the end where like every Muppet in history is there for the wedding of Piggy and Kermit.
That's a real feat of puppetry, frankly, that you know, when I saw it as an adult, I was like, God, damn.
It's like great Muppet Caper.
They ride bikes.
Piggy and Kermit are riding bikes.
And they're like, how the fuck did you do that?
I still don't know how they did it.
Speaking of which, I'm real excited for this dark crystal prequel series.
People are thrilled I haven't seen the trailer.
I was never a big fan of the movie.
I preferred Labyrinth.
I'm gonna watch the series.
I'm excited.
The trailer looks pretty goddamn heavy.
Two things I'm worried about.
Okay.
I went on the Wikipedia page and I was reading up on the characters.
Huh?
And who's voicing them?
Two of the skecs, which are some of the scariest movie villains of all time.
I like a lot of the people that are voicing them.
And I like everybody that's voicing them.
What worries me is they got Keegan Michael Key voicing one of them.
I'm sure he's doing something interesting.
And Andy Sandberg voicing one of them.
Okay.
So my worry is that they're gonna have comic relief skecs.
That's my worry.
Please don't do that guys.
And I also read descriptions of the new skecs.
Yeah.
One of them is the wardrobe maker.
And one of them is the one that plans the banquets.
Also by the way, Harvey Firestein is voicing one of the skecs.
I like that.
So I'm like, I'm just a little worried that they're gonna do like some comedic.
Like, I've got to get the dinner party together.
Before we worship the crystal.
Oh, right.
I thought calling it skexies in the city was a step in the wrong direction personally.
But we'll see how it goes.
Hold on.
Let me digest that.
That was very good.
Thank you.
Let me just digest that.
No.
I mean, from what I've seen, it looks very grave and somber and serious.
Maybe they have a few comedic skecsies.
I don't know.
Well, I will say the review I saw from Comic Con because they showed the pilot.
But the people, I forget what channel I saw the review on, but they said they were like,
when the pilots started, they were like, I was a little worried that they had kind of gone too far in a kitty direction.
And they go, and then the woman goes, and then it took a hard dark turn.
And she's like, it is darker than the original.
It's dealing with some really heavy themes.
So it's apparently it's gonna be pretty dark.
All right.
I'm in.
And I have faith that it's not called a light crystal.
Yeah.
I was key.
I feel like I would do.
Sandberg's the one that really worried me.
Yeah.
But I mean, then again, I don't know.
Key and Peele did really, really good voice work in Toy Story 4, which I liked a lot.
How was it?
Was that the last one finally?
Well, three is the absolute perfect ending of the series.
Some of the other day was like, I don't know why they did a fourth.
Three was the perfect ending.
I'm like, you ever heard of money?
Of course, that's why they did it.
That's why they call it money.
Yes.
Four is super entertaining.
It's the least of the four.
It's the least of the three, I mean.
Kind of didn't have a ton of fanfare around it.
And I was like, it must have been one step too far.
It's a really good animated film.
It's just not as good as the other ones.
And three, in my opinion, is maybe the best animated movie I've ever made.
So, Ned Bady is that...
Did you see it?
You haven't seen any of my best.
No, I've never seen one of them.
I don't like those kinds of movies.
Ned Bady plays this pink teddy bear who turns out to be the biggest son of a bitch in the world.
And it's one of the greatest reveals...
If you want to talk about dark, like...
Which one is that?
That's three.
Toy Story 3, I was on the edge of my fucking seat, and I don't like cartoons.
But it's a great movie.
Four, I liked.
But the show is stolen by Key and Peel.
They are really funny as these two like carnival prize stuffed animals.
And they have these running gags in the film that are the only true laughout loud moments they were great in it.
You want to take us to the corner?
Let's take us there.
Oh, but first...
What?
What do you mean what?
Let's get on.
I'd like to drop this, I think.
I mean, I'm out.
You know, I was out two years ago.
But let's get on with the show.
And on every song I think I've done...
Just say it.
You can just say it.
And on with the Joe to the world.
All the boys and girls now.
Right?
Joe to the people in the deep blue sea.
The fishes.
There aren't people in the deep blue sea.
Oh, fishes, sorry.
They'd be drowning.
Unless they're mermaids.
Speaking of which, what's your take on the black little mermaid controversy?
Are you losing sleep over it?
I've been awake for days trying to come to a solution.
I love people getting upset that the little mermaid is black.
It's hilarious to me.
It's a wild, it's just...
Holy shit.
But I mean, here's the thing.
This has to stop from all sides.
These people getting upset is as ridiculous as when like...
Disabled people get upset that Brian Cranston plays a guy in a wheelchair.
It's like, everybody has to stop because it works from every angle.
If you're going to get furious that they don't have a drag queen playing Ursula
because Ursula was based on a drag queen,
then you can't get mad when the stupid -esque white guy is mad that Ariel isn't white.
It's the same fucking thing.
Stop, everybody.
Take a fucking breath and stop.
Agreed.
And for God's sakes, create some new fucking characters.
Please.
Stop just changing everybody's gender and ethnicity.
Create some new characters.
But these scumbags, sexist races, studio execs won't let it happen.
These people are not on your side.
Stop trying to get things done in Hollywood.
Start doing things independently.
Use the outlets that are there for us to use.
Create your own product.
Stop asking for permission from these fucks because they're racist.
They're sexist.
And all they're going to do is let you do something that's already been done a million fucking times before.
And that's the end of ghost busters.
And it's a shitty movie.
And it's all women.
And they think they're breaking ground.
They're not.
They should have made a movie that was great with those four great women.
Instead of just rehashing some old shit.
Thank you.
I agree.
And that's why I would like to shine a spotlight on a truly original film.
That's in cinemas right now.
The Lion King.
Which I didn't see.
What is this tear Disney song?
Now there's a lady in the tramp live action coming up.
They're just remaking every and not giving the writers anything.
The people who did the like the songs make these these old animated movies.
And they're using the songs.
The dialogue.
And giving the original people no credit.
It's nuts.
And you want to talk about super crazy.
The Lion King is being touted and pushed for Oscars as a live action film.
Everything in it.
Is a computer gen there's no humans in it.
It's computer generated.
So what are you talking about?
That's that's upsetting to me.
I went to see the Lion King.
Heather.
My wife saw the Lion King as a little kid and it was obsessed with it.
I saw it at a birthday party when I was 13 and I was obsessed with it.
And I was like, all right, let's check this out.
What it is.
Is word for word.
Beat for beat.
Song for song.
The exact same movie as the other Lion King.
Except instead of cartoon animals.
They are computer generated animals.
Okay.
And I guess now because they keep making shit loads of money.
We're just going to exume these projects every 20 years for the rest of our lives.
And is that deeply depressing?
Yes.
Does this Lion King kind of work?
Sure.
Because it's a story that already worked.
What is good about it?
James Earl Jones is back as Mufasa.
Just hearing his voice on the big screen is great.
For some reason.
And, you know, I don't know if I'm bothered by this or what's going on.
But all of the Lions are voiced by black actors.
I didn't understand that choice.
It's like their Lions.
Right.
Beyonce plays Nala.
She is the least effective member of the cast.
It just sounds like Beyonce reading Lions in her normal voice.
And she doesn't really work.
Also, they bring in Chihuatel Edeafore to play Scar.
And I love Chihuatel.
He's an amazing actor.
But he does not have the voice you need for a villain like Scar.
In the original, it was Jeremy Irons.
You know, one of the most sinister voices of all time.
Right.
There's a million people they could have got.
Benedict Cumberbatch would have been great.
I don't know, man.
It's just that a lot of these voices lack personality to me.
And the songs are not great because they're being sung by and large by non -performers.
Non -singers.
Beyonce's original song.
I would guess that she recorded it into her iPhone while driving to the studio.
It is not even a song.
It doesn't even register.
And it's the only new song in the picture.
Right.
That said, I like Donald Glover as Symba.
I like that.
They kind of made Symba a little more kind of cocky, kind of gave him a little more spunk in this one.
I liked that scene Steelers really are Seth Rogen.
And especially Billy Eitner as Timon and Pumba.
They're the only people who are like improving and doing new material.
And that stuff is really funny.
Visually, it's cool.
People's criticism about the eyes all being kind of dead and it having that polar express effect are true.
It just leaves you when it's done feeling kind of like I saw a movie.
You know, it wasn't as good as Favaro's previous attempt at this, the jungle book.
It's also like as with every other big director now, you got to say, you know, Favaro's a guy who really had an interesting voice when he started out his career
and is now just mounting these $400 million Disney reboots.
The man wrote Swingers.
I look forward to his Star Wars series coming out.
Sure.
But I have no interest in these Disney things that he's doing.
If you're a fan of the Lion King, you'll like it.
You're going to have the same complaints everybody else does.
But it works.
It works.
I saw a picture called Slay the Dragon.
Very interesting documentary.
I'm going to keep mine to two today.
By the way, it was clear when I said I wasn't saying the Lions should not have been played by black actors.
I'm saying, yeah, you were clear.
Why are all the Lions?
That's an odd choice to make.
And what are you saying with that choice?
I don't get it.
Nobody's saying anything.
All right.
They're just, yeah, you're clear.
It's clearly a conscious decision on their part and I don't get the reasoning behind it.
I think because they were all family, I guess.
I don't know.
All right.
Well, that makes sense.
Anyway, I saw a picture called Slay the Dragon.
Interesting documentary, great documentary about redistricting and gerrymandering in Michigan and Wisconsin.
This must have been at the, at the Traverse City McCormore.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to give away the ending because that's what to me made the film most interesting.
But basically what happened in this thing is the, it's about the current state of the,
or the most recent state of the districts in those two states as they were designed by the Republican party.
So basically, they can draw such specific district lines that they can rig the election basically where they can't, they can't lose.
The part, of course, that is glazed over in this documentary, as is in most things from this perspective,
is that the Democrats did the same fucking thing in the 80s when they were in power.
That Reagan was railing against and, you know, and then the Republicans did it.
So look, it kind of seems just kind of like par for the course in politics, as far as I can understand.
But I will say this, the point of the movie was not right versus left.
It was about people, not voters, not politicians, I think is the movement's name.
And one woman who was interested in changing this, or fighting this practice, and saying this practice just shouldn't exist.
It started a thing on Facebook. It built from Facebook. It grew to 100 ,000 people.
And slowly but surely, step by step with all odds against her, she got this thing on the ballot as a ballot proposal.
It passed, and now, and it went to a vote, and Jerry Mandering has been made illegal in Michigan.
They're not allowed to do anymore.
So it is really the first thing I have ever seen that gave me any faith whatsoever in the voting process.
It was the first time I ever thought, oh, maybe, maybe there is something to this.
Maybe you can make a slight change.
I don't know, maybe, maybe not.
But it was a really, I would say, riveting documentary.
And it did anger me with the Republican Party, with what they were doing, with the districting in those two states, or at least made me angered with those people in the party that were doing that.
But again, I would have liked to have seen a little more light shed on what it was like prior to that.
But whatever, I guess that really doesn't matter.
It's just at the end of the day about this is a shitty practice, and they got it outlawed, which is pretty fucking impressive.
So good documentary.
And not as heavy as you'd think.
Like it's actually an enjoyable watch.
It's not like it's all dreary and dread and doom and everything.
All right.
I rewatched a picture that I am.
I remember liking a great deal, and now I am prepared to put it on perhaps my all time favorite list, sexy beast.
You seen this thing?
Yes, a long time ago.
Watch it again.
It's a god damn classic directed by Jonathan Glazer.
I mean, holy shit.
Maybe just because I got a little older or something, I liked it more.
It came out.
I sort of filed it along with all the other sort of pulp fiction ripoffs.
It's not that it's its own thing.
Ben Kingsley should have not only won best supporting actor, but been given his own new award generated just for him.
Ben Kingsley is an actor.
I'm sort of indifferent too.
I love him in Schindler's list, of course, where he did win.
But my god, he's amazing in this.
And he's never really in this mode.
He is like a unhinged Falmouth psychopath in this movie.
One of the most evil characters in film history, Don Logan.
My god, he's amazing.
Ray Winstone is amazing in the lead role.
And Ian McShane in a pre -deadwood role, I believe, is equally great.
Those are three badass fucking actors.
They are at the top of their game.
The movie is stylish as hell.
I give it an easy five stars.
If you've never seen sexy beast, see it.
If you've seen it, watch it again.
I'm very glad I did.
Because in my mind, it was a pretty good crime thriller.
And I watched it twice in a weekend.
I thought it was amazing.
I began watching, finally, Fossy Verdin.
Good show.
They finally put it on Hulu.
So I've been watching it.
Fucking amazing.
Yeah, I like the lot.
You want to talk about a tour de force.
Michelle Williams and Sam Rockwell just bringing it to the dance.
Yeah.
The acting coming out of these two is unfuckin believable, man.
Michelle Williams is one of our best actresses.
She's fucking incredible.
When I see a clip of her in Manchester by the sea, my eyes well off.
Just that clip of her talking to him by the bridge there.
She is fucking incredible.
Sam Rockwell has long been my favorite contemporary actor.
Sure.
This only takes it a step further.
I love this fucking show.
I haven't finished it yet.
Awesome.
Just awesome.
And I love seeing stuff from that time period with brassy broads
and smoking guys.
So you've got to watch feud too with Jessica Lang.
Yeah, I'd like to see that.
Fued is fantastic.
And Sarandon.
But I enjoy that period of the theater.
And it's kind of like back when it was a scene.
Sure.
Everybody's fucking and smoking and drinking.
And you haven't seen all that jazz, right?
Which I talked about on here.
I saw it a long time ago.
Okay.
I have to rewatch it.
I had the DVD.
It's great.
Got rid of it.
I got the criteria.
If you want to borrow it.
All right.
Stop bragging.
It's not a big waving contest.
I'm just saying.
Anyway, this thing, every actor in this thing, by the way,
is hitting a grand slam.
Paul Reiser is fantastic in it.
It's a great cast.
Reiser.
He plays the producer.
Oh, he's out of it immediately.
But yeah, I remember him being in it.
What have I done for you?
I've done two things.
I hide you and I haven't fired you yet.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, he's great at it.
Everybody is fantastic in this show.
But of course, the driving force is Williams and Rockwell.
And I mean, just the two of them.
They're doing these scenes.
And you're just like, Jesus Christ, man.
Yeah.
Put these two in a Broadway show.
Like, I want to see them put these two in True West.
Yeah.
Something with two people.
Right.
Where they just get to chew it up, man.
But anyway, awesome, awesome, awesome.
It's also the kind of performance where like if I was Sam Rockwell's wife,
the delightful Leslie Bibb.
Yeah.
I would be like, hey, maybe I'll be on set for this one.
Like they bring so much passion to it, it gets a little uncomfortable.
I would imagine for the spouse.
Are Bibb and Rock married?
They have been for some time.
I think it's an adorable couple.
What's Bibb been in?
Bibb was Ferrell's wife in Telodega nights.
That's right.
She's a real gorgeous blonde lady.
Yeah.
And a good actress.
No, she is.
I just don't remember what she was in.
So anyway, watch Fossy Verden.
Watch it.
It is a great show.
I mean, looking up Bob Fossy interviews and Verden,
Gwen Verden interviews and just seeing...
Well, when you look them up, it makes the performances all the better.
Because it wouldn't matter if they were great imitations.
But they are that too.
They're...
It's just an awesome...
And the makeup is unfuckin' real in this thing.
Yeah.
It's like an Oscar level biopic in eight episodes.
And it's on FOX.
FX.
Or FX.
For me, that's what I really...
I mean, I like a lot of FX and stuff.
But this and feud where they're playing Betty Davis and Joan Crawford.
Like, I love that shit.
I think they do a great job with it.
And it's fascinating.
It's like reading a Wikipedia page that lasts eight hours.
Yeah.
And you get every...
All the highlights, none of the lowlights.
Yeah.
You can close us out, Welsh.
Thanks, Joe.
Hey, you're welcome, Pat.
I'd like to showcase a smaller film that's in theaters now
because it's really something special.
It's called The Farewell.
And it's making a little money.
It stars Aquafina.
Who, obviously, the name is a problem.
When I saw that there was an actress named Aquafina with like three extra W's in it,
I was concerned.
But I liked her.
She stole Crazy Rich Asians from me, which was a...
I thought a pretty cute movie.
And she is fantastic in this in like a comedic slash dramatic performance.
The premise is this girl's grandmother is dying.
And apparently it is a tradition, or...
This is an actual thing in China, to not tell older people when they are dying.
So when they have cancer, they let them write out their final days in peace
and don't tell them what's going on.
So at first it's kind of this like dark comedy of everyone dancing around
telling this old woman that she has cancer.
The lady who plays the grandma is my god fantastic.
I'll definitely mispronounce it and I apologize.
But it looks like Zhao Xuzhen and I apologize again.
But basically her family, Aquafina's family is super repressed.
They are all going to China to sort of spend her last days with her.
And they're so repressed that they pretend that these two 20 -year -old kids in the family
who have been dating for like three months are getting married.
They pretend that's why they're bringing the whole family together.
But actually they're there to spend this lady's last days with her.
And you get a lot of comedy out of these two kids pretending they're getting married
when they hardly know each other and clearly aren't in love.
But this sounds terrible.
It sounds like a fucking Julia Roberts, you know, my best friend's wedding.
Well, I bet you'll get the screener because if they're smart they'll push it for stuff.
It was so sweet and so sad in parts.
And I know that premise sounds like it's a lot of high jinks.
It's almost no high jinks. It's beautifully done.
It is what I love about foreign films, which is it really helps you learn about a culture
and feel as, you know, almost more than visiting China would do for you.
You learn about the culture.
It's a great movie. I recommend it.
I'll be asleep at the wheel for that one.
You'll like it. I guarantee.
I don't care much to learn about other people's cultures.
All right. Fair enough.
I got enough. I'm trying to take it in this zany culture.
Fair enough. No. It sounds okay.
I'll check it out. It doesn't sound like my cup of tea.
You'd like it.
All right. That's one wild thing about not telling them they're dying.
I know.
Well, I almost thought to myself like, look, if I'm going to die in three months,
maybe I'd rather not know.
But I've been to China several times, Patrick.
I'd like to think I've learned firsthand about the culture.
I mean, do you want to spend your last three months on earth thinking about how you're going to die?
Or do you want to spend it just kind of going about your business?
Well, I think when you, once you start shitting blood, you go, hey guys, is something up over here?
That was my question. It's like, doesn't she have symptoms?
Yeah, I mean, come on. It's anyway.
Also, how do they know she's dying if she hasn't been to the doctor?
And if she's been to the doctor, how does she know?
Her sister takes her to the doctor and the doctors play along.
So the doctor will say, like, they all agree with her going to tell her,
which is like, you have, you know, something not non -bonign, whatever.
They make stuff up.
And apparently this is a real thing.
All right.
The doctors are in on it.
I have a friend who's Chinese who saw the movie.
Do you like it?
No.
She was very much like, it was all right.
The Chinese, they'd do a bad job with her Chinese and was very obvious.
That's a, you know.
I'm just saying what an actual change.
I go to the people themselves.
I don't let Hollywood deliver me my culture.
I go and meet the people.
Sure.
I get to know them.
I walk in their shoes.
I mean that, yeah, your average viewer is not going to know that
the doctor's Chinese is not up.
She's also playing a character who is not supposed to know Chinese perfectly.
I might check it out.
It's a good movie.
I believe you.
You know, I got to, with this AMC stubs, I'm seeing three movies a week.
And you just see so much.
Evidently.
I mean, you talking about the Lion King for 25 minutes.
You see so much shit when something comes along that's got a nice personality to it
and a nice, you know, I want to showcase.
I'm going to do a new psycho.
Oh, that'll get us a little traction here.
I'm definitely excited about this.
The Irishman trailer is finally dropped.
Didn't raise my pulse.
1b.
I don't understand.
Now, here's my question.
What didn't raise your pulse?
You, your exact words after you saw the Tarantino trailer, which showed literally nothing.
Except Leonardo DiCaprio four times going, I'm Rick fucking Dalton.
Right.
I can't wait.
You kept saying.
Now you've got Scorsese putting out a movie, the creator of your favorite movie of all time,
Goodfellas starring the cast from that movie in the same genre, in the same vein, in the same tone.
And it shows you much more than the Tarantino trailer showed you.
How could you not be excited about this?
How can you not just be excited about the vibe of it, the feel?
This looks like such a Scorsese movie.
You got De Niro.
You got Pesci.
You got Puccino.
It looks awesome.
I have no doubt that it will be great and that when I see an actual trailer, I will be excited.
That wasn't actual trailer.
Then I am concerned.
What is it?
I thought it was dull as shit.
I thought it looked like it could have been directed by anybody.
The D aging on everybody, I was like, what am I fucking looking at here?
Like, I'm concerned.
What are you concerned about?
I really don't get it.
Well, the D aging, they're still working on it.
First of all, nothing.
Nothing in the trailer is exciting.
There's no line where I'm like, ooh, that's a good line even.
There's no shots that I'm like, that's a good shot.
I think the shot of them throwing the cabs into the river wasn't awesome.
They look fucking amazing.
They want to take us to do a shot like that.
I was like, that looks awesome.
I mean, look, I am.
But I also, do you have interest in the hop?
Do you have interest in the Hoppa story?
Because I'm immensely invested in that story.
I love the movie Hoppa.
I was excited just seeing, oh, Hoppa, and more Hoppa.
And here's, we're going to learn.
Well, I own the book.
I have not read it yet.
I'm going to read it before the movie comes out.
And, of course, with this cast and this director, I'm pumped.
But that trailer, to me, was a cold fish.
I was like, eh.
All right.
I just, and I hope it's because they're withholding the best stuff till later.
I don't know.
Well, they don't even mention Kytel.
But my question to you is, how could you have watched the once upon a time in Hollywood trailer
and said, I'm excited because that trailer was wall -to -wall music and fun.
And it's Tarantino.
And I'm like, all right.
But that's what this is.
It wasn't to me.
I don't know what to tell you.
All right.
Because I watched the Hollywood trailer.
I was like, I don't even want to see this movie.
They're telling me, they told us nothing.
They did tell us nothing.
I think, you know, a lot of that's because there's, there are big chunks of that movie without much of a story as much as I liked it.
But in my mind, this is a teaser.
They're not done editing it.
I give it a lot of slack.
I just saying it didn't have me pumping my fist in the air for it.
I'm very excited.
I just, I'm so excited to see them all.
But this is where we always differ, though.
And this is where, and that's not me saying, I'm right.
You're wrong.
That's me saying, this is where both of us can't understand the other one.
Because you could equally say about me from the other side of the table.
Well, you didn't get excited about the Tarantino trailer, but you're excited about this.
You get excited about what you get excited about.
We don't understand each other, Pat.
That's a long been our problem.
Don't understand each other.
Long been our problem.
But we love each other.
And we're going to counseling to make it work.
I'm also going to do a quick scary stuff.
Video game folks.
Wait, what was the news like?
Oh, there's a trailer.
It's the trailer for the Irishman.
All right.
In release.
That's movie news.
That's pretty decent movie news.
Let me talk about this movie for fucking eight years.
True.
Scary stuff.
Video game fans out there.
If you haven't gotten this yet.
The Castlevania collection and the Contra collection.
I have them on my Nintendo Switch.
Our fucking fan.
Fantastic.
20 bucks.
You get the greatest hits of each collection.
Again, I have them on my Nintendo Switch.
They are amazing games to download and travel with.
I was hesitant to buy them because I was like, yeah,
it's just a bunch of greatest hits again.
I downloaded these things.
I can't stop playing them.
Contra.
You're getting arcade.
Arcade.
Supercontra.
You're getting Nintendo.
Contra.
Nintendo.
Super.
Supersea.
Japanese famicon version of Contra.
Contra alien wars from Super Nintendo.
You're getting hardcore, which is extremely rare and hard to find for cheap from the Sega
Genesis.
You're getting probator.
I think it's called which is the European version of Contra.
It's fucking awesome, man.
Castlevania, you're getting all the original NES titles.
Super Castlevania 4.
Castlevania Bloodlines.
Again a rare and hard divide.
Called the game title.
The game minor.
boy ports of the Castlevania game it's just fucking awesome. Some of the best
$20 I've ever spent on a video game title and these both of these together
for 40 are well well well worth it. I highly recommend buying this if you're
into fantasy horror or fantasy action video games if you're into classic
video games and especially if you have a switch and you want some really fun
shit to play on the go. All right also the addition of save states to these
things makes what are incredibly hard challenging frustrating games much
more playable when you can save at any moment right instead of doing what you
had to do back in the day which was scream go fuck yourself at the TV as you
had to start over again you know trying to get past the one jump you can't
figure out or whatever it's it's it's it makes it a much more tolerable
experience I got one the fly ultimate collection we're going to be doing the
fly coming up here it's it's a foreign title but it's it's all regions I own it
the blue race that you're talking about yeah it's amazing right I watched a two
and a half hour documentary that is an hour longer than the fly itself which
runs 95 glorious minutes this documentary is one of the best most
comprehensive behind the scenes I've ever seen and on a title from 1986 when they
weren't necessarily recording this bonus feature stuff that's very impressive it
reminded me of the amazing Adrian I'm sorry alien quadrilogy box set that came
out about 15 years ago I've never seen the fly too it also comes with the fly
too with tons of special features the Vincent Price fly curse of the fly
it's got it all we're going to discuss the fly in great detail coming up but man
oh man that documentary is well worth checking out if you're a fan of the movie and
you should be yeah it's a tremendous set and just to have all those the one the
classic one from the 50s on Blu -ray or just gorgeous yes well well worth the
price but it's also got a tremendous deleted scene from the fly too
starring Eric Stoltz that didn't make the cut of the movie where they're in
a they're in a he's in the backseat of the car he's door he's transitioning into the
fly so he looks very odd yeah and these like this gang of like meat heads drives up
and they're they're like kind of making fun of them and he leans out the
window and pukes all over their window and melts it why would you think it's a
little it's a little zany I gotta say but it's it's a funny scene the deleted scenes
on the fly are awesome too there's a cronum bird commentary which I didn't even
know he did those I can't wait to hear but the deleted scene with him making like
the cat hybrid thing it's one of the most disturbing things I've ever seen in my
life I've become obsessed I've watched the fly several times in the last couple
months so look forward to that episode from us and I can't wait let's get on to
Annabelle comes on me I know now I now what did you think of the spelling
CUMS home I thought that was it's set up you know a story that we did not get
and I was frustrated but yes Joe walk us through the premise have you seen all
the Annabelle I have she know all of them in theater okay and what's your
thoughts on the franchise as a whole this is my my my welcoming point I've only seen
conjuring one and so well Annabelle one came out I think between conjuring one
and two I don't think it came out after two but I remember being very excited to
see it and sucked it's the it's basically the origin story of Annabelle like
what you know the the dog this woman Annabelle is involved in some sort of black
magic satanic shit she does like one of these murder suicides of her family
things and her spirit goes into the doll and then people get the doll and
weird shit happens right the second movie was Annabelle creation which I guess
was about where the doll goes right after or how creation I'm sorry I'm sorry
creation is about how the girl gets the evil doll okay in the first movie the
initial something they both sucked yeah they both creation was better than the
first one but they're both not good movies they don't make a lot of sense they're
just kind of cash grabs as far as I'm concerned however Annabelle comes home I
went into it going I'm gonna see it to see it I'm probably not gonna like it man
oh man was I wrong they finally nailed this Annabelle thing this is in my
opinion look the loose premise here without giving too much away it's about the
Warren's bringing Annabelle into their house into that little room of their
cult objects that they've collected through their their encounters Annabelle
through a series of one or two events becomes a conduit for all the other objects
in the room releasing the haunted spirits of all the objects into the house and
it's a haunted house movie it's a bunch of monsters terrorizing some kids in a
house for 90 minutes and the monsters look scary yeah they're fun there's some good
jumps there's some great suspense there's great mood there's there's actual
eerie eerie moodiness to this thing it's got some texture and intensity to it I
really really really liked it I really enjoyed it I had a blast with it and it
made me think I should watch the other Annabels and I'm actually relieved to
here I don't need to go watch six more hours of doll movies but yeah it was so
much fun and to me it was elevated greatly by just how beautifully shot it was
how great it looked the the period details you know we'll also get into this
little with scary stories in the dark but there's something about setting these
movies in the 60s or the 70s that just gives them more life you know like
there's just it it separates them it sets them apart well I think right off the
bat if I may you may jump in right off the bat you got something in the 60s or
70s or even the 80s yeah right off the bat it's a simpler time everything isn't
connected everybody isn't to know it all there's still the suspension of
disbelief that people could believe in this that this could happen right and you're
also eliminating technology once the cell phones are gone once the internet is
gone correct once you got to do everything the old fashioned way your stakes are
raised 100 % agree 100 % and that might be why they do it I mean that people always
talk about how Seinfeld would not exist if cell phones were around you know
because it's all trying to find each other in the movie theater right right
yeah it might be like nobody would pop in Kramer would just text me exactly so it
might be why they do set these things back but either way it works visually for
me definitely this is 1968 it brings back Ed and Lorraine Warren from mega and
Patrick Wilson were they in the other Annabelle's no right they might I can't
remember if they pop up this is the most that they're in any of them if they
are in the other one yeah and even in this they're just sort of the book ends like
it's it's it's about their daughter yeah so they it's the ferryman the bride a
feeling melee board game and the black shuck are these other spirits and basically
it's like a babysitter movie where the babysitters are tormented by these
creatures you know plot -wise I can't say I remember too many details of it I
just remember having a nice time and being really impressed by the
cinematography the vibe the feel it's probably just about out of theaters which
means it's probably just about gonna be available to rent since there's no
window anymore between the two which might be why the cinema is dying I believe it
just a classy good time and it feels like it was not the cash grab you're
expecting somebody put some time in and it shows yeah and some really nice stuff
who directed it did you already say sorry I didn't but it was Gary Dobberman what
else is he directed he directed oh no he wrote Annabelle Annabelle creation the
nun and Annabelle comes home his directorial debut was Annabelle comes home okay
well he also co -wrote it and the upcoming it chapter two so he's a he's a
writer who they let direct but a good director he does some nice work in this I
honestly thought it was a foreign director because of some of the camera work
that they do in this yeah with colors and and and you know different different
types of angles than you see usually in these films right and letting some of
the suspense sort of happen naturally within within a shot and and not
relying as much on editing and stuff like that yeah I I thought it was very
well directed he wrote the swamp thing reboot as well clearly this guy's a big
horror guy I mean they got him on Salem's lot the you know it so he's a big
writer but this movie shows I think he's got quite a career coming up as a horror
director or is one of the few genres where like you do a 30 -second short you
could be directing a feature film the next month yeah and that's what's kind of
cool about it you get you know a lot a lot of up -and -coming exciting talent
because they take risks well and also too when there isn't some stupid as a
word on the line and I know earlier I was praising falsie verdine saying this is
Oscar material I'm not saying I'm not you know there is some worth to that idea
or concept sure but when there isn't a bunch of bullshit trophies on the line
nobody's getting golden gloves for horror right once in a while one of the film
sneaks past the goalie like us or you know or get out or or you know maybe maybe
the are yet you know the first one the hereditary you know yeah where it gets
the critical claim and the audience acclaim and the award recognition but most of
the time hereditary didn't know and I don't think us will either yeah think
what you will Tony Collette should have won best actors for her
hereditary she wasn't nominated for shit right you know that's a good point so my
point is is like there's pretty much and I hope it stays that way please god let
it stay that way but you know horror is kind of like a no -pissing contest zone
even comedy gets into the fucking award nonsense and the cool kids club and
all that shit right hard just doesn't get into that and you can put out a horror
movie as we've seen with Annabelle creation is or sorry comes home wine and with
creation and well creation had the what's his face from so I married an axe murderer
what's that guy's name the Australian Anthony Apoglia yeah original choice for
Tony soprano wouldn't have been as good a show by a long he was in it the first
one I don't think had anybody famous in it my point is is we saw it without
scary stories which will be discussing on an episode somewhere it's you can
release a horror movie with zero box office power star power yeah and it can
still be a hit because it's not about who's up there it's about what they're
doing while they're up there and quite frankly the the more recognizable faces
you have up there the more distracting it's gonna be yeah so and we saw it
with get out I mean aside from Michelle Williams well that had a fairly notable
cast show Williams not in get out Michelle Williams or Michelle what the fuck
should I mention Catherine Keener no the thought Allison Williams sorry oh and
Catherine Keener yeah well I was gonna say that that says a more of a notable
cast so saying but if you look at you know what the fuck I'm saying I know it's
anyway and it's been that way for ages I mean Sam Raimi made the evil dead for
a hundred grand and then the guys you know he's directing the biggest movies
there are it's it's a it's a truly democratic genre and that's what I love about
it a lot of big directors break in that way and you show you got some style and
then you move out of it or you stay in it so please let it stay that way let's hope
let's cross our fingers and that's that that's our show two hogs up for Annabelle
comes home Jotaro's a comedy on Twitter and Instagram you can catch me there the new
web series on YouTube distributing and produced by Comedy Central you let me
down you can check that out as well I am very rarely on Twitter and Instagram at
the Patrick Walsh and I'm about to shut down my Facebook but I'll be checking in
with you with an update about this podcast frankly and we thank you all for
listening we will see you next time and we'll see you in hell