Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gamling problem called 1 -800 -Gambleer.
howdy hellians we'll see you at hell we're back with a new episode this is your horror fantasy
sci -fi podcast and today we're gonna do a little review on a movie called a quiet play
place. But I'd first like to kick it over to my co -host with the co -most, Pat Walsh.
Hi, everybody. It feels like it's been a while since we've done one of these. I guess it's been a few weeks.
We had to do a lot of pre -recording.
Joe, you were out of town. You were in New York for Fleet Week. Is that correct?
Yeah, I went in to see the boys and the boys were happy to see me. Yes, well, why wouldn't they be? You make it easy for them.
Yeah, we're talking about a quiet place. John Krasinski's a quiet place.
We'll get to that. But what's been going on? How was how was NYC? NYC was good.
We had the dog back, cons back in the back.
Pat came in tonight, saw a con, exuded all the joy of a man in an electric chair, seeing
the person who sent him there through the glass.
How many of you was barking at me?
Well, they barked a little bit.
I don't want to say thanks.
But it's a dog, here's a treat.
But yeah, Kahn's back, New York was good, did a lot of stand -up, spent a week and a half
at my mom's and dad's decompressed, did a lot of video game hunting, and today, as we
record this, marks for me a full month without a drop of alcohol or a puff of weed.
So that's interesting.
and Joe's talking about permanent sobriety.
Well, I never say, Pat, I never say never.
Yeah.
But this is going to be a stretch for me,
because I am learning and discovering feelings.
Oh, wow.
That I have not experienced in a very long time.
Right.
Bowel control.
Yeah, bowel control.
p -control.
Yeah, but I mean, I'll tell you who appreciated the sobriety was those fleet wheat, boys.
Sure.
Because I didn't need a rest.
Right.
Less refractory period.
Yes.
Yeah, exactly.
The downtime between organisms as your refractory period.
Exactly.
So, you know, it's been an interesting stretch.
I've been, you know, I allowed myself a Saturday night drink, but I've been largely off
for about a month.
Saw Eddie Peppettone the other night, one man show, in the end of days, a scream left
from start to finish, over an hour, they had the rack with the costumes out on stage, you
know?
Yeah.
I love Peppettone.
and saw a Helian, the the Helian who wrote the erotic fan fiction between you and I.
Where did you see him?
Was in attendance.
He was there at the show.
And I don't like to throw out names in case people don't want their name thrown out.
Maybe I'll ask him and I'll read it next time.
Well, that's nice.
Now you are saying you're not high right now.
I'm probably still high from yesterday.
Why do you ask?
Could you seem extremely high?
Your eyes are half at half mass.
No, I mean, I'm really red.
I'm exhausted.
Oh, see, all right.
Well, then it could also just be exhausted.
But, yeah, I got very high yesterday.
And today, like I told you, I'm feeling a little sluggish.
What's all right?
Back off.
That sluggish enough to not get advantage.
The what what is really high mean for you because you have a pretty good tolerance
You know more more mg's than the norm
What about 40 mg?
I can't I can't come to get anywhere near it. I know I go over a 10 and I'm
You know yeah a lot you're peeling me off the ceiling
How do you get a new iPhone?
I got the red iPhone, the red.
It's hot off the presses.
What's the red iPhone?
I'm sorry, it's just like any other iPhone
except one of a kind and it helps people with AIDS.
Oh, that's nice.
When did that come out?
I think very recently.
Like I think the past week and it's pretty cool
and I'm trying to get it out of this case.
So the red iPhone is for age charity and they make it blood red. That's right. That's an odd choice
You know, I think it's like we're all one, you know, we're united by blood
Even if that blood contains the HIV virus. I can't have a thing for big an iPhone for bowel cancer and it's brown or something
Yeah, I can't disagree with that
But we're read quite frankly for bell cancer, but you know, I had the same iPhone for three, four, maybe even five years
So I'm assuming I've racked up an upgrade or whatever the hell
Yes, just look at me. They're like, yeah, you know, it's just full price
Yeah, you just pay full price. You're doing something wrong with these iPhones, man
This you should have gotten one for absolutely for
for some very cheaper amount.
They weren't offering it to me.
Maybe because you got the fancy charity warrant.
Well, they offered me, yeah, my iPhone 6.
They were like, we can give you another one of these for $2 .99.
What?
I'm like, but they're so far ahead of it.
Why would I do that?
You should have went to your phone carrier store.
That's where you would have got to deal.
Really?
Yeah, because you go into that Apple store
or it's just you're dealing directly with the Apple.
You gotta, who's your care, AT &T?
Yeah, Garbage AT &T.
You go on to the AT &T store, they'll say,
well, we have a promotion and for just $10 a month
on your bill, you can get the iPhone 8 or whatever, you know?
I don't need to be beholden to those fucks.
You know what I paid a little extra for today?
Freedom.
If only freedom worked that way everywhere, Pat.
And then I immediately put my thumbprint into the fucking phone and gave it to Apple.
Refused to do it.
Won't put my goddamn thumbprint into that phone.
Fuck that new one with the eye recognition.
Go get it out of my face.
I did not go that far.
I went with the eight something, but the ladies walk me through it real quick and she
goes, well, even I go, I don't do the cloud.
I opt out of the cloud.
I don't want to do it.
She goes, well, let's just check because maybe you have a backup on the cloud you're
not even aware of.
I said, well, that wouldn't be possible.
I don't sign into the cloud.
She clicks in.
I got a backup on the cloud from like a week ago
that I didn't perform.
She's like, you want to just use that one?
I go, well, I don't know if, click all my apps appear.
I'm back into my phone on this new phone.
Like, it's just fucked up.
They have everything, everything that is yours they have.
You want to hear a real creepy one?
Yes.
When I was at my mom's,
We were talking about watching Godzilla, original, sure.
And my mom said, isn't Raymond Burr in Godzilla?
Yeah.
And I said, I think so, but I also don't think so because it wasn't that movie made in Japan.
And I got very confused.
Right.
And my mom said, well, I think he was.
We talked about it for a while.
Then finally, I said, we'll just Google it.
See, she types in, she picks up a ripad,
goes to the search and it types in Raymond Burr and the first thing is was Raymond Burr in Godzilla
and she's like, how the hell is that the first thing? That's that's ridiculous. Yeah,
that doesn't sound right at all. That doesn't sound right. Raymond Burr Perry Mason didn't come up.
First thing. We're a window. Like when it gives you the choices to complete it in the Google thing.
Right, and she had the thing on her lap as we talked about it
Something's going on here. I don't disagree with you, Jim
Pat if you don't mind before we get too far into this I want to plug something. All right
I I'm in a new horror anthology thing called by night
Origins generally do the plugs at the end of the show but well I'm afraid I'm gonna forget this and I'm trying to drive a lot of people to watch
this thing, but it's on Amazon Live. I shot this a very long time ago.
Amazon Live? I mean Amazon Prime excuse me. I shot this a long time ago. It's up
there now. There's short form stories. The first three are up there. I play
the sort of Rod Surlingy guy in it. Judging by your reaction, I can tell you
haven't watched it yet. I haven't seen it. I'm sorry. You're like, are you the
narrator of it? Yes. I'm like the host. Are you like on like a late -night radio show from what it looks like?
No, you'll have to watch the
three episodes and then there's a little twist where it shows what I am
Well, you're not gonna do it. I can tell. I will. I'll watch
I thought you were the guy who's like, you know, it may be cold outside, but we've got some
jazz heating up in here.
Well, I am sort of that guy except I'm not a radio guy.
Oh, okay.
Anyway, that's out.
Go check it out, I hope you like it.
It's fun.
I love anthology hard.
Have you watched it?
Of course I've watched it.
All right.
I was in it.
I had to watch it.
A lot of people can't watch themselves.
I didn't watch myself.
I watched the stories because I shot my segments
after the stories were shot.
Okay.
So I had to watch the stories to kind of understand what was going on.
So I understood my intros and things like that.
Anyway, any horror puns?
No, no, there's no crypt keeper style stuff.
I don't say anything like, uh, ladies in, uh, uh, uh, I can't think of anything for
gentlemen. Can you think of something?
I'm not quite sure, bladey's makes sense.
Like blade, oh, knife.
Gotcha.
You know, yeah, no, I don't say anything like that.
I don't say this next, scary tale.
You know, I don't think I'd be like, nothing like that.
I'll have to watch it.
Is there nudity?
I don't, no, no, no nudity.
All right, I'll still watch it.
Yeah, well I would, I would hope so. It's your dear, dear friend is in a thing.
Hey, did you watch me when I portrayed Ben Fry water on Showtime's roadies?
Had I had the option to, I would have. I don't have showtime. And as far as I know,
despite popular demand, roadies has not been shuffled over to any of the streaming services.
No, it's, you got to pay a premium if you want to see it.
Pat, I agree. And you know, look, you tell me where to pay that premium I'll pay
because I want to see you in action.
I guess showtime on demand .com.
It's a good point.
Probably just buy it there.
Probably buy it for $199.
You know what, I'm gonna go buy your episode.
You don't have to do that, Joe.
I'm gonna buy it, I want to watch it.
I have three lines.
Oh, well then forget it.
I don't, my dad told me I leaned into frame
so that I could be seen even when I didn't have lines.
I was like, no I didn't.
I did what I was directed to do, you have marks, you old fuck, you have to hit.
Your dad critiques your body posture in your, his favorite show was Rodeys, he wrote
me like a giant's favorite show, he was obsessed with the show Rodeys.
So he'd write me these huge lengthy reviews every week of a show I was not watching, amazing
episode.
He'd talk about all the characters and everything like I knew who they were.
Then I was an episode nine and I get no review.
So when I told him I was gonna be in it. He was like, oh, I'm so excited. Okay. So he doesn't write me a review for nine
I go, hey, just see me on rhodes
He goes, oh, yeah, and then critiques my performance
Pat, I'm sorry
I got to remember that what you just told me that story
You mean in dealing with me on the future? Yes, I got no, I'm serious
Anytime I'm looking at you and I go, why isn't he giving me the emotion I need right now?
I'm serious. I got to remember that story. That's terrible. Yeah, and I'm being sincere. That's a recent story
That's not that's not for my childhood. Yeah, I'm not being a smart ass. That's that's terrible. Oh stop
I'm serious. It makes me feel bad
Stop
What
Can I feel for you? Oh my god the way you want me to oh my god. Oh, you know what we never did what we never got
But on, I don't know the song.
Oh, somebody sent me one, if you want it.
I always forget them.
And now that I have no apps on my phone, I gotta.
My friend, Amy sent me, and I said,
I think you've done this one.
Okay, well, how's that helped me?
Well, because then I started thinking about,
have we done magic?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Joe, Joe, it's magic, yeah.
Okay, well then that's what, that was right then.
and we have done it.
You know what, somebody requested that I remember.
Here we go.
Good on with the show.
And on with the Jelline, Jelline, Jelline, Jelline, Jelline.
There you go.
Very good.
What a part.
What?
Dolly Parton.
I know.
Huge cans.
That's my favorite line in all of the Jervace office
is the last line of the first season.
and when he says that really insightful thing
and he goes, you know what, which brilliant philosopher said
that, Dolly Parton?
Yeah.
People thought she was just a big old set of tits.
Very funny.
I see a white male, you the woman.
Why don't we get to the movie corner
because I've got a few things for it.
But also, I feel like we should allow ourselves
a little bit extra time for a quiet place today.
Okay, because I feel that it might be
a more spirited discussion.
All right.
In terms of the movie corner, I so love Simon.
Now, I've been wondering what the hell that is.
I keep seeing the title everywhere,
But I yeah have yet to even the same the same buddy of mine who took me to the greatest showman
It was like you got to see love Simon. You're gonna love it. What is it about all right?
It's a it's basically like a teen John Hughes type of movie about a gay kid. Okay, so he's got like three
He's trying to figure out who the this anonymous gay kid at school is. So there's all these possible suitors. Okay
And it was a cute movie.
I'm glad that there is a gay romantic comedy for teenagers that there hasn't really
been one of these to this point.
And I thought it was goofy at times, a little ragged around the edges.
It was not a perfect movie, but I enjoyed myself.
All right.
And the kid that played Simon was good.
All the kid actors were good.
Good.
it's an enjoyable film. Good. I watched for the first time. Yeah. Pat, you're not going
to believe it when it comes out of my mouth. Okay. The Shawshank redemption. What? I'd never
actually seen the movie from front to back. I just caught pieces of it on like TBS or whatever
channel, they reranted on constantly. I mean, what a stupid way to watch that movie. Well,
I didn't watch it that way. I would catch parts of it. And then I just never had a huge
urge to watch it. I was on an airplane recently flying back from New York to here. It back
into your arms, right? And I thought, hey, they've got Shawshank redemption on the classics
channel here on Virgin America. I'm gonna finally watch this damn thing. I loved it. It was a wonderful film.
It was, it was just really phenomenal and I mean, you know, there's really not much to say here.
I recently, very recently watched it again myself, it's better than I even remembered. It's a great
amazing story. Amazingly well told. Great acting. Yeah. Great story. Yeah. Great movie. It's a fantastic
fantastic film. Great cinematography by the great Roger Deacon who finally took home his
Oscar for Blade Runner 2049. And directed by the wonderful Frank Daribount, who also
did the Mist. And the Green Mile, I think, right? He did the Mist, the Green Mile, and the
Majestic. Don't forget the Majestic. I think most of us forgot the Majestic, folks. He also
created the walking dead and now soos them every week for like $90 million. Yeah, so anyway,
I, you know, let's take it back to 1994 when Shawshank came out. I rewatched a little
picture called the River Wild, which lives an infamy on this podcast because of the story I told
where when Meryl was reaching for a gun in the water, a very old man behind me at the mall theater
goes, REACH Meryl! And me and my buddy Ryan laughed for a half an hour. It was very funny to us.
But the River Wild holds up directed by the great Curtis Hanson, RIP, who did LA Confidential and
the Rocks the Cradle, many other films. River Wild's just like a classy adult thriller, the likes of
which we don't get much anymore.
Speaking of, I've never seen it.
It's good.
It's, Streep is good, Bacon is good,
John C. Riley is good, David Strathane is good.
It's a good movie, it's not terribly suspenseful,
but it works.
Speaking of past directors,
we also lost Milo's form in this movie.
Milo's form.
Yeah, so farewell to him and Rest in Peace.
You know what probably killed him working with Jim Carrey on that man with a moon project. Yeah, well
Where did that documentary Milo's for him and had it harder than anybody?
Pat he did one flow of the cook who's nest. Yes an all -time grade. Yes
What else he only did him like every you know Almedaus?
Almedaus he did movie every like seven eight years. Yeah, he did very fine work. He did
I
I, on the airplane, also decided to delve into the new Will and Grace, which I had not
seen yet.
And a TV show called Trial and Error, starring John Lithgow, I've seen it.
I got three minutes in a trial and error, almost, I mean, I was offended in a way that
that like devout Muslims were offended by the satanic verses book. You know, like,
this thing is one of the worst pieces of television and comedy I've ever said
eyes on. It made me weep for John Lithgow. This is an Oscar. I should tell you my
dear friend Jeff Astroff created it, ran it, wrote several of the episodes. He won't
be listening to this. It's fun. Okay. Sorry John. I'm sure I've met you. You're
probably a nice guy. And I did not know you were a part of this thing. Jeff, Jeff, I couldn't,
I mean, sorry, and I won't, then I won't bash it anymore. But, uh, did you finish it
or just watch? No, I watched the first, I thought, I thought it was kind of funny. I liked
it. The, the pilot opening, I don't like, and this goes for a lot of comedy that's out there
now. I don't like, now here's the thing, if you're going to do an absurd comedy, then fine,
if you're going to do like a sort of anchorman style thing where everybody is a sort of caricature
or a stereotypical or archetypal person, fine. I don't care how ridiculous it gets. People can
fly up into the air halfway through. I don't care. It doesn't have to make sense. It just has to be
funny. But if you're going to do a thing that I'm supposed to sort of buy into and I'm supposed to
believe that these are real people in a situation, the jokes in the first four or five minutes of
this thing were so absurd. You know, it's like, I'm sorry, I don't buy a news reporter on the scene
of what she believes to be the house of a murderer, John Lithgow, who's being brought out and put
into taking into police custody and I don't buy him handing her his dog and
going hold truffles wherever the dog's name was and then him gone and then the
reporter immediately breaking out of interest of the story and going yes you
will your doggy what's your name it's like come on man that's just that's a bad
fucking joke that's just a bad unbelievable fucking joke all right show I I
I recuse myself from the conversation.
I didn't say it in.
You want to drag more out of this.
You want to push me to answer you.
No.
I don't.
That's what I didn't like about it.
Will and Grace also had you see in the original?
Yes, and I will say this.
I never had.
I have only seen a few of the new one.
The new Will and Grace delivered in the way
the old Will and Grace did.
And for completely abhorrent human beings, thinking only of themselves, yet for some reason
I'm supposed to like them.
It had its moments.
I really like Jack, what's his name?
The actor.
What's the actor's name?
Jack?
The guy who plays Jack?
Yeah.
His real name is Jack oh no Sean Sean sorry all right. I really like him a lot
I think he's tremendous. I think he's funny and believable on the show
But the prep what's what's the girls name with the hair who's in that show that we watch
She's in the end not of the girl in the NCIS, but she was on the same night as her on the Leno
That's what I'm getting over here. Well, what do you want for me trying to help?
I like that character, but I think they kind of make every character also that self -centered.
Again, trying to buy into something realistic, I personally have really enjoyed the new
Rose Anne so far.
I think they've done a very nice job of realistically portraying the way people deal with the disparity
In politics and the current social climate and the arguments and debates that we all have on the different sides of the coin
I think they did a good job of that will and grace. I think started down an interesting road
And then it gets fucking absurd and unbelievable once again when it's like
Now grace has to redecorate the oval office. It's like come on man like right this is absurd
Well, that was the one I saw that was like the premiere. Yeah, so
So, you know, look, if they're fans of the show out there
and they're fans of trial and error,
more power to you.
If you like these shows,
I hope you enjoy them.
They just weren't for me.
What is this, stop with the show.
But no, no, you're doing like a kind of like,
hey, man, yeah, I guess if you don't,
if you don't like it, daddy, oh.
What is this?
What are you talking about?
Oh it cool thing that you're doing right now.
I'm listening.
You're talking and I'm listening.
All right.
That's all I can.
Well you can offer an opinion on these things, you know.
Well I can on trial and error because my friend made it and I think it's funny.
So there is my opinion.
And Will and Grace I've only seen a couple.
And I don't know that it was for me.
I have some friends on that show as well.
Oh Mr. Hollywood.
It wasn't my bag.
thing. This sort of thing isn't my bag. Sure thing is my bag, baby. That's all I was
saying. They neither were my bag, baby. Okay, that's fine. Yeah. Well, it's fine. I saw
you were never really here. Oh, that looks good. Starting Joaquin Phoenix. It was sort of
like a dark, indie version of Taken, but with a very unreliable narrator. And if you
don't like that sort of thing, if you don't like a challenging movie, if you don't like
a movie that doesn't answer all of its questions, don't see it. If you're pretty open -minded
and you don't mind having to do some work,
having to kind of fill in some blanks,
I think you really enjoy it.
It's basically walking Phoenix,
walking around with a hammer,
beating the shit out of people.
He rescues a girl from,
you know, like a sex dungeon type place,
underage sex dungeon.
And...
So, it was a dungeon.
He's got to get her out.
It's kind of like a brothel for little girls. It's a very dark movie, amazing
cinematography. It's a lady that did more of her in color. Later that did. We need to talk about Kevin. Oh, I like that movie quite a bit.
I did as well. And it's similar. It's very kind of creepy. Johnny Greenwood from Radiohead who does
Paul Thomas Anderson scores. He did the score for this. It was very
bombastic, very exciting. I loved the movie. And it was 90 minutes. Oh, they can't
beat that. No, you can't. All right, very good. I'd like to, I mean, if you want to
move on, I'd like to go on to Joe scary stuff. Go for it. I have seen a couple other
things, but let's parcel them out, you know, Hoka. I have two. I've seen other things.
you're not the only one. I know. I know. Scary stuff. I'm going to go back to the video game well
as I have to do on this. If you have an Nintendo Switch, which many of you probably do, if you're
into video games, check out the... Nintendo Switch is porting out a lot of third -party indie stuff
on their digital only store where you can, you know, go on and log on and download stuff directly to the device, as you can with all devices these days.
But one line of games that are really, really tremendous, Johnny turbos arcade, that is the brand or the line.
And what Johnny turbos arcade is doing is they are reporting the best of the old data east arcade games.
And so far, they have ported Gate of Doom, which is a really fun sword and sorcery dungeon
crawling arcade game from, I guess the early 90s, and then they also just recently
relates bad dudes versus Dragon Ninja, which is exactly what it is.
It's bad two bad dudes versus a bunch of ninjas.
But the day the East Games are really a lot of fun, and you know, they're the kind of things
you could play through an under an hour and it's just thought, you know, it's a lot of running
and fighting and running and fighting, but they're great games and Johnny Turbo is okay is doing
a very good job with these ports giving you tons of options to screen options and screen sizing,
the way the screen looks, making you can make it look like a VHS tape, you can make it look,
you can adjust the scan lines, you can adjust the size of the screen. It's just a very, very,
very cool port of old games and it's everything you want in a newly ported retro gaming experience.
Check that out and it seems like they're sticking to the more fantastic
games that Data East did so far. Anyway, check it out. Do you have anything Pat?
I don't, I'm sorry. It's fine. I saw a coyote the other night.
That's horror themed.
No, it's not, Pat.
They howl with the moon.
Saw a coyote.
All right.
Thanks for being here today.
I see a white male.
You the mother.
Let's get down to the task in hand.
Yeah.
We'll talk about a quiet place.
And you know, I watch an old Siskel neighborhood this weekend. And usually one basically talks for a minute does a summary, then the other does a summary, then they get into the meat of it.
Okay, let's try that for this one. Sure.
Quite a place is a second maybe the third film directed by office star John
Krasinski who I think really announces himself here as a great director of
suspense. This was a very exciting very tense thriller that uses its sound
proof gimmick exceptionally well. I would say hopefully we'll lead to a
sequel. When there's so many of these things that give you more and more in
cities, the last key comes to mind. This one actually seems like it could lend
itself to some more interesting stories being told because I felt like while it
did a lot with the material, there was a lot more they could have done. But this
This also was a tight 90 minutes.
I respect the hell out of that.
I was moved by it when I was supposed to be.
I had fun when I was supposed to.
And I thought it was a very scary movie.
Easily, for me, the best horror release since last year's get out.
Joe?
Uh, yes.
A quiet place is a film about an alien invasion that is already in progress or is already
transpired. The aliens are blind, but have a highly attuned sense of hearing. Therefore,
if you make any noise anywhere near the aliens, they will, I guess, eat you or murder you
with something. They never really totally explained that.
They grabbed that kid. Yeah, but it's, but it's, well, they don't show it eat it, though,
as my, you know what I mean? I rip it apart. Yeah. So they don't, let me, let me
phrase they don't really explain why the aliens are so hostile they just are
like you know so this is you know it was sort of like a more intense signs the
eminent Shyamalan movie people are raving about this thing the people are
saying as Patcha said it's the best horror movie since get out I'd like to start
the discussion by saying, it's a passable film. It was well executed. I will say John
Krasinski did an excellent, excellent job directing it. Excellent job. It was very, very
well shot. I don't know who the cinematographer was, but he did a great job. The script was
well written, and the actors were all very good. But at the end of the day, it's, is it the
best horror movie that came out since get out? No, it's the best horror movie that's
been in mainstream movie theaters since get out. I mean, you know, on this podcast here,
we solve super dark times. After we saw get out, we saw raw. I don't think this movie surpasses
either of them, but I also don't think that those are movies that are gonna rise to the
top of the American mainstream movie complexes.
It's a good movie, but at the end of the day, it's jump scares.
It's a lot of jump scares.
And having just recently re -watched it with my mom and dad because they wanted to see it,
which I actually liked more on the second viewing, I still don't think it's fantastic.
I felt that this was very similar to it and it is the highest grossing horror movie of all time.
Right. So these things have something in common. These are both very popular mainstream horror films in the United States.
You know, they're not bad. They're not poorly done. They're solid. They're good pieces of work.
But I just... I'm just tired of the jump scares. I just miss... I felt like the story of this...
I could have used, not because I needed information.
I just felt the movie would have been a little stronger
with some backstory just so it wasn't seen after seen,
after seen, after seen of,
we need to be quiet because the monster is right there.
It was a lot of that.
And after a while I was like, okay,
so you gotta be quiet because the monster's there.
What are your thoughts on that?
You didn't you didn't find that got kind of I mean
It's an issue we frequently have if you say anything in that voice. It sounds like a bad thing. What do you mean?
Like look out the monsters there, you know, you got to be quiet. Sure. I mean if you say it in that tone of voice then it sounds like
It's dumb
But I'm saying it's dumb. I'm just saying you didn't think that got old after a while
I didn't at all. I was I was on the edge of my seat as they say
from start to finish. Apparently, some backstory was cut out. They had flashbacks that Krasinski cut out
of the script. I didn't miss it. I think they would have been distracting, would have cut the
suspense. I thought it was just a good, solid, 90 -minute, suspenseful thrill ride. It is good. I didn't
think it had too many jump scares or certainly more than your average horror movie. That's all the
scares were were jump scares. There were literally no other scares. But I mean to compare this
thing to get out or to put it on the same plane as get out which had, I just an astounding
approach to a social commentary and a creepiness that wasn't all just jolts. I just don't think
it's a fair comparison. I don't I to say this is the best sense which I stand by. I prefer
get out get out is a lot more to say but in terms of horror movies that I think
will will be around for a while I'd put this up there I think it's a lot
better than a conjuring or a conjuring to I think it's a great modern horror
movie and a good comparison it to to Shyamalan because it feels like those first
few of his signs and breakable six cents where it's just a good solid well -made
screen machine. And the kind that's in short supply these days, I would say.
I disagree. I think Shyamalan, I think six senses was better at being creepy. I
don't like signs. I like this better than signs. And unbreakable, it's not a
screen machine, I don't think. But like it's but but I don't know. It's just it was
good. I mean, would you at least agree with this with the sentiment that it's the best
horror movie that's this popular since get out? I mean, it's not the best horror movie
made since get out. That's hyperbole. I mean, I think these discussions are not they're
not doing any anybody a service. We're movie or movie critic podcast. I know, but to talk
about, you know, which, which is which which is better, which is that to a certain degree,
I just think it's a great movie and shouldn't that be enough sure as if this was a like a
Cloverfield movie as it was supposed to be no that's was not true actually they said that that was never true
I read it. I know you read it and then the story came out later that said it was never supposed to be a
Cloverfield movie well who am I to believe in this world of fake news in this world of fake news
okay um you know I just think he got it at some point discuss a movie on its own
terms if this was if this popped up on Netflix one night you'd be like this
fucking great movie but I think you can't help when a movie is critically a
clan that everybody's going to see it and everybody's excited about it to push
back at it I don't think it deserves it I think it's a great movie but I'm asking
you because you said I think this is the best horror movie since get out. I'm saying yes.
Do you think that that's a little bit of a gross exaggeration? No, I do. I think it was a great
movie and I liked it more than super dark times and I liked it more than raw and I like both those
movies a lot. Okay. And I don't even like Krasinski. I thought he was good in it. Maybe better that he'd
not talk so much, and Emily Blunt was great.
They just did a good job of like,
oh shit, she's pregnant, oh shit.
She's gonna make noise, the baby's gonna make noise.
Oh shit, there's a nail on the stairs.
You know, like they kept, they kept ramping up the stakes.
They kept me in suspense.
And that's really all I can ask of a suspense movie.
Let's talk about the pregnant thing.
All right.
Now I kept an open mind throughout the film.
I said don't jump to any conclusions don't judge but in a scenario is dire is this right I wanted at least
Some sort of explanation as to why these fucking idiots got themselves pregnant
When they've already had a kid die and it wasn't like like when it's the so when the movie starts
It says the 86 day or the 93rd day right
They're like okay, this is just started going on
this weird invasion, things happening, whatever it is.
After, and then the sun gets killed,
and that's the cold open.
And I think they're clearly having a baby
to replace the sun.
Well, you would bring a baby into this madness?
I think they're doing it.
I think that's irresponsible, but that's what they're doing.
I mean, it's idiotic.
They show them, so wait, but hold on one second.
But so then they come back after the opening credits. It's as day 460 whatever. Yeah, so you're like, okay
This and then you see and she's pregnant. So the first thing you say is okay
Well, I maybe I thought she would have been pregnant when the other kid but no, this is this is a long time after she's she got pregnant after
Okay, well, maybe they're having a kid to as you said to replace the kid that they lost and
Then you see the other children playing monopoly with
Not with like the metal pieces, but with like pieces they knitted right so they wouldn't make any noise
And I'm like she you're going to the lengths to be that careful that the monopoly board can't emit any sound
Which is the tiniest sound in the world
yet
Willie nilly we're gonna have a baby
We don't even know if the soundproof room works that we built when she has the baby and they don't get killed
He got the first thing she says is it worked the room worked. It's like this all seems quite careless to me
In a world where your kids can't even have a toy that makes any noise. They had they did have a soundproof room
Which I guess was a risk. I don't know if they were planning to have the I figure either they were planning to have the baby to replace the dead
Sun or they were all dogged it up one night and
and she got pregnant. They don't want to have an abortion when there's like four people
in their life. It'd be very traumatic. I would have liked some at one line just saying
like I know I was like these people have suffered a loss and they want to replace it with
a baby. But you but but that's that's in consider to the baby for Christ's. The baby could
and crying get killed instantly.
All right.
But I mean, so you disagree with them having a baby,
that's a flaw of the movie to you?
It's a flaw that is never addressed.
Have one line where you say,
we got ourselves into the situation
and we have to do the right thing now and have the,
just address it.
Don't just act like it's totally normal
that we're pregnant and we're never gonna say anything.
I mean, you know,
I think you could go either way, like I said.
It was an accident or it was a planned replacement and I like both answers fine, but then say
But then you have to explain to me why a planned replacement makes sense to you
You can't here's the thing you can't tell a mother's love as a mother's love
Here's my point the kid at the beginning gets killed because he has the cop car with the bat or the rocket ship
Sorry with the batteries in it right yeah
And the rocket ship makes noise
John Chrysensky makes such a
Theament point to this kid you can't put batteries in this toy because it will make too much noise the kid doesn't listen
He puts batteries in the toys rocket ship makes noise. He gets killed. This is devastating
You're now gonna push out a baby
that is
By itself louder
you're sitting at any toy on the planet.
Right, so you disagree with them having a baby,
but that's the movie.
But you can't get over this?
No, I need a lot.
It's literally like if Richard Donner's Superman,
Superman just lives in a kryptonite house.
And they never, you're like,
why are you living in a kryptonite house?
You're fucking idiot.
This hurts you.
This is going to kill you like like the people on Maury. They don't need to have their seventh baby
They have no money. They don't live in a situation where where aliens are gonna eat them
If they bring that baby and the justice dangerous a world if they can't afford to feed it
I think it needed a liner to to just say this is what happened
I think that goes a long way because I spent a lot of that movie scratching my head going wait
Why the fuck are they having this bit?
What is, what, what the fuck are they thinking?
Didn't occur to me.
Replace in the sun is the easy emotional connection to answer.
I understand replacing the sun,
but you wouldn't replace the sun in a world that dangerous.
They, these people did.
And I think you gotta accept that.
Then they're fucking idiots and they get what they deserve.
They should die.
They should all die then.
They're idiots.
But they, they were willing to shove this kid
in a little uh... hand -made casket basically to keep it quiet
they had a plan it's a sick
that these are sick people
that are doing what they gotta do
you don't bring a kid into that
people talked about not even babies when trump became president for christx
these guys are going to babies in this fucking post -apocalyptic
maybe that's a little selfish
but it's very selfish they want to spread the love around
I think it's, I thought Krasinski's relationship with the other two kids was very sweet.
I like that.
At the end, which I, you know, were spoiling here, you know, when he's saying, I love
you very much.
I thought it was a very moving scene.
I like that.
You know what else the dad could have done, instead of sacrificing himself.
He could have just thrown a rock.
How many times is that trick going to work?
It works frequently throughout the film throw it and then what and then the alien would have run towards it
And then maybe he could have saved his kids, you know, he didn't have to sacrifice himself. I think in that instance
He did I mean, you know when the alien is in the literally in the bathroom with
Emily blonde as she
Finally screams because she's having labor pains
screens at the top of her lungs, it is distracted by fireworks outside that it runs outside too.
So clearly, these aliens are very cat -like.
You can divert the attention pretty easily.
That's true.
I think Krasinski could have saved himself, you know.
He had to save his kids, he acted, I mean, you're thinking too much.
You're thinking too much.
Here's the thing, if you scrutinize, get out to this point, you wouldn't find these
problems with it.
This is why I say this movie was fine. It was solid. It was possible. It's not a fantastic film.
It's just the best thing we've seen in a movieplex in a long time. That's all.
I think it's a fantastic thriller. If you look at it in terms of what is a thriller supposed to do. What is it scary movie supposed to do?
Then yes, it is an excellent movie on those terms. I
Think you all right. Well, I know I have to talk about it with regard to Chinatown. No
No, I think it was a great thriller.
But when I'm talking about it with a guy in the town,
talk about it as a movie, a movie,
it's like saying the expendable three was a good movie
because it had a lot of explosions
and that's what it was supposed to do.
It's like, that's not enough.
You have to say does the story make sense?
Does, you know, this story, especially by the rules
of like a supernatural thriller,
the story made absolute perfect sense
that I did not question.
If you want to pick away at what are the rules of these space creatures, perhaps it's not always a hundred percent accurate.
But I don't know what the inner workings of a space creature are.
You don't need to.
They play by their own rules.
I'm abiding by the rules that they set up in the beginning of the movie.
If you can't have a toy that beeps, don't bring a fucking screaming baby into the world.
It's not a good idea.
I don't think it has to be a good idea for this to be a movie.
People have to make bad decisions for movies to happen.
You saw the road, right?
I did.
I strongly preferred this movie to the road.
So did I.
I didn't think the road was great.
I just thought the road was kind of boring.
Yeah.
But you watched the road.
It's a guy who's the dad in it.
The guy from V. Jill Morton's.
Yes.
Yes, he's got his kid, dude, and it is like these are the fucking rules.
There is no compromise to a fault, he does it.
To the point where, at the end of the movie, when he finally dies and the kid is discovered
by a family, the kid realizes, oh, there actually can be love and joy in the world.
Everything isn't a risk.
That to me is what I'm talking about.
It's like, there is no like, well,
that's the world we live in, but hey, we're gonna,
that's like saying like, that's like saying like
if there was like a scene where they decided
to have a dinner party in the woods,
you're like, what are they doing?
They're gonna get killed.
You go, wow, hey, it's just what they decided to do.
But like, I've given you two possible explanations.
You could have plugged either of them into your brain
and enjoyed the fucking movie.
But you have to explain, you have to say that in the movie.
Okay.
When you don't say it, then it's just like, okay, so then which one is it and what's
going on here?
Why did they do this?
It just didn't bug me.
I also think, which I guess is why I enjoyed it.
I also think, look, as I said, I kept an open mind, but by the end of it, I was like,
you're not going to mention this once.
And then on top of it, you're going to say, Hey, our soundproof room worked.
Yeah, guys, you could have tested it before the fucking baby was born.
You got three people here four people you could have went down and do it and made some noise to see if it worked one of them is deaf
You didn't love the deaf girl. I thought she was great and
I was even willing to buy that everybody was seemingly fluent in sign language because they had a sister that was hard of here. You would be
No, you wouldn't be if growing up my sister was deaf my whole family would have known the sign language I guarantee it
I'm not saying your family wouldn't have known sign language. I'm saying forever. Look, I let that go. I didn't have a problem with it. I thought it was a little convenient.
I mean, I don't know how you enjoy anything.
You enjoy everything.
That's simply not true.
It's very true.
I hate a lot of things. Most things.
I like a lot of stuff. Sorry that I didn't like trial and error.
Well, I'm talking just about a quiet place.
But you did like a quiet place. Why are you saying you didn't like it?
You've said so many positive things about it and yet you're giving it this weird negative
undercurrent because it's not Chinatown. You want everything to be Chinatown.
I thought it was a good movie. I think to give it the praise that it's getting is it's
exaggerated. And I think that's the problem with everything now. Nothing can just be
good anymore. Everything has to be, it's a box office record breaking powerhouse of a
film. I didn't say it's the best. I just, I said it was good. And you said, but it's not
this. It's not that. You said it was the best. You're doing what you're mad about. You said
it was the best movie since get out. Yeah. I think it was the best horror movie since
get out. I think, and I'll say this again, we have not seen every horror movie since
get out. That's true. I think that's a gross exaggeration. Best movie I've seen, obviously.
But I need to have anybody says that they mean it's the best one they've seen. I just think
these movies come out and we see a lot of horror movies. We have a horror movie podcast.
Yes. And I think it's either everything is either up is either a disgusting disaster or the most
brilliant thing ever crafted. And I'm just like, can something just be good? It was good.
Because I go into this thing going like, okay, here we go.
And then I'm like, yeah, it was good.
Right, I would just concern yourself less
with everything you read in here before a movie comes in.
It's impossible, you can't.
I don't get that into it.
I didn't know much about a quiet place
when I went to see it.
I knew it was getting good reviews.
I mean, I wanted to enjoy it.
I hadn't seen the trailer for it.
I think that kind of stuff helps.
I liked it.
I would have liked a little more, my biggest gripe, fuck the baby and all that shit.
I would have liked a little more suspense and a little less jolt scare.
I wanted a little more Shyamalan.
I wanted a little more, I was tons of suspense.
I wanted a little more, you walk like in the visit, which is not a great movie, but it's fine.
I wanted a little more, the kid walks out of the room, sees the old lady naked staring at
the wall, doesn't understand.
I wanted a little more of that, creepiness.
But, you know, look, this is also coming off the heels
that I just re -watched, it.
And I was like, okay, I was a little hard on this movie.
It's not that bad.
It does stand on its own.
But my problem with it remains, it jumpscare.
It's my problem with the Conjuring movies.
And I really liked Conjuring too.
And I liked Conjuring one enough,
and then I thought Conjuring two was the same movie,
but a better version of it.
But it's the same thing. It's just jump scare after jump scare after jump scare
The exorcist like I why can anything be like that anymore?
Where are but that that's a very rare there wasn't a movie like the exorcist for 10 years prior for 10 years after
You know that that's a one in a million shot that movie. I'll cite a movie you love quite a bit that you've called me an idiot about
Uh, okay. Uh, Halloween. Yeah, virtually no jump scares in the original Halloween film.
Some, some, but um, you know, it's much more he lurks out of the darkness and it's weird and
creepy and, and an empty and I just want to like a little more of that. That's all I'm saying.
At the end of the day, I give the movie a solid B. Maybe a B plus. How about that? Okay.
I think perhaps you're bringing too much expectation positive and negative into the entertainment you consume
And you should try to avoid it go out of an open mind and read a review after and treat it like a discussion with an old friend
As opposed to letting it shape your opinion before going in. I didn't read any reviews and by the way mr
Go in with no expectations you fucking texted me the second you walked out of the theater said a dark a quiet place
tremendous picture killer picture.
Yeah, so that was so that was in my head that I said it's a killer picture. Yeah, and I go,
yeah, that's what I keep hearing. I'm not reading reviews. You know, a commercial comes on
for the goddamn thing. Huh? I won't text an old friend anymore to recommend a new film that
I enjoyed. You just want to hurt me. You just want to make it difficult for me. Yeah, it was
good all right yeah it was by the way thank you to what's the kid's name that
made the greatest hits oh I'm not sure I don't have my apps I have a new phone
buddy if you're out there you could find it's on your Instagram I know but I
gotta hold on let me find it can I turn on Instagram once without seeing
somebody posing sexily, male or female, I mean, it's just a
no following. I don't know. I got a gray model. I got it.
Would you say, lingerie models? Well, speedo models, mostly.
I guess I get what I'm bringing on myself. Where are we here?
Okay. Where the hell? Yeah, put together a little best of.
It's interesting to hear what one's best of might be, might
it might differ from another's.
Chris Marsh, thank you very much for the best of.
Loved listening to it,
little walk down memory line.
It was nice.
Soundcloud, it's on there.
We'll see you in hell on Instagram.
We'll see you in hell pod, I believe.
And the Facebook page.
Yes, the Instagram is see you in hell pod.
Yeah.
And the Twitter is WSYIH pod,
which is also the handle for the Patreon.
on. Thank you again, everybody donating to the Patreon. Very, very, very, very, very sweet.
Thank you. Thank you. Everybody buying the merch. That's fantastic. We're very thrilled.
Search the hoghouse on Etsy. Thank you, Emily Florence, for running all these things for
us because God knows. I mean, you hear the energy in Pat and me. We're not going to do
it. Yeah. And thank you to the fans. Thank you to everybody. I'm on Twitter and Instagram
at the Patrick Walsh show, Living Biblically is on Monday nights tonight. It's a Crumholz
tour to Forrest tonight, 839 30, one of them Central, one of them West or something, you
know how it works on CBS.
Be out, watch the show. Joe DeRosa comedy on Twitter and Instagram, but way more on Instagram.
You can check out by night origins, by night origins on Amazon Prime and regular Amazon and check it out. I hope you like it.
Do I have anything else? I'm supposed to be at Rooster T feathers at the end of May, but that's a ways off, so we'll talk about that later.
Guys, thanks a lot. We'll see you next time.
and we'll see you in hell.