Welcome to will see you a hell it's the podcast you turn to when it's time to
turn off the movies and turn on the talk wow okay all right just I'm just out
here having fun I'm just trying to play with some new stuff I mean yeah you're
turning on something else I'll tell you that much your old friend Pat with your
seamless transitions somebody's a mic stand just rose I got a pan I got to read
this panics tech message from Joe I got so I bought one microphone two weeks
later Joe's like you got to buy a different microphone I did no problem then I
get this text hey man sorry that this is a little last minute but if there's a
chance you can order a new cable for your microphone before we record on Tuesday
try and do so nothing wrong with what you have but the cable on mine just
shut out on me and I'm worried that yours might do the same I think it just comes
with a cheaper cable anyway like I said no pressure but if possible see if you
can score one overnight from Amazon or something sorry about that man it's it was
like is Joe in the end of good fellows here watching for helicopters above that
my cord would break because yours broke and you had the mic for years I know I'm
only the mic for a few months that's why but but but but I was in the I've been
moving for four or five days straight and every day I'm very happy with the new
apartment I'm very happy with the where I move to it's my favorite apartment I've
ever had in my entire life so that's pretty cool and I've had me a lot of
parts yeah yeah but it has been like kind of non -stop there's been like little
things to tend to amongst unpacking and running errand so I was sending you
that as like a man was coming in to flip the door on my refrigerator because it
was opening in the wrong direction you know that shit you know you now your
refrigerator door opened up like like the Delorean right well sort of it's
like it's like a Murphy bed it comes out of the you pull it down out of the wall
okay nice yeah and then you can lay in it if you want yeah
you asked me earlier if I moved by myself which I did I hired I hired
movers but that was it like I didn't you didn't move by yourself yeah but I mean
the unpacking and all that was solo which is very sad when you're after the
the long day you go babe what do you say we call today in order some and nobody's
there sure you could have asked the overs to stay I did I think I think the the
response was get your hand off of there okay that's a grab his dick joke folks my
mover was Terry Cruz I grabbed his junk Terry Cruz what an interesting character he's
a guy yeah he is look I know we're going through a lot as a as a country but I
would be remiss if I didn't say happy national coffee day to you Jim I didn't
even know see there's so much going on we even missed the big holidays meaning the
day that we recorded this is national coffee day for all these of you at home
scrambling to check your calendar it's past I'm sorry but it's like I need
grounds we need grounds running into the store maskless people shooting you on
site yeah yeah yeah starbucks refers this day is grounds zero because they're out of
grounds yeah ground question mark zero this is why the team works people you're
this that tandem writing a thing yeah I also happy national happy first
debates day is tonight is recording the day of the first days without movies being
released this is really what I'm most looking forward to I mean it's it's just the
thrill for once of not knowing exactly what's going to happen and that's what Trump
brings that's his one is one plus yeah no idea what you're going to watch I've
got a friend's birthday tonight which is nice yeah now I can't watch these
damn debates and I have a pile my other podcast with Karen is like about news
and stuff I need to I guess I can just watch the highlights on YouTube or something
aren't the debates on it like five the party is it's oh okay she really just put
it right where you could there was just a way around missing the debate after five
here they'd be eight there maybe I don't know yeah maybe we can maybe we can get
somebody to run a cable from inside somewhere outside like we're fucking camping
yeah I don't know we'll see I'm curious to see how these go we're probably more
realistically here how these go I don't know that I'll see much yeah I remember
when Obama was inaugurated so what's that 2012 I think I was at this bar used to
go to I believe it's been shut down but they used to do pint glass jack -and -diet
and there were seven dollars and it was walkable to my home I mean where did
where of those days gone the places of course been shut down and eventually they
caught them I think putting cheaper liquor in the bottles and stuff like that but
for seven bucks who's complaining yeah give me a beam and die cook I don't give a shit
give me a credit diet yeah seven bucks yeah a large a craig but the place was absolutely packed
and everyone was watching it was like standing room only watching this really inspirational moment
I thought for the country people are crying and there's two gals sitting in a booth just
wasted talking as loud as as you could ever imagine just oh my god he did you know like
talking right over so you couldn't hear the speech 500 people packed into this bar to watch the
speech and then two girls dominating everyone's experience so since I was next to them I felt it was
kind of upon me to go it could you guys be quiet for like ten more minutes till this is over right
and then came the loud mocking of me that went on for the remainder of it so then I made it so that
it was all focused at me now so my face was just getting redder and redder and more embarrassed as
they chewed me out loudly and then everyone kind of thought we were a group so everyone's telling
us all to shut up and this big historical moment just ruined by some seawards you know I was I
went for the first time ever to my local wine and liquor store charming little shop
co -run by a Chinese young Chinese man and then his Chinese father yes who
clearly immigrated here at some point I'm pointing that out because it make to me it makes
the story more charming so I got the dad when I went up to buy wine and they had a bottle of wine
in there that was six fifty nine okinawa and it's a nice shop it's not like you know it's not like
a sort of dumpy place and it was like I mean I mean I mean they don't even carry yellow tail
and they have that maybe that's actually good for the price sure so I asked the old Chinese man
I'm gonna do a slight Chinese accent because it doesn't make it more charming and it is how he
talked I'm not I'm not being racial but I said is there any way that six fifty nine
pinot noir is any good and he was like he was like you know when you go to restaurant and I go yeah
and he goes that's what they sell you that charge your twelve dollars of glass that's what it is
and then he started laughing hysterically like like and I started laughing because I felt like we
had really bonded he had kind of let me in on something I'm gonna start buying this
six dollar and fifty nine cent pino and then of course charging my guests twelve dollars of glass
yeah I should drink it I always used to go to this place bar bricks which is the closest to my house
and get a glass of wine with a friend or something and we became pretty close with the bartender
and he basically told us the same thing I just sat one day because we were always the only people
in there when they opened and I just started googling all the wines and they're all just cheap as
shit yeah yeah it's so imagine how much the wines are when they're charging like a thousand dollars
at a place in New York or something it's probably like a twenty dollar bomb it's criminal in some places
I went with the other night or the other week rather with Jay Okerson to get a drink yeah and it was
right after they had instated this fucking you have to buy food if you get alcohol thing so we sit
down at this bar we're like literally just like any bar let's just find a bar and just sit down every
bar in New York now as you got to buy food to drink yes yeah yeah to improve their their money
intake or what who knows and Cuomo they should be thrilled people are there I know well it's Cuomo's
law he did it okay and then and then so like dive bars started just giving you bags of like wise
potato chips okay and then he came out and goes that doesn't count it's got to be substantial food
so the sides this is this is what I'm getting at so me and Jay are just like it had been a long day
and they were just like that's kind of fucking drink man we sit down this bar I get a double jack
Daniels on the rocks he gets a double tequila on the rocks nothing crazy uh -huh lady goes you have
to order something uh two and I would say just get whatever appetizer you want I'm not hungry he's
like all right I'll just do this cheese and prosciutto thing nothing extravagant 71 dollars oh
I was like you gotta be fucking kidding me and that's you know look Cuomo like him don't like him love
him hate whatever the thing that pisses me off about that rule is it's like hey man 25 million people
are out of work I don't know what percentage of that is New Yorkers but yeah I hunch tells me
that some like pipe fitter who's out of work right now who needs to go blow off steam yeah doesn't
really want to spend 71 dollars to have like a beer and a shot because he had to order the fucking
pan seared trout with it or whatever you know what I mean like yeah it's fucking ridiculous man so
the dive bars have done they did a great thing they're all doing the great thing every dive
bar just started selling hot dogs for like a dollar or two dollars smart so you know what dive
bar's been doing that for decades Rudy's my favorite dive bar in New York they're all free Rudy's
are free yeah that's true they're bad but they're they're all free I went into Rudy's once at seven
a .m. having not slept from the night before let's not get into why at but yeah the monster energy
drink too late in the day no I had a damn cappuccino before bad I couldn't sleep yeah so I go in I
remember I was leaving I was I'd been hanging out with this woman and at like 7 30 a .m. she was
like I have to go to bed I have to work in like four hours no problem she has a bad and I'm just
like I got to find a bar that's open right now so I just start blind calling bars and the one
place that's open is Rudy's yeah and I go in I call buddy of mine I convince him to come meet me
he's like I fucking hate you all right I'm coming and as I'm saying I order a screwdriver and the
guys like you want a hot dog I would have taken it I would have taken it for some reason it seemed
crazy you're gonna eat the hot dog at 7 a .m. then have the screwdriver I can't explain why it just
seemed insane at that time I saw our old friend Jesse pop went and sat in the roost parking lot
um to do there they they have their tables and chairs about there but that you know New York
so a little by the way did he go I think he was with his girlfriend but oh I would man my hats off
if the man just went in there so low till I just saw the the Instagram I didn't uh good I told you
if I was there I'd be there every night I mean it's incredibly hot and the air is still bad like that
wore the shirt Sunday night and it reeks like a forest fire okay but I mean New York you can sort
of convince yourself you're in Paris or something you're sitting on the street you know with a umbrella
over your head the roost just has tables and chairs in a in a standard parking lot
New York is embraced it beautifully apparently they've already approved the outdoor dining for next
year again regardless of COVID right it's all become very European very bohemian there
there are bars that have installed in the like outdoor like you know covered patio areas
10 flat screen TVs like they're full on outdoor sports bars yeah um that you know like I said
the die bars all have like couches and shit outside that you can sit on and like
they're serving cheap drinks and hot dogs it's it's pretty fucking fun man when you need to when
you need to blow off a little bit of steam sure uh yeah I see people out at the outdoor restaurants
and stuff here I my one attempt was of course the uh double lunch that incident I discussed last time
but I'll get back out there everyone keeps saying you know fall it's going to come back double time
and who knows who knows um yeah I don't know um well I'm pulling up my uh you know I keep a little
file in my phone for things that I want to discuss on the show the movies I've watched I've got a great
news cycle okay um I can't remember if this came out after we last recorded or if I just forgot to
mention it uh this comes courtesy of vanity fair Francis Ford Copeland finally gets to release his
version of the godfather part three okay I was hoping you'd want to talk about this well here's
why I'm excited this film originally and he has said this over the years was supposed to be called
Coda the death of Michael Corleone right it was not supposed to be part three he has said he imputes
so didn't want to do part three it was too much there were going to be too many expectations on it
blah blah blah they just wanted to do something that summed up the life of this main character um and
apparently because of this anniversary I guess it's the 35th or something like that um Copeland was
allowed to go in recut the movie do like I guess a new soundbed for it right and he's claiming like
this version is the one that they wanted to release because he's never been happy with godfather three
it's not what he wanted either so I do feel very curious to see what uh what what comes I'm excited
I'm very excited I'll watch it for sure but um I you know I watch three within the year and was
just kind of it just did what it always did just kind of lied there it works as a as an average mob
movie I think it suffers from being part of the greatest franchise ever but um godfather's three my
thing my issue is when people do these recuts like he recut the cotton club I had never seen the cotton
club so I just I watched his version it's decent and you know when you can look online and see comparisons
between like the unrated and the r -rated stuff there's a website that does it movie
censorship .com or something but um his cotton club you know basically he put back some long musical numbers
it's a movie about jazz the jazz club so he put back some musical numbers the thing is this was a
three -hour movie I don't know how much footage you shot but like how different he can't so fee
a couple is still going to be playing the part you know it's not like he can sub in one -on -a -rider um
I never she's not she she's not what I've defended the film I I understand why people see it as
lackluster she's not what bothers me about it though uh I just think I don't know maybe the story
I don't know there's something about the story that's not quite look my glaring issue is Robert
Duval not being in there right he denied to do it that's what I was using Copa as an example of
is all these faults that are just structural faults like I mean like that that's a big problem not having
Duval uh having so fee a Copa not a more gifted actress but the story itself is not particularly
involving the movie works fine I just don't know what he's going to be able to bring to it if he if he
had no director cuts amazing scenes from the movie you know what I mean like it's not going to be
oh shit like that I can't believe he he left this on the cutting room floor because it was a three -hour
movie so I'm skeptical Copa always just needs money I mean he's a true artist in the sense that when
he makes nine cents he puts a dime into his filmmaking you know so I think he he does okay due to his
winery but all he does is hustle to make the money to make films that increasingly have lost tons
of money and he funds them almost all himself yeah I'm yeah I'm curious to see what he does I'm
what I'm hoping for ultimately and the saving grace for me of the godfather three is that you get
to see Michael Corleone his his guilt and regret about Frado I think that that's pretty great so
I am hoping that this film will have a more somber tone and be more about the emotional emotional
journey of this man in the last chapter of his life I hope who who knows um what we'll see I
don't know you know we'll see I'm eager to check it out uh at micestones it was the 30th anniversary godfather
three was 90 but um yeah I remember you know I was like nine or ten and at that point my dad like never
went to the movies you know just because when you when you have a 10 -year -old kid it's off the table
pretty much unless you're bringing the kid so but I remember godfather three being a day where it was like
I'm gonna need three hours to go to the movies and then he you know he came home I think up on it but
I think dads across the board were pretty let down by godfather three it's like when springsteen came
back I'm listening to springsteen's autobiography which is great and he reads it but um you know he's
talking about when the e -street band came back 10 years after being gone and I saw some of those shows
and he was like you know the people tried to tell me they don't want to hear just the new material you
know like what especially like spring springsteen going to play new jersey and then all these dads
getting licked up and being like yes they're back and then you come out and play land of hoping dreams or
some new song about Amata Diallo or whatever he was doing at the time um you know dads dads had it
rough in those days all the things that they think are good because you know you just think things
are gonna come back and they'll be just as good and they're never just as good right well I mean
look we're we're kind of at that age where that's happening to us now you know we're sure you know we're
seeing things come back for you know I guess the the most relevant example for me is Star Wars
and so much of the newer stuff being disappointing and you know and and you you just want it to be
the old stuff and it's not you know but then I don't know so yeah yeah I hear you uh I mean I was
and you'll think I was crazy but and the lusters worn off but I was legitimately excited that
they were gonna do a fifth Indiana Jones movie I felt like it deserved a better ending yeah
fourth film and now like Spielberg's off of it and oh they've been through eight writers and
and now with COVID the fucking things that could have come out to like he's like 85 it's like
it's kind of a bummer man who'd they get like to direct a Trevor Roe or something uh no it's the guy
that directed uh I got a directed Logan and uh didn't he direct copland as well
Bames Mangold yeah yeah well good for him I mean he's a great guy cool he is yeah and like you know
like any other franchise directors change and yeah and whatever but uh you know it's just kind of
uh it's just kind of a bummer that like everybody kind of waits a little too long to do the thing
yeah you know we lucked out with the Irishman but like when righteous kill came out it was like
they waited too fucking long man and then like luckily this weird technology comes out and they get
to do this epic thing together but like you know you see these things and you're like why didn't you do
episode seven eight and nine when everybody was in their fifties yeah I think what happens is all these
actors don't want to fuck up their legacies and they they made one perfect thing they don't want to
fuck it up so everybody involved and these generally with something like this are the most powerful
people in Hollywood Spielberg Harrison Ford whoever else uh they all just say we won't shoot until
it's perfect we got to get it right we can't let the fans down and they do this for so long that
they wind up yeah almost guaranteed ten drafts passed the best one in pursuit of the perfect one
and then they just go well we've all got six months free in our schedules let's just shoot this one
that we all know doesn't work it's why invariably an amazing draft of these big movies will come out
five years later they used to put them up on a cool news or whatever and everybody's like well this
is way better why didn't they do this it's just because of egos and money and and on and on you know
it's yeah it's like it's it's it's it's the classic too many cooks yes everybody's getting
dated cap who was the one of the previous writers on this Indiana Jones movie who left so James
mangold could bring in his own writer like out of respect for mangold uh kept left and uh he said
he was like we just couldn't get it to the place where everybody was happy uh everybody's got to be
happy and he's like and I'm not going to sit there and be the old writer with his arms crossed telling
mangold like well Stephen wouldn't have done that he's like that's a fucking drag sure
but you know man the the worst misstep to me was they had young castin on it
yeah who did a stellar job with solo he did clearly has a respect for the you know Lucas film
his dad it was part of the original indie film it's like why the fuck was that kid taking off
you know like yeah a lot of times it's just completely personal politics and you know it's like
just like how a new executive like let's say you've got a show on the air and a new executive comes
in they're always looking to cancel the previous guys shows the previous guys successes I think
what happens is James mangold comes on and he's like well I'm a big director I did do all these big
movies and I just coming off forward versus Ferrari I'm not going to inherit Spielberg's world I've got
to do this my way and it really just boil down to ego and I'm sure these are fine people or maybe
they're not but it just boils down to everyone wanting full credit you know like yeah because people
know everything now people know that the Lord and Miller were fired off solo and Ron Howard came in
and so on and so forth they they know all these facts so I don't know I'm really trying to cover
their ass that's why I've always hated a big writers room yeah for everything we're talking about I
don't want to hear 10 pitches on a punchline I just don't get too funny guys in there and have them
work it until the joke works and then move the fuck on man yeah but you get in there with 10
fucking people and everybody's got to get the thing in and everybody's got and it's Jesus fucking
Christ man it's too much it's overkill and then like you said you you go through a drive was on one
show and we would just I mean every script was rewritten I think at one point it was it's a draft
43 that's a nightmare or something and I remember telling that story to Vince Gilligan
when I was doing an episode of Better Call Saul he was directing it and it was the first time
ever I met him before but I never worked with him yeah and we were just in between setups and I was
telling that that was like how many drafts of a script you guys do he's like oh no man you know
couple yeah yeah I told that story and he was like there's no reason for that man no yeah it was
nuts it was crazy well the big note you know multi -cam is changing every day and the big note is always
like on Tuesday when you're taping Friday night like well let's just throw this one out and start
from scratch executive loves saying that and you have to be the one going no I'd rather patch up the
couple of issues with this one which is how the process works yeah they think somehow that's
starting from scratch and like okay so you're not going to have any problems with whatever thing we
come up with in six hours yeah they treat it like they treat it like an old casino they're just like
it's got to be leveled so we can build a better foundation because this new thing is state of the art
it's right oh god all right yeah it's a drag man anyway um
hey why don't you take us down I will but remind me when we record next that I have a couple uh
you know scream at ends well do you know what about us no I'm good I'll hold off we we we we we we we're
we're on we're on good time um so yes we're heading over to the movie corner sure all right um
um Joe would you like me to start if you want to go for it okay by the way today on the show we're
doing Capone um with Tom Hardy which I'm eager to get to um okay I saw I saw a movie that I had
long heard about as being a great cult lost movie of the eighties and I had never seen it called the
hidden with Kyle McLaughlin I've never seen that Michael Nory uh it is you know it's not a
lost masterpiece but it's a great kind of lost cult eighties movie I I rented it for two or three
bucks on Amazon I was glad I did so a really neat story um I think that you it's directed by Jack
shoulder who did night bar on Elm Street 2 and then this and then kind of not much else which is
weird because he's a good director this movie is pretty cool um and it's an early new line it's
it's Robert Che producing and then of course Lin Che has a small role okay but um it is a movie the
guy Jim Kof who wrote stakeout and a bunch of movies rush hour national treasure et cetera he wrote
this under a pseudonym so apparently he wasn't proud of it um which is nuts it's a completely
original creative movie it's basically about it's kind of like the thing where there's an alien on
earth who inhabits various people um an older businessman a sexy stripper a dog at one point much
like the thing and so basically comic lock then a Michael Nory are trailing this alien but they can
only kill it when it is between hosts which is kind of a cool gimmick that's what what does it
look like between hosts is it look cool disgusting alien but on a low budget uh it looks great I mean
they did a good job with it but um it's got some great effects some great like action some great
explosions some great like 80s music it's just a cool movie um and then you can't really call it a
twist because you find out very early but you know the scene where the like they have it in seven where
Brad Pitt invites Morgan Freeman over to have dinner with him and his wife
yeah yeah sure it's a big scene they didn't leave the weapon too except in that move those
movies it was always them like watching Danny Glover take a bath for some reason his whole family
surrounding him as he takes a non bubble bath so presumably his children can all see his penis
but um the hidden is uh the the twist and I'm you know I guess turn it off for 30 seconds but it's not
that biggest boiler is that McLaughlin is an alien and he is coming from his planet to get the guy
who killed his wife and daughter so it's it's a it's just a wild movie and they play it pretty straight
like it now how does this tie into the Danny Glover lethal weapon scene they uh they
they um he invites him over to his house and that's where they learn that there's like something wrong
with the guy oh I see like you're saying it's like when they have bell Gibson over and they're like
this guy is weird yes so it's a little off here I got the thing that's off about McLaughlin is that
he's an alien but um I did recently watch lethal weapon two again it it is so so nuts that his whole
family just watches him take a bath in that movie and then Mel Gibson comes in and it's like hey guys
anyway uh so yeah I recommend the hidden if you haven't seen it it's really hard to find because I
had tried to find it for years and and Amazon uh seems to be the only game in town to rent it
I'm gonna get a rewatch out of the way uh but it's worth mentioning uh I I re and only for the
second time of my life I rewatch there will be blood yes I mean what what is there to say it's a
masterpiece yeah it's just an impeccable film in my opinion from the films I've seen of Daniel
De Lewis it's hands down his best performance uh I was not a fan of the master which is
Paul Thomas Anderson's favorite film that he's ever made I tried to watch inherent vice you've
told me to revisit it I maybe I will one day but I couldn't get into it it's it's his worst for sure
but it's uh I rewashed it recently and liked it more than I did in theaters but it's still a lot down
I had no interest in phantom thread um love to missed out maybe I need to see that but I mean there
will be blood to me is sort of I feel like it's sort of a line in in Paul Thomas Anderson's
trajectory to me that's sort of the end of an error that to me that movie is the end of the
error that started with book unites for me uh -huh like his films after that one feel very different to me
um you know obviously inherent vice has very very much has like a Cohen brothers kind of vibe to it
the master plays a little more like one of the uh Kubrick movies that I would be less interested in
and um and I haven't seen phantom thread but but anyway uh I there will be blood is
it's just fucking incredible man it's incredible the movie is incredible he's in everybody is incredible
yeah uh I mean I you you don't dislike you love Paul Dano so much that you like Daniel
Day Lewis yeah and Daniel Day Lewis is such a bastard in this movie but you he's a bastard that
you respect and god damn it man uh who can relate to a man slowly going insane and imagine until he
eventually beats someone to death with a bowling club drunk yeah we we've all been there yeah
eating uh I my favorite uh detail that's seen that he's eating pork chops with his hands
just with that on the off of that plate and I always wonder is like that was that Daniel Day Lewis's
choice like I want a meeting I want to show that this man is devolved into a complete animal yeah
you meet off the bone with his hands sitting on the ground um drinking you know in his private
bowling alley but uh but what's it called I uh uh uh one of the things I like to do with movies
that are considered you know fair more or less across the board is impeccable I like to look at the
rotten tomato score and it'll always be like very rarely is it a hundred percent uh it's usually like
96 % I love to go through the top critic reviews and just be like what miserable piece of shit
sure gave this movie the one bad review I did it with platoon the other day um that's like who's the
one person that gave us a bad review yeah and I was some lady like you know that was just like
oh for all the guts there's no glory just a bunch of man acting what you know you're like uh uh
all right well I mean I'll admit the first time I saw it I I didn't love it I certainly
uh was was positive on it but I was just kind of like huh I need to give that another shot um and
I've watched it many times since and now of course I love it but it was a pretty difficult movie to
get into for me right off the bat for summaries I think because his other movies boogie nights
magnolia whatever are so different from it they're like relentlessly action packed and there
will be blood as much more slow so I think they're I think they're I think they're upon rewatch I did
find it a little more action oriented than I thought yeah I should say a vent oriented there's a lot
of shit that goes wrong yeah uh injuries and tragedies and and murderers and all these things um but uh
I uh the first like I said I'm only seeing it twice now the first time I watched it I was legitimately
disturbed at how much I was by a quarter of the filthway into the film relating to him as a human being
sure and I was like I'm not the conversation with several male friends never a woman but
yeah well and then Phantom Thread is nowhere near the movie that there will be blood is but it is about
basically a man who can't who wants to do his creative thing his gift but keeps getting interrupted by
the woman in his life and you got imagine he's writing that with his actual wife and family and
in the next room trying to connect to him you know but um he's he's one of our best easily he's
easily one of the best filmmakers there is yeah there's a new book coming out on him called masterworks
that's like one of these nice coffee table books and it's not too expensive I already pre -ordered my
copy but I like to one of the best imagine what it was like when Jordan Peele was writing get out
yeah uh the story of a black man going home to his white girlfriend's family and then
and then as Chelsea Peretti his newly wed wife yeah coming in the room what you're working on honey
and him just saying like nothing nothing nothing uh huh and then the family I assume goes see the movie
and blah blah yeah yeah it was an ex -girlfriend an ex -girlfriend yeah it turns into like a woody Allen film
for Jordan Peele you know who's the big uh the big critic who's like he's the anti -Peter Travers
who loves everything but this guy Armand White who has long been a New York film writer uh if not
the village voice you know similar papers like that but he's just this miserable guy who waits until
he sees what everyone says about a movie and then he says the opposite thing is passionately as he
can he's been doing it for decades look up just google like Armand White's craziest reviews and you'll
find and I think he loved Norbert by the way so you'll find some common ground there uh he sounds a lot
like Sandy Tankin I think his name is Sandy Kenyon or Sandy Kenyon yeah yeah and he's the cab draw you
know he's the cab uh movie review guy yeah and then he's on whatever TV show but he's my favorite
because he doesn't like anything yeah except absurd movies like Norbert like those are the ones
that he'll rave about but like just insane some of his fucking reviews well it's a perfect transition
into my number two pick which is a documentary called What She Said the Art of Pauline Kale
um this movie by the way it's like I think people are slowly catching onto this as the movie business
changes you know it does massive you what would have taken decade long changes every weekend now
but um this movie the Pauline Kale movie it was on Amazon for 599 three weeks ago then one day it was
299 and then within a month it's free on Amazon Prime so any movie any new movie you want to buy
on Amazon Prime wait a couple weeks if you can and I think for most of these you can uh and save yourself
some money but uh Pauline Kale to me there's Kale people and there's Ebert people I think uh you
know I'm I'm 1 billion percent an Ebert person Kale seemed like a snob Ebert never did Kale
seen her and Kale's whole thing is that she's mispopulous and like sometimes movies can just be fun
and what's wrong with that and I like her she's obviously a gifted writer but when you see her talk
and interview she seems so superior and dismissive uh and snobby that I can't really like her she has
a cool story I mean she she fought and kind of clawed her way to the top as a woman which is cool
the documentary is is average you know any documentary about a writer is usually not that
exciting and this is no different but um you know Pauline Kale is they they go into some of her more
controversial reviews and her shitting on Lawrence of Arabia and um what's interesting is stuff like
her reviews would get her fired from papers and get her death threats and stuff like that so it kind of
predates the fan culture that we have now but you know any film fans should know something about Pauline
Kale this is kind of a good place to start but um you know to me I'm just gonna buy one of her used
collections and read more of her stuff she's fine I'll check it out there's a great writer but I
there's something about a personality that kind of keeps me at a distance she also Warren
Beatty brought her in to like develop movies with him in the 70s and she moved out to LA and then I
think realizing that the movie she was working on was not gonna be a success she like quit doing that
out of the blue you know and it's the classic critic thing of the second they're given the tool to do it
they collapse but um I don't know she's an interesting woman I think Paul Shrader and other people
talk about having big personal problems with her I think she was difficult but she's uh she's a
good writer and the documentary is fine Mike message Jonathan Cazden is Lawrence Cazden's son and he
is currently writing Indiana Jones five all right okay great him and man gold I mean I'm there I'm
there you could tell me you know uh Sophia Loren was directing it I'd go see it
so that's what I could think of Jesus Christ I was trying to think of Elizabeth Banks
anyway uh I will go to a copula movie the time to the godfather news I watched I'd never seen it
all the way through but I finally watched rumble fish yeah good movie beautifully shot
uh as you've said Pat one of these movies any frame of it could be put into a frame one and hung
on your wall yeah impeccably acted by the great Mickey Rourke the great Matt Dylan uh this is one
of those pictures where the great uh Diane Lane this is one of those pictures where uh I it sends me
in a rabbit hole on YouTube where I watch the transfer the slow transformation of Mickey Rourke
yeah you know you there's only a few actors you can do that with like Pacino's one
Rourke is one well imagine how like when you were I I mean if you when you were on Facebook if you
get tagged in a photo or something and you'd be like oh man I looked so much better 10 years ago
or something imagine what Rourke thinks when he looks at himself I mean he was a male model and we
looks like dog the bounty hunter I think he thinks he looks great I don't think there's a I don't think
but yeah I hear you he's got it's it's it's a strange look uh what an actor though man it's like I
just you know like it's a shame because he's sort of I think kind of re -crazyed his way out of
Hollywood again and it's a bummer man because he's a fucking tremendous actor still is uh anyway rumble
fish did I enjoy it it's fine I mean it's you know it's like a darker outsiders it's the same
author based on a book by the same author um a lot of the people from the outsiders were recast in this
it's a plenty enjoyable Vincent Spano's enjoy everybody's really good at it and it's very
well -directed and impeccably shot it's just not that interesting of a film it's it sort of takes place
in this weird reality where it's not quite a period piece it's sort of present day
but everybody's sort of acting like it's the fifties uh -huh that's never really clarified which
is interesting and surreal um I just didn't find the subject matter that interesting that this gang leader
named motorcycle boy whatever his name is his come home and and you know he's gotta try to redeem his
little brother somehow through his own decline or you know I don't know yeah it's it's it's certainly
an art house type pick um I think Robert Evan said that when he saw this movie I think the quote was
I was worried about Coppola he had strayed so far from Hollywood at this point
which I would never worry about a guy for doing that but I mean you want to talk about a movie that
is just wholly unmarketable on every level uh in the time period it came out I mean this thing would
have flown under the radar in the seventies yeah let alone in the in the in the in the basically
almost mid eighties I saw it right after the outsiders like maybe 13 years old or something and I remember
like long shots of a fish bowl coming to mind uh make you want to see yeah they brought it out on
criterion yeah of course and you know look I own some of the criterion collection and I have great
respect for what they do but this film like so many of the criterion releases yeah criterion gives a
lot of points for effort they give me they give a big E for effort and they also give a big T for
nice try so like yeah they're not too concerned at the end of the day whether you were entertained
for two hours not watching this film right more concerned with what the guy was trying to do yeah uh
this is certainly one of those movies for me um you know that said I wouldn't necessarily turn it
off again uh I wouldn't necessarily turn it on again yes it's just kind of one of those flicks I'm glad
I saw it but uh but it didn't light my world on fire I love Matt Dylan and it though man Matt
Dylan is I want to see more Matt Dylan so I started watching the House of Jack build I need to finish
it I would love to review that on the show because he's good in that I reviewed it on the show at that
time but yeah maybe oh then maybe we just do a movie corner but yeah I that there's a lot to that's
a fascinating performance it is and I think a weirdly slept on movie considering how
beloved Lars von Trier is but the problem is he goes to these festivals and says like maybe
Hitler was right and then that becomes the story and nobody pays attention to the movie but uh can I
jump in and just tell you something like just send another update on Indiana Jones and you want to
talk about just a kick to the nuts Kazden actually was pulled off the project for Dan Fogelman co -creator
of this is us that's nuts I knew something bad happened that's just nuts I mean he has also made some
movies but um anything like Indiana Jones no and actually his last one was one of the most heavily
criticized movies of the past few years it was despised he wrote cars broke the cartoon the Disney
thing yeah yeah exactly the Pixar thing but um yeah he did uh life itself was his particularly hated
one that came out of fear is back with Oscar Isaacs the guilt trip with Seth Rogan and Bar was
rising right six crazy stupid love Fred Claus is a is a is a passable Christmas movie you know it's a good
family you watch it with your mom and dad kind of thing yeah I mean the guy not the guy throw on to
Indiana Jones uh everyone I know uh who watches this is us loves it maybe it's great but yeah that
does not seem a good fit he doesn't really do action even so let's say Harvey Firestein is brilliant
I wouldn't hire him to write you know the return of the Jedi reboot although I wouldn't mind saying it
I'd like him to just start voicing uh C3PO with no explanation goodness gracious me
we got to get the drill yeah good guys good news guys we just gave Bogosian his own star wars trilogy
all right um I watched the documentary that people are buzzing about called class action park
oh man I'm dying to see that it's on HBO Max I was baffled by this movie it was
class action park is a notoriously dangerous theme park um where the rides were just completely insane and
without regard for the safety of children or people that were there not far off from where I grew up
as a lad it's New Jersey correct yeah action park was was was infamous at our go no I wasn't allowed to
yeah that that place and our six flags which was called great adventure yeah uh also had a couple
issues nothing like action park right but between those two we were I wasn't allowed I we were only
I was only allowed to go to Dorey Park yeah and Hershey Park okay it's a very strange documentary they
they have a few comedians who basically do best week ever style riffs about going there as children
Chris Gatherer who is a comedian I have no real opinion of um more of a storyteller type guy like
Probeglia but he is featured on camera telling stories about action park for I would say 45 minutes of
this movie so and he's funny his stories are great but really it just seems like either they
interviewed a bunch of people and nobody had as good as stories as him so they just stuck with him
right or something but it's like every time they cut back to him you're like so is this Chris
Gatherer presents you know and it's not his fault that he was so entertaining that they let him take over
the movie but it I bet you it was I bet you it was shot when he was having not only faded but he
he had a pretty big pop like two years ago yeah with the HBO special and everything and I bet it was
probably shot around then and they were already excited to have him and then it was like oh shit like
he's gonna be like probably calling card it almost seems like maybe they promised like we'll have
all kinds of comedians come in and do it and then they only got a couple to come in as what could
have happened to but regardless you just start to feel a little strange about him him him basically
narrating this thing since that's not what he's there for to be like the host of this documentary
so anyway it's funny stories it's crazy stories that got some footage they've got people that worked
at the park talking and they're all funny and interesting then all of a sudden it takes this really
dark turn where it's talking about the people who's who died at the park yeah so there's families
grieving you know like sobbing and and the the owner of that park was a you know monster blah blah and
the tone changes 100 % then in the last five minutes which to me is where the whole movie fell apart
they combine the two so you've got Chris Geather literally going he's telling he's basically laughing and
kind of doing what you do if you're trying to like be funny and and get a documentary but he's
just going like hey tell you what maybe it wasn't safe maybe a couple of people died but that's what
it was baby fuck you if you didn't like action park and he's kind of clearly doing it with a little
glint in his eye sure yeah while he is saying it they play him saying fuck you that's what action park
was all about baby over footage of the family going to the cemetery and laying flowers on their
dead son's grave and then credits if I was Chris Geather I would sue them I would say so you're
going to use me to to make up all the comedy and narration of this documentary I'm sure he made
nothing for it then you're also going to make it look like I'm taunting families of dead people I
think he has a case to sue them frankly it drove me nuts the documentary is sort of worth watching
everyone I know seen it and has an opinion on it but that ending to me is one of the craziest
things I've ever seen in a doc in my life all right I'll close this out with a little bridge of
Matt Dylan yes into another project of his that I recently watched wayward pines oh I thought you're
going to talk about Capone oh no he's it oh shit I forgot he isn't yeah Pone okay good well I'm
glad I weren't with these Dylan movies well it's wayward pines the TV show I think produced by
Shyamalan Shyamalan yeah was that on Fox a few years back based on a trilogy of books
the it's it only went for two seasons first season stars Matt Dylan it stars oh what's your name
from Wintersbone oh Melissa Leo yeah Melissa Leo she's fantastic Toby Jones right yeah
I think it's right put it number two yeah just a really stellar cast of people though actually the
woman from and I haven't seen her in years the woman from rules of attraction is in it that she
in rules of attraction she plays the college girl that's obsessed with James Vanderbeek and then
like he doesn't even know who she is Michelle Moynihan I like her yeah right no not Michelle Moynihan she's
got dark hair no I'll know her when I see her she likes things that she's going out with this guy
and then like you know what I mean remember that and then I do he doesn't even know who it is anyway
great cast isn't live Tyler in it no but Shannon Saasaman yes I know it was a double
Julian Juliet Lewis is in it that's what you're thinking here oh okay okay she's in it a little bit
the sun is the kid from something or other I forget but you know you didn't know anyway wayward pines you
know typical sci -fi kind of beginning to this thing you know guy gets into an accident wakes up in a town
where nothing seems to really make sense everybody's acting a little weird you're wondering if it's
here and they do an excellent job throughout that first season of every time you think you figured it
out there's a new twist to let you know it's completely not what you thought it was going to be
I enjoyed the first season and there were there were if you are going to go in and watch it I
won't ruin what the twists are but but just know this there are some dips you're gonna have to
they're gonna be moments where you're like I get it I know where this is going on board trust me
just push through that because they will keep surprising you and as they keep surprising you you'll
be glad that you set in and and and got through the parts where you kind of assumed you knew what was
happening uh season one very strong uh very enjoyable then comes season two which I got I
think one episode into and was like I'm done I don't give a shit at all anymore uh and here's why
I went into season two knowing that season one was based on the entire trilogy of books
they took the whole trilogy and did a whole season on it so immediately I'm like well then what the
fuck is season two the way the first season ends is the end of the books themselves like what are we
doing here and sure enough season two begins and it's a completely different direction than season one
even if I don't know it might have been written by the guy that wrote the books I don't know I just
it wasn't as interesting um uh also none of the characters from season one are are heavily featured
because they took something like three years to get the ball on season two rolling and by the time
they got it rolling all of the characters had moved on to other projects so they couldn't they couldn't
come back so it's it's very very separate it it feels almost almost like when they reboot a tv show with
a new cast or something uh and it takes place in that same universe but now here's then it actually
you know what it reminds me of what the new uh home coming looks like like homecoming season one was so
great and that podcast was so great and now they have season two and it's all new characters and I'm
like I don't give a shit it's really hard to get interested I know like I really like to homecoming and
I have no real interest in season two and it's not even that I'm some huge Julia Roberts fan or
something it's just kind of well now you're making me basically decide if I want to watch another
show a different show and I don't right I do uh Fargo does the same thing but I think does a really
good job of keeping it interesting although Fargo seasons one and two or some of my favorite tv of all
time I thought three was not great this fourth season I mean Chris rock is has never to my
mind given a performance I don't think he's an actor and I certainly don't think he's a good actor he's
one of the best anaps of all time who is he playing and why is he in Fargo season four I uh I don't know
I mean I I think he was a public fan of the show and then Noah Hawley who writes a directs it
contact him and asked him to do it but I it basically I think they needed a uh a black mob boss in Kansas
city I just think that is it's sometimes casting against the grain works but only if you have an actor
who's really skilled Chris Rock isn't even a good comedic actor and it's weird that somebody that
funny would would not be but he's not it's just you got to call it what it is um I have great respect
for Chris rock but I don't think that he's a he's a tremendous actor and I but listen here's the thing
he's a competent enough actor he's a distracting casting choice for sure he's not able to disappear
into roles no so when you have somebody with that distinct of a personality that distinct of a voice
yeah and I mean the sound of his voice uh you can't it's it's too much it doesn't make any sense
you're the whole time you're like wait what you know like yeah like you know it's it's just distracting
it's just very distracting so and now he's doing this saw reboot now yeah I mean he's clearly just
bored with comedy or something but it's like you know you're one of the best to do it so we're kind
of new special but like I I don't know anybody who wants to watch Chris Rock and Fargo like they're
just piling up my DVR this used to be my favorite show well that's the thing too if you're gonna cast
Chris Rock in a serious role cast him the way you cast like Gabe Shapel in a star is boring
you know what I mean don't sure don't give him something that is so it's like when
when they cast Tiny Lister as the president in the fifth element and you're like guys this is insane
yeah you know meanwhile you have Chris Tucker in there who could have done that part and pulled it off
right and make Tiny Lister the goofy guy with the bleach blonde hair in the cane you know like
it's like what the fuck are you guys doing man Tiny Lister die I don't think so he used to be in
everything he's got a sizable part in Jackie Brown forgot saying yeah all right let's get to
the film that's three each we did three each let's do it well and let me quickly finish the fourth when
I was gonna do the big picture Christopher guests non improv type movie written with Michael McKean
about Kevin Bacon who comes to Hollywood to make it big in the business beat some down I should have
like this much more I saw it when I was a kid Martin Short steals the show as an agent with some
sort of bizarre facial tics I mean Martin Short is incredible in it is a scene where Kevin Bacon goes to
dinner with the agent and Martin Short is basically talking to everyone in the restaurant except the
person he's at the table with so he steals it it's got some kind of funny things to say about film
but we're already so far past it that it can't help but feel a little dated it's a pretty funny
move in them all right jump movie is Capone the movie is Capone I'd refer to it as a
generalist film I don't know what this why look I'll say this much right off the bat between
Gotti and Capone keep them coming if you want to make yeah some you know you're you're fucking
a passion project that's a tribute to your favorite mobster please go out there and do it because
these things have been just just joy rides for me I mean if you have to compare them
Capone to me is not anywhere near as entertaining as Gotti was we reviewed Gotti on the show and it's
trying to do something kind of interesting so it's Josh Trank who directed chronicle which was
of course a hit and acclaimed and written by Hollywood sweetheart Max Landis but then he did this
fantastic for that basically became a complete shit show he quit before he could get fired he's
publicly shot on the movie etc so now for his comeback project where you got to just be terrified
because you know one more and you're out of the game for him to make this movie this guy must be
completely nuts which I love and yeah that the movie is a biopic I hate biopics but it bizarrely
insanely whatever you want to call it chooses to focus on the last couple years of Capone's life
where he is slowly dying of syphilis and dementia so the movie both opens and closes with him
violently shitting himself firstly pisses himself at Christmas no thanks giving yeah in front of the
fire then there's the scene where he shits himself yeah in in such a manner that shit could never
have sprayed like that yeah I mean unless you're just having diarrhea in your pants but it was completely
outside all over like up his back you know yeah then the last time he shits himself it's in the scene
where the FBI is interrogating him with Neil Brennan as his accountant no lawyer
boy you're right you know we just talked about distracting casting Neil Brennan sitting there and then
Capone starts shitting his pants and you honestly don't know if it's supposed to be funny or not
because because you're hearing the farts you're hearing the you know they cut to every person at the
table going like whoo fanning their notes yeah yeah it turns into like this clump scene uh Tom Hardy
is literally doing like Al Bundy faces he's going like oh uh uh uh uh it's ridiculous it's
fucking crazy man my take on the movie is this I don't think I like Tom Hardy I was fooled early on by
Bronson and so forth and I was like wow this guy's great because he's acting so much but it's as if
Daniel de Lewis only had that there will be blood gear right you know Tom Hardy only does
these big operatic performances that sometimes are completely out of place he's always acting in a
different movie than the one that he's in I I actually thought Hardy's performance was good um
I mean look it's a weird role I was kind of I was a little perplexed as to why he was so drawn
to it well it didn't seem like an enjoyable role to play it didn't seem like a fun movie to be in
it didn't seem like a really script and I could only think that this guy just wanted the challenge
of this or maybe he was coming off of something big and he was like I want something where I sit
yeah and I don't have to do a lot of movement uh maybe that's what it was where I can have my face
made up with like luncheon meats every morning to show how the rashes of syphilis are taking over my
face and body and then also too like now I actually look this up he does this very strange voice
through this thing like it's very like it is the voice of stripe the headgremlin yeah yeah yeah
and I looked it up and I actually found a few articles on it that said like his voice was apparently
fairly accurate like this apparently is what Capone sounded like okay which fine but it doesn't
mean that it is not entirely distracting it's incredibly fucking distracting it sounds very
put on it takes a while to get used to it and get past it where you're not just kind of coming out
of the movie every time you hear it yeah because he's playing it in some scenes for comedy I would say
the scene with Louis Armstrong which is easily one of the most insane scenes I've ever witnessed
and the second movie of the year to feature a lengthy cameo from somebody being Louis Armstrong the
other one being Bill and Ted but he's making faces with the camera like oh while Louis Armstrong sings
and you know I'm sure Tom Hardy is a handful on set and he's gonna do what he's gonna do but like
some of the choices in this movie are mad yeah and I and as I said earlier generalist because
it's not really a mob movie it's not really a thriller it's not really a psychological
no not really a horror it kind of dips its tone to all of these pools at one point or another
uh and ends up just being a documentation of the part of one man's life that you don't want to
say this is Al Capone they're talk about the one phase of his life you don't it's like hey do you
want to see the part out this is like phantom menace shit want to see the part of Darth Vader's life
when he's a good kid no yeah let us see the part of Al Capone's life where he doesn't kill anybody
and shit himself no no I don't want to show me when he's like give me untouchables Al Capone when he's
tough fucking asshole and doing crazy shit all the time like that's what's interesting well I I mean
Al Capone that somebody describes him in the movie is like what is the difference we know Al Capone
and Hitler Hitler is dead you know apparently this horrifying monster and if you're just watching him
sort of literally sit in his own shit for two hours and beat his wife Linda Cartelini the most
thankless role probably of the year Linda Cartelini walks in and goes like well you've got to be
nicer Capone and then he slaps her across the face or whatever else yeah but then there's also a lot
of the to make her role even more thankless yeah scenes where it's like can he just hear or did he just
imagine that like what the fuck is going on here like I mean that's the point yeah they lean into
the unreliable narrator thing and it it builds steam as the movie goes until he's like full on fantasizing
about whatever that was at the end where the ocean comes over and you know there's like a big wave
you remember that at the end yeah yeah you know I didn't know what was even happening there at that
point but basically he is I don't think he he did a great job it's a memorable performance but I
didn't like him in it I didn't like learning about Capone I I knew what kind of what I would I
thought he was actually in that movie gangster squad where he I thought he'd already like played
Capone he was also that those twin gangsters in that movie that I didn't see that came out a
few years back you know my policy legend twin movies I know I refuse he just seems like a guy who's
just gunning for an Oscar and he'll do anything to get it but he's choosing the wrong parts and
it's always sort of awkward but Harrington says he's great in legend okay I have the screener they
send it out as an Oscar thing kind of I'll never watch it it's probably like sure something but
Capone I wanted to watch because like Gotti it kind of started getting this legend you know of like
you won't believe this thing and it's not that fun and it's not so bad it's good it's just very
strange and it's all over the place and you sort of got to admire the chances it takes I just wouldn't
recommend it to anybody I didn't like it no I'd say the same there's a chance at like Christmas I might
tell my mom to watch it because she likes gangster stuff and like maybe she would find this
interesting to see what it's not I mean really my grandpa died of Alzheimer's and like what it
winds up being is like sort of a depressing an accurate depiction of what happens when you have
Alzheimer's really has nothing to do with him being a mobster I think that the movie they thought
they were making was the tail end of the Irishman which either the Irishman came out and they were
like fuck or they just realized they're not gonna do it better so they went this other way but it's
not the Irishman and it's not really anything it's about Alzheimer's in Trump's defense which I
have no desire to defend the man but it was originally supposed to be called funzo right and I feel like
we did not necessarily get the movie that he intended to make but he is standing by this thing
and saying that he's very proud of it or whatever so maybe this is what he intended to make as soon as
they renamed it Capone I was like oh this is in trouble that's a terrible title yeah like it's not
intriguing at all like it's boring well funzo then everybody just thinks it's about the fonds unfortunately
right yeah so it's you know but it's it's there there is no juxtaposition in this film
if you got to see because here's the thing even when they start showing flashbacks from his life
to to to like the days of him being more of an animal yeah in those flashbacks he's in his current state
right so you never see the juxtaposition of the the monster versus the shell of the monster
you just see the shell of the monster the whole time and it it's it's kind of like if you turn a movie
on you know I don't agree with this assessment but it's kind of like what Stephen King said he doesn't
like about the shining where he's like Nicholson is crazy from the jump so there's nowhere to go
I felt like this sort of that that type of thing with this it's like he's just he's already incapacitated
and out of his mind from the jump so there's nowhere to go like it gets worse yeah in a sense of
will now he's shitting his pants in public right it's not that very of a degree so you never see
what he gave up what he's lost what he used to look like what he you know like I guess you sort
of know that Al Capone had this big life but it's like I don't know it there's none of that there's
no there's nothing to give you to give credence to why the FBI thinks he's faking it
and you know and bugging him to see that he's faking it or prove that he's faking it you never
get any information about these guys that are strong arming the doctor right find out where this
hidden ten million dollars is which is this odd subplot that goes absolutely nowhere literally nowhere
find the money so you you get you see none of the persecution of the family
in this from the surrounding community that led to the wife changing her name and kind of living
the rest of her life and hiding sort of yeah you see none of these things there's no conflict the only
conflict is this guy that we all loved because we say we loved him which makes you not like these people
that much because apparently an asshole in a in the state of deterioration and it's like well
it gives a shit I don't for I don't care you know like it's like when you it's like when you invite
your old high school buddy over but now he's 50 and fat and you're like this guy was the man tell him
the story about that you know like don't come in the story I wasn't there I don't give a shit yeah
so yeah I'm gonna say a hog down my hog is down I respect a giant swing failure more than I do
just a boring not trying failure so I'll give it a little bit of prop but um not a fan and you know
the sopranos did the is he or is he not faking dementia thing with uncle junior and it was hilarious
and suspenseful and weird and they probably got it from the actual alcohol poem story but just it's
just a strange to like see it played out in this way that like they don't even really get the dramatic
stakes of that right the easy faking it or not like you never you never care you're never um there's no
suspense it's a very odd and almost claustrophobic movie that you just kind of want to be over
and also this is one of those biopics that is that rests on you having a working knowledge of
Al Capone right if you don't know who Al Capone is which let's face it a lot of fucking millennials
probably don't yeah uh you know a younger audience somebody tuning into this is gonna be like who
is this guy and who gives a shit and what you know like you can't you know you watch a movie like
a shimler's list you don't need to go read about the holocaust first you you know what I mean
like it like you shouldn't have to do a Wikipedia dig before you watch a film so you understand who
this person was and what he did and all that stuff so um and Josh tranks thanks I thought
chronicle was way fucking overrated um I thought I didn't see fantastic four I thought it was
terrible I couldn't have had less interest in this now I mean the balls on this fucking guy
I mean apparently he's an asshole that's a lot of positive stuff but whatever uh but Matt
Dylan as we said is in this and gives a very nice performance he's fine calma colloclin it's
always weird to see him playing somebody normal but he was fine yeah uh it's weird to see him play
somebody who's kind of weak yeah right you know uh cartilini you can almost see on her face
that she's just wanting to be given anything more to do you know it's just a really nothing part um
yeah and the the the movie isn't great but uh I did on my letterbox account somebody commented that
drink and hearty hit it off because of their shared love of vaping and Tom hearty basically
agreed to do the movie because he loves to vape so there you go all right it's gonna take some times
maybe uh that's our show uh next episode we are discussing color out of space yes uh I'm at the
i'll be there for that color out of space episode that's all I got uh
uh joderosa comedy on instagram and twitter joderosa comedian on facebook uh and also
without a country worker in fishroom i self discuss the news and try to find some sane middle ground
between the hard left and the hard right uh only on gas digital uh exclusively every Tuesday night
seven p .m. is live stream and then it hits public podcasts outlets such as iTunes every Saturday
uh use promo code wac get yourself a free 14 days uh of gas digital content all right we'll see you next time
and we'll see you in hell