I'll see you in hell, it's the podcast you turn to.
When you're wondering, what's the hot goss in that Hollywood hubble? My name is Joe
DeRosa. My name is Patrick Walsh. Hello everybody. We're talking this week about the
slave horror entry antebellum. Although I don't even know if that description
fits the movie, but that's I think that's what they intended. It's I keep seeing it
touted as a horror film. Yeah. As a thriller, which yeah, okay, thriller a little closer to
to but but almost barely. It's it's a strange I'm I'm very odd that this to me that this film
fell into the category of of a genre picture. I think they thought okay, we will get the
get out audience and just go for that, but it's a strange movie. One of the strangest I've seen
recently and movies are getting weird. Everything's getting weird. Yeah. I mean, we're both sitting
here looking as if we just got out of bed. I did three hours later than you are. So that gives you
an idea of what time I'm waking up. Uh -huh. It's a Saturday afternoon. We've got all the time in the
world to record. That didn't used to be the case, you know, used to be on a Saturday. If we
recorded it, it was like, well, well, record. And then we're going to go out, right? Yeah. Now it's
like. This is this is the disco is the recording. Here we are. And I'm on a booze break, which
whoo. Real, real dicey over here with that. I mean, you're you're one of the few who gets way more
down when you stop drinking. It's like in kingpin when he says I, I, uh, I don't throw up when I drink. I
throw up when I don't. Yeah. Yeah. Very dark line. I find that, uh, I sleep better. I feel physically
better. I'm much clearer. I'm better rested. But the trade off for the zero fund is a tough one.
It's a tough one. But I try to appreciate the other aspects. The morning feels great. It's the
I find myself going to bed earlier and earlier to just get away from the day, like ended. Yeah. Yep. But
if I go too early, then I do the lie and lie and stare at the ceiling. So I can't go to bed at
like nine. I'll never fall asleep. So I got a time at just right. I do weed. I've given up alcohol
pretty much entirely. I mean, weed is, is just better for me. And alcohol was increasing my steadily
growing depression. So I stick with weed. In the morning, you know, I get up and I'm usually
fine. I got a little pep in my step. I'll, you know, I'll get a few things done. And then when I hit
that two to three wall, for me, that is, that is where I start to just lose my fucking mind. And each
day I go, I'm not going to take an edible today. I'm just going to power through whatever. And then
around that time, I'm like, I'm not getting to nine if I don't take that edible. Yeah. I'm, uh,
we're about 15 minutes out from that window on my end. Yeah. We'll hit it during this episode.
I, uh, yeah, I can't do weed. As you know, it's, I can't do it. It makes me crazy paranoid. I hate,
I hate the post weed feeling of the, like, hazy burnt -outed whatever weed hangover, whatever you
want to call it. I hate that feeling. Um, and I hate a booze hangover too. But for some reason,
it is harder for me to remember why I hate a booze hangover than it is for me to remember why I hate
a weed. I could contemplate smoking weed. And I'll go, you don't want that weed hangover. And then I'll
go, oh, yeah, you know, I'm not doing it with booze that almost never happened. So I had to, I got
to take a, and I hear you, I wake up well rested. I feel better. I feel good right now physically good.
But I know that, like, as this sun goes down and it's Saturday night, I mean, you know, it's like,
that's, that Nintendo Switch is only going to take you so far. Sure. Uh, so I'm going to start
eating in bed more. Mm hmm. Great. I did that last night. I ate four pieces of supreme pizza in my bed.
Okay. And then half a pint of Jenny's chocolate. Blackout cake ice cream, which is,
could be, shout out to Jenny's. They sent me a bunch of ice cream for free. No, I gotta get into this.
So we, hey, I didn't know Jenny's was anywhere, but L .A. That's great. Yeah. But Jenny's is $12
a pint of ice cream. It's absurd. But it is the best ice cream that there's ever been. They have
amazing array of flavors. And the other night, Heather was like, I hear they have a everything bagel
flavor. Yeah. And the iceings like cream cheese, not icing, the ice creams like cream cheese flavor.
And I was like, it sounds pretty gross. We ordered this stuff. I mean, you know, when the
gremlins get the chicken at like 11 55. Yeah. I mean, I was like, like, we were fighting each other
for it. And we got six pints. And we were like, let's just, we'll, we'll do it. So we each do two big
spoons a day. And we'll keep each other honest. I mean, this shit was gone in 24 hours. That's why I
got the free hookup is because so Sal and I on taste buds talked about, we did a debate. One of our
second episode was the everything bagel, which he was team everything versus the cinnamon raisin,
which I was. By the way, I feel like we usually agree on things, but every clip of that podcast,
I see on Instagram, you're arguing something so wrong. And you're always wrong. Well, welcome,
welcome to my life. Yeah, most areas of my life, my dearest friends are going, you're completely
wrong, which is a hell scape to live in as you can imagine. Sure. But anyway, so Jenny's reached out.
This is one of the only times that's ever happened to me in my life. And it really makes you feel like
a big shot for like five minutes. It's great. But Jenny's reached out to me. And they were like, we would
love to send you our everything bagel ice cream. We just came out with it. Yeah. And I was like,
okay, yeah, I'll try it. And they sent me not just that. They sent me like a eight pack
in like a dry icebox of ice cream. And I haven't even tried the everything bagel yet. I've been kind
of stair stepping up to it. Yeah. But last night, so so far, I did the chocolate truffle,
which was really good. That was a non -dairy. It was delicious. And then I did the straight -up dairy
chocolate. You're talking about the blackout chocolate fudge cake? Yes. Yes. Okay. It's insane.
Yes. Really good. It's insane. I was I had to find myself to not eat it for breakfast today,
which is a campaign they're doing that you should eat ice cream for breakfast.
I put a scoop into my coffee the other day. But to tell you how sick it got over here, when Heather
took a spoon of the chocolate blackout, she was like, hmm, I don't, so I don't like that one as much
as the others for some reason. It's two. It's too bitter or something. And I made a mental note,
avoid the blackout chocolate. You can keep that in the corner of the freezer. Heather's not going to
touch it. You need to get to the flavors that she enjoyed. That's that was my mental process.
But that's awesome. So yesterday on letterboxed, my good friend Kevin Porter, who famously hosted the
Gilmore guys podcast that I did. I would go in there and do that for four hours at a clip.
But Kevin is the best. He's selling cookies now to make ends meet much like Joe's sandwich shop.
And I highly recommend looking that up. He's on Twitter and you can find the information. He brought
me some of these cookies and they were incredible. So anyway, he puts this review up on letterbox
of postcards from the edge. And he's like, I'm watching postcards from the edge. And I realized
halfway through that I had six pints of Jenny's splendid sitting on the counter that I had never
put in the freezer. And they all completely melted. And I was splendid. Jenny's splendid. The ice cream
we're talking about. Oh, wait. So the full name of the ice cream is Jenny's splendid. Yeah, I thought
it was just Jenny's. They add a splendid. The splendid's terrible. They should just call it Jenny's.
I thought maybe this was a splendid flavor or something. No, they had. Okay. So he goes, I left it
out and all six flavors melted. And I thought to myself, I'm watching Meryl Streep have a meltdown.
Well, I'm having a meltdown of my own. I'm like, you know, funny little review. And I leave this
comment. I go six pints. You know, what are you? A thousand air or something like that? And he
told me the exact same tale you told me that he mentioned it on Twitter. And he in his words,
he became something of a cream fluencer, which was one of the most troubling terms I've ever heard.
But now that you're saying you got it too, clearly I just need to mention Jenny's on Twitter and get
my own six pack. I mean, maybe, you know, some of us have the clouds, some of us don't. Let's not
just stack like it. And he just anybody could do it. I think I'm roughly at a Joe DeRose, a Kevin
Porter level. Ooh, shots fired. It's not shots. I'm very cloud full.
I'm this is cloud fire over here. That's a good term. You should write both of those down cloud full.
Hashtag cloud full health tag misses cloud fire. Those are good. I'm telling you, I'm serious.
Those are good hashtags. Okay. All right. I would remember. I would infect. I infect if I were you,
I would start selling a t shirt that just says hashtag misses cloud fire on it.
And I promise you it will do very well. It's not going to do very well.
I promise you it will. I promise you it will. Joe, what are the six flavors you got?
We'll give you get the gooey butter cake. I assume we gooey butter.
I didn't get a new gooey butter. It's hard to remember the flavors because every one of them is like
pineapple collision course. Yeah. You know, the pineapple upside down cake is amazing.
That's that's the next one in line. So I have I got a I got a strawberry. No, I'm sorry.
I got a cherry goat cheese one that's like it supposedly tastes like cheesecake or something.
We did not get that one, but yes. I got the chocolate truffle dairy free. I got the chocolate
chocolate fudge blackout cake and the everything bagel the pineapple upside down.
And then I think there is that six. I think there might be one more that's like some kind of
don't say oh no, a banana a banana something or other banana cream. Yeah, Heather loved that one.
And I was like, let her take it. Fine. Not not my favorite, but the gooey butter is great.
Gooey butter is actually a St. Louis tradition that I had never seen anywhere but St. Louis.
My mom makes a great one. And then somehow it started spreading to ice creams around the globe,
but it's very good. What is goo? I mean, you want to talk to serving terms gooey butter?
Well, see my mom made this gooey butter cake and then like two years ago me and Heather went home
and she had made one for me and I was like, oh, fucking, we know we loved it. So Heather goes,
let me get the recipe. She comes home and tries to make me one for my birthday or something. And
she's like, are you aware there's like four sticks of butter in this? And I'm like,
I see now you've told me and I can't eat it again, but you know, it does have butter in the name.
So I'm on a, wow, you weren't kidding. I'm on the internet now. A pint of gooey butter ice cream
by Jenny's on Mercado .com is $16. Does that sound right to you? No, I've never seen it
above the standard 12. And if you go to the grocery store, sometimes they have it for 10.
Okay, yeah. Now, okay, 10 bucks. That's for some reason that Macara wanted. Oh, here you go. Banana
berry. Bramble berry crisp. Every flavor sounds like a willy wanker thing.
Bramble berry crisp is amazing. I actually, I think bramble berry is where, when
he the poo and piglet hung out as well in the bramble berry. And when he wasn't contemplating
suicide, I want to go to the, wow, raspberry rose jelly donut. So that's not even on our menus.
Sweet cream biscuits with peach jam. That sounds good.
You know, what they used to have was the munchies. And it was every, it was Snickers, M &Ms,
Pringles, and pretzels crumbled up into like an amazing ice cream. But before, I gave you,
so Kevin, Kevin's cookies, by the way, he does donate it to charity and they're amazing,
fucking cookies. But you want to look it up. Sam, it's called look pretty bad.
It's called Kevin Bacon, which is kind of funny. Kevin BAK, I am shop .com. And listen to these
flavors. Cinnamon Thia Nixon.
Pretzelie Sullenberger. I don't get that one. Like Sully Sullenberger. Oh, James Brown parentheses
id butter. James Brown butter. Okay. And Nicole Richai. All right. My, my strong recommendation,
they're all great. But the pretzelie Sullenberger is probably the best cookie I've ever had.
That sounds good. All right. Suddenly we're doing your other podcast. We've talked about delicious
treats for 20 minutes. But that's good. I was going to tell you, I can't talk about politics today.
And go to, and go to Joey Rose's sandwich shop. All proceeds go to charity, take by me a house.
Yes. Anyway, got a cat on the table, which she knows she's not supposed to do.
Well, there's a lot of new psycho I want to get to. Please, look, one of these skates along politics,
I'm not going to get into the politics of it. Don't worry. All right. But I do think it's funny that
so this lady that played cardoon on the Mandalorian was fired for her tweet in which she compared judging
political beliefs of your neighbors to neighbors in the 1940s Germany beating on their Jewish
neighbors physically. So she was fired. There were apparently were some other things that she had said,
you know, also online that were deemed problematic and she was fired. Now, as a free
speech proponent, I was a little troubled by the idea that you could get fired for expressing
a clumsy opinion. That said, the next day, any good will that I was able to give this woman
went out the window when she didn't know that she's now making a movie with Ben Shapiro. Yeah.
I was like, all right. I guess that's that. Now, look, Ben Shapiro is one of my favorite film
makers. But politically, we just don't get a we just don't get along. But no, I as I said to Joe,
this week, you're, you know, you know the climate, whether you want to agree with it or not.
If you find yourself typing anything about the Holocaust on Twitter or Instagram,
delete and go for a walk and don't post it. Now, that goes for everyone, but it especially goes for
those who can't act and have a starring role in one of the biggest shows on television, especially
if that show is produced by Disney who will have even less tolerance than most. Well, you'd think
you'd think a production studio that has put out the the healthy amount of racist
propaganda and children's cartoons that they have, they might have let her slide a little bit.
The old Walt was rumored to have some ties to the Nazi party. Maybe that's what they were mad about.
They're like, she's talking down about Walt. Yeah. So they start the thawing of Walt. They put his frozen
body in the microwave and set it on defrost for him to come back and kick her ass. Isn't he frozen?
They froze his head or something. That's the rumor. Yeah. Yeah. That's the rumor. Anyway.
Yeah. As I told Joe and this, this A is probably a testament to my weed smoking and B a testament to
how little I cared about that show. When I saw her, I was like, I've never seen this woman before
and I watched the first season of the Mandalorian. She was an MMA fighter who got an acting. Look,
this story was in haywire the Soderbergh movie, right? I don't know.
And that was a cool movie. But did you know in that movie and she speaks English, they dubbed her
with Laura Sanjicone. No. Soderbergh was like, we can't use this woman's acting. So they had to
dub her with an actor. She's not a good actor. But here's the thing. And I didn't like her character on
Mandalorian because it was it was one of these, and I love the Mandalorian, but it was one of these
pointless Star Wars characters. It's like, I don't need another rough and tumble gunslinger in
start. We've got plenty. Like, I don't need another one that that just kind of feels like run off
of Han Solo, like the 17th Han Solo clone or whatever. Yeah. So, but anyway, Hannah Solo.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to emphasis on Solo now. I could sell Hannah Solo Monday.
You probably, probably, I'm going to sell Han Solo to Black Han Solo. Okay. All right.
Anyway, the entire every element of this story is annoying. It's stop hiring MMA fighters to
be entertainers. Number one, Disney is completely hypocritical and full of shit and making big moves
to cover up their own sins. Number two, sure. We live in a culture where everybody tells you
to express yourself, but if you express yourself clumsily in the wrong way, you get fired. Number three,
number four, she comes out and does a movie with Ben. It's an adult film. What? It's an
adult film with her and Ben Shapiro, which I thought was even crazier. You're two of them making love.
Yeah. Oh, oh, oh. Every part of this story bothers me. But the crown, the icing on the cake,
chair on top bothers me above anything. Movie web reports today.
Carried to an action figure is canceled by Hasbro as Gina Carano exits the Mandalorian. Guys,
it's an action figure of a space person. What the figure out? I don't want to understand why you
can't. It's true. The figure now, you know, and I'm sure I think I saw Ted Cruz saying roughly the
same thing. And I hate ever agreeing with anything. But he wasn't he wasn't talking about the action
figures, but it's like, let's say there is a young girl who's that's her favorite character. Why take
that away? She doesn't know about the fucking Instagram post. But they'll find somebody better. They
can throw a rock and find somebody better. It's not a big deal. It's not a rock act. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, sort of, I mean, that's another one where it's like, you know, just I was always against that
as much as I loved the A team as a little kid. And I did love Mr. T as every kid did my age.
I was even troubled at as a nine year old when Mr. T was in Rocky three. I was like, guys,
we're getting a little let's not. That's just pump the brakes here a little bit. You know,
but I mean, has anybody have any of these athletes in recent years? I can't speak to LeBron James.
He's in space jam too. Maybe maybe he'll be great. I don't know. I never saw space jam one. I don't
know if Jordan was great or not, but but my question is, is have any of these athletes that they are
now putting into, you know, you see them roasting. You see them on TV shows. They have sitcoms. They have
this. Does any one of them hold a candle to Mr. T in the charisma department? Not even absolutely.
Well, when a when a 60 year old Mr. T went on Conan O 'Brien, you know, whatever that was 10,
15 years ago and they went apple picking together. You ever see that? It's one of the funniest things
Conan ever did. And you can see Conan is just in love with the man. He still has it. It's not like he
he lost it after being kind of thrown out of the business for a while. But man, he's he's funny.
I have an autographed card and comic book playing like like bait Mr. T baseball card basically
and comic book of issue number one of Mr. T comics. Yeah. From when he launched a comic book,
you know, starring himself. Well, he didn't launch it. A company did. I don't remember who
published it, but and he did a signing in my neighborhood at a bookstore and went to it. And I met him.
He goes, what's your name, son? And I said, Joe, when he goes Jeff, and I go, Joe, when he
goes Jeff, and I go, Joe, and he goes, all right, Jeff signed it. Set me on my way. And it wasn't a
bit. It was not a bit. Maybe he was deaf or something. Well, he's do an Andre the giant style documentary.
I mean, I don't I don't even know if he was a coke guy, a booze guy, a guy with who never dabbled.
I don't know anything about him. He was extremely religious. I don't think he was a drug guy at all.
I think he got sick for a while. And they thought he had like some kind of
immunodeficiency thing. And then, and then he was okay. I don't know. I think he was okay.
I heard he had a low Mr. T sell count. Oh boy.
People I send, I just want you to the listeners at home to know when Pat makes a joke like that.
And everybody endearingly laughs. Oh, Pat, I send him jokes like this frequently via text.
And I will get harsh judgment back as if I'm submitting them to be aired on a TV show. We're working
only if they're really bad when they're good. I tell you they're good. I bet they're
spoke. They're all bad. They're all really bad. Some bad jokes are worse than others. Was Mr. T a
wrestler? No, he was. Yeah. Actually, I don't remember how he came on the scene. I know the first
time I saw him was when PB was eating his cereal at the beginning of PB's big adventure. Yeah, I'm
kind of backwards. I'm sort of retconning this. I'm remembering incorrectly. And that's why I was
doing the MMA comparison to him. Mr. T was first a personality and an actor and then started making
appearances in like WWF and stuff like that. I think. Okay. Okay. So no, first he was the,
oh, and I really fucked this up. Mr. T wasn't the person I had the problem with in Rocky 3.
He was a great club or lag. He was amazing. What am I talking about? It was Hulk Hogan.
Sure. Was in Rocky 3. That's what I was thinking of when Hulk Hogan does the exhibition match
with with Balboa. That's what I was talking about. Yeah. He's an actor loving Mr. T. Yeah.
Right. I'm not mad. Google that Conan, Conan, Mr. T apapicking thing. It's great.
I will. Do you have other news, psychos? There was one more I wanted to talk about.
Um, uh, oh, firefly right boy, dude, when the heat comes down, baby, the heat comes down.
Why did you tell Joss Whedon to do what he did by the way? Firefly writer claims Joss Whedon liked
to boast about making female writers cry. This hits the same week. Well, as what's your name, um,
Trachtenberg. I think it's the last name said that there was a rule on set that he was not
allowed to be alone with her. Yeah. And she was like 15 when she did the show.
Whoo. Um, so, you know, every woman involved with that show, it started with
Charisma Carpenter, who I used to be obsessed with when I was a kid, even though I didn't watch Buffy,
I just thought she was amazingly beautiful. But, um, her galor Trachtenberg, um, they're coming,
they're coming out the writing staff like that guy from Firefly is like, yeah, he love making
people cry and stuff. Look, I've been on shows where the showrunner loves making people cry. Like,
I'm sure there are a lot of people, uh, terrified, you know, and it's weird because then it just
becomes the, I guess they're trying to paint the larger picture of the guy being abusive. But
when I saw that, I was like, well, being an asshole is not sexual.
Well, shit, you know, I guess if you want to add to his, his legend of being a prick fine,
but like, it was odd to me. It's odd to me that they're, they're lumping in asshole behavior
with like sexual assault. No, we don't know what he did to Trachtenberg. We don't know what he did
in terms of sexual abuse or harassment or whatever it may be. But, um, yeah, if you want to get into
assholes in Hollywood, I mean, 50 % of people are going down. That was kind of intriguing when I
saw that getting some traction about guy yells at, at writers and then they start crying. I'm like,
yeah, that's most jobs I've been on. It's not right. I hope it changes. But, um, it's an interesting
time, man. I, it's an interesting time. I know, I know people who should be scared as hell right now.
Oh, me too. Uh, I think what happens is, I agree with everything you just said, but I think what
happens is, um, the asshole thing comes out first. And sometimes these other types of allegations
are linked to it. Often if you do these other things, you're also an asshole. Uh, you know, but
sometimes it's a real nice guy that does this kind of shit because that's his, that's his game or whatever.
But, um, anyway, I think what happens is, is the asshole stuff comes out first. And then if this
stuff is also happening, it follows quickly. And that's when the hammer really falls.
Ellen has a shot to repair things because the worst anybody has said is she was an asshole,
right? You know what I mean? Like, yeah. But if, but if there were other things like Ellen
grobed to me or whatever, then, you know, she'd be in a lot more trouble right now, obviously. Yeah.
So, um, excuse me, um, sorry to clear my throat like that. Um, anyway, uh, that's it from the
news cycle for me. But yeah, weedin is a weedin. That's that's a, I mean, you, you want to talk about a
guy that went from golden boy to, I mean, Jesus Christ, they were people were, and this is
what I hate also about the climate and the culture. This is the part of it. I hate people were clamoring,
clamoring, they were excitedly ostracizing Zach Snyder from the DC universe. And remember,
if you remember correctly, I said to you, and it sort of happened, I said when we would argue Batman
versus Superman, when it first came out, we really debated it. I said, Mark my words. This will be
one of those movies in a year or two where they go list of movies that wasn't as bad as we said it was
when it came out or whatever. Now that has not happened. But what has happened is we went from a world where
everybody hated that movie and thought it was a disgrace and Zach Snyder needs to be taken off of DC
and whatever, to a world within three years where people are cheering for a four -hour version of
justice league that Zach Snyder is putting together, including myself, but I like Batman and V Superman.
So it's interesting with with with with Josh Weedin, because people were so excited that he was
going to come in and take the reins and fix DC and do all this stuff. And now everybody, you know,
hates his guts for other reasons. DC are justice league bombed, which is also interesting.
I wonder if if justice league had done well and had delivered what fans wanted,
would the narrative be a little different right now? Not saying he didn't do these things, but saying
like, would there have been more of a coverup with this stuff? Is the pile on partially happening because
they're like, well, we have no use for him anymore. He couldn't deliver. I mean, I think all it is is
once they see the writing on the wall, Weedin's been canceled four times. That's why that's what
people issue with the term cancel culture is. It's like, but he goes on and still makes movies. These
people are doing fine. He's just hit a point now where it's like how many times do you have to be
told, but he's a big money maker. So they look the other way. I do think now with the failure of
that movie, it's kind of like, yeah, get him out of here. But why do these idiots get so self -righteous
when they have so much dirt in the closet? I mean, it's like, dude, it's a mobster.
It's Teflon don shit. It's like, dude, you're a mobster and you're making noise. Stop it.
Yeah, the first time he went up there and started talking about what a great feminist he is.
It's like his wife was the one who came forward. She was like, excuse me.
What are you talking about? And you know, that he actually said, excuse me, bitch,
that that was a squeeze baking powder. What is the joke with a squeeze me baking powder?
Is it supposed to be begging pardon? Begging beg your pardon? I never heard that until just now.
I have no idea. It was a Wayne's world. It was Wayne would go, squeeze me, baking powder?
No clue. Yeah. But I'm glad you brought it up because for our final talk, let's talk about
that commercial. Speaking of people who don't do psychology, even though they've done nothing criminal,
aside from taking my childhood out behind the barn and assaulting it.
Look, I never cared. I never got people's anger over ghostbusters or whatever else comes back.
But Wayne's world hit me in that I was 10 years old. I was obsessed spot.
First, I saw the trailer for the commercial, which they did on Fallon.
I watched these two mug and do bits on Fallon while Fallon hyperventilated.
It was some of the least funny riffing I've ever heard. The commercial was awful.
The fact that they're promoting Uber Eats who is currently screwing over gig workers and
this economy who are trying to make money is even worse. And then when the commercial actually
aired on the Super Bowl, these guys are so shameless they're doing a promotion tour for a commercial.
And when the commercial finally aired, it was fucking embarrassing. It's Cardi B dressed as
Garth. I thought she came off better than the other two, frankly. Oh, no, dude, it was, I
disagree. I thought it was, now I know I know that it was written this way. It was obviously the joke.
But I was like, could anything sum up how awful this whole thing is other than more than the fact
that they have Cardi B and her stick and it is pretend you're not interested. Uh -huh.
I don't think I doubt you had to pretend. Yeah, pretend you're not interested and then we'll
throw to you and make it really obvious that you're just here for the money. Like every part of
this was so upsetting to me. Um, Mike Myers, as I said to you, looks like Raquel Welch. I don't know
what he's doing to his face. If anything, maybe he's just drinking a lot, but I don't, something weird
is going on. Uh, he could, it could also be he ages, you know, people do age, but when you,
it's putting them in the young person outfit and hair that makes them look so bad. I mean, they,
they look like he looks a little bloated, a little older, a little heavier, like we all do.
But to put them in that makeup and those clothes is like, Dana didn't look like that.
Dana didn't look like that. Well, he didn't look like Garth, but he didn't look like an old pile of
banana pudding either. And no, Myers and I'm a big fan. He's got that fatigue on his face, dude. Like,
it's like he looks like he just rolled off of a cot in between takes, you know, to come shoot
this thing. It was painfully on the Super Bowl commercials this year could be summed up as a bunch
of people I used to think were funny doing commercials for products I don't believe in. That was every
commercial. Uh, I tweeted this. I've said it before. I'll say it again. I honestly believe that I could
rise to the top of the advertising industry in three months. And I don't know why I don't.
Aside from you probably need schooling or something like that. But I would go in there like,
like a 90s, like a polyshore movie, you know, where I'd go in and like my dad died and I get promoted.
And then I come, that's the situation I want where I come in. They're like, what the fuck is this guy
doing here? And by the end of the movie, I've shown them all how to advertise correctly. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh, I used to be fresh new concepts. I mean, it's always jock humor. It's never really my
humor. But the commercials were always funny because they were original, fresh ideas, takes, etc.
You know, like, well, it's also the every commercial was old shit. And sometimes the fucking Timothy
Chamolay is Edward Scissorhands without a joke. I mean, also too. It's like, it's more of this thing
where it's like, I mean, people are rushing to cancel Johnny Depp right now. That's your opinion.
That's your take, whatever you think about that is whatever you think about it. But I just don't,
this is, and this is what I was saying, sort of alluding to earlier with the car of doing thing. I don't
understand a culture. I'm not saying because it's Johnny Depp or because I don't agree with the
accuser. That's not what I'm saying. What I'm saying is is I don't understand a culture where we will
villainize a person while simultaneously celebrating something that person defined. Yeah.
It doesn't make any sense to me. It's, it's like, you want to cancel Roseanne? Okay, cancel Roseanne.
cancel the Conners. The Conners is Roseanne. It's, it's what she made. Johnny Depp is Edward Scissorhands.
It's not Tim Burton. Tim Burton has proven to us that he didn't know what the fuck he was doing.
Once he stopped using those centabyte outfits for his main characters in every movie, it's a
shit show with Tim Burton. It is a shit show. Johnny Depp was proven to us over and over and over again. He
creates great characters. He's created like a dozen iconic movie that will go down in the tenets
of movie history. That's true. Why are we canceling him and at the same time making a super bowl
commercial about his most iconic character? It just doesn't make any sense to me. I don't understand.
With emotion completely removed from it, if you look at just what we talked about today, that they're
pulling this woman's action figure because of her beliefs and yet they're pushing Johnny Depp's old
characters despite it. It's the same thing but different and everybody accepts it and I don't know
why. I don't understand any of it. I don't understand anything that goes on. There's a lot of double standards.
I frankly think everybody's kind of a piece of shit but like do I don't I just don't like now how it's
how can we find out the shittiest things somebody did in their 45 years and hold it over their
heads forever. I don't like that. Johnny Depp, from everything I've heard, fuck the guy but we don't
know. We don't know. We don't know and it's it's just the I don't I don't quite it's odd.
It's odd anyway. It's all odd. That's our niche cycle. And again, you know, it's to me being an
asshole. It's like when the when this all started, they were saying Matt Damon saying like
Matt Damon saying like obviously there's something different from telling a girl she has a nice
ass and rape and people were mad at him. Yeah, yeah. For saying that. I can't even wrap my head around
that. They're saying well it all promotes rape culture. Fine if it all promotes rape culture but
there are degrees. So when when somebody is when it's and I said I wasn't going to talk about
politics and this thing but it's like if somebody's an asshole and they're truly sorry and maybe they're
not an asshole anymore. Mike Myers was supposed to be one of the most legendary assholes in Hollywood.
Hopefully that's changed. To me, I see that with a completely different lens than somebody who has
sexually assaulted. I completely agree, which is why I was getting worked up the other night when
we were texting about the about the this car of doom woman being fired because if you remember
just a suite, you know, 12 years ago, you know, we thought that George W Bush was the devil
incarnate and that anybody that publicly supported him should be should be ushered out immediately
of the room. What are you got that guy doing rounds on late night talk shows and getting laughs
and everybody's going, he wasn't so bad. So my point is is okay, we're saying the same thing about
Trump. Now I get it. I get the whole thing but you're going to fire people. You're going to put these
these you're going to put the vice to them. Now don't fucking go back on that in four years or in
eight years and go, Oh, well now it's worse and those people, you know, it's like the people in jail
right now for selling weed. You know, who missed that cut off by three months or whatever. You know what I
get. I get nug club, which is I think I told you this. I get a monthly box, which helps me control
my weed usage. I get a one month sort of like a grab bag of weed products. It's a good good deal.
This this month's box was beautiful. It was and it was covered in names and I'm like,
what's this about? And I look inside and it's the names of people who are wrongly imprisoned
for weed. And I'm like, but that's what you're doing is you're putting their name on the box
chock full of weed that you're sending to my home. Like, could you do any less?
If you want to do so, if you want to acknowledge these people, do something. The whole the whole
putting a name up now counts as activism. It bothered didn't bother me enough not to smoke the weed
inside. But I mean, look, we're all guilty too. We're all pieces of shit. Yeah. And we're trying
to get through the this thing called life as Prince once said. Yeah, this game called life. I like
to say game called life. But here are my rules. Don't talk about the Holocaust. Actually, if you work
where I show where you co -star with a puppet. And be don't sexually assault or harass people.
Right. And don't be proud of making people cry. That's probably a bad one. Yeah. I mean, see,
don't be an asshole. I've worked with nothing but assholes for most of my career. And I hope that
is starting to change. But I do think asshole is below assault. I agree. That's a great title for
your memoir. By the way, nothing but assholes. Fast times and hard times in the Hollywood show biz,
whatever assholes and assaults. The Patrick Wall story. Let's get over to that movie corner
because we're a we're we're we're we're deep in at this point. Yeah, we've been just going off
the rails here. Movie corner. I saw last night. It just released on demand for 20 bucks. And I'm
sure it'll go down like they all do these days. But barb and star go to Vista Del Mar with
Kristen Wigg and Annie mumble. I hate the title so much. I like the cast. Yeah.
Is it good? Well, I'll tell you. So I I met Annie a few times. She I don't know if it's out,
but she was dating somebody who was on the living biblically cast. She was? She was. Yes. Ian
Gomez. Ian. Wait a minute. Look, it's out. At the time he was separating from his wife. Oh,
he's oh, they separated. They were married to my big fat Greek wedding. Her name is Neav Vardalo.
No, they were separating during that show. And he started dating Annie mumble who co -wrote
bridesmaids and is Kristen Wigg's writing partner. I didn't know that. I met her. She had a fascinating
tale about how David O 'Rossel screwed her over. She wrote the script for Joy, that movie about Jennifer
Lawrence and the mop. Can I just side note for a second? Yeah. The two movies I have never cared less
about. Joy? Two movies I couldn't have cared less about. Joy and the Greg Keneer windshield wiper
movie. I mean. And I think I've said it before. The windshield wiper movie is good. I think
it's called it's called flash of genius. And it's pretty good. By the way, flash of genius. What does
flash have to do with windshield one? Nothing. Two biopics where I'm just like, I don't give a shit how
this came about. I don't care. Anyway, I remember I remember being sort of interested in it. I like
the movie. But mumble is great. She apparently wrote this great script for Joy. David O 'Rossel,
who is a notorious problem guy, was just a whole complete asshole. Through her off, forced her,
you know, went to the writers guild and begged her to not get credit. She's talking about that publicly
now, which is why I'm talking about it publicly. But I really liked her. And she's never really had a
performing showcase. But her and Wig have a lot of chemistry. They played two sort of middle -aged
lonely women who decide to break up their routine and go to Vista del Mar and have it get away.
But the movie is completely insane. Wig also plays a Dr. Evil sort of character, an albino woman
with a black bull cut who like lives in the Earth's core. So this movie begins with a heavy set
Korean boy writing his bike down the street and delivering newspapers. And he's listening to his
headphones and all of a sudden he breaks into like a musical number and starts singing. And me and
Heather realized we were screaming laughing. Like it's just getting funnier and funnier. And then he
goes to this tree. He like knocks on the tree. The tree opens up. He goes down into the Earth where he
meets his master who's Kristen Wig as like a Dr. Evil type. She has, she says, excuse me, I'd like to
make a drink. And she says, I call it the suicide. And then up from the ground comes one of those like
at subway, a six dispenser soda thing, which little kids call suicide where you get one of each.
You watch her get a little bit of each of the sodas. And then she goes, and now the secret ingredient,
just a splash of lipid and brisk iced tea puts the splash in. And me and Heather were looking at each
other, were confused. This movie, I saw a preview of this movie two years ago. I had no idea what it was.
Clearly they had no idea how to market it. And for a half an hour,
I was prepared to call this an all time comedy classic. We were how we watched this scene. It's
Vanessa Bayer. And it's like a woman's group where they're like sitting around and they're eating
hot dog soup. And there's this lady who asks, can we talk about horses this week in our talking
group? And Bayer clearly like runs the show. So right as it turns six, another lonely woman shows
up to join the talking group, Bayer runs for the door and locks her out because it is turning six o 'clock.
And she yells, woman, like, we're not letting you in. So she sits back down.
The lady asks, can we talk about horses this week in talk group? And Bayer decides to punish her
by taking her hot dog soup. She's like, you don't get any of that soup because you asked a question
out of line. It's one of the craziest scenes I've ever seen. I know I'm not explaining it well,
but we watched this scene ten times. So for a half hour, it's got this thrill of your like, is this
dumb and dumb or like, is this Tommy boy? Is this going to be anchor man? And then I have to admit,
it gets a little old and it meanders and they let it go on too long. They should have cut
easily 20 minutes out. Yeah, it's a bummer. But scattered throughout our laughs, it is worth
watching for the first half hour. I wish it had if it had maintained that level of laughs, man,
we would have had something good. But wig is funny as fuck. I hope she gets off this Wonder Woman
path and just starts making comedies because she is so funny as a writer and a performer.
Check it out. I watched a movie that I absolutely loved. One night in Miami,
I went in thinking, you know, it's a biopic Malcolm X's in my top 10 movies of all time.
I can't imagine that another movie that pretty much does focus on him. You know,
it is about the meeting in Miami of Malcolm X, Sam Cook and Muhammad Ali. By the way, and also
and one other person and also Jim Brown, Jim Brown, who gets no press in any of this.
Every advertisement is the three guys. They never mentioned Jim Brown. Jim Brown is an
integral part of this film and the story. Anyway, it's based on a real night that happened.
But I know it is. No, it is. It is. That's the other misrepresentation of this thing. They keep
going, it's a fictionalized meeting. There's a there's a there's a vignette on YouTube of Jim Brown
taking a reporter back to the hotel and being like, here's where it happened. This is where we all met
that night. Well, then why when I looked it up was it was like, it's fictionalized. I guess they
just mean they made up the dialogue. Yeah, that's it. It's a very mis -marketed film for what it is.
Because there are movies that are far more tailored to to to fit the the medium that are considered
true stories and this and that, you know, anyway. It's a wonderful film. But I would say the character
at the centerpiece truly is Malcolm X like the the main focus I felt was on him. And I was
floored by the performances in this thing. Everybody had a grand slam. It was called One Night in Miami.
I don't know if you've said that. Yeah, I did. Okay. And I thought it was perfect. I thought it was a
perfect challenging commentary on a lot of issues we discussed these days. And I for one was happy
to see it from the perspective of the people that are suffering in the struggle of this racism
discussion we're all having right now. Instead of some woke white person on Twitter explaining to me
what racism is. I thought it was brilliantly done. I thought it was brilliantly directed. What's
Jesus Christ? I'm an asshole. What's your name? Regina King. Regina King who, you know, first time
director is usually acts, right? You know, I mean, did I remember I first met Gina King on a show called
227. Yeah, no, she's a great actress. She's great. I hope she does something again. The writer of
the film who his name is escaping me. He's an older guy and he wrote the play of the. Yes, he also wrote
soul. It's just a great flick, man. And I thought I thought the discussion about race in America and
also to the discussion about using your platform for for a greater cause. I thought they just kind of
hit this thing from every angle. What is not militant enough? What is too militant? What are you
obligated to do? What do you not have a problem doing? Is is is is is what you are doing enough just
because it doesn't fit into the guidelines of this or that. I just thought it was a brilliant film.
I loved it. I thought everybody nailed the the reincarnation of or the incarnation rather of who they
were playing without it feeling like weird impressions. I was floored to the kid who played Malcolm
X's English. I was like, what? But I just thought it was an awesome, awesome, awesome movie
riveting. And I think it's a must watch for people. You know, I would I would say it's among the
best movies I've seen this year. Absolutely. Well, I guess I'll do one night in Miami too because I did
not like it. I thought it was very stagy. It felt like a filmed play. I was annoyed when I looked
it up and saw that it was not real. Although Joe's telling me it was a real event. And for me,
the dialogue was just not hitting. It was like, you know, it was very much that kind of thing of like,
but Sam, look, you've got the number one song on the adult R &B charts. And you've got the number
12 song in the pop. It felt like a Wikipedia page. You know, there's sometimes some clumsy
exposition in any biopic. I agree. Now, now, we're going to get into some real clumsy dialogue today
with Anton Bellum, but that did not even, you know, yeah. For whatever reason, one night in Miami
kind of bored me, I just did knock it into it. And the performers, I mean, maybe it's that I have
I've listened to Sam Cook once a week since I was like five years old. I always listen to Sam Cook.
I like it. It cheers me up. I thought the guy was just not capturing him well. The Malcolm X guy,
you can't help but compare it to Denzel. I just for whatever reason, and a lot of times these days,
it's mood. I freely admit that my mood going into stuff can really affect things. It just didn't
work for me. So I feel different than you. But there we are. One shocking detail was the
animosity, the portrayal of the animosity that Malcolm X is that Betty Shabazz had towards Lewis
Faracom. They talk quite and length. There's the first scene with Malcolm is a scene where they
discuss Lewis X, not supporting Malcolm in what's going on with the nation of Islam and Elijah
Muhammad having impregnated all these women and left them with babies and whatever. That was
surprising. And that was a very controversial thing to put into the movie because
there is that's a very polarizing subject, you know, you know, when it comes to the discussion about
all this. So I thought it was a daring film. I thought it took a lot of great chances. And I enjoyed
it. But anyway, okay, my turn again, I'll keep it brief. I did a rewatch. We mentioned this guy
earlier, Mars attacks. I've been told by people mainly my partner co -host on this show that I missed
the mark. And this was a good movie. I revisited what a piece of shit this film is. It is not good. It
is not funny. It's a fun movie. And it's kind of funny. It's a movie that could be fun. Yeah.
But doesn't ever hit the mark. I can't believe I LM did the effects for this thing. They are so bad.
And I thought on the rewatch, they must have done this on purpose. This must be a commentary to cheesy
special effects on cheesy and tribute to cheesy special effects. And then I looked it up and I was like,
no, it's just a budgetary thing. They couldn't afford to do animatronics. So they did CGI.
The aliens are so, it's just terrible. It's terrible. The effects are so unbelievably bad that you can't,
it takes you out of the movie completely. Jack Nicholson for some reason playing dual roles that
have nothing to do with each other. It doesn't make any sense. And look, I love Nicholson as much as the
next guy. Nicholson in a dual role doesn't work. He's not that kind of actor.
He's not disappearing into any role. Okay. He's Nicholson. Yeah.
What's his name is funny in it? I always say HR Geeger, RL Stein. What's his name?
Rod Stiger. Rod Stiger is funny in it.
Martin's not a love at the end. Tom Jones singing and then the woodland animals flocking to him.
I mean, it's, it's a good end. It's a humorous moment. But it's like that moment in like,
for instance, like the tenacious D movie where it becomes a cartoon. It's just like a zany silly thing.
It doesn't. Martin short is wasted in this thing. He has nothing funny to do. Michael J. Fox wasted in
this thing. Nothing funny to do. There's so many fucking people in this movie that you've got actors
that are doing the parts of like what are glorified extras. Christina Applegate is a great example.
I don't even think she has a line in this movie. Yeah.
Well, Sarah Jessica Parker. It's, it's too much. I just, I remember having a good time with it.
I haven't said it in 20 years though. I hate the film. And I do think that it is the,
it is the mark of the decline of a burden. After this, if I'm not mistaken, the only good thing he
did was big fish, which is I think what he followed this with. Sleepy Hollow. Oh, no, I'd sleepy
hollow. Yes, you know, he followed this with sleepy hollow, which was, I thought was awesome.
And then I think it was planted in the apes disgraceful. That's good. Then big fish. Yeah. And then
after that, nothing good at all. That's true. That's true.
I saw Malcolm and Marie, which oddly has become one of the most controversial movies of the year.
It is written and directed by Sam Levinson, who was the son of Barry Levinson. He does the show
Euphoria, which is, you know, I watch it. It's entertaining. It wasn't my adolescence experience.
I'll tell you that. But the man I feel like he's got to, there's got to be a come -up
and it's coming for this man because he's like a 40 something year old white dude who now does a
movie in this day and age with only two characters, black characters and they're talking about racism
and he wrote and directed it. Then he also does the show Euphoria, which is entirely about children
having sex and it's a show full of dicks. It's a show full of like graphic nudity.
So I don't know. If I was that guy trying to operate in this business right now, I would probably
just commit Seppaku and end it. But Malcolm and Marie, people hate this thing so much.
I will say that black people really hate the movie and not across the board, but I've, you know,
my friends who are black and the people I read on letterboxed and critics and so forth really hate it.
So I could be wrong. All I can tell you is that I sat down and enjoyed the hell out of it.
I don't know what people are angry about. I do. The reason critics hate it
is because there's a giant monologue about how useless critics are and how their virtue
signalers and how they're, you know, I love it. And it's very personal and he's referring to that
white lady from the LA Times and they love it. It seems to be a real film critic who gave this Sam
Levinson's movie a bad review. The first time his movie came out. So he goes after people, you know,
but it's coming from the mouth of Denzel's son, Washington, the other guy from Inception.
So it's all very weird, you know, it sounds like he's got a big axe to grind with a lot of people and
to put those words in a black actor's mouth, I understand the issue people have with the movie.
However, what I think why is it bad? And I don't say this to provoke. I'm curious. Why is it bad to put
those words in a black actor's mouth? Because it was clearly personal issues that Sam Levinson was
having with critics, right? As a white guy. And he's, and he's basically this critic's argument
like racist. You know, it's like, it's very weird that I get. But if you sit down and watch this thing
as a two character beautifully shot black and white film in the style of who's afraid of Virginia Wolf
or one of the framed Roger Rabbit or, you know, Blue Valentine or any one of these movies where a couple
just goes through the ringer and fights. And I thought the dialogue was good. I think the reason why
Hollywood people don't like it is because it calls them out on a lot of bullshit. And also this
Washington bitching and screaming about how nobody gets him and he's a genius and why doesn't anybody
understand that they're all taking that as Sam Levinson working out his issues when I think
and you never know what somebody intends. But I think he is using it to satirize how self -absorbed
and obnoxious Hollywood people are and how actors can only think about themselves. And the whole point
of the movie is that Washington is so obsessed and narcissistic and into his art that he doesn't acknowledge
the fact that the only reason this movie got made is because it's about his beautiful intelligent
girlfriends and Daya. So at the end, and I'm not, and that's not a spoiler, but basically all she's
wanting is for him to acknowledge her and love her as much as he cares about getting an award or
getting a good review from some lady that he doesn't even respect. To me, that's sort of a beautiful
theme and message. But, you know, a white writer director putting words in the mouth of black
actors, it's going to become a problem and it's going to be something we sort of have to work through.
But for me, you got the two of the biggest black actors in Hollywood and Daya in Washington,
they're great in it. They agreed to do it. They obviously agree with what's being said in it. I
don't understand how this became so controversial. But I will say that the fact that people are so
pissed about it means to me it's getting under people's skin which seems to be the goal of this guy
art. It seems to be what he goes out there to do. And I don't know, I liked it a lot. Maybe I'm
crazy, but to me, it felt real. It felt true. And even though I'm not in anywhere near as a toxic
relationship, I have a lovely relationship. I noticed my behavior changing after saying snap out of
having your head up your ass and waking up and being like, am I ever going to work again and so forth
and acknowledge that you have this beautiful loving woman here who makes your day better.
That to me is a good fucking movie. Yeah, you know, I like it.
Okay, I got to check it out. I have a screener. I look forward to watching it. I will close us out
with another rewatch. Also, a bit of a new psychotide into this. Bam Margera this week posted a
very drunken video talking about how he's been removed from jackass part four.
I don't know. If what he is saying is true in the video, now who knows because he's really
fucked up in it, but I will say this, the way he's saying it does sound believable.
And he's like, look, man, I'm getting kicked off of jackass four for being too much of a jackass.
He's like Paramount has made me take a handful of antidepressants every morning, every day at three
o 'clock. I have to blow into a thing for a sobriety check. Every day at six o 'clock,
I have to blow into this thing as a sobriety check. I am forced to go to therapy. I was forced to come
out of my own pocket to go into a rehab. He talks about and look, we've both worked enough in Hollywood
to know. Yeah, that sounds pretty. That sounds pretty much like what a big studio and make you do. Yeah,
so I think it is kind of bullshit if that's all that he had to do. I also understand that in this
day and age, they're just not taking any liability chances whatsoever.
But I will say this, I'm a huge fan of jackass. I hope BAM is able to be a part of the movie. I
really do. It's already bittersweet without Ryan Dunn. I can't imagine seeing jackass without BAM
there too. I don't, you know, you want it to be jackass. So anyway, I hope it all works out.
And that's, and the reason I say that is because I rewatched during this pandemic. Jack asked one,
two, and three, and there's not much to say other than what a delightful, amazing way to forget about
all the bullshit going on in the world right now, socially, politically. I mean, I watched these
months and months ago. So I mean, we were really in the thick of everything and every single thing you
saw on your TV being so negative and so catastrophic and disastrous and whatever. And just perfect
90 minute escapes from everything. You just laugh your balls off. And it's not just seeing a guy get
hit in the nuts is funny or seeing a guy's ass bleed because he tried to cowboy ride a fire hose
or whatever is funny. It's seen the camaraderie amongst them. It's seeing the stupid
goofy friendships. It's seeing them laugh. It's seeing them get quite frankly shit faced together
and acting like morons. It's just a beautiful way to escape. And I hope that part 4 brings some more
that in. Steve, I was saying that it's insane again. Like it's not going to be tamed down or anything.
So, you know, I know it'll be a much more sober production. But anyway, I highly recommend the
Jackass trilogy on rewatch. I talked about them at the very beginning of the pandemic. That was one of
the first things I did was watch all three and I did them on Pat Solo movie corner. I think they are
some of the best comedies I've ever made. I think two is the masterpiece. It also ends in their finest
hour, which is the pube beard behind the trunk. I mean, that's one of the best put together pranks.
I have ever seen in my entire life. It's insane. Huge fan can't wait for 4. And I really hope
we're not watching Jackass 4 on fucking HBO Max because there have been no better theater
experiences for me really than Jackass 1, 2, 3. They'd all be in my top 10. Me too. All right.
All right. Let's get to Antebellum, our movie on hand. We already gave a brief synopsis of it at the top.
But we didn't. We didn't. I mean, I'll just say there's spoilers. If you haven't seen Antebellum,
don't listen. It's on Hulu. It was available for purchase for a long time. But now it's free on Hulu.
So you can check it out there. The gist is for 45 minutes. You're watching
a very beautifully shot. The opening shot of this thing is absolutely incredible. It's this
big tracking shot. It's beautiful. I texted Joe like holy shit. Like what a shot that was.
That's what I thought too. And I went into this knowing very little about the movie, but knowing
you that had very poor reviews. And you see this opening shot, which is easily three minutes.
Yep. And it's so choreographed and everything. And the music is intriguing and enticing.
And it's like, this thing looks like this is going to be like an orson well in a masterpiece.
Like what could the problem be here? Yeah. It's got this really kind of haunting fiddle,
civil war type score. Everything's working. And then for about 45 minutes, you realize you're just
watching slaves be raped, beaten, tortured, yelled at, spit at. Now slavery is horrible. They
you know, I guess people what maybe there are people who have never seen a slave movie or never
studied it. But you're sitting there watching it and it's going on and on. And then at some point,
I found myself saying while this is certainly horrific, isn't this a horror movie? What's going on?
Then all of a sudden at about, and it does, let me just interject, it does kind of hit the point
with a movie like this. And I think you could say this about any movie that depicts persecution
and abuse of any kind. It's a fine line. It's a hard line to walk because you want to,
you want to convey brutality, you want to convey injustice, and you want it to hit home and
and really stick with the viewer. That said, you can also glide easily into that passion of the
Christ torture foreign area where you're going, you're kind of doing this now a disservice because
you're going to gratuitous with this a little bit. You know what I mean? Anyway, go ahead, sorry.
Yeah, no, and actually shooting it beautifully and making it look fantastic is also a little fucked up
because you're watching these horrific acts of slavery. At some point, you hear a cell phone ring,
and it's like, what's going on? And then we cut to the present day, for a moment, you're thinking,
it's all in the present day. That's what the eventual reveal is. But you're like, I actually thought
for about two -thirds of the movie that when we're dealing with Janel Monet and her family and her
friends, that that stuff was in the present and that the horrors of slavery were still present in her
life and in her soul, you know? And that sort of would have been an interesting take on it. How
the pains of slavery are within black people to this day, and they're also not really going away.
It's why these discussions of reparation keep coming up and so forth. But that's not what it is.
What it winds up being is sort of a Westworld type experience where it's all in the modern day. What
you're seeing as the present is actually the past, Janel Monet wound up getting captured by her boss,
her white boss, played by Jenna Malone in a extremely campy over -the -top performance as a southern
bell. I mean, Malone in this thing, I texted this to you, she makes Anne Hathaway and the witches look
like refined. Yeah, it's absurd, man. But you find out that after a night of hanging out with her
friends, including Precious as a relationship expert, Precious also just, and this is not a weight
joke, just eating scenery through this thing. Like, I like Precious. When she's interviewed and
stuff, she's always calling Precious too. You can't help it. I mean, just talk about getting
typecast. You're precious. But yeah, they have like a girl's night out in the town that goes on for
15 minutes. They're dealing with racism. They're making a lot of wise cracks. That's a
segment. It's poorly written racism, which is a weird statement, but it is. And I, you know, it
look, people, it takes five minutes of research just watching the news to find palatable examples
of racism that you could use in your movie that reflect real life that are subtle and that's the point
and not over the top. This thing is like, it's ridiculous. Like, they come into this restaurant,
they're dressed to the nines. Like, they clearly have some money to spend. And they go, we'd like a
bottle of champagne and the waiter goes, well, we have Perseco. I'll bring, it's like, guys, come on.
That this is a little like, like, for sure. This could be, this could be, this could be, is a stunningly
beautiful woman. And it's like, no restaurant wants you to spend less money. No waiter wants you to
to not spend money on the check. Watch one of the billions of videos, people have taken on their phone
of humans being horrifically racist right to their face. But the Perseco thing wasn't hidden. They
want to sit them at this table, like in the back. And then precious is like, no, we're going to sit
at a better table and study. I didn't understand why that part. I didn't understand, was that supposed
to be they were hiding them in the back? Yeah. I thought it was just because it was a small table. And
there was like, I didn't even understand. This is what I mean. None of it's being translated very well.
And then when they do translate it effectively, it's through the most brutal, awful, disturbing
shit you can think of. And it's like, guys, there's a line here. There's an in between. There's a gray
area that that involves nuance, which is going to hit a lot harder. And you don't see any of that.
You don't see any of the nuance that makes this stuff truly toxic in the modern age.
And then when they're pulled into the into what is supposed to be, like you said, it's actually
the present because you realize what is happening is as they've all, not they've all, but because
precious gets away. But they get abducted into a, well, you don't know just yet. Let's save it for
the big reveal. But they are abducted into a plantation, right? That is run by obviously racist
whites. And you start to get the impression, okay, something's a foot here. What's going on?
This is some sort of, because because when they cut back to the plantation, after you see their,
see her get abducted, then one of the Confederates sold, because you don't know it first.
You're like, wait a minute. Is she, is she now dreaming that she's in this plantation,
like what's going on? And then one of the soldiers cell phones rings. So they've given away,
they don't even execute this part of it properly where they could have kept some mystery going of,
like, what the fuck is happening here? They give it away immediately. And you're like, okay,
this is clearly modern times on this plantation. Clearly these men are playing pretend.
They're not really, they're not really, they're not really, like, hook and snowflake, then they're
part two is really dumb. And surprise, surprise, the big reveal is, is, you know, she's going to escape.
And when she finally manages to escape, oh, God, I mean, this is one of the most cringeworthy scenes
I've ever seen ever in a movie. She slow motion. So, so it starts with her dragging Jenna
Malone's character from the back of a horse. Which again, it's, it's a little disturbing to exploit
the awful thing that happened to actual slaves. Absolutely. And use that as like your hero
device or whatever. It just doesn't work. So she's dragging Jenna Malone on the back of a horse.
Jenna Malone dies because she slams her head as she's being drug into the statue of Robert E. Lee.
Very subtle, yes. Very subtle, right? And then in slow motion, our main character rides on top
of a horse with a sword in the air, past a sign or through a civil war battle, and past a sign that says,
welcome to Antebellum, the world's premiere civil war reenactment park, right?
Which is the final moment of the movie and where the movie fully falls apart. Because obviously,
you kind of knew something like this was coming. And I actually thought when I was guessing what was
happening, this is kind of interesting because there are these idiots that reenact the civil war
and they have this weird fascination with it. What if there was a camp somewhere where they went
way too far with it? And they had like real slaves and stuff. That's pretty fucking twisted and dark
and some weird underbelly of the culture thing. And it's like, no, it's actually a theme park.
And we're just hasn't gotten out somehow in a in a world where the president can't piss sideways in
the bathroom without it leaking. No pun intended all over the internet. Yeah. You know what I mean?
Everybody's dirtiest deeds are getting exposed left and right now on the internet. Everybody is
exposing everybody. Somehow this Disney world level park is just operating on the crux of kidnapping
people. At least do the barben star thing of having making the people who want to go to the park
have to knock on a tree. And then it opens going to the earth's core because this thing is just
sitting on the street like six flags. It's crazy. I will say in the movies defense that I think they
had a great idea here. At least they had they had kernels of something really great and powerful and
interesting that would have worked as a twilight zone style thing would have worked absolutely mirror for
sure. But something in the execution is way off. The tonal shifts are way off. And it just doesn't work.
But but there's there was something here. And I just kept thinking it was going to click and it doesn't.
So a disappointment as opposed to a disaster. I didn't think it was a disaster. I think that you guys
that directed it were music video directors. I think yeah, that checks out. And they wrote it.
You know, it's always a thing for me. It's always a problem. I've never liked the films of Mick G for
that reason. You know, it's like, um, but yeah, it just doesn't work. It would have been a killer 35
minute twilight zone episode. Um, the execution is just bad here. It's two they have way too much time
on their hands. Yeah, the dialogues rough. The acting's rough. And they give away so much that by
the time you hit act three, you see the ending coming from a mile away. And then they execute that
so poorly. You're like, Jesus Christ, even this thing I was expecting to happen is somehow being
done worse than I expected. Um, so it's just a bad, bad movie. And then the star of it, I'm blanking
on her name. She was she's mainly. I'm gonna. Janelle. I'm a great musician singer. Yeah.
Which again, this is another problem I have with with with the entertainment and stop putting people in
thing. And she's a good actor. She's actually really great. I'm not saying she's a bad actor.
She's been good at other things. I don't know. There's a lot of other actors that there's people that
have devoted their life to acting. Let them act. You know, right? I don't know. Anyway, she's great,
though. I shouldn't say that. Um, you know, she didn't interview. This is the horror movie people need
right now. It's like, you know, when people start saying shit like that, I'm like, up. Here we go. Here we
go. It's not gonna be very good. It's also 100 % not a horror movie. There's no, there's no horror
element to it at all. I unless you're talking about the horrors of slavery, but by that token is glory,
a horror movie. No, you know, it's the horror. Well, the horror element is, it's like, it's like in
the way that hostile is a horror movie. Like, could you imagine people abducting other people for their
fantasies? Like I get that part of it, but there are scares in hostile. There's no scare. That's true.
That is true. This is, this is sort of boiled down to a social commentary. Um, and it's just not
well executed. And I mean, my god, if, you know, if you think we're being harsh, going rotten tomatoes,
critics across the board. Yeah. One of the best reviews I said like was like, look, man,
anytime you're tackling this subject matter, you're on the right track. But my god, this, this just misses
the mark, you know, in every turn. It's, it's why you, why they have the, the term noble failure.
It is a noble failure. The tensions are right, but it just doesn't quite get there. And I also
thought it was in poor taste that they had the band lady and to Bellum do the soundtrack. I couldn't
agree more. Couldn't agree more. And then when Tyler Perry came in playing anti -Bellum in full drag,
I just thought this is, this has gone off the rails. Yeah, Tyler Perry and dual roles as anti -Bellum
and as the racist general. Yeah, exactly. All right. Two two hogs down an anti -Bellum. That's our show.
Thank you for joining us today. We appreciate your support. We really do. Can't say that enough.
I'm Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram. And I have just posted as of yesterday an hour long
Sundance really cap. I went to the Sundance Film Festival online this year. I've got such a sad
sense. It really is. I do a little one act play at the beginning where I'm pretending to be hobnobbing
with Sundance celebs to give you the feel. But it amounts to two hours. Last January was one hour,
February is one hour. So it's a two hour look at the movies coming your way. Check that out on the
Patreon. Thank you for being with us on the Patreon. Joe plugs.
Jota Rosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Jota Rosa comedian on Facebook. Check out the no -press
network channel on YouTube for the podcast. Hey, babe with Christa Stefano and Salvo Conno
and taste buds with Salvo Conno and myself. That's about it folks. We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.