I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell
Hey, quit the sound of your screams
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Folks welcome to we'll see you in hell. It's the podcast that talks movies and I'm Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh. Hello everybody and welcome. We'll be talking today about
two hot new horror releases. Don't breathe too, as well as the nighthouse and the next.
Yeah, so Joe, what's happening? You were busy this morning and you called me out of breath. I didn't
know what was happening. Well Pat, as you and the listeners know I'm in the process of opening
a bar in a sandwich shop. Exciting. It is very exciting. What's the opening date? We don't have a hard
date yet, but we're, you know, we're projected for late September. So okay. But anyway,
I go out last night for Chris de Stefano's birthday. Yes. All I had to do today was record
two podcasts with you. Right. Starting at 12 p .m. my time. Easy enough. No need to pump the
brakes on a night out when that's your sketch. Okay. We have a great time, you know,
have the usual zillion, you know, birthday drinks. Sure. I come home, I get McDonald's in true drunk
fashion. What did you get? Quarter pounder with cheese and bacon and a 10 piece big nugget and fries.
We're good Lord. Were you always able to add bacon to a quarter pounder? I didn't even know
they had bacon. I'm going gone over the years, but it's back for a while now. All right.
Eat it in bed. You know, the whole thing. You know how you do it. Okay. Yeah. You know,
you know what I mean. You can act like you're better than this, but you know what I mean? Well,
I can't eat in bed with my wife. I mean, that's a level of deviant. I'm not. That's like a
stanza move. Yeah. But I'm just saying you're you're aware you're I'm familiar with it. Yeah. Yeah.
Anyway, we uh, we what's it called? We uh, so anyway, I wake up this morning.
The can there's a guy going into retile some stuff.
Uh -huh. And uh, I realized we had to move a bunch of shit out of the kitchen in order for
this to be done. And I find out the guy we had on deck to move all the stuff for us that does
those sort of things for us so far was not able to come in this week. Okay. Which means if that guy
shows up tomorrow to do the tiling and sees anything in the kitchen, he's going to be like, I'm not
doing the tiling. You got to clear all this out. Right. So what a what a thrill to be roused out of bed.
Two hours early or the night plan to go move heavy a quick kitchen equipment and box upon box
of tiles that were in the kitchen, but in the way. Well, at least it's cool in in the city, right?
It's about 92 degrees outside. Okay. Uh, and so I went and did that. And then, you know, I got to
be honest with you. It actually felt good. I was sweat in my ass off. I got it got me moving. It
was definitely a workout. Uh, it took me about an hour and uh, and it felt good to do. And
and that's why I got called you out of breath because I was literally moving these like 30 pound
boxes of tile. Right. The boxes are really heavy. So so might this be a new thing for you waking up
early and fighting off a hangover by moving heavy boxes of tile. I got to tell you, it's the classic
thing for me with exercise. When I have a task to do. Yeah. I enjoy it. Yeah. Because I see a finish
line and I'm not counting the minutes. I'm going. Okay. When this is done, it's done. And it's what I
can't stand about exercise is there is no finish line. It's just you the time limit is the finish
line. That's true. And all you can do is go, how long have I been doing this for now? Jesus Christ.
If they just said, look, here's all you got to do. You know, you do this. Yes. Just in that. And I
guess there are workouts that do that. But I know, uh, Peloton isn't an everyone's budget. But we've
been enjoying that because it's uh, it replaced our gym membership. So that's how we rationalized it
and you get to compete, which is what helps me stay in the game. There's other people on there.
And I give them back stories and reasons why I hate them and need to beat them. And then by the time
I've beaten them, it's over. It's great. Peloton is a great product. They are now a sponsor on my
other podcast. Okay. Okay. We asked, may we have a bike? Yeah. They said no. Yeah. Well, I mean,
they still recommend the product. It's I've used it. It's a great product. They're really great.
And you get your instructors that you kind of form a little stupid bond with and you like more than
others and so on and so forth. I like it. You can't like, this is such a dumb question. I'm about to
ask you can't interact with the instructors, right? It's just videos that they make. No, you can
yell at them, but they can't hear you. I, I once in a while when they're like, all right, now turn
your resistance up to 80. I'll be like, how fuck you? But they can't hear me say that.
Right. Yeah. Because it's a video. It's just a video they made. Yeah. And it's tricky because if
you have good taste and music, it's, it's a struggle. You realize how bad most people's taste and
music is because the bulk of it sucks. But you can get online Google, like you can Google Pixies,
Peloton, it'll tell you which rides have Pixies. And then generally that, that playlist will be more
suited to your liking. Is there an option because there should be? Yeah. There should be a known
music option with just the instructions where you can play your own music. Like, well, you can,
you can select more, more instructor, more music. But if you're doing a class with an instructor,
you'll hear them and you'll hear the music. But they also have rides that are kind of cool where you
ride through like, it'll say like the Appalachian Mountains. And then somebody filmed it. So you're
taking that ride and you can play whatever music you want for that. And that's still a good workout
because you're going uphill and downhill and the issue there is you got to trust yourself to push
yourself. And I, I don't trust myself. I need somebody telling me what I have to do. But it's
nice. I mean, which brings us Pat to our president. Yeah. Where has this man been? I need somebody
telling me what to do every day. You know, it was when we had Trump, I saw him more than my wife.
I had to Google Biden the other day because I forgot what he looks like. And if I were Biden,
I would not show my face either. I would be like, why did I take this job? Why would anyone take
that job? I don't think it's, I don't think it's that's what it is. I think it's the man is deteriorating
mentally. And they're like, he, there was that clip now where he laughed at the reporter.
And she's like, what about these students that are stuck in Afghanistan? He's like, yeah,
he'll be the first one I call. And then she gruts off. Like, you know, I saw the VP Kamala do that with
but they were, they were getting on her because she laughed. And in my opinion, she was laughing because
it's like, guys, could I approach the mic before you're screaming? What are you going to do about
Afghanistan in my face? It's just a job that I do not understand. Why would anyone want it?
I also kind of thought she was laughing like the way you laugh at a funeral where it's like, yeah,
what did you do? You know, I always laugh at at at the disturbing the troubling, you know, that's
that's my coping mechanism. That's why I'm not the president of the United States. And it's the only
reason because people have asked. I, I, I, what's it called? Can you imagine I'm, you're, I'm applying
for president, you're my VP. And they just start are playing, they're going through each episode of
this podcast and just running through each thing we've said. I've told you before, this show is the
least of my worries. There's like four months worth of ONA appearances in me on YouTube. I mean,
I'm terrified. Yeah. You know, look, they're still out there doing it. I mean, yeah, without a
country and the thing I did with Corinne for a while, you know, it's like, you know, but what are you
going to do? You know, we can't all. It's eventually you just got to go, look, man, you know, I did my
best to be a decent person. And if you're going to cancel me because you're misinterpreted something
I said or I had a wonky opinion at some point or I got forbid made a mistake.
Yeah. Here we are. You know, what are we going to do? But it is funny, man, we did go from one
extreme to the other, dude. It was like every day with Trump, people, you know, and now it's like,
where is this guy? But I said to my friend the other day, I was like, I'm realizing I need somebody
in my life telling me what to do. Like this is why I'm with the pelts on. I go between Cuomo stepping
down the at all the ships surrounding that Biden was like just being MIA. You know, they're recalling,
I'm not a fan of Gavin Newsom, but they were calling him. I'm like, can somebody somewhere in
the country just tell me what to do, please? Yeah. I mean, it's like, it's like when you're like,
I would be in a rainstorm when I was a kid like on vacation or something and your dad's driving
the car, you know, it's like, it's a little scary. When it, you know, in Missouri, you get like
tornado warnings and stuff, but your dad's driving so you feel fine. And we just don't have that feeling
anymore. It's just there, you need somebody who seems commanding and that's not what we have.
Now, it's just really it's a real tough tough tough time and it does not help that it's all
happening as my parents are just on the log flume ride down into like old age. I call them. They
don't know what the hell is going on. My mom will just be like, she talks me in circles. It's like
she's like a Batman villain at this point. I don't know what the fuck she's talking about. Yeah.
It's just wild shit, man. You know, I just I've never felt more alone or more the need to get married.
Just to have somebody here, even if I hate her, just somebody I recommend it. I'm a fan. I
recommend it. It's very helpful. My dad who had not spoken to me in roughly a month, not not by
choice. That's just our relationship. He sent me last night a photo of what he had gotten at the
grocery store, which is Oreo mega stuff, which is beyond double stuff. And he got the family
size bag. He lives alone. And the caption says, and people say there is no God. It's a funny text.
It wasn't bad for him, but I was just like, this is how you reach out to your son after a month of
silence during a deadly global pandemic. He's doing his best. They're all we're all doing our best.
Let me stop you here. He's not. He's not doing his best. He's not doing anyone's best.
I know I should make you feel better. When I was going to say, is he's doing his best as we all are,
and what I'm realizing is our best is our absolute worst. There is no best. None of us are capable of it.
Yeah. It's a horror show. I put it to you like this. Mr. Mom was a better parent. Mrs. Doubtfire
was a better parent. Mommy Dearest, a better parent. Those are the only movies I can think of with
parents. My friend Geno quoted Mr. Mom to me the other day, the great line. You want a beer?
It's 9 .15 in the morning. It's got to. I can never watch it again because of our moles in it.
And I'll have. Yeah, I know. But by the way, we forgot when we talked about funny farm the other week.
We glazed over the arguably the funniest character and thing in the movie.
Which is his real estate agent who's the fat guy who's like, every time they show him, they just show
his hand and what he's eating and like the jelly and the donut dripping all over the paper.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Then it's like, you're not going to believe how thin I've gotten.
And then it cuts him on the track. And he's still a heavy man drenched in sweat and the gag is he has a
heart attack every time he talks. Yeah, I you really underrated funny farm. I feel there's
good. I'm sorry, money pit, money pit, not funny farm. Sorry, money pit. That's in money pit.
I didn't sound like it was from funny farm. I knew it was from some. No, that's in money pit.
And Tom Tom Hanks is like walking with him and he the the heart monitor is going crazy. Oh,
yeah, yeah, yeah. Is that supposed to do that? And he goes, it's fine. And then he's in the ambulance
with Tom Hanks. He's going, this how I'm telling you what happens all the time. I'm fine.
Love money. It's very similar also to splash, which was really at least like the same year where John
Candies always exercising with him in that track suit, which is some of the funniest stuff in
having the hooking drinking a beer. And then the classic, you know, the classic story of the
racquetball scene one take, yeah, one take hits himself in the head. I mean, that is that is just
you don't get you don't get humor like that in a movie anymore. Just a heavy set guy
taking one in the face for real. Yeah, yeah, going like, I've been loving all these
Gandalfini stories. I just heard Robert Patrick the T 1000. He played as a degenerate gambler on
the show, one of the great subplots of that show. And Tony goes up to him and the director was like,
you know, he's he's pretty method like if you piss him off before the scene, you're going to
hold onto your butts, but you're going to get great stuff. So Robert Patrick goes over to him and
he's like, hey, you want to run lines? And they run lines a little bit. And then he goes, by the way,
when they call action in there, you better fucking bring it to Gandalfini. He's like, he got leaned
in his face. And he goes, oh, I'll fucking bring it. And he goes, by the way, I'm hung over his
fuck. So we're doing it once. They go in and he was like, I honestly thought he was going to kill
me and I deeply regretted challenging him. Loved it, loved him. I have a quick story just so I can
I can close this thing on my screen right now. Right as I'm waiting for you to log into the zoom, I
get a next door notification. Next door is pure entertainment. It's people that live around you
complaining about things that are happening in the neighborhood. And you know, it used to be
extremely racist. It used to be like black man with a sweatshirt walking down my street at noon.
Where are the police? And you're like, what? What are you talking about? So today,
this woman posts, and I guess she lives in my neighborhood,
Lude masturbating on the, and then she gives the address. Young man just greeted me on my walk. This
thing that what I'm about to tell you has a twist that you will not believe. Young man just greeted me
on my walk with my dog with, how do you get to the beach while he was masturbating? Late 20s,
late 20s, she pulls, she dusts off Afro -American, which I haven't heard
in decades. Afro -American shirtless in underwear down around his thighs,
and then gives the address again. Description of person involved, hair, black, top shirtless,
bottom underwear, build excellent, which I love. So she enjoyed what she saw. Race Afro -American again.
Now here's where things take a twist. I'm reading through the comments, many of which are funny.
Then I get this comment, Lude masturbating is so much better than in different masturbating,
but I suppose that's just personal opinion. I chuckle, I look up the poster of the comment,
Bruce Valange. The Bruce Valange, who apparently lives near me. Amazing. Oh, that's incredible.
I've seen him at the airport, but I've never seen him around the hood, so I'm very excited
about that. I saw him at the airport once. He was landing on strip 7. That's an amazing,
that's amazing. I love that he's like, no one wants to buy his jokes anymore, so he's just riffing
on the next door app. Wow, that's incredible. A little quick news psycho because you mentioned splash.
Yes. John Travolta said in the press last week that Splash was actually written for him,
and he turned it down. Really? Interesting. Not a terribly interesting story,
but it's kind of interesting. He wouldn't have been anywhere near as good as Hanks.
I'm curious because it was a very different Travolta back then. So I agree, like Hanks brings,
you know, that young Hanks is like, it's like young Michael J. Fox. It's all like piss and vinegar and
like, you know, like, yeah, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a real prickly performance.
He was like a, a bit of a softer Michael Keaton as well, kind of vibe. Very likable,
men liked him, women liked him, but he was a smart ass, a bit of a loose cannon.
The difference is Michael Keaton seemed like he could fuck you up in Tom Hanks.
He didn't seem like he was, he wasn't against blown a rail or two in the trip.
What I've heard, he was a relentless coke addict right up until like around the dream team
area, he kind of pulled it together. I really would love to believe that he was on coke through
the entire clean and sober shoot. He may have been. I mean, I think he, well, I'm definitely talking
stories out of school. So look it up. But I feel like there was talk of him beating Courtney Cox.
He was dating Courtney Cox and he slapped her around or something. Really?
I could be wrong. I never heard that. I would hope that you're wrong.
He's, um, he's in everything now. He's become like the new Adam Driver. He's in like a Hulu show
and an HBO show. Greatest third act of the movie. Greatest third act I've ever witnessed in acting.
Yeah, I mean, I, when he, you know, jammed onto the scene in Jackie Brown, I was like, oh yeah,
like he didn't look great in Jackie Brown. He probably looks better now. But I was like,
oh yeah. Like why are we sleeping on Michael Keaton? And then he kind of came back.
Well, but no, after that he was gone for, remember he did Jack Frost and like it was like this
abominable movie. He did, like, he was, like, domestic, not domestic disturbance, but he did another one
of those like really shitty thrillers and something heights, specific heights.
Specific heights was around the Batman days. I'm talking about an even worse
movie. Um, yeah, go ahead, go ahead. But he did, but he after Jack Frost, he went away
and he started doing, he started doing super, super indie movies. Yeah, barely saw the light
of day. One was called Game Six. It was pretty good. Um, I think he directed that one. Uh,
and he was directing a lot of these and, uh, but they were super underground. He kind of went like,
and this was before, well, I guess it was. And it was after the Tarantino boom. But like,
he was way underground. And then the first thing he resurfaced, and I remember, was the other guys
where he played the manager at the bedbath and beyond. Yeah, that's right. And he was hilarious in
it. And it was like obsessed with TLC. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The, uh, I have two jobs because I
spent, what is the line? I, I, I have two jobs because I spent $150 ,000 to send my son to college.
And now he's gay and wants to be a DJ. Uh, we got, I'm looking now at the end. And he's like,
and then he just started coming back hard. But I mean, Birdman was what relaunched him. He got the
Oscar nom. Right. And then after that, he did the founder, which I think he also got nominated for
anymore. That was, that was it. He was back. Yeah. We got, it looked like weirdly multiplicity
was kind of the end of his a list run, which is weird because that movie was hilarious.
I love it. Um, multiplicity into Jack Brown, Jackie Brown. There was a phrasier appearance that I
forgot about. I guess as a caller, probably. Arguably my favorite episode of phrasier,
next to when they get into the new spot is the key one. The key one is incredible. Oh, so he's in it.
He plays Lilith's like scoundrel scam artist brother. And phrasier hates him. It's who's in
who's in that game six movie you mentioned, baby new worth Lilith herself. Really? And Lilith isn't in
the key in episode. Okay. We got, uh, we got Jackie Brown then desperate measures. The thriller I was
thinking of that just tanked. And then he popped up and out of sight. Same character uncredited.
And then yeah, it's a run of stuff that I'm just not familiar with.
Yeah, one of the movies was like this weird like salesman, Glenn Gary, Glenn Ross meets a thriller
kind of thing. And it was sort of a comedy, but then there was like murder and entry. It was very
strange. Uh, it wasn't a bad flick. It just wasn't. It was just strange. But I remember, I mean,
in this world, if you just keep your head down and do the work at some point, somebody's going to go,
what about that guy? Like, and you, you'll make it back as long as you don't be a fucking asshole.
What I'm incredibly excited about, obviously, is his return as Batman in the flash movie. Yes.
And Keaton has said apparently that so they're doing a Batman Beyond movie as well, apparently,
which will be in Batman Beyond. It's about an older Bruce Wayne passing the cow to the new Batman.
To the younger Batman and like sort of thing, the cow, the cape and cow, you know, yeah,
to the new Batman and like sort of training him and being like his Alfred or whatever.
So they're apparently they're doing a movie that and apparently the campaign from Keaton is he
wants Burton to direct it. So it can be the final official third Batman movie with them. Like they can
do if they can finally complete the trilogy that they started to prop up a dream. That'd be awesome.
Yeah. Yeah. So we'll see. If we're going to trust Burton, if we're prepared to trust Burton,
I would trust Burton with Batman again. Look, they're just signed. They're doing Beetlejuice.
They're doing the sequel finally. Burton's on Keaton's on. I think we're doing a rider's sign that
it's been confirmed. That was a month and a half ago. Oh, because it can't, five years ago,
they were going to do like Beetlejuice goes Hawaiian and then it never happened. Yeah, no, they just
they like apparently it's all officially confirmed now like it is happening. So I'm excited about that.
I mean, just when I think there are no more of these great like characters for my childhood that could
be relaunched, you know, I said Ghostbusters was sort of the end of it. I'm wrong. You got Keaton
coming back as Batman. You got Keaton coming back as Beetlejuice. Very excited about both of those.
You got an Indiana Jones five coming, you know, but have any of these have one of these been
very even very good. I thought Force Awakens was an excellent Star Wars movie. It was the one great
one of that trilogy. You know, so yeah, I mean, they can be. They can't, you know, look, I love, you
know, the the Irishman was my favorite movie of last year and I know they weren't reprising
characters, but I certainly never thought I was going to see another Scorsese gangster movie with
De Niro, especially one that had Pacino in it too, you know, right. So it can be done. It can be done.
I to do a little bit of a news psycho. I was texting. All right, sent you a voice note yesterday,
but it was Patty Jenkins of she's complaining now that Wonder Woman 84 like they did her so dirty. It
was heartbreaking for her that they released it on HBO Max. This thing was made for the I max
theaters. She you know, she shoots practical effects. She loves film and to have it put it. It's like
Patty, that wasn't anyone's fucking issue with your movie. You're trying to use COVID as an excuse
for why your movie was one of the worst superhero movies and that's a low bar. Right. I mean, just
it's enough. It's enough. And also how bad do you look in this day and age whining about your
fucking movie with everything that's going on? Like we're not sympathetic. You made a terrible movie,
move on, make a better one next time and shut up. That's all right. Yeah, it's like I got faith in
Janks that she's a good filmmaker and that she can make a cool movie. You know, I want to see what
she's going to do with this rogue squadron flick. What's rogue squadron? It's you know, it's a
Star Wars movie about X -wing pilots that she's doing rogue squadron was a series of video games
for Star Wars. They were really fun games. I mean, I'm not ever really terribly excited about
Star Wars stuff that focuses on non like force users. But you know, whatever, it should be pretty cool.
You know, I'm excited to see what she does with it. I'm excited to see, you know, I'm a fan of
Scar Jo too. But it's like, you're right. It's like guys, these like complaints, right? Look,
look, if legally they did you wrong and you got to sue like like Joe Hanson is doing, then that's
what you got to do. I get it. But this patty Jenkins thing, you're right. Like to complain about like,
it's like patty. You're a millionaire. How many times over from this franchise? It's like
big deal. Elizabeth Olson and these actors coming out like I support Scarlett, Joe Hanson in her.
It's like, okay, you know, fine. But like what you they're acting like they're going, you know,
they're going up against, you know, prejudice or something. It's like it's a difference between
20 million and 25 million dollars for somebody who already has 500 million dollars.
And do it. You get your money. Secure the bag, but do it privately. We don't need to
hear about all this as people are losing their homes and businesses. It's fucking disgusting.
I just want to say at the dinner table, I support Pierre in telling the waiter or caviar,
didn't come out quickly enough. You know, it's like shut up. Yeah. And then meanwhile, like, okay,
I didn't hear you say anything about racism, about police brutality, about global warming. It's like,
this is the issue you're going to bat for. It's it's all ridiculous. Yeah, it's all everybody.
And look, I get it. I get it. We all have to we all have to try to hold one another accountable
to be better and we should call out bullshit when we see it. I get all that. I'm not arguing any of that.
But this this concept now of like it's just okay all the time to bite the hand that feeds you. Yeah.
It's like, hey, I've been on SNL for six months and now I'm going to piss and moan that Elon musk it.
It's like, you used to get like they fired Nora done because you wouldn't appear on the
dice episode and look, I'm a huge dice fan. She actually had way more of an argument and way more
of a point. I didn't agree with it, but she had a point. Yeah. This shit, it's like, I'm just going to
shit all over the network and my boss is and then just show up at work on Monday. And nobody can say
anything to me. And if you penalize me, it's because you're silencing me and not letting me live my
truth. It's like, fuck you. Do you know the shit I've had to eat from bosses through my life?
And I hate needless do -paying. I hate the idea of shit rolling downhill. I always when I have this
when I open this place, I hope that I'm an awesome boss and I plan on treating my employees much
better than a lot of bosses that treated me. But the point is this, this concept that you can just do
whatever you want. Yeah. It's so crazy. It's so crazy. Like, I've never seen and you see it
everywhere. And I can't stress enough. It's got nothing to do with class. It's got nothing to do
with financial status. It's got nothing to do with race. It's got nothing to do with political
persuasion. It's got nothing to do with religion. Because trust me, people, I'm dipping my
toe in every pond in New York City. I got a lot of different fucking plates. I'm spending nobody
can appreciate their fucking job anymore. No, nobody. No, nobody. It's all owed to them. They should
be able to say whatever they want to their boss. They should be allowed to slack off, not do anything.
Speaking in generalities, of course, there are some great workers out there. But it's just, it is just,
it's unfucking real man. The entitlement. Well, I think people have just taken enough. And I get, I
get that too. But it's also at some point, if we don't all get back to doing things, then society
will collapse. If it hasn't already, and that's debatable. Anyway, anyway, I got a new, I got a scary
stuff. Yes. Because I mentioned Indiana Jones. I, I'd never played these two games, but I got for
my PS2 and for my PSP, Indiana Jones and the staff of Kings. Awesome, awesome, awesome game.
Same as the Emperor's Tomb, which I talked about on here before that I played on my Xbox,
the original OG Xbox. They're just awesome. The story, the storyline is so cool. You're trying
to find the staff of Moses, you're up against the Nazis. They're trying to find it because it can
rain fire down from the skies. It's, it's just like classic shit that you love from the movies.
Half Indiana Jones for me is the sound effects. They pull all the sound effects right out of the
movie. So every time you shoot your gun, it's like the movie sound effect. When you fight guys, it's
like that, you know, like those like really awesome punch noises. The whip makes the awesome noise.
You swing around. You're, you're solving puzzles. You're getting into fights. You're breaking
chairs over guys' heads. The guy playing Indiana Jones sounds a lot like Harrison Ford. It's written
well, like, it's, it's, it gave me faith that this new movie without Spielberg, you know, he's producing
it. But I was worried because I was like without Spielberg and Lucas really being involved.
Like, what is it even in Indiana Jones will be good? Then I went and played this game and I was like,
oh yeah, like it's possible to do this with people that just appreciate the characters in the franchise.
So I recommend they're both very affordable video games too, by the way. They're not like these,
you know, they're not like $75 out of print, whatever. I think I paid $17 for each of them.
Okay. Okay. Well, I guess we go to the movie corner.
Yeah, I guess so, Pat. All right. I didn't know there was going to be a controversial opinion.
I saw, you know what I rewatched the other night. I asked, usually when I ask Heather,
what do you want to watch? She's like, I don't know. Give me a couple options. You know, she generally
defers. I go, what do you want? Before the question is out of my mouth, she says, Captain Ron.
Jesus. And I go, look, happy to do it. Can I ask why? I saw this when I was obsessed with Martin
Shored when I was 13 years old and I recognize it as a bit of a stinker. She's like, my cousin,
we wouldn't stop talking about it. Said it was the funniest movie she's ever seen. Okay.
So we rewatched Captain Ron. It's a bad film and it's even worse now. It's short and
rustle, which should have been a great combo. I learned from the IMDB page that they were originally
playing each other's roles. Then they went out one night, got completely fucked up and traded.
They were really drunk and they were like, let's just trade parts. I want to do something different.
I can't really imagine Marty Short playing a pirate. Doesn't make a lot of sense. But
to have Martin Shored as like a neutered family man makes no sense. He is a complete drip in the movie.
He essentially gets cucked. I imagine there was a much darker version where Russell
fucks his wife and daughter because that's where I thought it was going. So Martin Shored's boring
outside of a couple really funny pratfalls that he does. And Kurt Russell is doing like this character.
It's beyond snakeplicin. He's like, yeah, I'm on the high seas. He's not funny at all. He's
got no charisma. And this is Kurt Russell we're talking about. The most charismatic man in the world.
So it's a huge swing in a mess. It's got classic touchstone, which was the adult
spent the adult Disney movies. Steak out Captain Ron. The Shelley long bet middler pictures.
These were all touched on. I thought this was like a family comedy. Captain Ron's PG -13,
but it's there's nudity in it. His wife is played by Mary Kay Place who was an actress from
like the big chill and stuff. She's naked in the movie. I didn't even remember this. And for me to
not remember nudity when I'm 13 is insane to me. But her and Marty Shored are fucking in the shower
and then the water they get trapped and it's like they're going to get drowned in the shower and then
they come splashing out on the floor. What I mean is it wasn't the Disney movies like the great
mouse detective. They opened up this adult division for like three minute baby was touched on.
But that's more adult than most of their fair. They all fit into this like safe boring thing where
the jokes don't land. It's like they're high concept but they don't bother developing it any more
than just the concept. It's just the bare minimum and it sucks. Captain Ron sucks. I know people
have affection for it. A lot of times the movies you see in your youth stick with you till you're
older. Not Captain Ron. Take that Captain Ron. I'm kind of short this week. I started rewatching
all in the family. Yeah. A hilarious show about a racist man who lives with his liberal son -in -law.
Very dips -dippy wife and a fiery daughter. It's a wonderful show. They don't make it like this anymore.
The jokes are so edgy and most of the time so racist.
But the jokes on him I mean that. Well sometimes it's not you know it goes kind of both ways but
but yeah he ends up with egg on his face more than more so than that. But it's just a relief to watch
it on show like that and see the edge and the. It just makes you sad. It does especially because
the very same people who want everything to be super sanitized would cite that as one of the most
groundbreaking shows in television history. It just doesn't make any sense but here we are. I'm not saying
why why did the racism leave from television? That's not what I'm saying at all. I'm saying
to to allow a character to be racist or to be problematic or you know. Or just to allow god damn
jokes to be jokes and assume the person watching it isn't a fucking moron. Right. But anyway
anyway go ahead. No it's true. I mean they I and forgive me if I mention this but when I read that
made men the book about Goodfellas by Glenn Kenny which is great. They they talk about how like
Squarespace he gets a lot of shit about being racist and the only reason for that is that there's no
third character walking up to peshy and deniro and saying hey you guys are being racist. You know
which would be nuts. Right. Anyway my next picture I watched on HBO Max the other night called
Midnight Family. It's a documentary a fascinating documentary about in Mexico City this statistic is
how it starts. In Mexico City the government operates fewer than 45 emergency ambulances for a population
of nine million. So this has spawned an underground industry of for -profit ambulances run by people with
no training or certification. This documentary is about one such family a dad who looks like he is
seconds from death. He's highly diabetic and just smokes and eats throughout. They bring along a 10 -year
old very overweight boy with them on all these journey and he watches people die and bleed out and
everything while eating chips the entire time. Wow and then a 16 -year -old kid who's holding this
family together who drives the ambulance who also much like the old jokes about lawyers racing to
the scene of a crime they write these ambulances race because they're trying to get money so they'll
race to the thing and edge each other off the road stuff like that. A fascinating movie my one issue is
they don't they don't take the time to answer a lot of questions because they're they're going for a
you are there fly on the wall kind of feel and just thrusting you into the action but you know I'm
watching it with my wife and we're like where's the mom did she die you know like if we're gonna
spend 90 minutes with his family we got to know a few basic things about them and you really don't
find a lot of stuff out that's a style that's a choice but it's what keeps this thing from being like a
classic documentary however it's only 80 minutes long it's intense as hell
and it's just a wild ride it was sort of like a real life bringing out the dead
that score says you move with Nicholas Cage which I love but it's I highly recommended it's on HBO Max
right now I think it was a Sundance choice and it's it's nuts you know everything I just told you if
that doesn't make you want to see it I don't know what I can do it's really fun and exciting
I watch started rewatching the Jefferson's okay spin off the ball in the family uh -huh about a racist
yes who hates at least whites yeah and his bossy wife and his fiery maid once again hilarious never
seen an episode so there it is yeah absolutely hilarious and they don't make sure it's like that no more
right that's it oh all right fun uh I rewatched get him to the Greek who
who Jonah Hill uh Russ brand who man that that guy had a five -year streak and then gone gone
I met him I met him and he's one of these guys who was like me to set this restaurant and then he
was in a closed -off back room with a restaurant like a mob boss and he was pitching uh he wanted a
rewrite of this script it was a movie called bad father was whenever everything was bad this bad
that and the premise was a guy on the run from mobsters goes into a church and decides to go
undercover as a priest and so the first words out of a mouth in the meeting were yeah you know it's a
great idea you know kind of do the reverse sister act thing and he goes what's that and I said yeah
you know sister act with a guy right and he's like oh no I don't see it that way at all I don't
see it that way at all just pretending he didn't know that it was the exact verbatim plot of sister act
right beat for beat um he also said the phrase my wife kitey parry he said that five million times to me
and I'm like I wanted to be like I know she's your wife she's not anymore Russ but um you know he was
he wasn't as annoying as you might think now he's got this kind of like I'm a I'm a shaman vibe
that rubs a lot of people the wrong way but whatever he he enjoyed his uh podcast or
his youtube thing that he does very balanced politically very fair very uh I like it he seems like a
super interesting guy but also one of the strangest like bouts of stardom of all time like he was kind
of funny and ceremonial and they this I forgot the character and get him to the Greek is a spin -off
of forgetting ceremonial it's his same character where he's the rock star uh this movie doesn't really
work there's a couple laughs most of the laughs are in the first half Jonah Hill is funny in it his wife
is played by Joe's favorite actress Elizabeth Moss her girlfriend um she's not funny believe it or not
there's a extremely weird and uncomfortable scene near the end of this movie where Russell brand
Jonah Hill and Elizabeth Moss have a three way which I will never forget about that why does that happen
and it's it happens with like 10 minutes to go in the film like you're just like what are you guys doing
there's an energy to it they throw everything at the screen to kind of see what sticks but it's like
it's really hard to give a shit weirdly stealing the show is puff daddy or p -ditty he's funny in
it as like the the record executive um you know it just doesn't work it doesn't work I don't really
know what to say but it it passes the time sort of like a sitcom the the two have a good a good chemistry
you know Jonah Hill was also in forgetting ceremonial but he's not playing his character from that
it's confusing uh but you know I saw it in theaters I remember thinking it was pretty good
and you know I definitely took a notch off but it raises a larger question I'm wondering lately Joe
do you think that you like movies more when you're happy and you hate movies more when you're in a bad
mood for me I have to admit that that's true uh my mood affects my enjoyment of a movie great
yeah absolutely absolutely not great it absolutely can it's not always the case a hundred percent
of the time but it's it's it can be the case you know sometimes the movie turns by mood around can
sure but yeah I would say I would say it's certainly possible you know it has happened to me
it's an interesting thing for critics to reckon with it's like you know I've never seen a critic say
look in fairness my uncle died last night so that might be why I didn't like this movie you know
they never tell you they're in a bad mood but uh just something I was thinking about I think it has
a lot more effect than people admit especially critics so I also once saw a man sleep soundly through
memoirs of a gaysha at the theater and then give it a very good review in the New York post my final
thing is I've been watching Sanford and Sun or rewatching I guess I should say I sitcom about you want
to be in the 70s basically well I'm just noticing if you're not noticing the thread here this is a sitcom
about a very funny racist man yeah uh who lives with his fiery son uh and they argue all the time here's
the point I'm getting at with this arc people you got one show with a white guy that hates everybody
that is white you got another show about black guy that hates white people you got a third show about
a black guy that hates everybody that isn't black yeah they're all prejudiced when it comes down to
it they're not hateful they're just prejudiced um but uh and they and it's all challenged by other
characters in the show so even if they are even if they are just to have this conflict so uh and
there are three of the funniest shows that have ever existed on television yeah since Sanford either
it's great I mean it non -stop calls his son a dummy um every five seconds his sister -in -law
hates his sister -in -law to only talks about how ugly she is she talks about she's gonna knock him out
all the time okay uh he's afraid that his son is gonna catch Puerto Rican from their
it's wild it's insane uh it's insane yeah and then and then his son is there to be like you're
an idiot dad like what is wrong with you you're an idiot yeah and then once again Sanford usually
ends up with egg on his face as does George Jefferson as does Archie Bunker right
they're just dynamic shows that are funny just because they're funny and they're and they're
challenging and I don't think anybody I know there was controversy around these at some of them at
the time I just have I'm just hard pressed to believe anybody's watching one of those shows especially now
going yeah that's a good point you know uh yeah I don't know was Sanford Sanford Sanford Sanford wasn't
a Norman Lear joint wasn't no Jefferson's in all the family were do you notice a drop -off in
quality without the the Lear touch since he's considered the only person in the seven days who made
good television no not at all Sanford and son went here's the interesting thing with Sanford and so
Sanford and someone five seasons Red Fox left because he got offered a variety show at a competing
network and I know they were having money issues yeah they then tried to keep it going with the
show called Sanford Arms where two new people take over the junkyard okay turn it into like a hotel
that bombs in a season then they bring Sam his Sanford's our Red Foxes solo show gets canceled
any within a year they bring him back and relaunch Sanford and son under the title Sanford
okay because um demon Wilson I think his name is that played his son refused to go back over a
money dispute this time I think it was so he just goes back and it's just called Sanford and he just
does another few seasons of that show like it was immensely popular the show was did Sanford
recapture the magic or was it like the golden palace it was like golden palace it wasn't that good
it it it was like running on films but it's still it still went for a little while but you know have
you seen golden palace with Don cheetah on the gals yeah I don't like it um no but also too it's
what's fascinating to me is the Archie all in the family only became Archie's place it didn't that
was not a spin -off it became they retuck packaged the show because Jean Stable didn't want to do
the show anymore right so they just repackaged it and and made it Archie bunkers place or whatever
and that was hugely successful that went for like five fucking seasons why wouldn't they just kill off
Jean Stable they did they killed her off they killed her off in the at the beginning of the
second season of the of the solo show yeah and they said if they were going to continue on he couldn't
be in the house oh okay they didn't have meathead anymore they didn't have Gloria you know it's like
they're like we got to get you like into a workplace just an old racist man staring in the mirror
hating his life he's yeah they took they really take a lot of the teeth out of him in in the Archie
bunker he's much more open -minded yeah about things you know he's got a black neighbor and he's very
friendly with her whereas in all the family he's like uh geez these people are losing it you know what
I mean well it's it's definitely an evolved version of the character but um but anyway
let's get to the movie let's do it I'll start with a brief recap of don't breathe and you can
take us through the plot of don't breathe too because I watched don't breathe before leaving for
the theater to see don't breathe too I saw it I think you and I saw it in theaters Joe yeah but uh
don't breathe the original I still think is is a really solid good little horror movie with
some great scares you know some fun kind of jump scares it's it's it's three teens or 20s whoever
who break into a house they break into houses and Detroit all the time they hear there's a blind
uh Iraq war veteran played by Stephen Lang who was sitting on three hundred thousand dollars
they break into his home thinking it'll be a piece of cake he wakes up and basically uses his
training to fuck them up even though he is blind and uh you know it's one of those one location for
the most part horror flicks I think they do a great job keeping it exciting keeping you on your toes
and then in the home stretch it becomes insane when they find uh the girl who who killed his daughter
in a in a car accident tied up chain to a wall of mattresses in the basement
and you learn that Stephen Lang is impregnating her using a turkey based her full of semen so that she
can provide him with a new daughter uh that scene to me is where the movie jumped off Joe was kind of
teasing me about that this week and I said no yeah you're right I think that scene is what separates it
from other horror movies it shows a much in the same way sleep way camp ends with a
child's dick hanging out who you thought was a girl it's one of those real wrist -taking shocking horror
twists that they just don't do anymore it's got it had a grind house feel to it that I loved
and that to me took it from being a solid little b horror movie into something a little bit better um
don't breathe too I didn't really know where they were going with it but I assumed that when they sent
the lead girl uh who's the girl from Zoe's playlist or whatever at the end she goes off with her
little sister and she learns that Stephen Lang is still alive and it's really setting the stage for a
classic battle between the two of them another rematch that doesn't come that girl uh Jane Levy is
not even in this movie it's a completely different story and aside from Stephen Lang it's completely
different characters it's a bold choice and I like that choice Joe what is the plot of don't breathe too
so the plot of don't breathe too is he's got a daughter you don't know where he got the daughter from
you're assuming it's not from the girl he had captured in the first film obviously um but you're
wondering did he do that again to somebody else or did he just adopt a girl or whatever
uh it's it creep me out in a big way because I was like is he grooming this young girl to someday
impregnate her which is really fucked up because it's a little girl um that was all in your head
I don't know why your head went there uh because that's what he was doing the first time you know he
he was the in the first movie though it's it's grotesque what he's doing but he's doing it because
he's saying you took my daughter from me and now you give me a new daughter and then I'll let you go
all right um so anyway he uh um he's training the daughter to defend herself in the way that he
is able to um because you know obviously he thinks something eventually is coming and you don't
know what that something is and then we'll be hold it does happen where his house is again attacked
you're not quite sure why and then the reveal is that this these are major spoilers by the way so
um the reveal is that it's because this little girl is not his daughter it's a little girl he found
uh who was uh stranded basically on her own because her parents were meth
lab people their meth lab blew up they went to jail the mother was presumed dead
and he took the girl and under his wing a because he wanted a daughter and b because he wanted to
give her a better life to get her you know he hates criminal scum you know he's one of these
right so uh so anyway you know it's a lot of that whole thing again uh of his house being attacked him
defending his home and then the nice flip is they managed to get the girl and make make away with her
which which now forces him now to descend upon them and they're on their turf which I liked I
thought was that was a pretty cool twist um I liked the flick a lot I thought it was much much more
entertaining than the first one uh I found the first one to be fairly boring um you know I'm
definitely willing to rewatch it I certainly went in not with grind house expectations but more just
you know regular old popcorn harm movie expectations and also this was a release that came up before
the pandemic so you know I I'd like to think that it'd be a little more accepting of the film now
uh because of how bad everything is yeah and then also too just my appreciation of going into
the theater now is a lot different you know yeah I was at a point when don't breathe came out where I
think I was actively saying I'm never gonna go to the movies again every movie fucking sucks yeah so um
anyway I liked it a lot I thought it was a really fun ride I thought that I thought them turning him
into an anti hero was a really interesting and cool approach and also a typical approach with a
sequel you see that a lot with sequels when the villain has to come back um you know I know there
was some controversy around that you know and you know I guess I get it I get questioning it but
at the end of the day I thought they made it work somehow after the vial stuff he does in the first
movie um but you know since when our horror movie icons not the not the hero you know not the anti heroes
I mean it's like I get it Freddie does terrible things and he's not an anti hero but he's the one
you're there to see yeah you're there to see Jason you're cheering for Jason you're cheering for pinhead
you know like so right the same thing difference is it's weird though it's like uh and he didn't
he didn't rape the squirrel but it's like what he was doing was in a weird way more fucked up than
like killing teenagers he was had this kind of devious sexual plan that kind of makes it creepier
but um it's definitely it's it's grotesque I told you that turkey baster filled with semen was where
I checked out of the first movie and it's where I checked in you know I'm gonna be honest with you
but um I was really excited about this because Sam Raimi who I of course respect he's a producer on it
and the first one and he said it was only the greatest idea for a sequel I've ever heard and I'm not
kidding now that's extreme but I do I do really like that it didn't go expected because and maybe
that was as simple as uh Jane Levy not wanting to return and they had to come up with something more
clever I don't know but uh I did really like it and that twist the turkey baster moment in this is
when you find out that they're kidnapped this girl basically you know take her organs and it's it's
in a similar way to me that elevated the movie into wow this is fucked up I like this more kind of
mode and maybe that says something about me I don't know but um I dug it too I did not like it as much
as the original I do think you know I don't even see a lot of the true f horror that comes out your
bye -bye man's and all that kind of stuff the empty man and all these movies um but I know horror is
pretty bad right now in general as far as horror movies go this isn't above average one no question
um well that's always sort of the case with harry it's it's you've got to sift through and that's
the fun of the genre yeah you know and some people really love the bad stuff you know and some of
its bad on purpose and whatever but harry has always been a a a a curators game you know yeah I have to
imagine that Lang might have been like a little disappointed because it's for quite a while
in this it's not really his story but uh he's great in it I love the guy and I'm on Wikipedia here it says
in a post -credits scene the dog comes by Norman's body I was not still in the theater for that but I assume
that's leaving things open for a third entry and that he's potentially fine yeah I was surprised at
the end of this that they killed him yeah well it seems like it's that the dog comes by Norman's
body he doesn't say if he's alive or dead but if they put that in there they must be yeah so that makes
sense then that makes sense oh I read it wrong it says the dog comes on Norman's oh good and do it
out of out of a baster yeah a bit of a homage to the ridge uh anyway um my hog's up firmly for
don't breathe too I was not excited to see it because I wasn't a fan of the first one uh but almost
immediately I was in uh my only criticism of the film is I felt they did a bad job of establishing
that he was blind I was like if I didn't see the first one which you could have totally watched this
without seeing the first one you wouldn't have been lost or anything I would not have known he was
blind until like an hour into the movie so yeah I they didn't really have much fun with it in the way
they did with the original which is such a strange but I dug it it's um to me my my hog is straight
out ahead of me it's not one of those boners that that goes up towards the chin but it's certainly not
flaccid either that's our show folks tune into the next episode we're gonna cover the nighthouse
starring Rebecca Hall the woman who rolled over on Woody Allen the hardest what did she do
she did multiple films with him oh yeah yeah yeah then suddenly was like I am embarrassed of what this
man it's like okay Becky uh anyway uh Rebecca Hall stars in the nighthouse she is a fine
actor and uh we will talk about that film it comes to you via the kids that wrote what was it super
dark times and they're gonna be doing the new hell razor but we'll put in all them all right folks that's
our show we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell