I'll see you in the air, I'll see you in the air.
Vandeshayan air, your Beach Pecos, a tank on the drain, big mothin night, I'll see you
in the air, I'll see you in the air, I'll see you in the air, I'll see you in the air,
We'll see you in how bonus episode things are going to go a little differently on these apps there for you
Patreon subscribers that gave
Ten sweet dollars or more to what we hope is your favorite or one of your favorite podcasts
We thank you and this episode is just for you folks. Nobody else gets it
You're exclusively in the exclusive zone and I'll tell you it's where
It's Pat
It's where it's Pat. What does that mean? It's where it's at. Oh, it's where it's Pat
You know, I don't think it's gonna catch on. I don't think it will either but you don't have a name that's
It's it's I mean have a good name, but it's hard to put it into a thing like there's no way like phrase. I could think of
I've hated my name since the it's Pat character hit the airwaves right as I was entering puberty. How about this?
Congrats, you're getting the bonus episode because you gave to the highest donation tier
Time to patch yourself on the back time to pat yourself. Yeah, how about compacts
That's worse than either of them nothing's great
folks
We're having a lot of fun here tonight
But I think it's time for us to get on with the show and and in the process on
Who is it?
Now I should have said this before we start recording. I don't think you should do that in these episodes
I think people would riot if I didn't I think these should be like like how Star Wars puts out like Rogue One
There is no opening crawl in these episodes. These are different. These are special. No
I think I think the people want the all with the Joe. All right. I don't think anybody's gonna take your side on this
Hope when we could start a new thing where I on these episodes I say a pat thing
Well, I mean, I'm telling you none of those are catching on it might be something for the for week two
Okay, but it was none of those. I'll try it next week again or next month
Month two these are once a month
Folks, I want to tell you about the day I had I'm getting very
Down on our society
I wouldn't you now obviously everything that's happening in the news is a disaster and I'm not gonna get political
I'm talking about everything talking about Harvey Weinstein. I'm talking about everything. It's also like
Everyone's kind of been joking about Harvey Weinstein sexually assaulting people for decades
And it was kind of like a weird joke
And then now it's like oh everybody's all outraged Rose McGowan called him out for raping her
Like a couple of years ago, and everyone was like all right Rose. I found it and I found out yesterday
She was she was banned from Twitter for it. She got banned from Twitter. Twitter brought her back
Man Twitter. What a bunch of fucks. They're real fucks over there. Twitter is as bad as it gets
I was taking the lengthy walk from your gate to your apartment door. I
Decided to check in with Twitter and I had been been away from it for a bit
And what I saw was I
Forget the exact name. Let me bring it up, but it was a
a new breed of guy who is so homophobic that he will not wipe his ass
Mm -hmm. There was a Buzzfeed article about this that is being shared
So he'll walk around with a shitty asshole because he thinks touching his asses gay to avoid putting his his hand in his ass
Man's missing out on one of the greatest joys in life by the way
You consider wiping your ass a joy one of the only high points of my day is really getting in there. Oh my God and getting it clean
I enjoy that. Oh boy. It feels good. It's a man's g spot ladies
It's called septic masculinity
When homophobia presents men from literally wiping their own asses
septic
I had to look at my Twitter likes and in doing so I want to I want to call attention to a great follow
Mr. David Angela, one of my favorite comedians. I like David quite a bit and
Here's this tweet. Dr. Phil's guests are all crisis actors, right?
I mean this family can't get their son to stop using drugs, but it'll hop on a plane to talk to Phil
The next one is a little play sobbing. He's violent. He's abusing drugs. He won't listen to us
Where is he now?
Drinking la Croix in the green room
Hello area, followed David Angela. He's a great man and a very funny man. That's very funny stuff
Folks, I called a lift and how many occasions I've been frustrated with a lift on my way over here
And yes, I'm responsible enough to know that if I hang out with Joe, they'll be drinks and I need to lift
This woman I'm hearing that more frequently from more friends and that's all right
Don't worry. You want a friend who encouraged you to drink and you're that friend. That's good
You kind of rolled in here
Ready to do it tonight. I needed to do it. Yeah
That's got the shirt wide open speaking of Weinstein rolls in. He's got chest hair out of this button down
Wearing an open robe
And nothing underneath
Yeah, I call I have to call the lift and the uber to a different address than my own because if I simply type in my address
They go to the street below mine. So already it's like yeah guys
We have the technology
So I enter the address I enter the address across the street
This and everyone can find it that way. It's worked a million times this girl tonight
She's nowhere to be found. I get a text. She's here. I walk outside. She's not there. This happens very very often. I'm like
Okay, what's going on she calls?
Hi
And I'm hearing the way's voice talking louder than her in my ear. Yeah her radio is full volume
And she opts to add a phone call into the mix without turning anything down
So I answer the phone and it's like hang on
Like just three people screaming in my ear. Yeah, yeah, so I said ma 'am
I can't hear a word that you're saying. What what do you need for me?
She goes where are you?
That's how she starts it. This is a woman who is supposed to be providing me a service. You're getting me. You're getting me wrong
Roundup. I said ma 'am I am at my address. I'm at my address that I enter. I don't know what to tell you
She goes well, can you look on on the app but with disgust in her voice?
Can you look on the app and see where I am and tell me where I need to go?
This is how she's starting the conversation
Not not and by the way
There's a million ways to start it where I'm not mad at you at all. I understand GPS can fuck up. What I've been there
She's disgusted with me. She goes well, then can you find me on on the map and tell me where to go?
I look at the thing I would have said no I would have said bye. Yeah, exactly. Sure. Sure sleep. I look at the thing. I'm like
All right, you're you're on my street, but you're you know two minutes away just
Turn around and come back down the street. She goes well, I'm looking at this thing and it says I'm at your house. I
Wasn't there right right right she goes sir, sir, and then finally I had to say can you please turn off either the ways or the radio
Man, I can't hear what you're saying she goes okay, well
What I need you to do and now she's practically yelling
Is tell me how to get to your house? I
Said okay
Drive down my street you're on it and she goes but sir there is a fork
In the road. Oh my god. So when I was coming down the street, I made a left are you saying I need to take a right and
This is the voice she's using. I said there is no fork in my road, so I don't know what to tell you hold on
Sorry, I didn't know my ringer. I'm sorry. That was an accident. That was an accident. Sorry. Sorry
The ball of this episode is a disaster. I said there's no fork in my road, so I don't know what to tell you but
Just drive your face in the wrong way drive down to me. So now I'm guiding her while on speaker phone watching her
Little toy car on the lift app
Make its way down to my house. She says I don't see you. I don't see you. I said right. You're still a minute away
Oh my god, she's driving she goes sir
I don't see and I said look I put my address in so you have it right right I'm telling you you're on my street
Look for my number right. She says okay and hangs up on me
Why did you not cancel this ride? I don't understand I'm waiting. I'm waiting. I'm hovering over a cancer because if I if I do that
Then I get here 20 minutes light. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. She does not come. I call her back
I said I don't know I don't understand how you're not here by now. She goes well
You told me there wasn't a fork and I'm here at the fork
So I said can you just put your car in park and I will walk to you
She goes okay
Okay, this is the the level of customer service. We're at so I walk down because it's because it's your fault pet that she
Yeah, she because she should make money for not knowing how to do anything right I know everybody's attitude now
I should just make money because it's like yes do a thing do want the one thing you're supposed to do do it okay
Fucking hey
This is coming on the heels of Heather and I went out the other night and the girl is
Practically screaming at us because of how narrow my street is
Yeah, I got into a lift the other night now. Here's why can't call a lift and I'll say this flat out
I know uber's got a lot of evil under its belt
As far as as far as ride share goes evil is the is the most devilish
He over is over is excuse me is the most devilish uber is the wall your first drink of the night
Yeah, why what did I just say you're saying words in the place of other words would I say
You said like evil instead of uber. Oh, well, they're similar words to me. Okay, evil
Yeah, no, that's what I'm dealing with it. Yeah, no, I was not okay. I wasn't you know not in that bad estate
Uber is the most devilish of all of all the apps Uber is the Walmart of
ride share services. Yeah, however lift
Is the Walmart of ride share services?
Lift is terrible. And do you get what I'm saying? I do. It's like you're you're not you're not going into a Walmart for customer service
No, it's like you're on your own. Yeah, I'm the shit wherever it is
Yeah, they're terrible and I don't want to support uber and I'm not saying I've had a great experience with them either
But this was nuts. I will say I
Know at the top of the uber chain. There's some really nasty shit. Yeah, it's mostly at the top
And I know some of the drivers have done some nasty shit
But I will say this I had an incident recently with uber and they really came through for me customer service
Why I had a driver who said it's flat out said to me. I'm crazy
Okay, and then went on and made up all these like bullshit stories about me being an unruly customer and uber called me
And I just went through the whole thing with them and they were just like
We believe you we know you're telling the truth like and they were very helpful
They gave me like bonus money and on the shit, right so I appreciated that you know, I don't think you're gonna like I work on
I work in the Warner Brothers lot you get a parking ticket on the on the Warner Brothers lot
It's a it's a joke under yeah, obviously, it's a joke. I would hope so so when uber will try like I'll get a ride
I got a ride canceled on me leaving the bowl the other night
The Hollywood Bowl after petty
That's exactly what I wanted to meet you guys at the roast. Did we talk about seeing petty two days before we did we must have okay
Sorry, but I wanted to meet you guys out of the bar and I left I was walking out while he's playing American girl
I beat the rush. Yeah, that's what we did, too. I'm out there. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. This girl calls me
Honestly, it was a similar vibe. She was like, I'm not seeing you and I said, well, where are you? She was among
Kahwanga. I said, I'm on Highland. I said, that's what I've entered here Highland and Odin. You have that information. There's no way
They don't know where you're at, right? So she's like, well, how far is that from Kahwanga?
It's nuts, dude. I got into a lift last night because
Uber
I don't remember why but I picked a lift for whatever reason. Yeah, you know
I my mood determines which one I'm gonna go with pink it stands out. I got oh I remember why I took a lift last night because I
Couldn't remember the address of where I was going. Okay, and I didn't feel like searching through the dark part here
Folks as it was his home
It was I didn't feel like doing the thing where you got a dig through a million emails to find the at and I was like
You know what? Lyft doesn't require the address. I know how to get there. I'll just tell the guy right
Says
My book the ride. Do you care to enter the address? I say no. It says fine, right guys shows up
This is the first thing the bug meets at three minutes. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. It's like five minutes
I look at the app it says we found you have even better driver. Yeah, it's like no, you didn't the driver canceled
Don't rub my balls. Just tell me what happened. Yeah, but whatever
So now the other driver comes and it's taken twice as long as it was supposed to but whatever I
Get into the car the guy goes where we go in I said I'm gonna direct you he goes he turns me goes
You didn't put the address in the thing no
I didn't and as a driver for this service you should be aware that that's an option of mine
Yeah, I don't have to do that. I will direct you right and he goes and I didn't say that part
I go I go so I'll just tell you where to go and he goes okay and
Immediately it's like it's it's like this this this now that this this
There's this energy like we're diffusing a bomb or something danger it
Like you can't even wrap his head around
That you were probably going to pizza right five minutes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, and I go five minutes away
I go go back out to Los Phyllis Boulevard and head towards Los Phyllis. Yeah
Didn't know how to do that had to tell him which direction Los Phyllis was in which is where he just came from
How are you a driver and don't know the basic streets? It's like so so he didn't know that Los Phyllis was to the right and Glendale
It was to the left right fine. I job. We're on Los Phyllis Boulevard. There's there's bumper to bumper traffic as always
I say listen. I'm on the phone by the way with my friend Jerry
Who's my buddy of mine since high school who's telling me about how his mom died three weeks ago
Okay, and we're trying to have like a heart to heart and we had already been talking for a while
And he's like dude if you got to go don't worry about it. You're in the car now, and I was like Jerry
We it's fine. We can still talk like I want to talk to you about this shit
And I say to the driver I said Jerry hold on one second
Sir
So we're gonna be on Los Phyllis for a bit listen. You're gonna make a left -on hillhurst, right?
That should be the end of that exchange. I go back to my phone guy turns around he goes
Well, where is that? Is that the next light and I go no, it's not the next light
It's coming up you like you and I start getting attitude because it's like dude fuck you
Yeah, it's not my job to make you a decent driver. No, if you can't
fucking
It's the base. It's basic shit. It's basic shit if you can't even be responsible enough to say I'm gonna keep my eye out
For the street we need to turn on to and it and how he said okay cool is that a ways down or whatever like yeah fine
I got you. I would have said it's half of mine. What was that the next light?
It's just I can't stand this shit. I can't fucking stand it man
Everybody went you know, and I do think it's appropriate. We're talking about this on the first ever bonus app
How long we do this podcast two years before we even put a patreon page up?
Yeah and said like hey if you want to donate it'd be nice. Thank you
We would like to try to make some cash off of this thing sure
Two fucking years before we even dared say like you know if you want to donate please do if you feel like it
Yeah, and like everything is flipped to the customer is an annoyance
Yeah, like I was just trying to drive, but now I got this loser in the back seat
No, no, no, that's not that's not the way this works
And my hats off to my hats off to booze cheese sticks one of my favorite spots
They are not a sponsor. I just love the place in silver Lake
Great I went there today for lunch. It's an awesome cheese steak and if you live in LA
And great customer service
I'm sure I tell the lady at the counter what I want she flips the little screen around she goes is that correct
Yeah, go that is correct
I order my food to go I go sit outside on one of the picnic tables to get some sun
Yeah guy comes out yells my name gives it right to me sure
So it's like yeah, and you know what a tip 15 % at the counter for that sure
You know, it's not a way it's not a waiter coming out. I tip. Yeah, it's time to get it to go
I'm still tipping and it's good customer service now asked for tips as well and I'll do it when when warranted
This lady tonight after all that then she starts driving forward and I'm watching her ways because she has a GPS and
It says turn left on Claremont and
She is making a right and I said ma 'am. It's a left and she was oh, thanks for letting me know you have a GPS
The lady the other night who can't find Highland arguably the biggest street in Los Angeles
So now I've beaten the rush. I missed Tom Petty's second to last performance of American girl to beat the rush and
She's nowhere to be found so then I get the we're sending somebody else to come get you
This girl calls me she's furious. She's like where are you and I said well
I'm down at the best Western because the other girl who was lost
I said I'll meet you halfway your uncle hang out. I'm on Highland. Let me meet you down here at the best Western
That's the halfway point she goes great
During the interim she cancels the ride on me right so now I'm at the best Western
Then they send somebody else to get me, but they send them to the old address
So this girl's like where are you and I said I'm at the best Western. Why are you there?
It says you're at this intersection. I said I know but I spoke to the previous driver
She was lost so I agreed to be here because previous driver. I'm the only driver. Oh my god
She didn't even know about the other thing she hangs up on me and I'm on on driver 3
I didn't go out as you well know because I was furious right now today I
Wake up
Recently, I judged a an aspiring TV writer forum sponsored by PlayStation. Right a
A bunch of kids, you know, well, you know
Freshman in college basically pitched some TV showrunners
Including myself their idea for a show and the best five out of 10 who were out of like 10 ,000
Got to produce a pilot that it's gonna air on PlayStation. It's great
So some of the kids had really great ideas. It was very fun and then as a nice little bonus treat shows about my house last night
PlayStation 4 VR headset. Yeah, all kinds of accessories and ship beautiful. So I wake up
I'm kind of hungover from last night. We had our dear friend Pete's bachelor party
Not hungover, but I was high. So it just felt dumb right Joe proposes a diner hang we go. It's great. I
Come home and Heather my girlfriend had just watched broad city this week
And on broad city they had mushrooms
Mm -hmm. This way the episode was about them being on mushroom right Heather's like what are mushrooms like? I've never done
I go well, I have like a chocolate bar of mushrooms in the fridge so she goes well, could we do it sometime? I of course, right
They're that we get them out. I'm making sure we have them whatever but in my stupidness this morning when I come back
I see a piece of chocolate and I throw it in my mouth. It's a very minor dose of mushrooms, but it's how I started my day
Jesus Christ, honestly, it felt like a few hits a weed. Okay, it was pretty minor, but I was like okay
And then I'm feeling good. I had a very stressful week as I always do and I'm like I'd love to just play this PlayStation and not have to set it up
I want to just play the thing. So I'm sitting there. I
Reading reviews and everything and I'm like fuck this I can hook up a PlayStation. I'm a grown man
Yeah, I go to hook it up
Not only do I not successfully set up the PlayStation one cable to an HDMI to your TV
Well, I also ruined my
Tilt my cable viewing my turntable viewing so now I can't listen to music
How I ruined everything how
Because the setup in my home is in a closet that is rooms away from the television and
I just didn't think it through I've been plugging things into the wrong thing. So I go fuck this. I'm calling a professional
I call a guy this guy comes in my house
He shows up
He goes, what do you want to do?
Armandian guy I go I'm just trying to set up a place that this guy's job is setting up home
Theater systems and I told him on the phone
I want to set up a PlayStation and I got too many cords. I got all these core like it looks like a god damn
You know like Christmas vacation in there. I go. I just want to clean down so that I can as ludicrous said once
Open his trunk so many wives it looks like a bowl of spaghetti. That's correct. Yeah
I said I just want to look in there and not be intimidated and know that if I want to plug A into B
It's not gonna fuck up my whole system
I go the guy that set it up did to he's trying to do too much. All right, so he's looking at it. He goes, okay, okay
Gets in there
He's looking at it you can I am starting to realize almost immediately he doesn't know what a PlayStation is
He's like a 55 -year -old guy. Oh boy. So he's looking at it. He's looking at it
Then he comes in my TV is mounted on the wall
You know, and it was a very professional job and not a cheap job either
That's what this is this is exactly where I'm against the wall mount is because you can't get to anything. Yeah, but
It was all set up that you can do it in this back closet, but this guy's I guess old school
But he's also a guy who all he does all that it's like when the when they any anyone like who's coming to repair a toilet or something
Comes to your house and they start asking you questions about it's like I don't know anything about toilets
You're a plumber like I just I hate it so much
So he comes in and they make you feel stupid
But he's looking at it and he goes well, how do I get to the wires on the back of the TV? How do I get to the wires?
Well, they're in this back room. I said
Sir with all due respect is exactly what I said to it. I said with all due respect if all you do is home theater setups
Have you never seen a TV that's mounted on a wall? Right and he stares at me. There's a bit of a language barrier
But he goes no, so you go so the plugins are behind the TV I
Said well, maybe and while I'm answering his question. I
Should also point out that below my TV. I on my on my little
cabinet is a
pricey high -end
Turn table because I I really get into my vinyl and my music you like your records
I like my records and it's a nice system speaking of which I got some gems today that I'd like to talk about I loved
I'd love to hear it, but you know of course is the glass
Top the glass top to the turntable and it's right under the TV and this guy and I am not exaggerating
Who is a let me just say it a third time a home theater installation expert
grabs with both hands the side of my flat screen TV on my wall and
Yanks
Seemingly as hard as he can the left side of the television
I'm not kidding rip out of the world
A piece of plastic from the back goes
Shatters and goes flying out the right side of the television
I jump off the couch because that's where I should be on the couch letting the professional fix it right because I called him to do so
I jump up and in the nick of time grab the TV a
55 -inch television as it falls off the wall and
Into my hands because if I hadn't jumped up it would have landed on my expensive turntable
That was below it and both would have broken both would have broken. Yeah, and I said I you know, I to be honest. I lost it
I caught myself pretty quickly, but I was like what are you doing?
What are you doing?
He's like, well, sorry, he's like it should be hooked up better. It should be hooked up better. I
Said you get it. It's it's wall mounted. I haven't had a problem in three years, then you yanked it off the wall
So he goes you you have it do you have I said no, I don't have it. You need to help me
So I start trying to move my turntable and I'm unplugging something that is very carefully wired and hooked up
Trying to protect it. So then I get it down
We get the TV
Rehooked up on the wall. So it looks okay on the wall again looks okay on the wall
He's like sorry. Sorry. He goes out to his truck puts on one of those like a coal miner helmets with the light
How was he need that for looks behind it and he goes oh here it is
Moves the TV a quarter of an inch and finds the hook in that he needed
Plugged it. There was no tech. He was gonna just yank the fucking thing off. I don't know what he thought he was doing
Jesus Christ and honestly
Once I started talking to him at the end of the night
I'm sorry at the end of the the the transaction. I saw I was smelling alcohol and I had had nothing to drink
Well, you were on mushrooms. I had had nothing to drink. I know, but I'm saying you were on mushrooms
You sure you were smelling alcohol the lowest of doses. I mean
I wasn't like spiraling or something right now right there, but talk about an experience you don't want to have when you're on any dose of mushrooms
The guy finds it plugs it in he sets up the PlayStation
We just kind of basically I wind up setting it up in the end because he doesn't understand what come it's this cross here. I'll tell you
We get the PlayStation set up
Then he goes, okay, you're good to go. He's gonna ready to leave my home. There's shards of
The TV connecting device on the floor of my living room. There are cords
dangling out the back of my television and
The PlayStation is sitting on my coffee table
Well, so I'm worried about you. You you're real you're real. This is high tension right now
I'm serious you're having a stressful week, and then this is this is your Saturday by the way
This place has five stars on Yelp those are probably fake reviews
So I said sir you you can't leave here. He goes what's the problem? I go
So for starters, I go do I need any of this shit that's sitting on the floor that fell out of the back of my television?
He goes, no, you can throw it away
Okay, I'll do that, but obviously I don't want my PlayStation on my coffee table. I want it set up
In my closet that I have for my blu -ray player and etc. Well, you can't do that
He did it and it works. Oh, we did. Okay, so you have it so the PlayStation is accessible, but in the closet
We set it up, you know, it's close enough that the sensors pick up and everything so he takes it back and he's like all right
We good and he starts to leave and I go but sir the other reason I caught there were two reasons is that none of my stuff works
And he goes I fixed it so it all works. I go can you please let me check and make sure yeah
I check my direct TV. No nothing no signal. I
Put on a record no sound
So I said you see so you got a he's looking he's looking he's there for like 20 minutes finally I
Go you know this antenna box back here is for this remote and
The remote doesn't work because something's wrong with the box. Can you check the box? He goes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, he goes out
He yanks. I have this this nice cabinet. I was yanking the cabinet is full of you know a bunch of books and stuff
but you know you can move the cabinet with two people and
I tell him he's he's ganking on the cabinet and he can't move it and I hear a
That I'm not gonna say how much this fucking cabinet was but I had a decorator do my house
I wanted to at least I have no taste in any other aspect of my life. I want to have a nice -looking house
This guy is yanking on this cabinet underneath the thing and I go sir, please stop doing that and I hear
I hear a snap of wood
On this like
Crafted cabinet that I got I got an antique shop. I go sir
Why are you yanking on that? He goes I need to get to this thing back here
I said sir you need to ask me if you're gonna do that what you're trying to get to because there's a box back here
I'm trying to get to I go sir that is not a box that is the
Part of it's part of my turntable and it's the the the subwoofer thing just before or after the diner
It's like 4 p .m. It's 4 p .m. Yeah, I go that's for my subwoofer. He goes that you sure that's not the remote
Yeah, I'm sure what what you need to look at is what I've told you three times to look at right he goes back there
He's like I can't figure it out. That's how we're about to end the transactions with him saying I can't figure out as a home audio engineer
I can't figure out how how you can watch TV how you can listen to music and
He's getting ready to leave my home saying I can't figure it out right
I get up there. I'm on a ladder. I
I'm tweaking things around and I go here we go
I turn the thing I push it up against the wall and then suddenly the sensors working and everything's fine
And I go all right, man. I think we got it working. Thanks. He was okay. Good. Good. Good. Can I get some water?
Did sure I give him a glass of water
He drinks it and I am not thankfully it was water, but I'm not kidding you Joe
I give him a
Solo cup of water he drinks it and and you know takes a big swig of it
He hands it to me and he goes good. I get another glass
Fine, okay, pour him a glass of water. I hand it to him. He takes a tiny sip off this glass
Sets it on the edge of my coffee table
In a way, I will describe as criminally insane where he's got a fourth of the cup on the table right right
And three fours off right and of course the cup falls maybe this guy was drunk splashes to the ground
And then I put together that the man is drunk at 4 p .m. And I said driving around driving around doing cup
So I said, you know what man? There's no real apology to that. I'm like it's water. Don't worry about it. It's fine. I go
What do I owe you?
It was I don't know you want the invoice I
Said I'm just asking me this number baby. I want to hear it. I want to hear this number
100 bucks
With a question mark
I said is that like a usual rate is that the rate for what happened because that's sort of a skulls, you know about a hundred bucks
Okay about a hundred I write the man a check. I get him out of my house. I just couldn't
I sat down. I played a little bit of a game. I was rattled by the encounter. I was rattled by the encounter
Well, yeah, yeah, that's a and this is your you got a pet and I as you mentioned earlier we hit the
Diner first thing this morning about 9 a .m. He orders a plate of what looked to be
Nothing more than nachos to me with with with a substitution of eggs for a little lettuce. Joe stick
What nachos do you know have lettuce?
What nachos usually have like lettuce tomato and onion on them and she melted cheese
This was melted cheese beans a meat and then eggs all over chile
It's a it's a Mexican breakfast. It's on it's on every menu and call what you want
It's god damn nachos in the morning. That was a special. It was 9 .95. I said I'll try it
I got people at a joining table saying are those those chile keelas they look good can I try some
Now I had half of it at most
Chose over there eating pancakes and shit as well. Why is that I'm I'm not saying it's an unreasonable breakfast
Why is it a more reasonable breakfast? I'm just breaking your balls
But I'm saying you go home with a belly full of breakfast nachos. Yes. Yeah
Just a piece of candy laying out in the open, which is it without choice in my opinion even in your own house
Certainly couldn't question that to see candy just laying around on that. Certainly couldn't question that that was a strange move
What what daddy that now you're on mushrooms now you got a guy coming in with this on mushrooms is a heavy exaggeration
I want to stress that I want to stress I'm saying this to support you
We're not in a state that you could you you'd like to be in to deal with something like this
I'm just saying like and and and the last one on this is 30 seconds when I walk up to your gate tonight
There are three ladies sitting out there ladies
And I buzz and you buzz me in and these ladies are sitting out there silently and I open the gate
And I turn to them and I say are you guys trying to get in
It's three very innocent look ladies. I it looked as though they were waiting for somebody to open the gate right
I could not have been nicer with this are you guys trying to get in
Two of them say nothing the third looks at me with like a a heavy sigh and an eye roll and she goes no
I gotta get out of this town. What are we doing? I gotta get a sigh it's this town
It's this town. I got a I had two encounters with drivers
The one I'll talk about pull up to a red light today
On my way back from Amoeba where I picked up
And I'm not going to go into a great detail
Across by the way, this this show is going to be
In a few minutes here we'll get to the topic, which is Pat and my favorite number one horror movie. Yes
I go to me, but today first two jets to Brazil albums have been re -released on vinyl finally never heard of the band
Just the Brazil was Blake from Jawbreaker. It was his band following Jawbreaker
So they only had three albums. I really like the first two quite a bit. So I grabbed those that was a nice surprise
I grabbed Elvis's first album on vinyl found original fantastic pressing great got
Uh
Buck Owens record
What brought you to Buck Owens. I heard him on I've been listening to Willie Nelson's Roadhouse a lot on
On serious and Buck Owens has a great song with my favorite country artist Dwight Yoke. Yeah, great figures film
Oh, that's on the one I got
Well probably the original version and Dwight has a an album of like 25 Buck Owens covers that is a masterpiece
uh, and I got
um
An album by the sloths who were a garage rock band in the 60s that put out a couple singles then broke up after two years never released an album get together
Like two years ago get back together like two years ago after 1964 to 2015 or whatever it was
60 and record the album they never recorded and it's so where do you hear about the sloths?
I saw it in the oldies section and I was like this looks new
Why is it in the oldies section and I previewed it on iTunes and then listen and then read the story and I was like
This not only sounds awesome
But that's a great story. Yeah, so I bought that record
And I also got I think that's it actually so anyway. I'm on my way back from Amoeba
Guy in front of me would light turns red where I see it and there's a guy in front of me almost blows through the red light
He almost blows through it fine. Not in my business. No. He's not in the crosswalk
His car is two -thirds out of the crosswalk on the other side
Because that's how far into the fucking crosswalk he got before he hit the brakes and stop
Out of the kindness of my heart I back up significantly to give him room to to reverse go on he does
light turns green
He then sits there for a
solid 10 seconds
12 seconds as the light is green I
I don't lay on the horn, but I give him a bump like come on buddy. Let's go
He turns around like
what
Then sticks his hand out the window and does like this waving like what's your problem and I
Driving full speed behind him reach around my windshield and plaster my middle finger to the windshield and start screaming fuck you at him
It's like dude
Not only did you almost run a red light not only did I accommodate you and you're dumb fucking mistake
Now you can't even admit to the fact that you you're seeing there's a fucking green light and it's time to go and now your dead stopped at a green light
Everybody in this city. It's it's it's accommodate them 100 % not part way
Not meet me some of the way on this not can you give me a break here it is this is what I am doing
And if you don't accommodate me 100 % you're shaming me or you're you're being derogatory
Or you're being rude it is these people are people are not born here
So does it does you become that through living here you what happens because everybody that comes to the city thinks that they deserve to be a movie star
Yeah, that's the problem everybody comes here, you know from wherever going
I'm gonna be and some people come here because they just want to do good work
And they they know that there's industry here and we know a lot of people like that
So obviously I'm speaking in generalities sure, but most people come here because they're like well, I want to be Tom cruise
Right and and they're completely entitled and then they get here and they start drinking the cool late
I can't take it anymore. Dude. I was like I got to get out of this fucking city. I have to get out of this city
I can't do it anymore
It's I'm filled with rage whenever I go into public filled with it right filled with it guy the other day turns in front of me makes not just a right hand turn
But a right hand turn as slow as humanly possible with no turn signal
So I almost rear end him because he and I fucking honk at him and he's like what what the fuck man?
It's like this is your fault you asshole
You know
Everyone makes mistakes driving
If somebody honks at me
You get it
You know like yeah, yeah, you're right there unless they're honking for no reason my what I get a lot in L .A.
Is I'm waiting for a family of four to cross and a crosswalk. I want to make a right turn
Right and the person behind me starts laying on the horn
To to what plow down a family
It's disgusting. It's disgusting. The city's filled with disgusting
No etiquette. There's no manners. This business is disgusting. Everything's a pig fuck terrible
And onto our topic for today
You know, we're about 42 minutes in and in typical
The typical we'll see you in how fashion we have not even
Graced the topic at all yet. Well just so you know folks. We're recording two tonight
We're also doing the blade runner, which is our standard episode
And you know, I came in with a head of steam about this uber thing, etc
I said you know what I'm giving it to the patreon people
We're launching this thing
We want you guys to feel like your money's going to good place and we need we set it a little bit up top
We really do appreciate like how quickly this this money added up for this patreon. It's a beautiful thing
The Facebook page is off the charts. Joe's still not on Facebook
but uh
I'm on there every day. I look as always
Please keep the transcriptions coming
They're very funny. I always screened rather than send them to Joe
It's a very positive community. Also, I'd like to address
We were informed the other day that someone on the Facebook page
Uh was was fake trolling us for being racist
But it was a quote joke
Right and they've been shut down
So whatever that was the gentleman has said it was a joke. I don't know what's funny about that joke
Or who he was, but it seems kind of stupid to me
Um, Joe and I love people of all racist colors and creeds
Uh, I'm gonna though. I'm gonna say I discriminate against certain creeds
But races and colors. I'm fine with. Yeah. What's what is creed? I never knew what creed was. Is that religion?
Apollo
Scott stabs band. Yes, the only ones I run. I think creed is and clear water revival
But you know, there's enough creed in there. Creed might mean religion. I think it does. I think it does too. I was just joking anyway
Listen, uh, we're here to talk about our two favorite movies
Is that what we're getting to? I mean look Pat. I think this title or the the title of the episode might be retitled pets
Therapy session. Please help this man. You're having a hard time
So let's talk about something like this was my relaxing day off and I felt like I was gonna pop a fucking blood vessel
We're gonna talk about our favorite horror movies meaning each of our number ones
Of all time of all time
We've said before these episodes will be lists. There'll be things like this
So I and Joe and I do not know each other's choice
So your surprise will be our surprise. I believe I've mentioned mine on the podcast before because I think no
We never covered this movie
So I'll tell you now we haven't covered mine either
The exorcist is my number one hard to argue. I think it's
I yeah, I think it's it's an inarguable choice. It's it's it's a film
Now you mean dominion
Now you mean Leslie Nielsen's repossessed. Where's my order? Yeah repossessed number one
Exorcist is on it. Exorcist to the heretic number two. Yes
Susu exorcist the beginning number three. Sure dominion number four. Yes
Go on. I don't count exorcist three and then exorcist one comes in line. Yeah, absolutely right. I think that's the right order
No extra the exorcist the original and even the director's cut that added some people were mad about the shit they added in the
You know, I guess it was the late 90s early. I love the spider walk
I love the quick I love the quick shots of the demons and everything. Yeah, I think it adds to it. I did too when I saw that new version of the theater I
I really fucking loved it. I don't know why it gets that wrap. I was scared shitless when I resold in the theater
And they'd seen it many times already and it still terrified me
I remember I went with my dear friends scotten Dan and Jamie from back home. You've met all of them
And we came home. They were all living together at the time. We came home
And we were downstairs in the living room talking about the movie and we were really freaked out and like man
That was really scary and then I remember this scot goes where is Dan by the way? Where did he go?
And we're like, I don't know. Where is he? And Dan came
spider walking to the best of his ability. Sure down the stairs. Sure at us
Almost broke his neck. Yeah, because he couldn't do it. Was it a reverse crab walk down? He tried to do it
But really was just sliding backwards down the stairs and almost killed himself
And we laughed like
We were doubled. It was one of the funniest things I've ever seen. Yeah, yeah
But I took a core. I always liked the film The Exorcist from the very first time I saw it as a kid
It was one of two movies my mother refused me to allow me to see
When I was very young
Meaning 12 -ish, you know
It Scarface was the other one
Okay, interesting. She said those movies are too graphic. You can't see them, right
So when I finally did see the Exorcist
What is the graphic scene in Scarface is the like the the chainsaw bed? I think it was the chainsaw and I think it was just the utter
The utter lack of respect for the word fuck in the film. I mean, it's just left and right. Yeah
so
In the drugs and all that I guess, you know, but anyway
I finally saw The Exorcist when I was probably 14 or years old. There's a
scared the living shit out of me
Couldn't watch the movie by myself until I was in my 30s. Yeah
uh, and I took a course. I took like a music and film
Like summer camp thing when I was in high school and
And
There was one of the classes in the film side of it that we took was a dissection of the movie The Exorcist and
all the class was it was a one -time
Thing and the guy showed us the Exorcist
and then broke down why the movie is so effective and
Yes, and it was a fascinating course and so aside from the movie being
Extremely well written. I've also read the book. It's one of the best adaptations of a book you will ever read
or ever see excuse me
The it's superbly acted it's superbly directed every part of this movie is is is just perfect for me second only to eat prey love in terms of adaptations
So um
Um, but then on top of it, there's all this technical stuff that you don't really I guess
Maybe initially realized well freaking. I mean freaking was a uh can
Easy contemporary of your Scorsese de Palma's et cetera, and they just kind of lost his way
But he'll bubble up once a while with a great one. He does um
Yeah, he never quite got the notoriety of those guys, but he's still doing this thing and he's still great in fact
I just found out I think October 26. They think it is he's signing
At Amoeba record. Okay. He's signing the double vinyl soundtrack release of the exercise that just came out or is it about the tubular bells over and over
Uh probably it's a spooky soundtrack. It's not something I'd ever put on in the house
Right. I don't see how you could ever feel good to it. It's weird that he would be signing the soundtrack
He had nothing to do with the soundtrack
Well, he's the one guy probably from the movie that's yeah, I mean
Anyomorakonis not gonna come in from Italy to sign it right and William Peter Blattie. I believe is dead
So um the extra says what is weird about you saying that it was one that you could not watch is that was the only r -rated movie my father would let me watch
What and it's I don't know who will get an r -rating release today with the crucifixion masturbation and all that show
I don't know how it will be yeah, it's um and my dad was like I was probably 10
Jesus Christ and you know, I would beg and beg to see PG -13 movies
But he was like cool of the excess and I watched it
And then I was like why could I watch that and I also it made me think that that's what all r -rated movies were that level of intensity
So he said well, you know, I wanted you to learn about Catholicism
Which oh my lord really shows you how uh how fun the that religion is
and then
He took me down to downtown St. Louis the night after we watched it we had dinner
And he said you see this staircase here, and I said yeah, and he said
According to legend and many news reports that is the very staircase
Where the priest was thrown down the flight of stairs because the extra story
Happened in St. Louis Wow, it's what he told a 10 -year -old boy
So I'm already
fully traumatized by it and then he let me know that it happened here in my hometown
That's upsetting. Yeah, that's upsetting
Yeah, when I when I first saw it the the whole movie
Disturbed me and I loved it
It has a level of evil that every horror movie has tried to get and can't get it. They can't even come close. There's something
And these exorcism movies that come out now that are completely about the movie. Yeah, these movies come out
They're PG -13 exorcism movies. Yeah, it's like get out of my face and even the R -rated ones don't go that far
There's only one scene in the book
Dealing like in the graphic
There's only one graphic scene in the book that they did not put into the movie. Yeah
um
But the fact that they kept that cross scene is pretty unbelievable and you know what this was 1972
Yeah, when you could
Which makes no sense because it's that classic argument of you could do more than then you could do now
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense. Well midnight cowboy in 1969. Yeah, it was rated X right you watch midnight cowboy now
It's the teamest of ours. There's like some tits
Yeah, you know, he's a male prostitute. There's literally no gay sex nothing nothing happens. There's no profanity hardly
Uh, three years later the exus gets an R rating and they have a 12 year old girl masturbating with a crucifix. Yeah saying f me Jesus
She says may Jesus fuck you
Yeah, and her vagina is bleeding because she's stabbing the cross into it so hard and Linda Blair is the massive box office hit
They asked Linda bear what Blair much later in life like how did you shoot that scene?
And she was like I didn't really know what we were doing. She goes
They just put a like a box between my legs that have like a sponge in it that put out red stuff
Oh my god, and they were like just just stab that box with this cross
And she was like, okay, so she did it and then she's also not in some of those scenes
It's like another actor portraying the but she's in a lot of it and yeah
You know, it's it's pretty it's pretty heavy stuff. It's like in Gerald's game. Yeah
The scene where spoiler alert the scene where uh, uh, the ET kid Henry Thomas plays the dad
He's masturbating to his daughter who's sitting on his lap. Yeah
And I wondered like
Does that kid know what this scene is how it is or I've always thought do they like super impose her in somehow
Yeah, where she's sitting there and they're just like okay
So now he's just gonna like rock the bench and say just keep watching and you don't need to know
You know, it's very strange but like to I guess but um but anyway um
The you know, they talked about when they that Dakota fanning movie came out where there's like oh
She gets raped and they said they were like look she's not
We didn't shoot the scene as a rape scene. We shot close -ups of her
Crying and then we we cut in the other shit, right? So um
You know, I don't really know how they did all the stuff in the exercise
I kind of don't want to know to be honest. I don't want to ruin uh, it feels like watching a documentary
Yeah, exactly. It's crazy. I mean just crazily well -acted by everybody
So some of the things and then we can move on to your movie some of the things that I learned in this class
Yeah, he said he said look in 1972 73 whatever was this teacher said
Huge fear of Islam
Okay, and it was like sort of the initial
The initial Islamophobia was was that was the first time was happening that to me much like close encounters
The boring desert opening of both those movies. I'm like, I don't need this so
This movie start you go first thing you hear in the film
Islamic chance right he goes so that's already it's 72 people are already set off
Yeah, you know
He's like you he played us a bunch of scenes and he goes do you hear that noise in these scenes? That's the sound of bees
Yeah, because they recorded the audio of beehives and they were like it's just the thing where
It was tested that this sound makes people very uncomfortable. So it appears here here here here here here in the movie
Uh, he's like if you notice like they they show this shot of these wild dogs fighting
Uh, maybe they're coyotes. I don't know and he goes later in the movie you you hear the sound of of the dogs come back
But there's no attention called to it and we're not looking for it. You're not going to notice it
He was like pausing it like if you see here the demons face is found in the flame
Of the candle that that blows up when she's in the attic for like a frame right
It was shit like that
He said uh this part here. He's like that's the sound of people fornicating
And you again you don't know what it is because it's the sound that you're hearing does not match the vision right visual excuse me
It's just a superbly made film. It's to this day
In a good way the most disturbing movie I've ever seen yeah
Uh, the most disturbing movie I've ever seen in a bad way
Still is antichrist
Sure, and I still kind of want to own antichrist for that reason. I do own antichrist. I like to but uh, but antichrist is
You know that hits points where I'm like do I need to see this right now? Yeah, I don't know that there's as much purpose
To the upsetting nature of that film in my opinion as there is to the exercise
Yeah, to me the exercise is spot on you're gonna make a movie about the devil
This is how low the devil sinks to quote Richard prior devils a low motherfucker jack
Uh, you know, so it's like
It just hits it. It hits it in a way that no movie ever ever has including the hellraiser franchise and I love the hellraiser movies
No, nothing's come close. So anyway, that's my pick patty. What do you got?
Uh, my pick is a is a much lighter
film um, but
It's not even close for me my favorite horror movie is poltergeist. Okay
Um, and part of that may be it's one of the very few horror movies that was rated PG
And I could only watch PG movies until I was 13
so when I saw
Poltergeist to me that was as every bit as scary as the exercise and it remains a pretty terrifying movie
um
One quick side note this week on my show
I was able to cast Miss Joe Beth Williams the mother and poltergeist to play the mother of a character on my show
Which I am very excited about I always really loved her and she looks
Exactly like my mom did when I was a kid which I think also adds to my enjoyment of it
Craig T Nelson
Is like a I don't even really like Craig T Nelson, but he is just a classic 80s dad
And poltergeist to me blows ET and all that shit out of the water. I've just always liked it more
It's a cooler story. It's better
And I never really understood how ET became this all -time classic and poltergeist is kind of you know
Cool almost a cult thing, you know, it made $60 million where ET made a thousand, you know, I love a I love Craig T Nelson
By the way, I just want to go on record saying that he's a guy that I hope to meet one day cuz you'd you may you need a horror public
I didn't know that big gun dude, but you know if you met him
You'd feel like you were just with your dad. Yes. He's got a hair. It's Harrison Ford's like that. Yeah
Dabney Coleman who we've discussed, you know, smells like coffee. Yeah, there are just those guys
You go if I met him I'd art. I just would start calling him dad immediately, but poltergeist, you know
When Joe Beth Williams and Craig T Nelson are in their bedroom and the kids are asleep and they're gonna smoke a joint
Yeah, this is a PG movie as well like I for for me this movie was a big
I would say even more than like seeing tits for the first time there was a lot of stuff in it where I was just kind of like
Do my parents smoke pop like I didn't even know what that was when I was a kid. I don't know that I did either. I think it was cigarette. I didn't know weird and forbidden to me
I bought the DVD of poltergeist poltergeist yeah
probably at this point 10 years ago, but
But when I got that DVD I hadn't seen it in years and I remember when that scene came on I was like
Oh, yeah, smoking weed right I was such you was just rolling a cigarette when I was a kid
You know, I never realized that and then they'd never even let you do this now
Like and they you know, they didn't in the remake of poltergeist, which is an abomination, but
Oh, what Craig T Nelson like devils work that film. I love Sam Rockwell. I fell into a bit of a depression
I fell into at least a week of depression after I saw but
Craig T Nelson then in a parapagyamapant stands in front of the mirror and
does tricks with his belly fat because he's got this big beer gut
Right like in the mirror like there's just these little touches to it where you're like
They wouldn't let the male lead of a movie do that now. They you know, he'd be standing in front of the mirror
Like actually a great example is like that amity of ill thing where it's Ryan Reynolds with a 24 pack. That's your dad now, right?
That's your dad. There's just something so much more
I don't know those two are like a real family. Those two are real family. Those two reminded me so much of my parents
The kid is so ugly the boy was so fucking ugly. I was just gonna say the kids don't look like
six -year -old models yes in waiting like they're they look like normal kids the boy is hideous
He's got those fucked up teeth, which is why even though two is
Obviously a lesser movie
They did a perfect scarcity by having his braces attack him because obviously the kid needed braces
Did you know this by the way there was supposed to be
There was an idea never got out of development, but there was a script floating around to do a pastor
Creed or whatever the fuck his name is from the two they were gonna scream right past. Yeah, they were gonna do a pastor movie
Wait, is he the same guy from Phantasm? This is always trouble. No, Angus Scrim is the tall man in Phantasm
But this other guy and the other two different actors the second one the movie the guy that plays him in the second one died
Then they'd get a different actor the third one. They're both equally creepy. Yeah
But they were gonna do a prequel to poltergeist about just that preacher
Would love and how it all started right that would have been very cool anyway, sorry go ahead
No, I just I mean for me even though it terrified me. I remember I threw up when I was a kid because I watched that scene where the guy's face falls off
That's scared the living shit out of me as a child. It's scared. I believe in like shit out of me really pure like film school effects
Which I love about it, but right after that and this will sound like a joke, but my mom called me in for lunch and it was spaghettios
And they looked exactly like that guy's melting face and I threw up
Because I was I was such a pussy when I was a kid that poltergeist played like the exorcist for you as opposed to this big brooding
Yes, broad chested man that sits before me. Yes. Yeah, all right, but I really
uh
To this day I watch it at least once a year
Both of these movies the extras and poltergeist you have to see in a theater because the the sound design and both these movies
is unbelievable and
At the very least watch it in your home with a good sound system and the lights off because they do those strobing effects in poltergeist
Yeah, that really make you feel like your house is I it's a it's the best movie for me in my opinion to watch like in the dark around Halloween
And there's never been anybody better like when you when it comes to the horror movie trope of
We're gonna have an older person come in who's the expert yeah on all this stuff
There's nobody better than Zelda Rubenstein who cut or styled however you pronounce it
She you're her coming in and then in the second movie when
The shit starts up again and Craig T Nelson is like tell the magical midget. We said hello week. We're we're out
I remember my mom thought that that was like the funniest yeah call back to the first one like you know
Do you like to uh law you seem to like it more than most I like it. I like it. I don't like it as much as one they they get success
Successively worse yeah
Three is not a good film, but I mean I enjoy it Tom scared anytime you're gonna talk about he's another guy soon as I met him
I just start calling him dad
Hug him
For me the the perfect level of horror comedy outside of like outside of misery, which is always discuss in this podcast
Is them checking into the hotel and pushing that TV out on the balcony that is such a beautiful perfect ending to this movie great
And they're all exhausted and whatever but and the guy by the way yeah the guy where it's like uh
Yeah, yeah, you move the headstones, but you didn't move the bodies. You son of a bitch the bad guy the old guy
Yeah, or the older guy
So there was a local supermarket chain on the east coast where I lived called pathmark
Sure, I'm there and he was the spokesperson for really so like yeah
You'd have these like small budget like local commercials and that guy would come under TV
Like come down to path mark apples are 39 cents a bundle
He seems to still act. I don't know if he's still alive
But I feel like I see him all the time he pops up in shit
Hope pop up on like you'll see him on like the golden girls like blanch of you like so rose you really like this new man
You've been seeing right and it'll be that guy
My other favorite thing about poltergeist in terms of structure
as a as a writer myself
is that
It has a structure that goes again. I would say goes against the rules of screenwriting
As much as anything from like the you know the french new wave and all that shit that everybody raves about sure breaking the mold
And it's a huge right down the middle stevens billburg
A picture. I told me hope her let's not leave tobs out of the to be hope her but as we know I know I know but tell me still
I think we discussed on this when to be died and I'm calling him to be now
I admit my mistake and here's the beauty of him being the stand -in for Spielberg. Yeah
It let it be a movie where you saw a woman smoking a joint
You weren't gonna see that you weren't gonna see that in ET. That's right
It got it got Spielberg more edgy which he needs to be
And it got to be less fucked up which you know that is why that's my favorite movie
I saw it at an age where I that's what I could handle
but
Basically poltergeist ends and climaxes and it's done
And you're like holy shit that was crazy and scary and really exciting and they're packing shit up
And it's daylight and the movie is over
And then she goes upstairs and takes the bath and you're like why am I watching Joe Beth Williams take a bath right what's going on here
And still I forget now and I've seen it 55 times
She gets in the bath and I'm like oh right we got another 20 minutes of even better
They they claw they climb actually movie yeah, they get the kid out of the the further whatever it's called in poltergeist
And then it gets better and scarier and more fun and also let's not leave out when they finally get carol and out of the
Other dimension or whatever yeah that disgusting shit. They're like wiping off of her face
It looks like she's just covered in alpo
Well, they use that shit in Ghostbusters, too. I think it's just like pink
goo ectoplasm or what I don't remember what happens in Ghostbusters, too
They do a bathtub of pink it's well that but when carol and comes out at the end and she's going oh baby
She's like wiping that like chunky soup off of her face. It's fucking disgusting
Yeah, there's something very viscerally gross about that film which I really enjoy
Um the biggest laughs
Because Spielberg is the best attention laughs
Where it's just somebody saying something straight and it gets a huge laugh because you're so tense
That's the best kind of laugh really in these kind of mood
In these kind of times Pat quite frankly
But it's when Rubensign goes you're right
You go
You remember that no, I don't remember the line. I wish I remember the setup better, but it's like
He's like don't she she goes I've got to go
She's got to hear my voice and he goes don't you think she should hear my voice. I'm her dad
She goes you're right you go. It's like it's it's always every time I watch like this massive laugh
It's at her being like you know idiot. I have to go
Yeah, well no she's scared basically. It's the one moment where the midget's like yeah, I'm terror and it's supposed to be funny
It is it's a big laugh in the movie
She's not a mid oh wait, I know we're not a little person. I'm sorry. No, but I'm saying she's not even a little person, right?
She's just short okay. I think great. I think so. I don't know little okay. Sorry
Well in any case if you've never seen it and I run into a lot of people who have never seen this movie idiotic
It has become kind of a weird cult thing and it's
To me if we're counting it as as a Spielberg movie
It's probably my favorite Spielberg movie
It's not going to top Raiders for me. It does top Raiders for me Raiders is a blast for me, but I'm sorry Raiders is a top 10 or for me
a temple of doom tops Raiders for me
I I would take that over Poltergeist will never top in Indiana Jones flick
But I will I would I would accept the argument of temple of doom being your favorite. Yeah, I don't understand when people should on temple of doom
I fucking love temple
Um, but I also liked crystal skull and gave it a lot of forgiveness. So I almost
Today rewatch crystal school. I've only seen it once in the theater
But it's time for me to do a expectations lowered revisit of crystal skull
Look up until shyla buff starts swinging on those vines
Which if you can block that out of your head and just go oh god. Yeah
It's fine. It's fine. I remember there being a lot of prairie dog reaction shots in the crystal school mere cats
Okay mere cats. It's fine, but it's still fun when he like, you know, it's still got its moments
It's not a great flick, but it's not sure. It's not a disgrace
You're just like
I have a bit about it in my eye can people say like this the worst movie I've ever seen
I'm like, same in the worst movie Harrison four's ever been it. No, that's a long shot. That's all enough
So anyway
Folks, that's our show. There's your bonus episode and now we're 10 you happy your mother fuckers
We'll do this so much folks for your for your patreon contributions
A special shout out to what what's the gentleman's name?
Well, we're gonna do the shout outs on a regular episode because the shout outs are
People that donated five or more get a shout out. Yes people that donated 10 or more get this okay
So we need to do the shout outs on a normal episode because
Everybody that donated you know has to has to hear it. Yeah, yeah, so uh thank you for your donations
We appreciate it and the blade runner episode will contain the shout outs
Uh, and that's it
That's it folks. Do we need to do plugs in a patreon? Let's do it. No, let's you know what let's leave it's not about us
It's about you the fan exactly all right
Thank you very much folks. We really we really appreciate it and that's why we're doing this and anyone who's giving money up at a
time when money is tight it's
very much appreciated and honestly
You know it helps to have a little motivation to do this like we every week we were we're kind of like why are we doing this
And to have a little extra spending cash is a great reason well and we don't do it begrudgingly
We're not saying this sucks. We're just like it's sometimes it's tough when
It's just the thing you're doing as a labor of love and it does help to have a little income coming in from it to make it a little more of a job
So thank you as much appreciate take it easy