Hey folks it's your bonus
great start weird pause there sorry it's your bonus app it's your bonus app it's
the app that you get for giving money over you sexy motherfuckers we're
recording on Thanksgiving day and we are thankful for all of you boy we sure are
and Joe when you told me you'd worked for weeks writing that new intro song I
was supportive but now after hearing it I feel like you might have wasted your
time happy Thanksgiving everybody you're gonna be getting this when December
December 1 right it'll be out the end of the month you know what if we have
time today we'll post it today I mean if we don't we'll post it well thanks
given to me I tell you what if I was around my family I'd need something to
listen to for an hour who boy yeah besides you're people are rough folks
dad rough uncles rough mom drunk I'm not home I was the first holiday season
and yeah well I always I always stay here but Thanksgiving but I'm not gonna
hope for Christmas either I yeah I've never felt so dead within my heart and
so just it is it's pushing a hundred degrees in Los Angeles the sun is
blinding it's just fucking miserable how are you supposed to have holiday spirit
folks I wake up this morning I turn on the macy's day parade I wound up like
throwing the remote across the room and walk down to the gym get there all dressed
up try to do the right thing of course the gyms closed on Thanksgiving walked
around the neighborhood said hello to three different people who did not
respond on Thanksgiving turned on the macy's day parade today people turns out
it's being sued for people thinking Woody Woodpecker was sexually
inappropriate folks folks that's my dentist Miller style joke on Thanksgiving yeah
the parade was going fine until snoopy felt up rainbow bright next next to a
fucking hot dog vendor meanwhile yasser arafat still in the hoochie goochie over
oh yeah now that's uh Dennis Miller is dead or what he's doing he's doing right
when comedy he he's gone quite political uh he he doesn't lean pretty right I
would say uh at this point I mean tours with Bill O 'Reilly were used to until
Bill O 'Reilly right did something terrible I I don't know did he fill up
women or did he just harass them in the office you've heard that voicemail where he
talks about loofing his dick no I shower I have it and then he just gets on tv
and is like morally outraged by America it kills me this way I logged into twitter five times
this week uh like once a day and each time it would be like republican senator caught
butt fucking a male intern on his desk while signing into law it's it's a bill that that takes away
all rights of homosexual I mean it's it's just comical at this point it's stoop they they are
and I don't even I don't even talk about politics but you hand me a microphone and I got to do it
they today Donald Trump I don't know if you saw this this to me is it was one of the the true low
points of this presidency somebody calls him out and says I don't know if you guys are picking
up in this pattern but Trump loves publicly destroying the credibility of minorities uh so he can
embolden his his base to think that minorities are people to be slapped around taunted whatever
else okay this was a just a random tweeter Trump replies to this tweeter and says in all caps
make America great again the exclamation point so he's just saying I am doing that I don't think
that's what I'm not supporting Trump but I don't think that's what I think he's being like this
will piss this guy off if I just write my slogan uh I can't do we can't do that listen he shouldn't
be on god damn twitter to begin with I mean this is ridiculous the world we're living in I don't care
who the president is when Obama was in office I hate it that he was on twitter the president shouldn't
be on fucking twitter with uh my Lee Cyrus folks folks you start to feel like you can walk into like
grocery store and just point a gun at somebody's head and be like I'm taking these fucking groceries
and walk out it's starting to feel like thunder dome out there uh it's a mess uh it's it's it's
coming on it's coming down on all sides more and more the left are now calling for the reckoning
day with Bill Clinton very rightfully so sure it's son of a bitch I was just listening to uh Gilbert
Gottfried's podcast which I always know but he's there's nobody knows what side we're anybody's
on right now but godfried had on uh David Zucker discussing some of my favorite movies of all time naked
gun top secret bear plan hot shots the classics and he's talking through them and uh just a random
offhanded story about uh naked gun 33 and a third the Clintons asked him to come screen the film
because Bill was a big naked gun fan right which I love no surprise makes sense they go and and
Clinton was like uh hey uh what's up with that girl in the movie like pulls him aside and he goes
well you in Priscilla Presley it was Elvis's wife and he goes no no no talking about the young girl
and he goes oh yeah and in a cold Smith and he goes what's her what's her story
whoo I barely know her she had like four oh she's a guest jeans girl right he's like yeah
and he was proposing to Zucker that the two of them like get some girls Zucker brings her for him
Clinton will set him up and they're all kind of laughing about the story but I was like
this he's going down on when what a matter of weeks it's it's it's clearly what happened to
Frank and Trump paid off this girl I would say it's come in it's come in law hard and fast
Frank and Frank and got a nice one across the face yeah look I I'll say this whoever you are in
whatever set of the political coin you're on when you're that fucking self righteous and
it bites you in the ass I kind of like it look I love it myself you know but uh but but I mean
Frank and just when they released that picture of him grabbing her boobs with her eyes because I was
like clearly this is being spun it's going to be that he's like no we all posed for this together
it's a joke and then he just came out and was like I'm sorry I should that was meant to be funny
I guess it wasn't I was like he actually grabbed her tits while she was asleep well they've
gotten in close on it and there's you can see the shadow between the hand and the tit and apparently
he clearly is not touching her it just it doesn't look right now somebody went after him about his
huff his shoot with area out of Huffington and they released all these pictures they didn't release
yeah where he's like grabbing her ass and stuff and he's like you know that's his whole deal he actually
gets funny but it's it's not a joke it's his way in but yeah I'll tell you the one that broke my
heart I heard a story about someone you and I know quite well really doing one of those alleged
jokes who somebody who's a very very vocal feminist I'm gonna pause this for a second folks be
right back and we're back I had to get that name off the air it was exactly who I thought it was
yep happy to hear it because I don't like that guy I'm gonna tell you though folks you know
here's what I would say don't trust a guy who's like never talks about this stuff or refuses to
talk about it but by that same token don't trust the guy who won't stop talking about how these
men need to be shamed for their crime because largely the people that I'm seeing doing that are people
with some real rattly old skeletons in their closet as well and I know about those skeletons friend
of mine once said to me never trust a family man oh well that's weird like like not not a guy with a
family I would say you should trust most family not a guy with a family not a decent guy with if
that's not what he meant okay the guy where his whole persona is I'm just the old family man I don't
do anything bad sure the guy where he was like never trust that guy that guy is bearing shit it's
the Robin Williams thing yeah it's the clown exterior and not not that Robin Williams assaulted
people I'm just saying like it's the idea of the exterior does not match the interior where you
have a very depressed man that puts out the crown image all the time family man's the same thing
usually with but in perversity right uh you know so I'll tell you the one that broke my heart I'll tell
you where the broke my god damn heart Neil de grass Tyson that was a tough one they do he's getting
accusations now apparently somebody told me I mean I think I think I saw a rape allegation I had yes
fucking Neil de grass Tyson yeah Jesus Christ Jesus
taste should call him feel harassed Tyson right well the last thing I saw this guy fondle was a
fucking telescope yeah it just I mean to me what makes me laugh the hardest is the guy's obsessed with
morality you know it caused me of course but everybody in government that guy I did you see this guy's
dick pic that went around that's like 70 year old morbidly obese guy no and a dick pics I mean his
dick from an under the dick pose meaning it's it's shooting up beneath his gut and tits so hey
teach the man how to take a fucking dick pic right but it's on Twitter for all the world to see he's
like a republican congressman is it a is it a tiny little dick he's like yeah that's my dick uh
I'm probably gonna just go ahead and drop out of office now if your life's work is stopping gay people
from doing gay things when you've never met a gay person uh the odds are you're jacking off to gay porn
day and night yeah so it's there's a fight going on within you there's a there's a we we see through
you there's a sensual battle happening on the inside of you yeah yeah everyone loses we can all be
happy if you let people do what they want to do without it turning into the fucking purge we could all
be happy we can't all be what's not gonna happen in my life we can't all be happy and here's why because
people are happy when they're stressed out I have this theory I'm not happy I'm stressed out this is my
theory had this theory for years called the every day is a bad day theory I had to write this stuff
down maybe put out a self -help book wow uh every the every day is a bad day theory this is my theory
that everybody has to act like their problems are monumental because if your problems are average
then your average so people choose to not be happy people choose to create problems for themselves
that don't need to exist whether it's being inappropriate with other people or being way too upset
about what other people are doing uh or saying or or whatever and not having any sort of not that we
shouldn't be upset about this stuff but not having any sort of rational or nuanced way to look at
anything going on see they end up with these senators who instead of saying let's discuss homosexuality
it's no it must be stomped out and I'm furious and then whatever that output is is you know as we
already established usually directly related to some internal fantasy or something um so it's it's uh
everybody's got to act like every day such a bad day because oh god if nobody does problems then
god forbid yeah that's what you go into a fucking AA meeting and it's it's you know oh you think
you were bad sure well you know everybody's got to outdo everybody all the time uh with their with
their their plight and their struggle and they're you know and it's you see it now in the in the
victimization of everything where people are comparing like cycling in in New York City to the
struggle of like black people in America it's absurd it's fucking absurd so um so nobody's happy
but hey it's Thanksgiving and I'll tell you what wash you know who I'm thankful for the fans I
already said that but I am for me yes thanks Joe and I you thank you thankful for you I got you and
con here because Pat and I are going to go get a steak dinner today I thought we were doing a
traditional tea gives well I think they have a traditional thing there but it's a steakhouse you're
not doing a traditional well I do I do want to do it but my fear is is you know the plan is to eat
dinner at 4 p .m uh uh well did you eat today I didn't eat tonight I ate a sandwich because I
didn't want to get there and pig out sure so my point is to the seas up up up up here's my thing a
turkey for energy reasons I want to be able to go out after dinner have fun like I don't want to
fall asleep at dinner I think we'll all go out but it's not going to be a shut the bars down if
you're starting it for it having a giant dinner it doesn't have to be Joe do you know who we're going
out with today yeah we'll probably be out on my point is is I get real tired after Thanksgiving dinner
I just want to get tired at dinner all right and then I'm going to want to just go home immediately so
you do a bump in the men's around this nice restaurant today Pat not today I bet you it's floating
around this place though the uh oh the the restaurant stay counseling L .a. on Thanksgiving
for Christ's sake yeah you're right full of real fucking it's like at first when you think about it
that would seem a place where you could not find cocaine but then when I really think back because I
was never in the coke culture I don't like it I don't like doing it um but when I would look back
and be really baffled by people's behavior in L .a. like man this fucking asshole what is going
it all connects back to cocaine I just didn't know it at the time yeah and they're usually
happening at places like that stay causes there was a bar I used to go to I never made this connection
either but the bar was called the white horse uh up here at Hollywood in Western it's in the white
horse heroin white maybe it was called white lady here no no the white horse was named in the bar
oh okay white lady is maybe it was a heroin bar too I don't know I know heroin is heroin sorry
okay white lady is cocaine yeah uh yeah no I see people all the time and I'm like
the guy there they just parked in the turning lane yeah doesn't have his blinkers on doesn't have a
signal just stop talking on the phone I'm honking behind he's not moving I pull around him I go what
the fuck are you doing and just go eh get fuck you like like it's my fault well I would say that's a
cocaine addict that's sure it's something here in L .a. and I would say maybe it's spread across
the country in terms of like pills you got a lot of people on opioids Xanax etc and that seeping
into driving yeah but for L .a. I would say way more than a drunk driver I am behind a very clearly
stone driver and there are there are differences of course but just that that kind of like almost
adrift into like oncoming traffic and snapping back and you go up and the people are like
young healthy people you're expecting to see some decrepit old woman or something
uh and just like these young people like with glazed over eyes like lounge back like like in a
snoop dog video yeah and it's like you were you're blazed high like where if somebody was if
somebody's at a party like look how stone that guy is and they'll just drive everywhere because
it's not drunk driving but it's certainly as dangerous did you uh speaking of snoop dog we're
getting to be like old man on a on a porch stoop here nothing gonna make me happier
I would love to just sit in a porch stoop all day sure that's the last time I sat on your porch stoop
I got molded by a dog that's on my the buildings front steps on my porch stoop uh speaking on a snoop
dog if you seen the ads for this joker's wild game show he shows me what the hell is going on
get your money snoop that's all I can say man uh love snoop but what the heck is for a guy whose whole
thing is like appealing to like young potheds and guys career star when he was 19 the fact that that
guy's like 50 and host and stupid shit doing a Martha Stewart show make your money anyway you can't
snoop and he still gets respected same with ice cube he'll do these shit movies stack them deep
but we all still will always respect ice cube it's very true I love ice cube I love snoop yeah doesn't
mean I won't call something a little bit when I when I I can deal with the Martha Stewart show
that makes sense the jokers have you seen the actual ad well I guess not I don't know what the
jokers wild is it's a game show he's hosting yeah and it's like a zany game show and one of the
things on it is you you spin a fucking casino machine thing slot machine and if you get three four
20s you win it's like observe where's this airing it's like spike or something look I better
forget I'm telling you when you saw when you see the trailer you commercial you it looks like it's a
sketch and then you realize it's real I'm telling you I know what you're picturing you're picturing a very
like blunted out sort of gangster funny take it's not like that okay it's snoop dog in a very like
polished sort of game show network environment and it's it doesn't make sense it's in a suit yes
yeah see I never liked um what was the one they well the when Mike Myers came back I was actually
very intrigued by that when Mike Myers was gonna be playing that character and they had really
funny guests yeah and I like game show they've always like games that's the gong show that's the gong
yeah but you know I got about 20 minutes in and I tried a second and a third week because I
I do love Mike Myers it's easy to forget how at at a time not that long ago he's one of the funniest
people in the world I love Mike Myers too but it was another guy that suffered from in my opinion
unfair bashing it's like he did the love guru which was not a good movie but no he got hit with all
that racism stuff where they said he's being racist sure and I was like guys again let's have a
nuance discussion can we talk about whether or not it's appropriate and not assume that Mike Myers
is rubbing his hands together going I'm gonna go be hateful right now well I forgot I actually had
forgotten about that now that you mentioned of course I remember it the braces backlash I just
thought everyone thought it sucked but Mike Myers would had essentially devoted his life at that time
to that lifestyle and that religion like so to say he was making fun of the culture is actually
pretty fucking stupid like people just don't even do their research yeah well but I'm not saying Mike
Myers hasn't had some weird questionable you know accents voices in his career don't get me wrong
but you know that one seemed pretty misguided because it changed his life for the worst I don't
sketches is one of the darkest things they ever did which was Mike Myers hosting a Japanese game show
oh yeah with Chris Farley that's what's an amazing sketch it's one of the best sketches I've ever
read that's an amazing shit yeah that's what he's surpey Niko yeah where they were Farley keeps
guests that's Farley's best it might be the biggest laugh outside of the mat Foley the first
forcefully sketch or chip in that chip but I mean audible laugh like I could hear right you could hear
laughter there's but the biggest audible laughs I think I've ever heard on SNL ever are the first
mat Foley sketch yes and Farley's first line in that game show sketch when he goes oh there has been
a mistake I don't speak Japanese yeah the place goes to fucking speak Japanese yeah yeah I mean the
best the best I know that's not what we're talking about but we might as well because it doesn't really
fit our format what are your favorite SNL sketches of all time my number one is probably the mat Foley
the original yeah the first mat fo none of them could ever even come close that was like it uh I mean
that you're talking like I loved anytime a cold open was clean and that's that's a pretty clean one
because I would have to see each week how long into the show I could watch for my dad would make
me go to bed well Matt that was not a cold open though then then maybe it was the first one back or
something it was early I remember because I was like yeah why I'm why I'm getting to watch something
this fun Christina Applegate the one with the word David Spade and Phil Hartman but I would always
hear my once my dad sent me to bed because something would get too raunchy I would hear him laughing and
like I would have tears in my eyes because I was a nerd obsessed with writing right it's helped me that's
my job now I'm living the dream folks where do I get to wake up yeah careful what you dream about
baby but uh Foley it was on very early and really uh you know people always say this shit changed
their life and it probably didn't but I was that was like I knew who wrote that sketch yeah when I
was a kid like Bob Odin Kirk wrote that's yeah yeah I was like I need to know everything about this
what's going on and my baby decide do I should I go into performing or writing well I'm never
going to be as funny as Chris Farley why would I do that but I can write funny shit for funnier people
in my opinion Bob Odin Kirk is the greatest sketch writer that has ever lived like I've never
hard thing to argue with okay and Farrell had their classics ever key and peel of that amazing
skill had their classic I just say if I had to pick a number one I don't think you're wrong uh
that guy has cranked out more when I'm just like Jesus Christ yeah it's so funny but yeah the Matt
Foley thing uh and then uh that's your number one I'm gonna put that as my number one it's just
the one I remember best and can encroach the most and whatever my number one I think is a Farrell
and it's called red ships of Spain I never saw that word the next time you're at my house we need to
watch this it's red ships of Spain Alec Baldwin hosting it was like the five till one in the morning
sketch the last sketch and Farrell is playing Goulet Robert Goulet he bald wind is playing Goulet's
brother and then Parnell is playing a third like much less talented Goulet and it's an ad for a
Broadway show called red ships of Spain starring these like brothers Goulet but they're all like
alcoholics and they keep getting in these horrible fights and then throughout it they show you scenes
and they're all singing these songs from red ships of Spain but throughout they post reviews right
that they're like obviously like this is the worst thing I've ever seen or whatever but they are
the funniest fake reviews I've ever seen it's clearly on the K Farrell sketch right I wouldn't even
need to look it up it's very obvious but so like you're getting the meat of the sketch then performing
these songs is the funniest should I've ever seen and the reviews are arguably funnier and they just
keep cutting back and forth and the first time I saw it I was well I was very very depressed right
very depressed I had moved to New York I was living like Travis Bickel I didn't eat I was doing
like 300 push -ups a day I should do it now frankly but I was in a dark place I didn't talk to people
for like a week at a time I wouldn't talk to anyone right then they showed this best of Will Farrell
volume two the original had all your classics but volume two was like they let McKay and Farrell
pick their favorite weird sketches right and that was on even at the end of of that best of Farrell
two thing and I was rolling around the floor and I like hadn't smiled in a long time but I laughed
for like an hour and kind of like blacked out and went in and out of consciousness so that's my that
has to be my number one all right that was the right time it's a very funny sketch I'm gonna put my
number two by the way this isn't the topic of this week the topic of this week we forget you're
getting two a plus topics the topic of this week is scariest scenes in non -harm movies correct
and Pat and I are gonna go down and do a couple of those but we're just warming up you still haven't
even really started the show yet but hold on let's finish this first oh yeah you're right I'm gonna
put in my number two it's gonna be like that departed credits yes my number two is gonna be the
Sinatra group oh sure which which is a contender for number one with Stephen 80 with my Myersam
yeah it's just every fucking line and the fact that they sting Billy idle on that one sting is Billy
idle so that's I had I got chunks the guys like you in my stool and the fact that on national television
they got out the joke Millie Vanille what's with this faggot crap I mean that's that is insane to me
that they got that out do you know speaking of Gulae that there is a feral sketch I think from
when I was working there where he is playing Gulae and is it's Gulae rap Gulae wraps the hit so
whatever yeah and he aggressively with a hard art I says the end words while staring the camera down
I've seen it and the gag is that he's drunk and he's yeah but it's insane I mean that that is so crazy
to me yeah I'm not saying I laughed I just kind of was like wow that's something I laughed at it
and it's not because I'm a filthy racist person I laugh sure because of I get that it's a joke I get
that it yeah you know I'm a big believe I get push back swing I'm a big believe it's a credit for
the bravery of those two I get it I'm a big believer if you're if you're joking it's okay even if the
joke falls flat is as long as we know you're not saying I'm really truly a hateful where
whatever this is not my real opinion but I I'm a big believer in that philosophy but anyway I'm
the I don't mean it's brave to say the end word I'm saying those guys are doing I don't know this
is see this is kind of the it's quite the opposite this is sort of every time Pat hosts one of our
town meetings it sort of digresses into this direction at some point here here's what I am saying when I
said I hate when they call anything brave other than like going to war but what it was so all I'm
saying is that for decades now those guys have been doing like the weirdest possible comedy at a very
high level and making a lot of money do it's an edgy joke it's an edgy joke to me I'm going off
their whole career we're off the end word that was insane but these are guys who just clearly were
not fearful of any of this but that's what which is cool that's what comedy should be and almost can't
be anymore we're we're admiring not just the end we're about the whole career I know we're admiring
chance taking comedy and sometimes that chance is saying a very offensive term sure it in a in
in what is meant to be a humorous context sure and sometimes it's many other things I get it
no we're gonna sue you Pat relax no I know but also a part of that joke is that they they sugarcoat
these people like their portrayal of Trump even once ball one started doing it is too nice and you
start to kind of have affection that's what happened with Ferrell and George W Bush they humanize
these people through them but the truth of somebody like ghoulay is like an almost guarantee ghoulay
uses the end word on a regular basis why do you think ghoulay is a racist where's that coming from
is he alive still ghoulay I believe he is I don't think he's racist you know that old guard like
you know you know Sinatra had it in him you wasn't a racist man Sinatra he dropped that
N word Sinatra was Sammy Davis juniors best man at his interracial wedding I know where they ostracized
Sammy Davis juniors I've had two massive Sinatra biographies I just feel like that old guard
you get a couple cocktails in them they don't see anything wrong with it well that was part of
the joke I think of the ghoulay sketch but I don't know maybe I'm wrong I always took you just as
isn't it funny to hear the whitest man on earth rap like street rap lyric sure sure that I just the
delight almost with how hard he hits it it like takes your breath away it's insane
one of my other favorite feral sketches and I'll put this in my top five
and it's even better now that I am a dog owner dishing your dog is your tremendous oh boy sketch
I introduced that to Heather pretty recently and she was blown away because I was doing it to our cap
yeah and she kept laughing laughing and I was like I got to give credit where to do I'm basically doing
an impression of the old wolf feral ska she hadn't seen it that's the great thing about having
these collections and they're five dollars on amazon best of feral best of heart I have all of them
that to introduce somebody like oh you've never seen like I'm excited to show you red
ships from fucking Spain I want to say it I gotta say it it's gonna blow your damn mind but the one
part in that one where he's like you know the palm wasn't taking reservations so what do you say we
go with the kibble tonight okay great and then he backs up off camera then slides back in and
goes also you're a fucking dog fucking dog yeah the bit the bit is a it's a commercial basically where
wolf feral is talking down to his dog about what a snob it is kind of because it won't eat because dogs
do that my dog will do it won't eat yeah like asshole it's been two days I don't understand
dogs can go a real long time without eating yeah so they'll do they'll do a fucking standoff
with you yeah and try to get you to give them something else right and it's just it's just a really
funny sketch my number two well mine I'm gonna say mad folie and then toss it back to you that is my
number two I know when my folie got dark and then we'll start the show when mad folie got too dark
is when he came back right before he died yeah it's too much and he's peddling on that bike and
drenched and sweat yeah I mean I I yeah I it's very sad my number three and you know I got to tell
you folks I've gone back and watched those first five years the classic years the years we've all
been trying to get back to it's hard to find a laugh on those first five years ass and it's hard
to find a fucking man yeah entire episodes of bombing their entire episode and it's not just
dated shit it's not just like on a weekend update when he's talking about some you know something
with Nixon and I'm like what the hell's he talking about I'm talking badly written unfunny lame sketches
and I know they're pioneers and they're testing out the format and yes thank you you got us where we
are today but to go back and watch them now it's like oh boy I've said it I've said it a million times
gems in there I mean it's cool to see a young Murray ackroy whatever but I've said it a million
times it's it's it's it's it's it is a it is a sign that show is a sign of the times yeah people were
coked out of their heads yeah they thought the funniest thing they ever saw was John Belushi and a
samurai outfit yeah putting for a bit yeah like literally just like that was the whole joke yeah exactly
or like him waddling around like doing gibberish yeah it's like why are this giant like five disc set
of all the best of their musical performances and that's a good reason to watch all the old ones I
mean to like yeah you it's like the Ramones around one week the clash the talking it's incredible
those are the days but to me the show didn't become a powerhouse till those amazing late 80s years
I'm part of that's just because I was growing up and getting an economy leave out don't leave out the
Casarinsky Eddie Murphy years when Lauren Michaels wasn't even there see I I couldn't even watch it at that
point but though those sketch I mean note that's when like Martin shorts in there no I've seen them
now just for gas they had some great stuff no I'm saying if you go back and watch that now it's 20
times funnier it's funnier than the than the 75 yeah and some of the some of the sketches are like
gut busting yeah funny and the feral the earlier feral years I think can rank with the
Myers Hartman well I mean Hartman Jesus Christ Hartman was in every sketch and killed it as did
Ferrell there's a real nice it's very brief but there's that real sweet spot where it's like
they had everybody Hartman Carvey Farley then they're then Sandler and like yeah it's like
there's a real brief sweet spot where it's like they're all Tim Meadows like they're all
there together yeah no it was incredible my number three I guess would have to be and that's
tough do you have yours go ahead I said mine already I did Matt Foley sent out your group
dissing your dog oh dissing your dog yeah it almost have to be a feral or are a Farley I mean
you got the glue sketch needs more horse well you know what you know what I got to do and I'm ashamed
of it is is if I'm being honest to myself more cowbell I there's nothing to be ashamed of I saw
that the night it premiered as did I and I told it in link in great detail to my roommate at the time
Jim Cargill when we were in college yeah and he was laughing uncontrollably by the description of it
yeah and what's it it works so well that like oh like I would say most of the people who love that sketch
know nothing about blue oyster cold or that that song even had a cowbell it's just so funny that
doesn't matter but if you know the music of blue oyster cold it makes it something very special
because you know somebody who's listening to it and started doing it as a bit walking it's
walking's funniest performance including in film yeah it's is the best he's ever been and who
who ruins it in the end if anybody's gonna bring it down fucking Jimmy Fallon as he ruins everything
but it's one of the few times I gave Fallon a pass oh I would have made it through that sketch without
laughing either I think I've mentioned this in the podcast I haven't I have a little acting exercise
I do with myself sure by myself where I will watch the best of Will Farrell outtakes which begins
with the eastbound and down run of him talking about his plums the funniest outtakes in the history
of film and television and I mean that yeah if you haven't seen it I advise you to watch on the
eastbound and down DVD to make sure you're in you're getting the full version but if you got to go
YouTube make sure you're getting it all but it's Craig Robinson and Will Farrell and each other's
faces and Danny McBride and McBride and they're standing in like a three -way and they are talking
each other's faces for like 10 minutes and it's the funniest outtakes in the history of movies and or
television the exercise I do is to try to get through it with a straight face yeah and I've seen it
now a hundred times I still can't do it yeah but the basic gist is Will Farrell was playing a like
like a this asshole that runs a car dealership with one of the biggest swings at a wig I've ever seen
since absurd and it works and he's writing their faces talking about how excited he is about like
making a sale and he keeps he's talking about it in a sexual way and he's going I can feel it
down in my plums yeah and he keeps calling his balls his plums he describes with the light a time
when his son walked in on him and his wife having sex and he turned and said no let the boy watch
let the boy watch he goes yeah he goes my son came in my wife said get out of here I said no
that the boy watch he needs to learn as his father learned before him and his father before him
it's the best uh the best set of outtakes I've ever seen him on
um all right holy god almighty that is so funny let's get on with the topic at hand which is
well yeah I guess if we're gonna get on with the topic at hand we might also want to get on with
the show and at the same time get on oh yeah yeah yeah uh that was a very late one folks we're
talking today about what are your favorite what are your what are the scariest scenes that you
have ever seen in non horror movies yes and I woke up this morning and realized I hadn't quite given
it the thought I wanted to but then I decided what I wanted to pick but I did a quick google to see
if this topic's ever been discussed before and all the choices were from what I would call
clear horror movies like I have seen did a list and on it was a scene from seven seven's a
fucking horror movie yeah we're talking about scenes that aren't in are scenes that are in movies that
are not supposed to be scary that are scary yes either because they affected you personally in some
weird way or because they actually put a scary scene in a comedy or something I'll start with my
number one sure because I don't I don't have an exact number of these I just have a handful and I
don't want to do the I don't want to not get to the number one should I go backwards let's go
backwards I want yeah I want to try to do my favorite one last okay so I'm probably not gonna go
on any sort of order these other ones are in no particular order but I'll start you know what I think
happens with alcohol now hey I I didn't need to I'm just I'm baffled at how drunk I am after as
you can see half a drink they didn't even know you were drinking well now I've told them but it's
Thanksgiving like that made a difference but what I think happens is like generally you and I go out
we have a couple whiskeys we go home staring to each other's eyes staring to those eyes or you know
a couple of macasodas and go home that's just what I tend to do one or the other I never fucking drink
gin and I think when you introduce a foreign alcohol I think it gets you drunker like it like it felt
at that first time like a virgin like what Madonna sang about in the song like a virgin now before we
start it makes you feel like a virgin to this new alcohol yeah I'm fucked by it for the very first
time for the first time now when you did you know the original lyric to that was not being touched by the
very first time was it getting fucked no she had to she did have to change those two dirty it was
getting fingered for the very first time no dot dot long pause in the brown that was the
actual lyric before the label made a change was in the brown and parentheses she delivered it as it
were or maybe an ellipses had come before it or something but she didn't rush right into the
second half of that sense yeah now you so I always say we're gonna do this and then we don't you
should you need to come over and watch that sketch and watch sling blade with me one of my five
top five favorite movies and you've never seen it I've never seen it so you come over and watch
it but is there one of your scenes no no no well it could be but in the director's cut there is
a deleted scene that they put in that is so fucking funny where yoke him who plays the villain of the
movie right one of the best villains ever yoke him and his crew are getting together he's they're all
raging alcohols and they get together to like play music in their band all night but they're like
this terrible bunch of alcoholic red next and they're trying to write the songs and they're arguing
about where the ellipses can the dot that that should come in the song and the parentheses and everything
remind me of this discussion that's very funny folks if you haven't seen sling blade please do I'd like
to see it I'd like to see a mashup of sling blade in bad santa okay a third bad santa movie sure he
plays bad santa and then his sidekick is this guy from sling was this time around did you ever see bad
santa too I saw that half of it I look we we had a big that was a big thing on our show I didn't think
it was that bad but I also caught it on Netflix streaming like when I didn't give a shit at 2 am you
know what I mean so it had some funny parts but I mean I also didn't feel compelled to finish it see
bad santa 2 for me was kind of like how you how you feel with these new star wars you know like I
you're real excited and I and I had a fear in the back of my heart but like the hardest I've ever
laughed really was bad santa thanks giving day 10 years ago I believe to the day maybe 11 years
ago bad santa's a masterpiece New York City my buddies came in from Missouri we saw it wasted I've never
laughed so hard on my life bad santa too it's not funny it's okay you just can't go back to that
well yeah it's it's there's no right way to go back to the well because it's either now he's a
redeemed guy and it's not as funny or the way they did it oh he's still the same piece of shit so
then that discredits the original film right it's it's like there's no real good way to do it it to me
felt like a lot of if you had a lot of bonus scenes from the first bad yeah they did rightfully
deleted scenes and then they you know it's easy to underestimate how much Bernie Mac and John
Ritter had to do with how funny bad santa was yes and now they're both fucking dead yes and plus the
guy who created entourage wrote bad santa 2 and the Cohen brothers wrote bad santa 1 so I'm just not
a big fan either when I don't know why they do this but why every sequel has to be now they have a
son yeah now their mom is there you know sometimes it works it worked great the last crusade it worked
very well for me in the force awakens it worked at bad moms christmas part two i'm a dea christmas by
the way no disrespect by the way I'm driving around town saying post for bad moms too right and most
of the make sense it's a it's a Christian battle a bell bransky you know it's christian bell it's
Susan serandin it's real akunas then it's Cheryl Heinz right what was does anybody know who Cheryl
Heinz is by name that didn't religiously watch curb your enthusiasm so I thought you were going to say
she was too young to play no I'm saying like they're they're they've got her on these posters like
she's like look at Cheryl Heinz is it this wow that took a turn I mean I I love Cheryl Heinz
I find her character on curb your enthusiasm to be one of the most annoying characters in television
history well I think without her the show falls apart I mean I especially she needs to be a mouthpiece
for a normal normal society it is very clear to me I think you and I probably relate too much to
Larry and hate her when it starts when I when they divorced I was miserable I felt that when they
got divorced when it's because I think they're perfect for each other when it starts okay when it's
starts I'm like that's how I felt yeah first couple seasons I was like I get it she's got to be the
person that's like your lunatic then it becomes clear to me that Larry David saw that divorce writing on
the wall yeah had hit some kind of point with his own wife and she becomes literally the wife that
just sits in the billion dollar house all day being like that's true Larry you idiot and it's like
do you see where you're living right now can you get off this guy's back do you know his situation
yeah she cheated with the guy she she starts to come across that way yeah Larry David's actual wife he
was building her her own like home and the wife was fucking the contractor in the home and Larry
didn't find out about it and because it had been more than 10 years in the state of California even
though his wife who he was building a home was cheating on him he had to give her half of his money
and half of Larry David's money is an absurd amount of money it's yeah it's at least $250
million so yeah I mean I would say the portrayal changed but yeah she certainly never reached the heights
of like Jeff's wife no but Jeff's right the Suzy Esman is it's cartoonish she's so fun she's
great she's great she's great they make Suzy Esman a little more cartoonish yeah but there's a turn
in the for me now the show is is really about funcows are talk about a guy coming into his own talk
about a guy coming into his house and and part of it is how bad his face looks honestly helps it
but my god he is so funny when he and even stuff that you can tell is not supposed to be jokes like
when he keeps talking about in this past week's episode which wasn't even that good but they open
the champagne and he goes oh I love that sound I love that sound don't you love that sound and it was
so it's so perfectly captured like how boring everyone is like that he had to know how funny that
was to keep saying how much he loves the sound of champagne and he's like we're gonna live it up aren't
we let's live it up tonight we're gonna live it it's a parody of like it's great people who never go
out like going out but holy shit he makes well it's like the deleted scene in about Schmidt where
they go to the prime rib place yeah and they he's the voiceover saying how they go every Sunday
right such a routine and he's so miserable right and then he's there with the guy that you find out
his wife was fucking yeah and they put this the prime rib down and the guy goes whoa they do it
nice here and all they and you just feel so sorry for him yeah this is the highlight of this guy's
week yeah it's why I'm not going home this year it's awesome but fun cows are I haven't seen the
season yet but I did see the one scene I'm sorry I'm sorry have you seen it about Schmidt oh
sure the deleted scene where he goes and orders the Blizzard yeah I don't remember it though I've
seen all the deleted scenes it is about a four -minute scene in real time of Jack Nicholson ordering a
Blizzard and I think that it's supposed to be a parody of when they wouldn't make what he wanted in
five easy pieces right and they go you want me to hold it because I want you to hold it between
your knees like choose the girl out slams the tail so now this is him like 50 years later that's I
think that's the point of the scene is parodying that same where like they wouldn't get him what he
wanted he blew up at them so they keep telling him like what substitutions they will him want to
allow and he's trying to get like he only wants his like Reese's pieces and M &M's in the same Blizzard
and they won't do it and then finally he's like all right well I'll just go with the Reese's pieces
and of course the scene had to be cut right but man it's it's like like all of about Schmidt
and something he's never been able to do since it's like super funny but also very sad to imagine
that at some point your life will become arguing about a Blizzard which it will and honestly I'd
argue about a Blizzard right now if they weren't making it right but the scene the one one of the
only scenes I saw of the new season because I don't have HBO and it was the fun count of the fun
cows are seen big shout out to Elizabeth Perkins in the new season Perkins oddly never better my left we
follow each other on Twitter don't know how it started don't know where it came from we just started
following each other yeah she's faved some of my tweets I have a great admiration for the lady I
remember first seen her in about last night where she sadly had to simulate interest in James
Belushi big exactly yeah and I'm not shitting on Jim Belushi I'm just saying you can I've heard a
lot about Jim Belushi you can go ahead anyway she but the scene where she's like do you like my water
and he's like I hate your water yeah I feel like I stuck my head up a dog's ass or skunks ass
whatever yeah he just goes on that it was incredible that scene really made me laugh and I also saw the
scene it could be the greatest line ever on curb your enthusiasm huh the namaste thing for the ladies
like it says that my light inside of me is recognizing the light inside of you and he just goes uh you see
there's a problem there is no light in here I was like that could be the greatest Larry David line ever
I love the show I mean this this seems been light on classics but I mean any criticism of it I'm like
you're getting new episodes of curb your enthusiasm shut up we're roughly 10 minutes away from
the end of this thing we haven't gotten to the subject let's do it holy shit now for me
that we give the people what they deserve folks uh for me the scariest and you're gonna make fun of
mine but I had to go back to like childhood um the one we've always discussed in the show number one
I was gonna say mohalon drive but having lived in a lay for 10 years mohalon drive is a horror movie
yes no question yes the guy behind the dumpster at winkeys in mohalon drive um so my pick is and go
ahead and make fun of me but it really did traumatize me when I was a kid a picture called return to
Oz I am a huge fan of return to Oz I own it on a DVD I could kind of say any scene from return to Oz
because rough one uh I would say no movie has ever scared me more if I'm being honest and because of
the age I saw it and etc I had never seen anything scary and was not allowed to see anything scary
and return to Oz you're not expecting to be scary and it's like uh you know it would be like a hard
PG -13 now I would say it's a very very dark film it's great for me when all the uh all the heads
yeah the queen the queen changes her heads every day which is like an amazing set piece yeah where she
has this like chamber of heads and she can change her head to everything but all the heads and they're
trying to sneak through the heads without waking them and I remember being like honestly like
shitting my pants yeah and then of course the head start coming to life and they all start screaming
at the same time yeah I and even now I haven't seen it in years I bet that would really fuck me up
it's a scary scary scene and they're escaping from a tower where the queen mom be your name is
uh yes has locked dorthy away because she said I'm gonna keep you in here until you're old enough
for me to cut your head off right and then I'll add you to my collection right so it's a very
disturbing the whole principle premise the whole thing is very disturbing that movie is very
disturbing uh the good guys are scary tick -tock is scary yeah the scarecrow king is scary for some
reason I always found this the most disturbing part to be when the the wheelie the wheelers are we
sure set me there's a gang rape element to the wheelers there is must have been intended and when
the one hits that sand that you can't touch and he turns into sand immediately it's a great special
effect yeah he just collapses and shatters yeah that always disturbed me it's still kind of
I find it still a bit haunting return to Oz uh I would say even like by cult movie standards it's
culty like like no one really knows the movie sometimes people from our for our age group do but
it wasn't available for a long time I bought it on amazon for five bucks if you haven't seen it
check it out it plays like an amazing horror movie it's better to me than both the dark crystal
and labyrinth which get a lot more discussion uh I would put it above labyrinth I will not put it
above the dark crystal but you want to talk about non horror movies that scared the shit out of me
I mean that movie the dark crystal sure when I was a when I saw the commercial for that movie as a
child I started crying yeah at the sight of the skexies and the missed the mystic in particular
because all you remember was trying to describe to my ran upstairs to my mom crying and I said why
because they said Jim Henson's name in the commercial I said why would Jim Henson make something like
this uh and I said there was a man in it that looked like he was a thousand years old and it really
really disturbed me uh and to this day that movie if I'm in a dark room alone and I start thinking
about the skexies they still freaks me out a little bit sure very excited for that new Netflix
dark crystal series coming out really who's doing that the Henson companies doing it oh I can't
wait for the prequel series to the movie what a dream yeah that's gonna be very cool yeah be honest folks
I love puppets who doesn't who doesn't the great muppak paper is one of my favorite movies of all time
the great muppak paper is is so fucking funny I get I it's on HBO now so if you have HBO go whatever
you can watch it I mean holy shit now so not only do you have the muppets and like their best jokes
of all time and like cool action sequences frankly right you also have Charles Grodon playing the villain
and a love interest for Miss Piggy Kermit is battling Charles Grodon for the huff of Miss Piggy is
Grodon funny in it Grodon is incredibly funny in it yes he doesn't just play an asshole I mean
he's like a funny asshole he's really really funny yes I'm gonna walk oh Piggy Piggy Piggy Piggy
I know I love you Piggy Grodon nobody better Beethoven not my shoes Beethoven Beethoven not
of a lawn oh Beethoven no we're we're we're recently talking about midnight run just going why would
you eat like that I eat that stuff you can't see it stuff will kill you Teresa and eggs yeah yeah yeah
uh cuz I ordered Teresa and eggs but Joe I was telling you on my sitcom we had on shoot him again
Chris from McDonald one of the great characters of our time nicest man loved him
and he was telling me that he had played the Robert De Niro role in three midnight run sequels
and I was like what the fuck are you talking about because they were they were talking a few years back
yeah about making midnight really really stemmer they're they're out
there are three like direct to DVD midnight run sequels starring Chris from McDonald that's
like when I found out there were two or three more smoking in the banded films yeah which the two
sequels that was the police that was too much yeah there were two or three more that were like direct
to like USA right flicks where somebody else played the band it and we're on in my uh career I was
approached to write a direct to DVD money train sequel well and I watched money train out and they
didn't have either Harrelson or Snipes yeah yeah did they just assume the money train brand would be
enough yeah that's like when they did Carlitos way rise to power right yeah exactly all right listen
what are we doing here okay we're running out of time we picked our top our top no we didn't we
are crystal you said dark crystal and I was agreeing with you I said return to Oz and you said dark
crystal I don't know you said it for five minutes you said I'll put it above dark crystal and I said I
wouldn't but I'll put I'm gonna give you a quick runner up no number one go with your choice my runner
up uh high school hallway scene in juice when overips shuts the locker at two pocket statement you
realize it's already after he's attempting to you know he's gonna start killing all his friends after
he's already killed the one friend and you guys how sinister he is and he just does I mean
talk about a guy that it's a shame I really think he could have done some really wonderful film work
yeah is that monologue where he's like you know what last time you call me how's crazy I was kind of
tripping right but I thought about it I am crazy yeah what else I don't give a fuck yeah he tells
him he's gonna murder him he goes as soon as I realize he goes I ain't shit I never gonna be
shit as soon as I realize you ain't shit yeah it's it's a very upsetting scene that I get nervous
every time I watch it it is as threatening as I've ever seen a human being I love juice that that
was that was a great age of let's let's say it of black crime films yeah there was some of I don't
know what else I would call it folks but uh menaceous society dead presidents set it off it's
fucking amazing yeah uh and then the comedies Friday uh next Friday yeah don't be a menace like I
miss those it was like hood movies it was like they don't have boys in the hood well boys in the hood
as a master higher learning higher learning which more of a race movie but you know it's it's it's that
I fucking love higher learn and they're just not made I don't know why they're not but they're not
made anymore well the I the great beautiful irony and what made it such like an awesome Michael
Rappaport moment yeah because that guy's awesome of course but uh that that that Twitter video he did
which was so amazing yeah of trashing the white the the alt right net white nationalist whatever
in in uh down south and being like you fuck a tiki -touches why don't you try to get the second base
with a girl your nerds yeah that that was pretty great it was it made it even better that he plays the
Nazi in yeah higher learning yeah like and he's and he's shitting it's yeah it's great uh
okay my number one is on higher learn hi JR Ferguson is on higher learning he is pretty pretty
size of a world my number one no no I didn't do my number one yet pet you just went so I go no I
said I'm gonna give you a quick one runner up and then my number one my number one I've already
texted it to you uh army navy back room store scene yeah falling down yeah sure when the guy is
basically gonna rape Michael uh Dougal I was in Michael Cain I'm falling down yeah and finally stop
ripe and they thank you Michael Douglas does not bend first the prep stage then the triple prep
stage then you're right me in the back of the all me navy store the all me navy store that's not
a bad Michael Cain that's good the all me navy still governor all go ahead uh it's just such a
scary scene because the guy is clearly pissed off yeah Michael Douglas doesn't want to go all the way into
like white supremacy territory with him and then Michael Douglas as crazy as he is in the movie
stances ground and goes he the guy goes we're the fucking same don't you get it in Michael Douglas
goes no we're not the same I'm an American and you're a sick asshole yeah and uh you're like here he
goes Michael Douglas is about to get raped by this fucking lunatic right in the back of the store and
then uh things take a turn but uh that's this hands down the scariest non -harm movie scene I'd ever seen
him falling down is incredible yeah um this was not gonna be on my list but I I would be remiss not to
mention being 13 years old and seeing pulp fiction and seeing that scene in the bottom of that
wreck room yeah with that with that rape I mean that uh you I mean I had never seen anything like that
in my entire life or even thought about it and to see vingrames getting butt fucked in the basement
of a gun shop I was like what in the name of guy I was I was and uh Heather so when I if I saw
when I was 14 whenever it hit VHS I was about 14 and Heather said her dad had rented it and she was
about 12 13 it was watching it Heather has never seen past that point in pulp fiction because she said
she like passed out like just rough scene you know it's when you're a kid yeah yeah you know like I
obviously now I'll watch fucking anything I might have a very open mind to anything but it's just
kind of like what's like you don't even really really know how to process and you buried the lead
a little bit on it because it starts with him saying bring out the game bring out and I remember seeing
it in the theater being like what does that mean I know and they drag that guy out from literally
the across space that is and you're it's that's that's a real real rough scene that it's the best
scene and then and then right into him walking across that crosswalk with the donuts and him slamming
on the gas like folks have you heard about pulp fiction it's very good movie you probably don't
even tell you that my number one this is the one you're gonna make fun of me for because you watch it
now and of course it's not scary if you're watching that's an adult but something about it still does
get to me because of how badly it affects me when I was a kid and that is the large margin scene in
PV's big adventure because much like how when I saw pulp fiction when I was 14 I had never thought
about somebody getting asked right before and there it was in front of me I had just never seen
anything scary in my life and I was so excited to see PV's big adventure and I was obsessed with it
but for the 10 minutes leading up to the large margin where her head turns into like
claymation and makes a scary face scared the shit out of me as a kid when I would rewatch it even
the 10 minutes leading up to it I would be sweating as a little kid sitting there sweating
dreading this moment when large margin face was gonna pop out of the screen and I mean that's
one of my favorite movies as well it's it's incredibly funny but just to throw that into the movie is
insane and I love it it's great and that's why Tim Burton used to be the best and now he's a massive
disappointment at every step that he takes folks folks you wanted a bonus app there's your bonus app
we'll see you soon no plugs on the bonus apps we're thankful for you's thank you