Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
More Puff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days, all on our players'
favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all of the bacon on the game everyone's
Huff and About!
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly, 21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania,
and West Virginia only, void in Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
See terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st,
2025.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off
your car's maintenance, and you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're
at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Hey folks, we'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast about movies, just movies anymore, you know, used to be hard and sci -fi fantasy
now.
You know, these other genres have been creepin' in.
Why do we don't put baby in a corner?
That's right.
I'm here with Matt.
Jennifer Gray.
Jennifer Gray, Skies.
Patty Sways.
RIP.
How did Jennifer feel when she heard Patrick Swaysie died?
Go ahead.
Gray.
Kind of just sad, really.
That's what sad is, God's slapping me in the head with his tail.
His asshole is right in your face.
What I want to need it after a long day, Joe's moved into somehow the most exclusive parking
center in all of Los Angeles.
You can find a spot in Beverly Hills faster than around here.
I can't believe there's no parking around here.
I finally find a spot and it's like no parking from 6 p .m. to 8 a .m.
It's just like an abandoned spot under a tree somewhere.
Like, okay, go up to sunset, can't park here 6 to 8.
What time is it?
6 .49.
Jesus Christ.
Tyred.
You're having a hell of a day.
Tyred of it.
Pat's having to work.
I mean, does that tell you anything?
This is what I want to work.
Pat is dressed like Roseanne on the early seasons, like pilot episode, sweatpants, hoodie,
star.
I want you to look, let's not discuss it on the show, but I'm concerned about you.
I'm concerned about myself.
I mean, that's sincerely, Pat and I, I'm a testament to our friendship.
We had a text to change today that would have two years ago come, turned into a fucking
World War III, but I resolved to fuse very quickly with both of us, almost saying I love
you to one another.
Well, I just, you know, I confessed to Joe.
I was like, look, until you texted me, I was unaware what day of the week it was.
So like, forgive me if my scheduling's a little hazy.
I've been up about 48 hours.
I almost went to the red bull today, but I knew I would just wind up feeling even shittier,
so I didn't do it.
My entire room is ill.
There's no one there.
It's fallen apart.
Jesus Christ.
All they get a multi cam on the air, you know, it's exactly right, it's exactly right.
It's like the people in the White House are like this stress.
That's, that's honestly true.
And it could be so easy at the end of the day.
It's that the people holding the strings have a fundamental lack of understanding about
why people watch television.
But let me leave it at that.
Fair enough.
I'm not talking about it.
Well, I'm going to get off this topic.
Folks, let's get on with the show if we could and at the same time on with the Joe man.
Terrible one.
All right.
It's okay.
It can't all be just a terrible.
I don't hate it.
Scooter's gone.
That's new in my life.
So now tell me about that.
Is this something you can talk about because I know you were starting to rant about it the
other night.
It's excited about this scooter.
I bought it called the shop when I bought it said I don't need a driver's license, right?
Yes.
Because my license has expired and I'm having a hard time getting in for a test for a
new one repeatedly.
Yes.
Yeah, you're fine.
You're fine.
Buy this thing.
Wheel and all over fucking town and this thing.
Yeah.
Meanwhile, there's a little space on the back that looks like it's for a license plate.
So I call the manufacturer today and I go, are you supposed to send me a license plate
for something for this thing?
They're like, no, no, no, no, no, no, you got to go get that yourself when you register
it.
I go register it.
I thought you didn't have to register this thing.
He said, no, you got to register it.
Why wouldn't you have to register it?
I was like, well, you don't need a license to drive it and he was like, what are you talking
about?
You need a license.
Long story short, I find out the, yeah, this thing is not a fucking, they told me the
dealership that it was classified as an e -bike, even though it didn't have pedals.
It's not.
It's actually considered a mo -ped, which is a level above scooter.
So I look up maximum penalty for driving without a license in LA six months in jail.
Whoa.
So you could have been arrested.
Yeah.
So I call the place.
I'm like, guys, you sold me this thing.
You told me I didn't have a license.
I'm driving around all over the place.
I could literally went to jail.
Do you realize that?
And with, I will say this, with very little pushback, they gave me my money back.
They had a strict no returns policy.
I got into a little bit with it.
I got into it a little bit with the woman that it sold me the bike, because she was kind
of doing the whole like, well, I thought you meant motorcycle life.
I'm like, you didn't think that I meant that.
Yeah.
I gave you an expired driver's license and you let me test drive it.
She's like, well, for a test drive, sure, it's like, you can't test drive anything
with an expired license.
That's not how this works.
So she then kind of, in a roundabout way, put me, I thought she was going to get me to run
around.
She gave me the owner of the shop's email, and I'm like, you got to be kidding me, man.
She won't even give me his number.
Yeah.
But I, lo and behold, I emailed the guy he called me back within minutes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Was apologetic.
Okay.
Called me later again that day.
He's like, I'm just going to give you your money back.
Came today, did the refund over the phone right in the lot there, and wrote off with the scooter.
Beautiful.
So, you know, nothing lost, nothing gained.
It was, you know, I got to ride a scooter for free for a month.
Right.
And that's where we're at.
Now, I don't know what the statute of limitations on this crime is.
So people, you know, if your brother or your husband, there's a cop or your mom or your aunt
or whoever.
Yeah.
Don't go blabbing about what I did, you know.
Right.
I got to, you know, I don't want to have to fly to Bermuda until this thing blows over.
Um, I guess I can just take us over to Pat's movie corner.
That's, this is a, this is a broken man.
Folks, I should tell you, we're, uh, it took me about an hour to be able to form sentences
today.
So I understand.
You're lucky.
You're lucky you're getting what you're getting.
Listen, I understand.
Uh, I've seen all these movies.
They're all like Pre -Christmas.
I feel like, but I'm just like getting to them now.
Um, what did I watch?
What, well, you know, when I watched the other day, Joe, it's what you talked about last week.
UHF starring Weird Al Yankovic.
Pe -pe -pe -pe -pe -pe -pe -pe -pe.
Uh -uh -uh -uh -uh -uh, uh -uh -uh -uh -uh -uh -uh.
and watched that Harvey Leeds state of shock video by Weird Al that Joe had told me about.
I screamed laughing. I had a great time with it. And I also watched the John Candy food repair,
which I found hilarious as well. Then we watched another sketch where John Candy just basically beat
the shit out of Gulda Radner for five minutes. And that sketch was hilarious. What was the person
they were like they were, oh, it was mailman. She went to the post office and she didn't put a return
address on her package. Correct. And she's like, why can't I just send it? And like they take
Dave Thomas takes her in the back. And he's like time to play good postman, bad postman. John Candy
comes in his bad postman. He's throwing her into these boxes. And God bless Gulda Radner. You could
see in the sketch, it was like she's sick. It's towards the end of her life. And she's still doing these
pratfalls and everything. She was very funny in it as well. Yeah, she's amazing.
Never, never a good movie career though, you know, like she never even found one vehicle that was
a good movie for her. I feel like she didn't get it much of a shot, right? I mean, she had, I mean,
haunted honeymoon, hanky -panky, you know, she did pictures. Oh yeah, I guess those that did go on
for about a decade. Was Jean Wilder ones. I mean, none of them were any good. They never really gave her
anything funny. Anywho, UHF, while it did make me laugh out loud as much as it did when I was a
kid, let's say, it's just a very charming movie. Yeah. And the whole, you know, it's not just a
collection of sketches, which would I, you know, I think have bored me. But like the story where he
just picks up all these misfits. And they all get their little moment of triumph in the end. They're
all bullied in some terrible way throughout the film. And they all get their triumph in the end.
You know, it shows the heart behind the hair, if you will. Weird out as a very sweet side.
Billy Barty is great in it, you know, getting his revenge. Michael Richards, I forget, they wouldn't
allow that performance today. I forgot that he was basically playing a mentally handicapped person,
which I didn't think of him as that as a kid. Right. But it's, you know, it's clear that he is,
but he does it with respect for the character. It's a really good performance. Yeah, he's great.
And Fran Dresser is wonderful. She's great. And it, it's a great movie. I love the film.
It originally was supposed to be like a Walter Mitty thing where I was just about this guy with
an overactive imagination, which happens in the beginning. Yeah. And then they kind of never go back
to that premise. And also the part of the best friend was offered to Seinfeld. He turned it down.
Right. Yes. We were at the same Wikipedia page apparently. Yeah. I watched some of the special
features. There's a new shout -out factory DVD. It's great. My one drawback of the film is I'm sure
they told me had to have a music video. And I don't understand why he didn't do one of his classic
parodies. He does this Beverly Hillbilly's, it's basically just singing the Beverly Hillbilly's theme
to the tune of money for nothing by dire straits and sting. And it's lame. And the animation
sucks. And it really bogs down the film right in the middle when it's kind of taken off.
One minor quibble. The rest of the movie I really love. He was pitching also, that's another little
fact about weirdo. He was pitching that Beverly Hillbilly's premise like around. A couple people
said no to like pet. So he got it in his head that he wanted to do a song about the Beverly Hillbilly's
for some reason. He was pitching it around the song. Like I read that he had approached.
It was Prince I think. And to do a parody of kiss, but it was going to be about the Beverly
Hillbilly's or something. And Prince said no. Yeah. It's on his page where you read like the people
that denied him. Right. The whatever. And what was one of the other ones? One of them was,
Oh, Eminem approved the parody of lose yourself, but didn't approve the video. Okay.
Because he, I guess he thought it would be bad for his image yourself. What was the, what was
the song snooze yourself about hitting the alarm in the morning? You're going to be shocked when
I tell you this. Jews yourself. And it was about converting Judaism. Good Lord. It was kind of a
kind of a heavy topic for a weird outside. Very heavy. Not a joke in the thing. Okay.
No, I don't know what it was called. It was called like, I don't think it's a play on the name.
It's just he just wraps it though. All right. Folks, I watched a little picture called leprechaun
two. Wow. Sequel to leprechaun one. The original sequel to leprechaun one, not leprechaun returns that
hard thing that was just released. What's the story of leprechaun two? I'll tell you the story.
He is a thousand years ago. He falls in love with his slave's daughter. Okay. His slave won't let him
take his daughter. So he thwarts his efforts to land the daughter. And then the leprechaun says,
in a thousand years, I will wake. And I will find my bride then. Okay. And they're just kind of
playing by the sea of their pants at this point with these rules. Sure. You know, anyway,
thousand years later in Big Bright, Los Angeles, the leprechaun awakes. And of course there's a girl
there that looks exactly like the girl he was in love with a thousand years prior. It's sort of a
fun movie. I will say this about the movie. It you can see the effort. It's not very well directed.
But you can see the effort. And I like that. I like that you can tell they were trying to make a fun
horror movie that kills in it are fantastic. They're sort of like practical effect kills. All right.
I've had more fun watching it than I ever do the first one. And I would quite frankly return
to it. And a little fun movie fact. The guy that plays Jack Klampus in Seinfeld is in it. Okay.
He plays like a drunk that owns like a tour of the horror hills of Hollywood. Yeah.
And he's like sort of the comic relief. And his death is really great. He makes the leprechaun promise him
that he'll give him a bunch of gold. Okay. And the leprechaun does. And then all the gold appears inside
of his stomach. So his stomach just starts bloating out and clinking and clanking. It's actually
some very cool practical effects. Does he explode? I think so. Yeah. I forget. All right. But when did you
watch it? Week ago. That's troubling. That I can't remember if he exploded. Yeah. It was a week ago.
I mean, look, I got to be honest with you. Leprechaun 2 is not a film. You know, it's not the paper.
You know what I mean? You're not sitting down going. It's not spotlight. I'm going. I got to really
keep track. Yeah. Now did you do other things while you're watching it? Did you reference as like the
kind of movie that that rivets you to your seat? The paper starring Michael Keaton and Glenn Close?
Wasn't that Tom Hanks movie that just came out called the paper? The post. Yeah. That's what I meant.
That wasn't fucking riveting either. I just meant like it's not a newsroom drama you're dealing with.
You get up. You walk over to the window. You go get a drink of water. Right. You know, the paper
not a terrible film. I believe he does explode because he keeps going get it out of me.
Sure. And then I think it's stomach explode. Sure. I watched a film that I saw
opening night in theaters. One of two movies I can recall where opening night me and my buddy
band were the only two people in the theater. One was the now beloved cult classic office space.
The other is the very little beloved by a very small cult cabin boy.
I love cabin boy when I saw it in the theater. I love the cheesy sets and effects.
And I thought there was a lot of big laughs to be had. When I was a kid, I loved like the cupcake
flying up and spitting tobacco at him and stuff. I was just, you know, I didn't even smoke weed at this
point. I was just I thought all that stuff was funny. As an adult, I find that less funny. I find
Chris Elliott about equally funny and annoying and equal measure but sometimes the he's so annoying
he's funny. And what I found particularly great this time out were the four performances of the
Seahands on the boat. Brian Doyle Murray, you know, like just these like old gruff dudes.
You were an odd like comedy team. They cracked me up. No, Brian Doyle Murray and Chris Elliott
because Brian Doyle Murray was also on get a life. That's correct. Yes. I love I love older
Chris Elliott stuff is newer stuff. There's something Eagleheart. It's like two I don't know what it is.
It's two adult swimming or something. I don't know. But I like that older Chris Elliott stuff. I
don't like the film cabin boy though. I like the first like half hour. Yeah. And then once they get
out to see and it gets all like Bertony, I'm kind of like. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I watched a pretty
sizable documentary about it with Adam Resnick and Chris Elliott. They talked about just how
absolutely heartbroken they were when it came out and their agents were like, you'll never work
again. And they sold a pitch, like a TV pitch like bought it in the room and that they were
not to their car all excited like, let's go get a beer and celebrate. And somebody in the meeting
told their boss who they hired a pitch from and they were like, the cabin boy guys call them now
and cancel. Wow. So they're like driving to the bar and they call them are like, yeah, we just
realized you guys did cabin boy. So the project's done. Jesus. And essentially neither of these guys
worked for many, many years. Cohen brothers, I mean, excuse me, fairly brothers used them to
great effect and Kingpin used Chris Elliott and something about Mary. But, you know, he didn't
really get to do anything creatively just as an actor and that sucks. But the movie Adam Resnick
is like, no, if it was me and Chris Elliott and we got our chance to do a movie, we would have done
a one million dollar thing where Chris works in an office or something. Yeah, where he's like a
loser. Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly. But they were like Tim Burton loves the show Get a Life and he
wants to do, he wants to get back to his peewees big adventure routes and just work with on a small
budget with a, with a, with a comedian and have some fun. And Chris Elliott was like, amazing.
Well, we'll write this for Tim Burton. So they spent forever getting it into this C adventure with
all these big sets and the Bominable snowmans and everything, which is not their comfort zone.
Tim Burton drops out but felt bad about dropping out. So he goes, you should have Adam direct it.
And I'm like, I don't direct how I'm going to do this big budget action movie. And that shows,
you know, the movie is not well directed. But I do think it looks cool. It's got a nice energy to it.
It's very short and director is funny in it. And I just had a good time with it. I liked it.
And if you've never seen the film, do yourself a favor as David Letterman says in the film.
Watch it at least for the Letterman scene because the David Letterman cameo.
Amazing. The only time I've ever seen him in a movie. And he, it's one of the funniest four
minute scenes I've ever seen. Keeps calling Chris Elliott Jennifer. Yeah. Which is the weirdest name
you could pick. Like, you know, you'd think Sally Beverly is always in there. Yeah, Nancy or so
like, but Jennifer is such like a weird choice. Yeah. I mean, if you have no interest in this
film, I'm sure you can find that clip on YouTube. And it's incredible. I think the only time
Letterman's ever been in a movie, although he almost got the lead role and airplane, the Robert Hayes role.
Oh, yeah. Okay. Anyway, fun fact. Uh, sticking on the course of the first film I talked about,
I watched The Howling 2. Okay. I've seen one, but not the sequence. One is an interesting film. It's,
it's, you know, it's a cool flick. It's not Joe Tante's best work. And it's certainly not the best
wherewolf movie I've ever seen. But it's a solid horror flick. And it spawned a series of many
sequels. Obviously The Howling 2 stars Christopher Lee and was panned. People hated it. I thought
this thing was fucking great. I thought it was impeccably shot. The director did a lot of really
wonderful stuff with flash, flash cuts and edits and things and these weird inserts throughout the
entire film. The acting could use a kick in the pants. But the lead actor, the lead female actor
in it is quite good. And Christopher Lee is always as mesmerizing. Unfortunately, the head villainous
vampire is terrible. And the head male lead is really bad. But it's worth the price of admission
for Christopher Lee for some really fun practical effects for some good deaths. And it's just a
shot. It's very well shot. I don't know who depaid it, but whoever did knew what the fuck he was doing.
So go check out The Howling 2. Okay. How many Howlings are there? It's like seven. Oh wow.
Or nine or six. I don't know. Somewhere in there. I think we're up to three or four fucking how to
train your dragons. I think they think they think they would have learned how to train it by now.
Yeah, I love. I saw like a headline today like how to train your dragon three doesn't bring in the
bucks at the box office. It's like I didn't even know they were still making these fucking things.
No, I think think everybody's about done. It's like when a new ice age comes out. Yeah.
They're still making ice age movies. Romano as a squirrel or whatever. Dennis Lerius, like a
Mongoose. Yeah. Mongoose smoking cigarettes. Yeah. That's a good message for the kids.
Well, he's not really smoking cigarettes. Oh, I'm just saying like, you know,
it's a Mongoose with a tube. It's right. It's Dennis Lerius. Right.
I dusted off another old chestnut goes by the name of Splash.
Wow. Tom Hanks, Darrell Hanna, John Candy, Eugene Levy.
I remember this being one of those and I've mentioned a few of them lately on the show where like
when I was a kid, it's like holy shit, a movie with Eugene Levy, John Candy and Tom Hanks.
It's also rated PG and there's nudity in it quite a bit of nudity.
I just thought what a dream and I'd rent it fairly often and I'd always be like,
I didn't laugh much. I know it's a beloved classic. It was a huge hit.
Is it funnier now that we're older? No. It's very charming. I enjoyed every minute of it.
That's how I remembered it. You know, Hanks and his prime, there's almost nobody better in terms of
especially a guy who can handle the Romantic side and the funny side. There's very few better.
We don't get this anymore out of Hanks. That's classic annoyed Hanks.
There's a lot of like, come on Freddie. He's getting really wound up through the whole movie.
Yeah. Well, it's get that kind of Hanks anymore. You never get it. I thought it was going to be Lady
Killers and then he was playing Colonel Sanders when I went to see it. But like League of the
Hanks. Yes. And a true classic. John love its performance. Who will be coming up shortly on
the Cool Kids and was an unbelievably sweet man. I loved him and he was very, very funny. That's
good. I was doing his voice all week. He had a line that we've all been doing all week in the room
where he goes, he said a joke and then he goes, that's my little joke. And at every time I would
pitch him a joke, he goes, do you want me to do it as me? How do you want me to do it as your
Lord impression of me because I couldn't help but say the line in his voice with some actors take
as a line reading man. They don't appreciate it. But he was very cool about that. That's great.
I just was like, love it's it up, man. We're not looking. We want the hits. He's calling already,
right? Or you see him? Do you have you shot? Can you get him a message? No, we've shot it last week.
All right, worst week in my life. All right. Well, not because he's in one of my favorite
tales in the crypts ever. Oh, okay. I would have let him know. He was, you know, he hung around
one of the talk. He's a nice man. He's in an awesome tales to compare with John Aston about what
it told him a failing actor who gets cast in a rendition of Macbeth. He's really, it's a great episode.
And he's funny in it. And then it also he's also great in the dramatic portions. I love him in the
opening scene of happiness, some great dramatic work from John Love. It's the beginning of happiness.
Anyway, the hell was I talking about? Splash. And, you know, Ron Howard's second film,
after night shift, it was a huge hit. Lowell Gans and Bob Ballou Mandel wrote it who did a lot of
the best movies of the 80s and early 90s. A lot of them directed by Ron Howard, but they did
you know, parenthood and cities slickers. They wrote all kinds of like, you know, classic,
multiplicity, which doesn't get enough love. Anyway, Splash is charming. The romance is good.
Darryl Hannah is naked a lot, especially for PG. The hair doesn't cover the boobs as I thought it did.
They're pretty out there. And John Candy, okay, he's very funny in it. He plays a racket ball
while drinking from a can of beer. And then it's a great scene. He hits, he hits, and I watched this
when I watched the A &E biography of John Candy, which had footage from his funeral that was real
hard to watch. People just sobbing, but Candy, they've said in this biography that he did this in one
shot. They had cleared like half a day to do it. And they were like, yeah, you know, we'll probably need
about four hours till we get the shot right. And it's just John Candy, it's like, all right, I'm up.
I'm going to serve, drops the ball, hits it, it bounces off the wall straight back at him and hits him
in the head. And then he falls forward onto his face. So John Candy walks out actual beer. And he
had drank like 12 that morning, actual beer in his hand, hits the ball. It bounces directly back into
his head. He lands the pratfall perfectly. And then he was like, all right, let's go get drunk.
Because they had four hours for him to schedule. I mean, just a dream. Eugene Levy's, you know,
he's kind of annoying in it. He's got that old fro. The greatest line in comedy history and film
is in splash. The little boat? No. Jay O 'Cerson and I say it to this day and laugh hysterically.
Okay. But when she shows up naked at the Statue of Liberty, the tour guy goes, BOTCHY BALLS!
That, yeah, since I was six years old, like levels me. That was screenwriter Laulgan. Oh, I didn't know
that. That, that punchy bull. Yeah. And that's what always made me love the tour scene. And so I
married an expert. Incredibly, it was sort of a little nod to splash. That scene is incredible. And so
I'm very nice. I watched and I like hang on. Oh, sorry. Hang on. Because I was going to say my favorite
line, which is Tom Hanks is knees to knees with this old sailor like fat guy in a tiny little boat.
And they're out in the ocean. And it's like sputtering along or whatever than it dies. So John,
Tom Hanks is like, what's going on? What's going on? And he goes, I don't know. It looks like the
engine's broke. I'll be right back. So he jumps into the water and starts swimming. Tom Hanks is like,
you can't leave me here. The middle of the ocean. He goes, be right back. I'm going to get the little boat.
And then Tom Hanks looks around this tiny boat. He goes, the little boat!
Incredible. And that is the old frustrated Hanks that you don't see anymore.
The one thing that always bum me out about that movie as a kid was the entire movie is overcast.
There's a little gloomy. Yeah, there's not a sun -shiny shot that they're always down with that
dock with like, where the fish come in or anything like. It's a gloomy film. A lot of dock stuff. Yeah.
I saw a horror new war, but I'll tell you what, it's on. I want to watch that. I think we should
actually review it for the show. Right. It's an excellent documentary. We've never really done a
documentary. All right. We'll save that. And instead, I'm going to jump to a different documentary
that I watched. There's also about a 80s horror movie staying on theme.
Unearthed and untold, the path to pet cemetery. I think I've maybe talked about this.
I maybe have talked about this on the show. I don't know that there's enough here to
that we could review it. Right. Okay. horror noir, there's a lot to talk about. It's great, but I'm
and I want to talk about this pet cemetery documentary because I just rewatched it
and it's also going to lead us into screaming in. I, you know, look, it's a low budget,
though, no frills documentary. You're not getting any Stephen King interviews in this thing,
but you're getting interviews with basically everybody else that was in the movie from
the man they had to hire to play Zelda. Right. Because they needed somebody so skinny with literally
no shape to his body that they had to hire a guy and then put him in like this bone makeup.
Yeah. Which makes it even like that scene even stranger. You know what I mean? Right.
And, um, belief pet and Oswald sites that is the scariest scene in horror movie history.
It's the scariest thing I've ever seen in a movie in my life. I watched that. I watched pet cemetery
with my friend Brian Peck for a sleepover when we were about 10 or 11. My mom let me rent it.
That scene came on. We were white as ghosts. We were so fucking scared. And we made a vow to each
other that we would stay up all night because we were too scared to go to sleep. Yeah. And we would
keep all the lights on. And I kept up my end of the bargain. He fell asleep. Okay. I felt so betrayed
and I was so terrified. But anyway, you could have just stopped it. Well, no, it was after the movie.
It was like later tonight. Yeah. Anyway, it's a great doc. They interview everybody. They talk about
where Steve, the place where Stephen King wrote the book. Which was in a room that he rented in
like the local, you know, was that a Coke book for him? I know. Misery was his. It's like late 70s,
early 80s. It's way earlier King than I thought it was. I think Misery and Kujo are supposed to be
like his coakiest. And the shining was his alcoholiest, I think. But he was teaching at a college up in
Maine. They show you the real pet cemetery. It's based on they interview the lady who started the
pet cemetery that it's based on. Yeah. And she's like, I can't believe it. My little pet cemetery
became a book like. Right. It's a really cool little documentary. They talk about what it was
like on the set. Lots of love for Fred Gwyn. People can't say enough about this guy. Like everybody's
like, you just wanted to hug the guy. Yeah. Hey, y 'all on going up to that pet cemetery, are you? Yeah,
with the kitty cats and the dogs. No. Right. The famous line. Yeah. No, I remember. Can you do a main accent?
I got to go out. Not on that road. All right. That's pretty good. I feel more like I'm doing a Fred
Gwyn impression. Yeah. Kind of like your love. It's thing. It's not really that we're doing the accent
rapidly. We're doing the guy that does it. Right. I always do a Fred Gwyn when I'm dry. And it was
a vine of mine. Whatever I'm driving to Vegas, you see a sign that says this way towards ghost town
road. Right. So I always do it. And the vine I was in a rocking chair on a porch. I was rocking
back and forth. And I was like, you teens ain't going up that a ghost town road. Yeah. Last group of
teens went up a ghost town road. Didn't come back down. That was the whole bit like the guy at the
beginning of the cabin fever type film. Yeah, yeah, I got you. Congrats. By the way, getting joke of the
day on a. That was cool. I hadn't seen that punch. What was it? It wasn't punchline. It was some
comedy club. Funny bone. I believe it's a St. Louis comedy club. But if you played the funny
bone in St. Louis, I have not, but I've played other funny bones here. Let me let me do you the theme song
from when I was a little kid that they would play on the radio. It's it's awful. Here you go.
Funny bone comedy. Funny bone. It's a comedy club. Jesus. You like that?
Like with that that shitty like trombone voice where the guy's like, I gotta tell you, you're in
stiff comp when you're when to get the shittiest comedy club song. Yeah, it might have just taken
shittiest. It's real bad. I ever talked to this show about the store and their commercials called
Dirt Cheap in St. Louis. Yeah. It was this place and unfortunately it was before I drank, but it was
kind of like a precursor to Bevmountain. It's called Dirt Cheap and they had like clearly off the back
of a truck whiskey beer cigarettes, etc. But anyway, they did commercials from when I could remember
watching TV till when I left Missouri when I was 23 years old and it was this guy who looked like
he had been drinking the big like the tall Jack Daniels, like the the one that like kind of
waged your arm down and look like he had been having one of those every day since he was 16 years old
and he was about 60 or he might have been 30. No one had ever aged more than this man. He looked
terrible like his teeth were rotten. You can find these ads I believe on YouTube, but he's a terrible
looking man and he's the owner of Dirt Cheap Fond Funny and since then I'm being the commercials
and there was a chicken which was a man and like a stained chicken suit, the yellow with the orange
beak chicken suit. So it really showed the dirt and like that they hadn't had the suit cleaned.
So the chickens going around and then there would always be a big jugged woman like some sleazy
skank if you will not to judge in like a bikini or something. So then they'd be like dirt cheap.
So the chicken guy would go cheap cheap fun fun. That was kind of their hook.
Then the hideous man who owned it the hot woman would look at him and his face would be replaced by
like Fabio. Then it would come back to the ugly man which would actually make you jump. It was so
horrifying and he would go come on down to dirt cheap and remember like he was out of breath.
The more of our whiskey and beer she drinks, the better you look. So a pirate ran dirt cheap.
That's right. All right. You can find it online. It's the real deal. I'll look it up.
Back to pet cemetery on earth and untold you know folks you get it. It's a fucking documentary about
the movie. It's worth watching. You get to learn some fun stuff. I'm excited to get to scream
in and a second trailer for pet cemetery 2019 has been released and they have made some major changes
in this thing. Yeah. I don't know how I feel about it. Starting with this, what are the things they
say in the documentary that everybody sort of agreed upon and also Stephen King wrote the
screenplay for that adaptation? Yeah. Boy did I hijack your review by the way. I don't care. Tell
on a full story of my childhood. I kind of had nothing else to say. It's a fucking, you know,
it's a making up. Sure. You know, sure. Worth my time? Yeah. I think it's fun to watch. That's
why I said like it's not one we could really get a lot of discussion out of. They talk about two.
I've never seen two. I don't think they mentioned two. You hate two, right? It's dog shit.
How's Eddie Furlong in it? How's your Eddie Furlong? My Eddie's all right. I mean, he's as good as
you can be with this fucking material. He's like sure. It's dog shit. I mean, Clancy Brown's in it and
it still sucks. Yeah. It's a terrible movie. But anyway, so Stephen King wrote the screenplay
of the first film. Adapted from his own book, of course. So I thought, you know,
obviously he did a pretty good job of hitting the what's important of this script or this story
to get on the screen. This and one of the things they say in this documentary that I found fascinating
is they said what this story is really about is the secrets of men and how men destroy a family.
You know, so it could be a metaphor for adultery or addiction or whatever. But this concept of
the man of the house ruining his family because of his own ego and what. And I think that's
truly insightful, especially today. Sure.
Would I don't like have you seen the trailer or the newest trailer?
No, but I've heard it. It just tells the whole plot. Well, it tells the whole plot. But I've read
the book. Well, but here are the changes. Okay. Gage doesn't die. The daughter dies. Okay.
The wife is there the whole time. Okay. So those two things right off the bat, you're like, wait a
minute. What? Like so I get veering. Like if you're doing a remake of a shitty horror movie and
you want to veer off and do your own thing, great. You've got a beloved classic Stephen King
source material. Why are you riffing on it at a time when nobody can land a decent horror movie?
It's, look, I still want to see it. I'm still intrigued. But I just don't know how I feel about this
because the wife being there the whole time. There's a scene where the dead daughter, the zombie
daughter walks up and he goes hug your daughter and the wife is terrified. You know, like
the whole point of the wife going away is so the husband can execute this horrible deed of
burying their dead child in this Mac Mac, whatever the fuck it's called burial ground. Yeah.
Now she's just there or she comes home. I mean, maybe, maybe this, look, maybe the footage in
the trailer is that it's when she first comes home and then she gets killed like it is in the book.
Maybe that's all it is. I don't know. I'm a little perplexed by the choice to kill the
daughter instead of the son because it sort of ruins to me the concept of from the original story
which is the daughter being terrified of death and not understanding it and then having to learn how
to understand it through her own little brother dying. Right. Now, maybe that's just next out of this
thing completely. I don't know. There also seems to be this new element of a child cult
where they all wear these animal masks and it seems, it seems a little stretch to me. It just
doesn't seem very plausible. To me, what's so scary about the original is it is supposed to be this
place of purity for children to find closure with their dead pets and then when you go
past that place, there's a soil, there's a spoiled ground where evil lives and when you got kids
dressing up in these like paper mache bunny rabbit masks going out to bury, it's just odd. And it's
not something that I believe kids would do ever. Now or then or any at any point, it just doesn't seem
believable to me. And then last but not least, and I hate to criticize the man, I'm sure he'll bring
the emotional weight to the part it needs. But Lithgow said in an interview, he was questioned about
why would you not do the main accent. And instead of just saying, because then it's going to sound
like I'm doing a Fred Gwynn impression. Right. And I had to change something. Right. Lithgow goes,
you know, we just felt that when you try to do that accident, it sounds put on. And it's not
necessary. It's like, are you taking a shot at the Fred Gwynn? Did you? What are you doing? Uh -huh.
Now I will say, I think I read in Entertainment Weekly or some shit
that Lithgow did say I didn't want to do an impression of Fred Gwynn, maybe two different interviews.
But I think he was given his props. I love Lithgow. I don't think we need to take him down.
I'm not trying to take him down. But he did say this thing. And he said he did two reads,
one with it and one without. And they decided to go without. But look, I'm intrigued. I dare I say,
I'm still excited to see it. Maybe they made these weird changes and it works. Right. And it's
this awesome new alternate version of PET cemetery. I mean, it's like debut directors,
right? I think it's the guys who did starry eyes, which I never saw. But I heard was a really good
horror movie. I don't, uh, I believe it's the, isn't it the producers from it? Yeah, but I think
the director is the guy that did the starry eyes. So my fear is, is that it's going to be another
it's an area where it's like, you take this really dark, deep material and then you kind of
reduce it to like a fun, jump scary thing and then you don't give a shit. Let me go ahead and
give you what a 100 % guarantee that's what it's going to be because they don't look at the box
office of it. Green light, PET cemetery and say, do something different with it. They're going to
want the exact same shit. Apparently it to is three hours long. And actually, I was kind of like,
okay, good. Maybe they're going to do it justice. And they're like, no, we're going to cut an hour out
of it. Get it down a size, uh, you know, Bill haters in it. I like the, you know, I, I like the
kids side almost as much as I like the adult side, but I don't have the highest of hopes for it too.
Because it's the same team as it one and it won. Folks was not good. I look forward to seeing it.
So I'll be their opening night. In the way that I looked forward to seeing kill Bill too.
I don't know. I don't know. I remember seeing kill Bill one and thinking, okay, that's pretty cool.
Are you kidding me? I don't love kill Bill one. I love kill Bill two.
Well, I certainly agree with you there. Well, I agree with you that I love kill Bill two, but
I saw one. A. I had had a picture of sangria with my dear friend Sarah Pontear. How you doing, Sarah?
Uh, I went into this thing drunk as fuck. It was like 90 minutes long. I just thought it was so fucking
awesome. And if it hadn't been the midnight show, I would have gone in and seen it again. But then
two, of course, I'm much deeper, more awesome experience. Who's the Tarantino movie?
Two is an amazing movie. The first one is the Grindhouse movie. The first one is so it's so cool.
Listen, it's it looks incredible. The music's incredible. The fighting is incredible. I am not saying
kill Bill is on the same level as it. I'm saying like, I like to kill Bill just fine. But when I
went in, what I wanted was not what I got completely. And I left going, all right, man, that was,
you know, I'd see it again. And then when I saw the second one, suddenly the quality of the first
one jumped up immensely for me. Right. So I hope that that happens with it too. I hope that
I see that. And I go, here's the depth that I was looking for in the first one. And now this makes
the first one kind of a fun, just a little intro. What I'm thrown by is why they they threatened
or not threatened. They they promised they were coming out with this kill Bill, the complete,
the whole bloody affair. Like it's a cut that Tarantino did himself. That's like the whole movie
edit or both movies edited into one thing with additional scenes. And it's like a four hour
the entire kill Bill epic. And Tarantino apparently edited this thing and it was rumored
to be coming out and never did. Maybe that's tied up with the Weinstein shit because it's
you know, Weinstein and him were pretty tight. Tarantino. I'm dying. I see I want this. I want
to be able to watch this right now. Tarantino promises things that are heartbreaking when he doesn't
deliver on. Yeah. Remember when he said his next movie was going to be the Vega Brothers? I do.
He was going to be mad sitting in trouble. I was like holy shit. Yeah. And then he never he just
never did it. You're like, he probably wrote it and it wasn't up to snob for something. But
let's get to our movie of the day. We haven't even announced what the fuck it is yet. A little shop
of horrors. I mean, it's mainly we're going to talk about the the 80s version I assume. I've seen both
of you. I have seen both. We can kind of cover both here. Yeah. I mean, I find the original. I don't
know a great deal. I know a lot about Roger Corman, the man and the career. But I haven't actually
seen many of his movies. But the original will show up. Horrors is pretty fun. Jack Nicholson plays
the sick dental patient that Bill Murray plays in the Frank Oz 1986 version that we are discussing.
And it's okay. You know, it's cheap. It should be looking. But it's got its charm. I think it's considered
one of the Corman classics, right? That would be on any one of your Corman box sets or whatever.
For sure. It's got it. It's got its charm. It's weird. I saw the I saw the newer one first and
wasn't thrilled that it was a musical when I was seeing that. I remember showing it to my cousin Dominic
and he was all excited to see it. And I was like, yeah, it's a fun movie. And then we were watching it. And
he goes, damn it. Why didn't you tell me it was a sing along. And I was like, you mean musical
sing along. But then when I remember, I was like, yeah, I kind of was disappointed by that too, man.
I'm not thrilled that it's musical. But then I went back and want, but then I learned that the
remake was an adaptation of the stage, the Broadway show, right? And then my mom was like, you know,
there's an old movie called Little Shop of Horrors. And I rented that and she even told me Jack
Nicholson plays that Bill Murray part. And then when I watched that, I missed the sing along.
Sure. It didn't seem right anymore. So it was not that enjoyable, as if I can remember. But
yeah. But I don't know. I haven't seen it in years. But the remake I still I find enjoyable. You
know, we can start with the best performances in the film. Well, hey, I'm going to say I don't like
your tone. Why? Because it sounds very dismissive of what I consider one of the best movie musicals
of all time or sing alongs, if you will. It very well may be. Like for me, we're talking top three
easy. Very well, maybe I'm not a big musicals guy. It's a wonderful comedy. It's the songs are
awesome. And I remember every note of them, which like, you know, you want to talk about Mary Poppins
returns. As the movie was playing, I was forgetting each song as it played. Like there was no hooks
to anything. Little shop of horizontal hooks. It's Howard Ashman. And Tim Rice, I might be wrong. I
was wrong last week. I kept saying Bernard Herman instead of Edward Herman. Bernard Herman is the
composer for Hitchcock. Edward Herman is the dad in the lost boys or the guy should be in
Wises dating in the lost boys correction. But yeah, the songs and this thing are incredible. They're
like 60s do up songs. You got the girl group stuff with the shantels, I believe, including
Tishina Arnold from Martin. Yeah, Tisha Campbell's in there. Tisha Campbell. I just for me, this was
everybody I loved in 80s film. And they're all at their best. I mean, this is my favorite Rick
Moranis performance by far as Seymour. The song suddenly Seymour is a fucking banger. Ellen Green,
who I like that song. Let me get that in. I don't like that song. I think it's one of my favorite
songs of all musical history. And I am a bit of a student. Ellen Green almost never acted again.
She's incredible. She's the only person they brought over from the Broadway show. Where's she
been? What happened to her? I think she was on like pushing days. That's right, pushing daysies.
But obviously she didn't have like a conventional Hollywood look is probably what herter. But
she's awesome in this movie. Steve Martin is so good, should have been nominated, so funny as the dentist.
And you know, it's one of his few performances where he really inhabits a character and like blows
it out. A lot of times he's kind of just like Steve Martin or, you know, in the early days, the dumb guy.
But he's awesome in that character and like really menacing and scary. And his song dentist,
another classic. I like that song. John Candy has a cameo. He's hilarious as the very weird,
the weird radio guy. Yeah, he's great. You got Jim Belushi coming in for a pointless cameo and
he's fine. You got Christopher Guest who's hilarious in a very tiny early role from him. The movie is
directed by Frank Oz, one of the most underrated comedy directors of all time, also the voice of Yoda,
Miss Piggy, etc. I love, I love that Frank Oz director. Look, it's a spectacularly crafted film.
I'm just not a huge musicals guy, but that doesn't mean it by any stretch. It's a bad movie.
It was written by Elliott Miles Goodman who wrote dirty rotten scoundrels. Great movie. No, I'm
sorry. He's best remembered for his frequent collaboration with film director Frank Oz for whom Goodman
scored such films as dirty rotten scoundrels. What about Bob? House sitter. For his score to Oz's
little shop of horror, Goodman was nominated for a Golden Globe for best original score. Songs were
written by Howard Ashman, both of these men are dead. Ashman died young. He's from complications of
AIDS at 40 point. That's correct. That's a shame because he was he was hit in fucking grand slams.
Is it Ashman and Tim Rice? Just as Ashman. I mean, Ashman also did like little mermaid and stuff.
He did lit. Yeah, he's he collaborated with rice for Disney stuff. Okay, but not a little mermaid
beauty in the beast Aladdin. Jesus Christ. Yeah, those are some fucking hits. What the fuck, dude?
That is, dude, 89 mermaid 91 beauty in the beast, 92 Aladdin. It's pretty impressive.
He he created the off -broadway musical version of The Cormin Show. Okay, so this this film was based on
that. It seems like that's mainly what he did. And then he wrote some songs with this with this
rice character. Well, the only new song in Little Shop of Horrors that wasn't in the musical on Broadway
is Mean Green Mother from Outer Space. I like that song, which was nominated for best song. That
would be one of my least favorite songs of the soundtrack. Of course, because you've got to be
difficult. You've got to disagree with me. I used to mow a lot of lawns listening to that soundtrack,
but you got to shout out Levi Stubz, the lead singer or at least one of the lead singers of the four
tops, who voices Audrey too, and just a perfect fucking choice. Not even like a big name choice,
like they probably could have gone with Prince or Little Richard or something. Little Richard
would have been great too. But it's just the perfect voice for it, feed me, see more, etc. I don't
know. If you've never seen it, I highly recommend. And when I was a kid, there were a few movies I
loved more than Little Shop of Horrors. And it does make you miss Moranis. I mean, what a treat,
what a delight. I miss him, although, you know, I think he'd be, I've seen him recently, like he,
he went on today's show with like some cowboy songs he had written, like wearing a cowboy hat.
It's all he does now. He just does these music albums. And, you know, it certainly didn't make me
feel good. I'll tell you that. They were comedy songs, right? Yeah. Yeah. He had one,
but like gentle comedy. Yeah. Yeah. He had like a bar mitzvah one or something. Yeah. Like,
there was like, he does like these theme comedy genre albums. Right. What can you do?
Go see Little Shop of Horrors. Go see everything we talked about. We didn't talk about one bad
thing today. And check out that pet cemetery trailer. I'm sure most of the hellians have already.
Let us know in the Facebook group what your thoughts are on these changes. I'd love to know.
Coming up in future episodes will do hard noir. We are going to do the Hills Have Eyes remake.
And, you know, some of their bold shit. Oh, well, you're going to watch the Spiria.
Oh, yes. The Spiria also is coming up. I think we're going to have a real nice conversation about
the Spiria. I got to get that from you. Yeah. Oh, yeah. You're right. I'll bring it over.
Let me add it, though, because I'm making a list here of stuff we're supposed to cover.
That's our show, Joderosa Comedy on Instagram.
When's this come out? Monday. So March 29th and 30th, bonkers comedy presents me
at Topgolf in Las Vegas. Two shows one per night. Is that like one of those indoor golf places?
I think there's like indoor driving ranges and shit in there. But I'll be there. There's a chance
Paddy Walsh might be there. Yeah, I look indoor golf. Who knows? I mean, I'm not saying if you come,
we got to hang out at the golf place all night. We can go gamble. I was saying like,
it sounded like you were saying I was coming to see you, but I was saying, yeah, I might be out there.
I like indoor golf. Oh, I see. I get it. Little slam. Now I get it. My next short story premieres in
the March, April issue of Penthouse. It is called Menu Change. Look for it on stands.
Also Penthouse .com is now live and you can read my past articles, my op -ed pieces that I wrote
for them. I don't know how many are up there, but a bunch are up there. So check that out. And also
uninformed podcast with Bill Burm myself at patreon .com slash burrow. Thank you very much.
Folks, I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram. Cool kids. There's on Friday night,
starting, well, actually the previous Friday if we're airing on Monday. We're doing like a run of
eight new ones in a row. So be sure to check them out. Great run coming up. Also on Hulu. And check out
our fantastic Instagram page. See you in hell pod, right? Yes. Run by Emily Florence at Emily Florence.
That's probably not right. I follow her, but I guess you could look. But anyway,
on the Etsy page, it's Hog House. It's the Hog House shop or store. The Hog House. Boy,
we should really know this stuff better, right? Well, I know I knew the Instagram. You dropped the
one on that. No, I said it's see you in hell pod, right? Yeah. Yeah, it is. See you in hell pod.
And then let me just confirm Emily's because she handles all the Emily DE Florence. Emily DE Florence.
Emily DE Florence. Okay. And thanks to, and I do follow you. I just don't always know what you're
doing. Thanks to Joe Tilly for the, uh, Frazier mock up. That was awesome. It was disturbing. And it was awesome.
It's awesome. Mine, I look as if I look like the hills have eyes in that, in that thing. I mean,
I don't look much better. But, uh, yeah, it's, it's a lot of great fun posts, audio clips, uh, fan art,
which we always are just blown away that even exists. Uh, check it out. The Hog House page on Etsy is
where you find the merch. And, uh, if you want to listen to the Patreon, go sign up. Joe, what's
that address? Because the Patreon, uh, you know, especially with the Oscars coming up, we did a
pretty in depth. And I think very funny like one of our best episodes. I think the discussion of
the Oscar films. I believe the Patreon is patreon .com slash W S Y I H. And it might have the word
podcast on it. Jesus Christ. I mean, I don't know. Now we need to look it out. This is if you just,
if you Google, you will see you and how in Patreon, it'll come up. But hold on. Oh, look, oh, look.
Now you have to. Okay. Okay. Down for maintenance. Thanks, Patreon. Wow. Yeah, they really are
down for maintenance, aren't they? All right. We can't tell you. But if you Google it, you will find it.
Thank you for listening. Thank you for all your support and love. Have a good week. Bye.
You