I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's, we'll see you in hell, and by you, we mean you specifically, you guilty
dirty bitch.
Guilty?
From Joe.
Because you'll go to hell, get it?
Oh, okay, yeah.
From bitch, I meant, it is in a non -binary sense, applicable to all genders.
Sure, no, I know.
Yeah, it's a little odd today, I don't get to see Joe, I just see an old picture, at
least 10 years old photo of Joe that he uses to represent himself.
First of all, I don't think I picked that photo for Zoom, I think Zoom just somehow
finds a photo.
Are you sure that Zoom just scrolls the internet for a photo of you and uses it?
Disturbing, yeah, I've got my laptop, I got this MacBook Pro, it's a great computer, this
new one, but I hooked it into a monitor, see the beauty of the laptop is, is you can, some
of the laptops, is you can get a laptop and then still have it as a desktop.
You can get an affordable monitor, and I already had a wireless keyboard and wireless mouse
and I thought, well, instead of a big old desktop, why don't I get a really nice laptop
and then I can configure it into a desktop, which I've done, it's great, but I still need
to get a webcam for the desktop so I can still use the camera part, everything else works
like a charm though.
Now, are you getting a little like circle, one of those webcams from the early days of
jerking off online?
Yeah, I was thinking about something like that, you know, either that or I'm going to
go if you ever do like a cam, get in one of those weird like adult friend finder type
rooms or whatever it is online.
Yeah, online.
That was all they had web.
Yeah, I know, I didn't I never did jack on cam on the internet.
Yeah, I mean, I might have on Zoom during the pandemic with somebody, but not like one
of those public things and then and I never did sex chats.
I've done sexting on the phone, but I never did like the.
You know, you go into the chat room and you go, hey, ASL, age, sex location.
Oh, is that well, clearly you've done it because, you know, you're the shorthand.
I don't know.
No, I did.
I remember a buddy of mine when we were like 11, 12 or something, he was showing me some
chat room and he'd get on his screen name was I'm packing 69 and yeah, he'd get on there
and talk to people and then, you know, presumably jerk off for what I'm sure were
beautiful young women on the other side of the country and not creepy old men in the
basement as their family slept upstairs.
Yeah, yeah, that's, that's a little odd.
That's a little odd.
So much went on back in those days, those early Hallison days of the internet.
Is that the first time I've ever said that word, Hallison, you ever heard it?
I'm sure I'm pronouncing it wrong.
Halla con Halla con.
It must be Halla con Halliburton.
No, you mean Halle Berry.
I meant Halle Berry.
Yes.
No, I meant Halle con, which is where everyone goes every June and celebrates the films of
Halle Berry by dressing up as her different characters.
Yeah.
Actually, when you look at it, it's a very problematic festival.
There's a lot of people in blackface.
I thought you were going to say a lot of people doing monsters ball, just laying on
a couch and being like, just give it to me, daddy, give it to me, wild, wild Halle
Berry at her hottest with Billy Bob at his most bad Santa.
Yeah.
Like, you know, it just crazy that scene.
But I had a feeling watching that now would be such a laugh riot.
It was, everyone was like, this is important filmmaking, whatever.
But even at the time I was like, this is nuts.
Wasn't even remember the plot of it.
He's just a guy who's racist and he falls in love with the hottest black woman alive.
Yeah.
Is that what it is?
Yeah, that's, uh, I think that's pretty much it.
Okay.
Halle con or Halcyon is a period of calm during the winter.
Or so you would, you would say like, oh, and my Halcyon days of youth, like I had
no problems, baby.
So I was using it.
I still don't know what the fuck you're talking about, but, uh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I've lost my mind.
Who's referring to their use as youth as the quiet days of winter.
What are you talking about?
No, like you, they, like authors use it.
These were the Halcyon days.
Uh, sure.
And it, and it basically means these were the good times before the bad shit began.
So that's like the worst time of the year to me.
Yeah.
Cold days of winter.
Boys is summer.
Now we're talking and raising Arizona.
Don Henley saw, saw a dead head sticker on a Cadillac.
I guess that's a good lyric, but then it's like, Don, you have a hundred million
dollars.
I hate when people do that shit.
What do what?
Say a memory.
No, like this, the criticism of capitalism when you're a hundred million air, you
know what I mean?
Is that, oh, I didn't realize it was that was, I thought he was just being like,
when I was a kid, this reminds me of the summer when I used to see dead stickers
everywhere.
Oh, okay.
Now he's saying, I saw, can you believe that this whole free love movement that
the grateful dead had, and now it's being used on a Cadillac and then Don Henley's
like disgusted as he gets into his Lamborghini with the door that goes
straight up into the air, you know?
It's like one of my favorite lyrics.
And I think I even mentioned this on the show is Elvis Costello, the other side
of summer, wasn't it a millionaire who said, imagine no possessions, a great
line.
What is the obsession with old rock stars using summer as like the, to
criticize the other musicians?
Cause both of those songs have summer in the title and both of them are used to,
or part of them are used at least to criticize other, uh, you know, I don't
know that Henley's criticizing the dead necessarily, but no, he's actually not
criticizing the dead.
He's criticizing the people who took their movement and, and, uh, pretend
that they're all about the grateful dead lifestyle, but they're driving around
in a Cadillac.
It's a great, I mean, it's a, it, Don Henley's kind of a Jaguist, but it is,
it is a great lyric because it's, uh, I mean, there was nothing worse than when,
um, well, there's of course been worse things, but in this department, there was
nothing worse than when Al Gore would talk about how much he loved the dead as
Tipper Gore was leading the charge of the PMRC.
It's like, Oh my God, fuck off, man.
Like, you know, that's why I'm really gross.
I keep railing against, and nobody wants to get on board with me.
It's not, I'm not really against him.
I'm really against the use of his music, but I keep saying this man, like old
late era David Byrd music to me is the sound of the aging, rich, out of touch
liberal, like that's what it sounds like to me.
I wish it wasn't true, but I hate most of his new stuff too.
Yeah.
And it's, you know, I know, you know, did I tell
you the whole band from his show came down to my bar?
Really?
Not the whole band, but a lot of the female members of the band are friends
with my Bart, one of my bartenders and they came down to the bar.
We all hung out.
They were very, very nice.
Oh, that's awesome.
I mean, that's as a, as I have said, a truly amazing show and the
band is a huge part of it.
Yeah.
I should go see it.
It's really great.
But, and then, you know, he does too many of his, uh, modern works, but they given
this new arrangement, they're still fun.
They don't hold, hold a candle to the others, but you know, you knew that going in.
Um, speaking of musicals, Christ has crossed that.
Sorry, before we go, I need before we had too many conversations started.
My brain is diseased.
You want to talk musicals and we'll get back to that.
But then have you heard the Atari's version of boys of summer, the punk
cover, where they change it to a black flag sticker on a Cadillac.
That's the other thing I hate when people do a cover and they change the
lyrics to apply to their life.
Yeah.
It bugs me.
That's fair.
I don't write music.
Sorry.
I saw them at the warp, which is the warped.
Yeah.
What was I doing there?
Which is why, when I did my cover of fuck the police, my fame cover,
yeah, all N words left in, it didn't change it.
In fact, in fact, rage did do that.
I'm making a joke, but rage did that.
When rage did their cover, their, that shitty renegades of funk record, they
did, it was all rap covers left all the ends right in really, which yeah, which
at the time I was, I was like, and I only judge it by the time at the time it was
like, no, he's like paying tribute to these songs.
Now you'd get like crucified if you did that, you know, Ben folds, did a, a very,
it's funny, it's catchy cover of bitches.
Ain't shit.
And nothing worse than that.
I mean, I, it would put my teeth on edge now, but at the time I liked it, but he
had some guy come in and do the N word parts, but it was white British guy.
Oh boy.
It's like, no, it still means the same thing over there.
It's not like, uh, cigarette and, and the F slur.
Yeah.
It's not like cunt where it's like, it's different for us.
Love or Fanny, you know, that's really, we're talking about the beef, man.
Uh, I was watching outtakes of season three of afterlife, the Ricky Gervais
show.
Oh, okay.
Did I do my review of the season three yet?
Yeah, either of us did.
I watched each of those seasons.
I watched the entire season and one evening and thought, no, that was fine
and moved on with my life, but I always watch it.
Season three was, was a little, um, it was just too much more of the same.
I enjoyed moments, but him sitting down at the end of every episode to watch
the video of the dead wife.
It's like, okay, Ricky.
Okay.
And then this was part of your pitch.
When you first pitched it, we're 20 episodes deep.
We know you miss your wife, buddy.
And the fact that it ends, the whole series ends with him becoming
like a philanthropist.
Like if you start giving everybody money and he saves the town and then it's him
walking away, fading away, like it's like, all right, Ricky, take it.
He's a little self -indulgent and then they all, he always picks the most
expensive overuse song in the world to play over the credits.
So like it ends as like, he's like w looking up at the sky and you see a
rocket and then it's like, oh, rock it.
Which is the most obvious choice or like four ended with paradise city.
Yeah.
It didn't even make sense.
I'll see you guys later.
I'm, I'm heading over to, uh, California.
I'll probably stay in a hotel over there.
Henley again.
Um, but anyway, the season three outtakes are some of the funniest
outtakes I've ever seen.
And when you see the show and then see the outtakes, you're like, you're
watching two different shows.
You can't believe these outtakes.
And just how maudlin the actual show is you mean?
Yeah.
The outtakes are outrageous.
So the, the, but he's got that guy that plays like the disgusting guy.
Yeah.
Uh, with like the mullet and the thick glasses, it looks like a pedo.
Right.
Yes.
First outtake is him talking to the secretary in the office.
And he goes, want to hear a joke love.
And she's like, yeah.
And he goes, why did the two gypsies cross the road?
Or no, no, no.
He goes, why did the chicken cross the road?
And she goes, I don't know why.
And he goes to get away from the stink of the two gypsies,
fucking my ex -wife.
And the lady goes, it's not even a joke and it's racist.
And he goes, how's it racist?
And she goes, you're saying the gypsy smell.
And he goes, no, the smell was coming from her.
Right.
That's great.
That's classic old office.
I mean, he's been using that, that bit forever, but it's always very fun.
Cuts back to the same guy later.
And he goes, he goes, my wife said, if, if God wanted me minge to smell good,
then why'd she put it next to me?
Asshole.
It's, it's crazy.
Meanwhile, none of these jokes get into the show because they're laughing so hard.
And you see this in the outtakes.
They have to stop doing them.
You're like, I can't get through this.
Like there are outtakes where, like from Derek, the show he did before,
it's where Ricky Gervais is with that same guy.
And he's literally like, oh, fuck off.
And he just, he's like, I'm out of here.
Just shoot it around me.
I can't stay in the room.
I'm laughing too much.
And then you see the final thing and you're like, you're like, oh man, they
cut all the funny shit out because they were fucking laughing through all of it.
They had to like tone it down.
Well, and also it's that people don't like laughter anymore.
It's like, it's a, there's a, there's an error when you're on a TV set
sometimes where like, if, if it's fun and if you got good people where
everybody's laughing and crapping at cracking up and improvising and
fun and something, and then like the director will go, all right, everybody
calm down, stop laughing style.
Everybody calm down, quiet, quiet.
We're going to shoot a comedy scene now.
And then the entire like joyous, fun attitude is gone.
It makes no sense.
And that's why things suck, you know, one of many reasons.
I just rewatched his, um, humanity special, the one he did in 2018.
And, um, it's a good standup special.
I think it's really funny.
It gets a little too into like Twitter for the second half of it.
Oh yeah.
What's more just like him talking about like tweets, people wrote him
and him responding and whatever.
He's got a bit of the Chappelle issue of like, you're, you've got a brilliant
mind, stop using it to, to shoot back at your fans because now you
have the ultimate platform.
Like we, you've already beat them by a billion percent, write some comedy
that's not responding to these idiots.
Yeah, no, I agree.
I agree.
Oh, so wait.
I was going to talk the musical musical.
Oh yeah.
The subway stop.
So the subway stops in New York.
A lot of them now have these, um, screens on them.
Okay.
Because that's what New York needs is they strive to take away outdoor dining
from everybody that tried to stay in this city and contribute back to the
economy because some fucking prick once his bike lane open.
Oh, now they're taking it back.
You can't do it.
There's a big, that's a whole thing.
But yeah, but no, you know, instead of, so instead of a bailout,
the confidence of just being like, well, it's over, you know, hopefully
it is, and it may well be on the way out, but just the fact that they
would remove all of it, knowing that the pandemic is still going on.
It could come back is so short -sighted and stupid.
It's, it's, it's insane.
And it's just, don't get me started.
But my point is instead of, you know, Hey, give a financial break to the
people that tried to help contribute to this economy.
Yeah.
Put video screens on the subway stops.
Cause that's what we need.
Anyway.
And what do they do?
What do they say?
They just play clips of things.
Like it's usually like, yeah, it's mostly ads.
Like the ads and cabs that you get.
Yeah, basically.
But the one near my apartment that I have to walk by every day.
The main clip on this thing is from tick tick boom.
So I saw it once a day.
I'm walking by the subway stop and I got a look at Andrew Garfield being
like, with that other person, the lady singing with it, it's the most
obnoxious white bread theater geek fucking thing I've ever experienced.
And I was a minor in theater.
I've experienced a lot of that in my life, but Jesus Christ.
I want to throw a coffee at it, man.
It drives me crazy.
That's the movie too.
I mean, he is a theater kid, Garfield playing a theater kid.
And it, it's a lot.
It's a lot.
I, I, I've never seen a movie like it.
And I sometimes that's enough for me to go, okay, I'll give you a little
respect, but it's, it's not a great film.
I did read a headline the other day set that said, um, I'm pretty sure
this is verbatim, uh, Andrew Garfield talks about his tick tick boom of a year.
What, if you're not going to pay writers anymore, that's what you're
going to get is, is headlines like that.
Like that, it wasn't a good year.
So was it a bad year?
It sounds hard.
I don't even know what you mean.
I saw one today that, uh, I almost just called you and just canceled the podcast.
Cause I was like, I'm just going to actually kill myself.
All right.
Here it is.
I'm listening.
How Reese Witherspoon overcame the best actress curse to build
a $900 million empire.
Oh Christ sakes.
The, the curse of winning best actress.
What, what in God's name are you talking about?
As though, as the world literally burns every, I just love the,
the victimization of anything.
Yeah.
You have to make everybody an underdog Reese Witherspoon.
Are you fucking insane?
And it's been a millionaire since she was 14.
You have to make her Rocky now.
Oh my God.
It's unbelievable.
Everyone is a, is a victim.
An underdog came up by their bootstraps, whatever.
It's just so fucking stupid.
Whatever happened to the Allie sheeties of the world, you know, just walking away
from the biz, showing up 20 years later and a talk show looking like they haven't
had their coffee yet.
I miss that.
I miss the people that just, you know, that were like, ah, go fuck yourselves.
You know?
Well, that's only can go a sad way too.
I mean, I don't know if you read that Shelley Deval profile, but is there
a new one?
You mean the one where she just had lost her mind and left the business and lives
on a farm with alpacas or something.
There's a, there's actually a bright light at the end of that tunnel.
They, somebody did a follow -up story because they felt that she was not done
justice by Dr. Phil and that it was, you know, yeah.
Oh, I know.
I read the story and I saw the Dr. Phil.
I like to hear that she's still a pillar in her community and everybody likes her.
It's not like she doesn't have lucid moments or doesn't live a normal life
and still is married.
And I was like, this is nowhere near as bad as it seemed like it was.
It's still not great, but you know, I don't know.
I just feel like there was some hope there with, with her, with her shit.
It's, uh, you know, these, and they're, they're dudes for the most part, these
big, powerful dudes, uh, that, you know, like Kubrick doesn't have a Polanski
issue on his record or anything, but driving a woman completely insane to
get a good performance out of her as an insane person seems like something that
people should take more of an issue with, with regards to Stanley Kubrick.
Yeah.
I will say this though.
I did watch a recent episode of fairy tale theater, which was her kid show.
I remember it well.
She starred in the Rumpelstiltskin episode, which was one I was loved as a kid.
Yeah.
And, uh, which, uh, if they ever redo Rumpelstiltskin, he'll be played by the rock.
And it'll be Rockle Stiltskin.
Yeah.
Uh, but anyway, um, and, uh, she goes, uh, she introduces the story and then she's
like, can I, I'm playing the princess in this, whatever the fuck it is.
Yeah.
And then, uh, or the Miller's daughter.
And then it gets to, uh, it gets into the story and they're like, the Miller's
daughter, she's the most beautiful woman in all the land.
And I'm looking at Shelley Duvall, like, uh, she's beautiful lady, but the balls,
the ego, you saw the script and you cast yourself in this part.
Yeah.
I mean, that has been doing that for forever.
You know, like the, like, I'll write a movie where I play like the hottest guy
on earth who can't stop falling into vaginas.
Uh, there's a bit about that.
Holy shit.
In the new, uh, I know you didn't see it, but in the new, uh, Louis CK
special about goodwill hunting.
Okay.
About Matt Damon, Timely, Timely, Matt Damon and Ben Affleck writing
the scripts and Matt Damon being like, now he's a cool, I'm going to butcher
this, but he's like, no, he's a cool character.
He's a genius.
He doesn't, he doesn't feel like being a genius.
Hottest chick comes in the town.
She's totally in love with him.
It's really funny that like this guy wrote this for himself.
Uh, I never quite stepped back from it and was like, oh yeah, that's a good
point, like you really just threw yourself into the role anyway.
All right.
Uh, address any of his stuff and stand up.
He's addressed it a zillion times.
None of it's ever good enough for anybody, you know, I don't
mean, did he apologize?
I just mean,
talked about it in the last special.
He's like, you need to check in.
You need to his joke.
The joke he made about it was, was, uh, well, he made a few jokes about it, but
he, the joke, the funniest joke I thought was he said he can't, his opening joke
was when he comes out, he goes, not the last one, the one before he comes out
and he goes, so how's your last two years been big laugh, obviously.
He goes, anybody else get the same peewee bit when he came out and was
like, heard me get jokes lately.
Well, not really.
It's the exact same thing.
Oh, stop.
You just want to not like it.
The, uh, I look, let me finish this bit of personal Piccadillo's.
I've always been a fan.
Can I finish the bit?
Well, then he says, did anybody else get into global trouble?
He, Pat couldn't hear that because he unplugged the headphones by accident.
Man does not.
Oh boy.
Now he's looking at it.
Confused that can't figure out how to plug them headphones back in.
Cause they doesn't remember the port.
They came out of dear God Walsh.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
I just gave a blow by blow commentary to you unplugging the headphones.
Oh my God.
He still can't hear me.
He doesn't remember where they came out from.
Doesn't remember.
This every week.
Can't remember how this mic works.
Yeah.
Unplug your headphones.
What happened?
Oh Jesus.
We can all hear you, Pat.
He can't hear us.
Oh, this is gold.
This is gold.
Oh my God.
Beautiful.
Folks.
That is a, that is an all time low for Pat Walsh on this pocket.
I just gave a blow by blow that entire breakdown.
Couldn't figure out why his headphones weren't working.
Cause they unplugged.
Didn't realize the plug came out of the headphones itself.
Yeah.
And was plugging one, it had one of them to the headphones plugged into the mic.
It was trying to plug the other end into the computer.
It didn't understand why it wasn't working.
Wow.
It's early.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not a technical logical with it's just insane.
The word a man has run television shows.
Yeah.
This is what they're talking about.
When you hear the artists go and these idiots that run things, they mean Pat Walsh.
Uh, a creative mind is, is rarely a technical mind, you know?
Um, anyway, he says, anybody else get into global trouble?
And then he says, Oh, sorry.
What's your, did anybody else get in the room, get into global trouble, which is
funny, uh, but then, uh, but then the joke joke is he talks about it later.
And he says, I have, the lesson I learned is that even though it seems like somebody
is okay with something sexually, you have to keep checking in because even if it
looks like they're having a good time, they might not be for instance, Pat,
what are you doing with the mic?
I'm taking it out so I don't have to deal with him.
All right.
Uh, cause even though it looks, did you hear the setup or do I got to tell
them?
No, I heard it.
Okay.
Because even though it looks like somebody's having a good time or
appears to be having a good time, they might not be.
It's kind of like a slave spiritual.
If you heard that, you would say they're having a great time out there.
They're all singing, but there are nobody's having fun.
They don't like it.
It's a funny joke.
It's a very interesting in the, uh, in the defense of, uh, sexual misconduct.
I knew you were going to say this.
Oh, so predictable.
You bring slavery.
It's just kind of like interesting, you know?
Well, you know, he gave a full formal apology that everybody crucified him over.
I I'm so past Louis CK.
I don't care.
I think the man is a, is a funny comedian.
I, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not this man you're painting me to be.
I'll paint you all to be out there.
You, you Hollywood libs.
I mean, you libtards done his time.
How much does he make off the, uh, off the specials?
I mean, is he.
I know he's out for shoots him and sells them himself.
So, and at what?
Five bucks a piece and he sells probably a million of them.
Probably.
Yeah, I would think so.
I mean, that's, that's the other side of this that that always cracks me up
is like people are like, oh yeah, cancel culture.
Sure.
Um, Chappelle and CK are still doing, and it's like they're gazillionaires.
Right.
That's like saying, look at Elon Musk.
He's not canceled yet.
You can't cancel a gazillionaire, an average person.
You can cancel them.
And in this sense of cancellation, Roseanne is an average person.
You know what I mean?
Like, like somebody like that could go away.
Norm MacDonald could have gone away.
If all this stuff that they brought up after norm died, came out when he was
alive, that would have been a rap on Norm MacDonald.
The guy lives in a two bedroom apartment.
He did not have Louie money to go.
You know what I'm saying?
Right.
Well, I mean, I don't know, maybe because I love him so much.
You put blinders on.
I never heard anything particularly terrible about Norm, aside from him just
being kind of a creepy old guy a little bit, but no couple, there was like a
waitress that came out and said, he held my hands above my head in a green room
and like forced me to make out with them.
You know, look, not good.
It's all alleged.
Who knows?
I don't know.
You know, but I think though that the two bedroom apartment deal was him
gambling away all his money.
But that's my point.
My point is, is like, it's like saying, well, Nike didn't get canceled.
It's like, yeah, Nike will never get, McDonald's been in for all intents
and purposes, as much as I love it.
Poisoning people for the last 50 years.
Yeah.
You can't, you were saying Nike.
Did you mean Nike?
Nike.
Yeah.
You wait a, wait a minute.
Well, thank you for taking the focus off my microphone.
This app you pronounce Nike, Nike.
Uh, I've never heard anyone on earth pronounce it.
Nike.
I might've just mispronounced it then.
I don't know if I do.
Yeah, no, I've heard people say Nike's my Nikes.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah.
I guess I've heard both.
It's outrageous.
Doesn't hold a candle to you plugging the headphone cable.
I think we should maybe take that to a vote.
I mean, I've never heard at all.
It's a mispronunciation.
And after all the mispronunciations, if you had said Mcdonald's, no,
no, no, no, no, it's not Joe.
Nike is one of the most popular recognizable brands on earth.
Nobody's had more mispronunciations on the show than you.
Tiffany Hadish, uh, I thought she was a, uh, by the way, every
week, the hard R and saw Joe.
I swear, I swear you can't tell if you're saying you soiled your pants.
What the hell are you talking about?
No, I don't even know who talks like that, but there is a small.
Part of the population that says, Oh, I saw it.
I guess it's a New Jersey type deal.
No, it's mid it's Midwestern.
It's where you're from.
Like I've heard people, I'm doing that as a conscious choice.
I don't actually say sore.
I honestly didn't know that until now.
I wasn't sure.
Yeah.
Because no, that is a myth.
That isn't even the R heavy, just so it's clear that that's what I'm doing.
Um, yeah, I didn't know.
I'm relieved that you're doing it on purpose.
I was a little concerned, but now, all right, let's get off of the
canceled culture stuff because nobody's here for that, but I don't ever want
to hear the term again, frankly, but speaking of which, uh, for Christ's
sake, what the fuck do you guys want from me?
Not you, not the audience.
Nothing.
I just got another email.
Yeah.
I love my manager dearly.
He's a good man.
He does a lot for me.
He's a pain in the fucking ass.
Okay.
Can you get back?
He emails me something and it's like, can you give us an answer on this?
It's like, he's texting me right now.
Can you get back about the press stuff in Philly?
Zach, there's nothing to get back about.
I have to do it or I'm in breach of contract.
There's nothing for me to get back about.
Yeah.
You want me to get back?
I don't feel like fucking doing it.
How about that?
Right.
And then you're going to complain and tell me that I have to do it.
And then I have to do it.
So what's the problem here?
Zach, just confirm me for the goddamn press.
The micromanaging of everything in this fucking life is just absurd.
I love that you're super confident that there's no way your manager
would listen to your podcast, which is always the sign of a good man.
You think he's paying $10 a month to listen to this shit?
No, he gets enough of me for free.
He doesn't need, you know, he doesn't need any extra.
I almost forgot this, by the way, this guy, which has happened to be all the time.
Now somebody ordered a blue ray for me on Amazon.
He then wrote, um, cancel please.
Four hours later.
So luckily I hadn't mailed it.
Usually what happens is I mail it and then they write back, Hey, I don't
want this and then it's your responsibility.
He writes back, not even please.
I'm looking at the email now.
Cancel.
Then three hours after that, he wrote an all caps cancel with 45 exclamation points.
And I wrote back since you asked so nicely and canceled the order.
And then he responded, Joe, all in the subject line, by the way.
Uh, so probably some sort of, he was, he lives in Florida, of course,
gonna be a smart ass with me.
Question mark, question mark, question mark, question mark.
I asked twice.
So there, what, what is this?
What do you do this to yourself?
This is a $5 blue ray.
Why do you do this to yourself?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you going on Amazon and selling your goods?
It gives me something to do.
In this case, Criterion came out with a, with a model and I
sold my, uh, my old fashioned copy.
Go trade in an amoeba and just buy a record.
Honestly, very few things make me sadder these days than going
into the new amoeba so I don't go.
I went, I went twice.
The first time was, Oh my God, this is like a piece of my life is dead.
And the second time was, Nope, confirmed.
This place sucks.
Go to any one of a million media store.
You're in the land of milk and honey when it comes to media.
I mean, there are so many stores you could go trade it in, get a credit,
support a mom and pop.
Why are you doing this with Amazon?
It gets most of the time a headache for you.
It is, but yeah, you'd go in.
I mean, basically you, what you can get $15 for on Amazon.
The guy at amoeba goes, I don't know.
I'll give you like 15 cents.
Forget amoeba.
There's like places in the Valley and stuff.
There's plenty of like stores that specialize in that sort of stuff.
Usually though, I bring in a big paper bag full of DVDs
or whatever handed to the guy.
He, I wait in the store for 90 minutes as he peruses them while
eating an overstuffed burrito.
And then he goes, Hey, I'm going to take this, uh, this one.
And I'll do a dollar.
That's, I mean, it's same difference.
Not really.
I mean, I get it.
Don't support the shitty mom and pops if they're going to be shitty,
but there's good ones out there.
And I don't know.
I just feel like it's just, it's not seeing moms or pops.
I'm seeing big fat guys in sweatpants with just stains all over the crotch.
Why can't that be a pop?
It could be a poor mom.
I feel like the pop would have a better place to put that gist than on
the front of a sweat.
Um,
well, we can go to the movie corner just after this.
I got a new psycho here.
Speaking of people I'd like to see canceled.
Yeah.
People I think can't get canceled.
Well, next episode, we got to address Sam Elliott, by the way.
Uh, I laughed my balls off reading that interview next episode.
The fervor, the anger.
Let's just talk about it now.
I mean, he is a show staple.
He was so mad about the chaps.
I was laughing my balls off.
He had two pairs of chaps, a furry one and a leather one.
Then he goes up and lays in his damn bed and his chaps.
I mean, at this point, it's nearly been a full week of news stories.
I get on this morning.
They asked the kid who plays the, the kid in power of the dog.
What did you think about this?
And he's like, nothing.
I I'm an adult, you know, like basically he can say what he wants.
And they're like, he slams back at Sam Elliott, a Sam slam or
whatever the fuck it was.
But this is an 80 year old man being asked on a show spur of the moment.
What did you think of this movie?
And he said, I thought it was a piece of shit.
This has been going on for a week now.
You, you just simply can't say you don't like something anymore.
Now, granted, he got a slight bit homophobic there in his, in his description
of it, but like he's 80, he's a true cowboy.
He did not feel it painted an accurate portrayal of the West.
He said he loves Jane Campion's early work, which was both surprising and
cool that he said, no, my issue is not a woman doing a Western.
My issue is a New Zealander doing a movie about the American West.
And he also completely inaccurate important to important to make note.
He was a, uh, spoke highly of broke back mountain.
Oh, see, I was just about to say if I was Mark Marin, my, my immediate
next question would have been, so what did you think of broke back mountain?
He spoke positively of broke back mountain.
Um, good.
It's a wonderful film.
I think his beef with this was when he, people were saying it was homophobic.
When he was saying what was with all the homosexual stuff in it, he's saying
during that period in the West, that is not a thing that would be out in the
open like that, even if it was closeted to, to some extent, just like I have a
hit my act about when they remade a Christmas Carol for the 87th time, the
guy Pierce one, you can't have a movie that takes place in 1800s in England
where Bob Cratchit is in an interracial marriage.
It is insane.
It doesn't make sense.
It's not how history was.
And this concept now of we're just going to make history the way we want it to
be under the guise of it's a movie.
Relax.
It's like, okay, fine.
You can do that.
You have every right to do that.
Just like you have every right to make a movie that fantasizes about
what the future might be.
But then if I say, I don't think this is accurate, just like somebody might say,
Oh, star Wars is supposed to be the future.
Yeah.
Okay, guys.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
You know what I like to ask somebody, why is that so, I don't understand why that
suddenly becomes some sort of prejudice.
I just don't get it.
Everything.
I mean, the simple discussion of race by a white person, let's say, but it could
be anyone in this day and age, but the simple discussion of it puts everyone's
ears up and back like a dog and everyone is tense and waiting for you to fuck up.
And even if you don't fuck up, it's just like, there's a white person talking
about race and, and we've got to stop this and make this into an issue.
I think it happens all the time.
I start sweating.
Anytime we talk about raising the show, but, and you know, I know my heart, I
know your heart, it's just a matter of how things get interpreted, but how are
we, I mean, this, this critical race theory thing that's going on now, the
exact same people who would say, of course you have to tell things how they were.
You have to tell kids how American history was.
And I agree.
Obviously.
Then why are you also saying out of the other corner of your mouth that movies
should be like this, where, where it is, what you're describing in a racial
romance and in Scrooge times, like it doesn't make sense.
You, you want things portrayed accurately, but then you also think it's cool
that things are portrayed on actor inaccurately.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes, it, you are making sense.
And what bothers me about it is it does a disservice to the
people that have struggled.
It erases the past to make it look like everything was just honky
dory the whole time and it wasn't honky.
No, no pun intended.
Um, and it's, it's pandering, it's, it's, it's dismissive.
It's, it's condescending, blah, blah, blah.
But most importantly, overall it is racist.
And this is a thing that I say in the bit.
God forbid these racist pigs in Hollywood just make Bob Cratchit
and his whole family black.
Right.
They won't do that.
That'll cut into their white quota.
Yeah.
So instead they make it.
And really that would make a lot more sense and maybe make the
story a little deeper and they won't do it.
There's a reason, uh, um, they did it in Scrooge with Bill Murray.
That was the black family.
Yeah.
And that also, but also too, that took place in 1990 or whatever.
You know what I mean?
But like, but like, so if it was an interracial relationship with Scrooge,
you wouldn't be like, that's weird.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Uh, but like the, the, the, what's his fate?
Mario van Peebles.
There's a reason those filmmakers existed existed, uh, uh, Melvin van
Peebles, Mario van Peebles is the reason Mario van Peebles made posse.
The, the black cowboy movie, because he talked about how there were so many
black cowboys in the West and nobody ever talks about it.
And here's a portrayal of one of those stories.
It's like, it's just spitting in the face of that sort of thing to just
act like, no, no, no, it's just like this.
This is just how it was.
And you're like, no, it wasn't just like that.
Yeah.
Um, you know, so I don't know.
I just think it's, uh, you know, um, I don't know.
It's just, you know, whatever, who cares?
Uh, anyway, so that's our, that's a new cycle for you.
But speaking of people I'd like to see canceled.
Yeah.
Jason Blum, dumb shit that he is gunning for this guy forever.
Well, stop making the worst fucking movies that have ever been created.
And I'll stop gunning for this guy.
Blumhouse is now, uh, their latest abomination.
I just saw the trailer is the fire starter.
Oh, remake new adaptation.
Whatever fire starter.
The original sucks.
That's a bad film.
Yeah.
It's a bad film.
Although I like George C.
Scott as like the native American guide or whatever in a, in a truly
insane bit of cast and, and the one thing, yeah.
The one thing that that movie has gunning for is that Drew Barrymore is
good in that role movie itself sucks, but she's very good.
They've got a remake now or, or a new adaptation of the book, whoever
you want to say it, it looks fucking terrible.
It was in it.
Couldn't tell you actor one in this.
They're doing the $5 million Blumhouse or no cast.
But I'll tell you this, I'll tell you this, the big line that
closes out the trailer, you're ready for this is it.
Let's get this fire started, baby.
It's worth it.
Okay.
Guy, little girl with, you know, military guys sending across her
military guy goes, we don't want to hurt you.
And she goes, liar, liar pants on fire and starts a fire with her mind.
Holy shit.
Blumhouse is like a moth to a flame from the sci -fi original.
That's horrible.
I got to watch this trailer now.
Do they play prodigy's fire starter over the action they play?
We didn't start the fire because this film is, but from the perspective of
the military people, it's just, he, he, he just, he does bad work, you know,
and he's proven it over and over again.
He's proven over and over again.
He outside of a money -making standpoint, he doesn't know what the fuck he's
doing and to the point to, to my point is this, B, you know, I'm not
Be the plastic factory churn out the fucking widgets that are garbage that
people overpay for and that make a lot of money for whatever good, God bless.
Go do it.
I don't care, but stop talking to me.
Like you're a player in this game.
Okay.
If I want you to culinary round table, I don't want to see Dave
Thomas from Wendy's sitting there.
Right.
That's my point.
So do what you do.
Blum, just shut the fuck up and stay out of the real conversations.
And shame on you, Billy Bob for hat or shutter, whoever's fucking decision
that was to have this numb nuts.
Come on.
Yeah, I've never heard Joe Bob speak favorably of a Blumhouse picture,
but he did have him on everything.
Joe Bob hates is Jason everything.
And the fact that that guy was on the show and poured, I don't know,
maybe it is poor Joe Bob.
Maybe Joe Bob's just old now and doesn't give a shit anymore.
I mean, he's a guy is 80 or whatever.
So, yeah.
Or maybe shutter said, you have to do this.
And Joe Bob was like, what am I going to do?
Say no to shutter?
What am I going to do?
This is my gig.
What I mean, he's, he, he's today's soulless corporate version of a Roger
Corman, he doesn't have the independent spirit.
He doesn't have the eye for talent, but he's making, yeah, he's making
a horror cheaply and maybe Joe Bob connected with him on that level.
But I guess so.
But Corman believed in what he did.
And I don't think Jason Blum does.
I don't think he gives a rat's ass.
I don't think he knows what he's doing.
And like I've said a million times, once in a while, he
lucks out with a masterpiece.
Why?
Because he doesn't know what he's doing.
So he stays out of the artist's way and they, and they pull it off.
You know what we're going to do?
I'm going to do as a segment on this show, uh, and in, in coming up
as soon to be episode, whatever, I'll do this.
I'm going to go and read the critics consensus score of every Blumhouse movie.
I want to see how many of these things are certified fresh on
Rotten Tomatoes because I promise you.
I find the whole system of Rotten Tomatoes flawed, but most of
the movies I'm sure we'll have largely bad reviews.
Yeah.
But, uh, but anyway, all right.
That's all I got.
Just gone in for him.
It's like he fucked your wife.
I can't stand him.
And he's a blowhard.
He went to that, uh, that Israeli film awards thing and made that big, you
know, I'm staying on this stage till you get security to pull me off.
I hate Donald Trump.
It's like, shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up.
Blum.
And then of course, before security came, he left Mr.
fucking big talk.
Anyway, I'm out.
Thanks guys.
Yeah.
Anyway, go ahead.
Sorry.
No, that, I mean, I don't like saying anything.
I don't like, uh, and thanks to my well, thanks to my well buterin, I
will not regret this rant later.
That's good.
Maybe I feel like I should be on well buterin instead of what I'm on.
Mine's stopped working.
Um, I, that's why I switched.
So, yeah, you were on the Zach, right?
Zach attack, Zach attack.
Yeah.
Prozi pro pro, whatever you want to call it.
Uh, let's talk movies, movie corner.
I saw the worst person in the world.
Um, to me, I learned a lot of stuff about Joe that I didn't know going in.
Um, see, cause it's called the worst person in the world.
Um, this movie I have heard raves from, from so many people and I completely get
why it's, uh, I actually saw it twice.
It's just kind of fascinating.
It's basically four years in the life of a young lady who's in her 20s.
She's dating a couple of guys.
She's trying to figure out her career path, who she is.
Um, the, the actress is great and chanting.
I rarely use the word enchanting, but I'm using it here.
Her name is Renata Rainsvith.
Uh, the movie is foreign.
It is directed by Joachim Trier, who I always thought was the son of Lars von
Trier, but that is not correct.
He is a distant relative to Lars von Trier.
Um, it's a Norwegian picture.
The guy also did Thelma, which I thought was a pretty decent little horror movie.
And, uh, reprise, which is a great indie from about 15 years ago, but this is his
film for sure.
It's great.
Screenplay is great.
Um, it's just the kind of like slice of life movie we rarely get anymore.
You got to go to the Indies for it.
It's funny.
It's charming.
It's sad.
It's interesting.
It'll remind you of a lot of bad decisions you made in your 20s.
Um, I dug it.
I really dug it.
Check it out.
Uh, all right.
I got, which, which group of stuff do I want to go with here?
What are we discussing on today's episode?
Texas chainsaw massacre.
Yeah.
The remake of TC.
All right.
I guess I'll go with horror movies.
Uh, I watched finally, you know, I'd never seen it interview with the
vampire and never seen it.
I dig it.
Uh, I enjoyed it very much.
A little bit miscast.
I love Brad Pitt, but Brad Pitt was, um, you know, you know, it's not a regal type.
No, no.
But, you know, enjoyable enough.
Kristen Dunn, Kirsten Dunn steers steals a show.
She's fantastic in it.
Um, Cruz is, is serviceable.
Uh, Slater is serviceable, but it's very, very well shot.
It's a fun movie to watch.
There's some great, great horror sequences in it.
Uh, particularly, uh, the sequence, Ben Dares is really good at it too, but
particularly the sequence when, um, um, Pitt kills all the vampires by setting
all the coffins on fire and they're like jumping out burning and he's cutting
their heads off and everything.
Yeah.
That part was really cool.
Um, I like that they specify and I'm assuming it comes from Anne Rice, but
in her book, but I liked that they specify that there's a way they have to turn a
person versus just sucking a person's blood because too many vampire stories.
It's like, well, why didn't that guy turn?
Yeah.
Why'd that guy, you know, I'm glad they summed that up.
Uh, and I wish they would have continued making movies of those books.
I think they're pretty cool.
Bit of an odd ending.
It sort of ends with almost like a buddy cop movie ends with Slater driving away
from the movie, yeah, driving away from the interview and Tom Cruz pops up in
the back, you assume he's dead and he goes, uh, I'm sure I need no introduction.
And then bites Christian bell on the neck and then says the line that he says to
Brad Pitt in the beginning, which is I'm going to give you the choice.
Nobody gave me, which is meaning I can turn you or not turn you.
Yeah.
And, and he looks at the camera and goes, I feel better already.
And it starts playing sympathy.
Oh, the amazing cover by guns and roses.
Yeah.
It's a weird ending for the movie, but, uh, it's still, it's a, it's fun.
I don't know.
I enjoyed it.
I got to wonder why, like, I remember it being a big hit.
Everyone was talking about it at the time.
And there are many more books that they could have done that they just didn't do.
I know they did queen of the damned, which was a disaster.
I didn't see it, but it lost a lot of money.
I know.
I don't think it's, I, I went down a rabbit hole when I was watching
it, reading about the other novels.
Yeah.
And I got to say, Annie might've blown her load of that first one.
Cause some of the later stuff is like, like in the queen of the damned book.
Yeah.
I don't know if they did this in the movie.
Lestat is awakened by a rock band playing too loud.
Okay.
And then he joins the rock band and becomes the singer.
And then that's what wakes up the queen of the damned is the band.
And she's so annoyed that she's woken up that she swears revenge.
It's, it's pretty just like, all right, what are you, what are you doing here?
You know?
Well, I mean, Hannibal, the book was not what anybody wanted either.
And it's just like, I guess they kind of adapted that, but you can also change
things like I'm in kind of circling to make it sound fancier than it is doing
an adaptation right now.
And it's like, you can change whatever you want.
You don't have to do it exactly as it is, but people sometimes
don't realize that I think.
Yeah.
So anyway, um, I, I have not seen much.
I've been working.
Um, but I did see in its entirety, the peacemaker series, which Joe and I
briefly flirted with doing, but I don't think are going to do.
Um, I love it.
I it's, it's maybe my favorite of the superhero shit.
I haven't watched a lot of the, the Marvel shows, just the movies, but.
It went in that same direction as the new James gun suicide squad, which Joe
and I both enjoyed, except it turned the comedy up and it's not comedy in the
Marvel, uh, quippy way of like Hulk going like, did I do that?
It's, uh, just kind of funny character based, very R rated, very blue comedy.
And it's very funny throughout.
John Cena is great.
I got to admit it.
Surprising, right?
I was shocked.
He's really funny.
That last scene with, uh, the justice league showing up.
He's like, you're late.
You're fucking dickheads.
It's very funny.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's great jokes.
There's great in jokes.
If you're, if you are a fan, there's great jokes.
If you're not, there's, uh, it has the best opening credit sequence.
I'm, I'm prepared to say of all time.
I looked for, I was giddy each time it came on with all them dancing,
AG, the fact that they have, uh, the janitor also in there, the janitor
who has one scene in the pilot.
Uh, that guy is very funny.
He was on outsourced, which is one of the first jobs I had and
was on shits Creek as well.
But, uh, and then Robert Patrick thrusting and the Eagle and
just everything about it works.
I love the entire cast.
I think age is great.
Divine and joy, Randolph.
Great.
Uh, Saina.
I got, it's got no weak links.
And even though I couldn't quite tell you what the plot was, uh, I loved it.
And I'm happy that they're making another season.
I like what guns doing.
I like what he's doing more than his early stuff, except for dawn of the day.
Uh, yeah, I, I, I was not a fan of guardians too.
I'm not excited for guardians three, but everything else gun has done.
I've, I've, I've pretty much enjoyed.
Uh, and I thought that this was great too.
Um, you know what I'm going to pivot.
I'm going to go off a horror here.
Cause I want to, you mentioned.
Peace pivot over here.
Oh boy.
Right.
This is the, uh, creative mind Pat was referring to earlier.
Yeah.
Anyway, I want to pivot, uh, to, I rewatched cop land.
I fucked up.
Would you fuck up?
Is that not what?
No, I just, I need to get this lady's name right.
Oh, okay.
Well, I'll start talking.
I feel, I feel terrible.
But I feel terrible.
Uh, Danielle Brooks is the actress from orange is the new black, not
divina joy, joy, Randolph divina joy.
Randolph is the lady.
They're they, they, I'm sorry.
That was a mistake on my part.
I just feel bad.
Uh, I don't know who you're talking about, so I don't have any frame of
I'm talking about the black lady from piece.
Oh, oh, okay.
I got you.
I met her up with somebody else and it makes me feel bad.
Dolomite is my name is divina joy.
Randolph.
She stole that film.
This is not the same lady.
Um, I, I rewatched cop land masterpiece hadn't watched in a while.
It is every time I get worried that the new Indiana Jones might not be good.
I remember the James Mangold also wrote and directed cop land.
Unfortunately, I then also remember he wrote and directed Kate and Leopold.
But I was just about to say, I like the man's whole career for the most part,
but Kate and Leopold is one of the worst films ever, ever made or really.
Anyway, um, I rewatched cop land.
I was just in the mood for it.
Talk about, I mean, my God, dude, it is just a, it is an impeccable.
It's up there with Glen Gary, Glen Ross and the 12 angry men, both the
original and the remake as far as casts, you can't beat the cast.
Let's start with Robert Patrick.
I mean, he's so good in that movie.
He just plays such a piece of shit.
Yeah.
And he's amazing at that whole sequence with him and Leo.
I was taught a friend of mine had never seen cop land, which is what got me down
this road recently talking about it.
And he says, is it good?
And I said, it's great.
And I said, every person in the movie gets to play the
most fun version of themselves.
Yeah.
So you've got Robert Patrick playing a total like almost backwoodsy creep.
You've got who's the guy that directed battleship?
Peter Berg, Peter Berg being like a jockey asshole.
You've got Ray Liotta being a sweaty coke head.
You've got Stallone being a dumb lug.
You've got De Niro being like the most De Niro De Niro's ever been.
You got Rappaport and the fringes.
Rappaport as like the white guy with the city vibes.
You know what I mean?
That bad, right?
Yeah.
And then you got Kytel being like explosive out of his mind.
I tell it, the whole thing, you got Frank Vincent in there.
It's like the, the wise guy, like internal affairs chief or whatever
the hell he plays the whole thing, man.
Front to back.
Uh, one of my favorite, you got Garofalo in there as like the endearing
sweet, but quippy, funny, uh, female cop that doesn't take shit from the man.
Like everybody is playing the perfect, most fun version of themselves.
It's awesome.
Um, well, and, and again, uh, the Copland, Copland shares a casting
director with Sopranos, so there's a lot of overlap, but, uh, Annabella
Siora, who, my favorite season of the Sopranos as one of, as Tony's really,
uh, nuts, suicidal, Guma, but I love her in this movie too, in a very different
role. And this was around the time, I believe, because of it, it's being a
Marimax production where she had her, uh, Harvey Weinstein experience, but.
Oh, then you also have, what's her name from raging bull?
Um, Cathy Moriarty.
Yeah.
Cathy Moriarty.
Great white.
Yeah.
Who's like through the whole thing in a, in a, in a house robe, smoking
and like drinking at like 10 AM.
Like you go tell Ray that if he doesn't like me, like everybody gets
to play the dream version of themselves.
It fucking rules.
And that sequence, man, it gets me so excited.
That sequence with Leota and Robert Patrick in the bar.
When Robert Patrick is going in on Leota for being a coke head and he starts
insulting his Puerto Rican girlfriend.
Yeah.
And he's like, he's like, I mean, shit, Freddie, you're supposed to fuck.
I'm not open up a methadone clinic and Leota just makes that face and like
grabs him and shoves him against the wall and puts the dart up his nose.
Dirt in the nose.
And just the way that whole thing unfolds, Kaitel get him out of here,
Freddie, you know, like the scene, my friendship and I've laughed about it
since we've, since the movie came out, the scene where De Niro is antagonizing
Kaitel and he's making his coffee in that, like, don't you mean, oh, you
kite the Kaitel scene or the Stallone scene where he's eating the sandwich?
No, no, no, no.
That scene's great too, but there's a scene where in the beginning where
De Niro shows up in the cop town to like antagonize Kaitel to let him know he's
watching because he's the internal affairs guy and he's making his coffee
and he's just, he's making it so slowly.
And he's just going, that would happen, right?
And he's doing all those De Niro faces to the point where he puts the coffee
into a paper bag to get it to go just so he can spend extra time.
They're fucking with him.
It's so fucking great.
And then, yeah, of course, the quintessential scene from the movie
is Stallone in like full on.
You told me, you told me you were going to, but no, that's not what you said.
It's not what you said.
I gave you your chance and you blow.
Incredible.
And clearly De Niro should always have some bit of business either.
He's preparing food or eating food, but that's when he's really shines.
Eating a sandwich that as far as I can tell is a slice of
baloney with lettuce on it.
It's like the saddest looking sandwich I've ever seen.
Yeah.
Um, bitching about how they never give you a napkins at this place.
You know, it's just, uh, God damn it.
It's an awesome movie, man.
It's just awesome.
And then you watch the bonus features.
James Mangold is like 26 when he made this thing and he's like,
yeah, it was a Western.
I wanted to, I knew I wanted to make a Western, but I knew I, I
didn't have confidence that I could accurately write one.
So I wrote an urban Western.
Yeah.
And then you're like, Oh yeah, that makes perfect sense.
Big shootout with the literally the sheriff at the end.
Like the whole ending where he's, he's, uh, you know, his ears busted and
they're, they're using the sound design to kind of like put you in his head.
That all feels very Western to me, but that, that ending, I mean, it gives
me goosebumps thinking about it.
I, it sometimes makes me emotional.
That's, that's the Stallone who is one of the all time greats.
The other, you know, jacked up, oiled up, ripped Stallone has
never really been for me.
He doesn't move me.
I don't find him funny.
I don't find him interesting, but when he is in sad sack mode like this,
like Rocky Balboa, uh, I love them.
I was the first one to sign on and said in this bonus features, this is a real
full circle moment for me, Robert and I debuted at the same time he had taxi
driver, I had Rocky, our careers obviously went very different directions,
but this is a big moment for us to be back together doing this.
Like, it's just fucking cool, man.
It's just more than holds his own.
Like that's the amazing thing.
I mean, he, he's doing something completely different than every
other person in the movie, but in a weird way, you could almost say
he steals the movie, even though he's the star, because all he's
doing is just getting shat on.
But somehow he comes away from every scene, like the Victor you
cause you love him so much.
Stallone playing vulnerable is your favorite Stallone.
Of course, when you, when you want to reach out and hug Stallone,
it's your favorite Stallone.
Schwarzenegger is the guy you don't want to see vulnerable.
You always want to see Schwarzenegger be the smart ass.
Yeah.
Um, but yeah, the movie is just a full on masterpiece.
Leota is, I'm not exaggerating, sweaty through the entire movie.
Yeah.
With these lines, like, like, like these, he's, he's like these
full, like it, he's so dramatic when he's like purge, Freddie
cleanse, fucking cleansing, get it out.
You know, like he just, well, he's sort of the Mickey in a way.
Yeah.
Kind of amp and rock amp and Stallone up throughout there.
I remember the, how, what a huge deal it was that Stallone put on
weight, that it was like the only news stories about the movie.
I saw it at some weird outdoor drive in at a mall, like they had a
premiere and I saw it there.
Then I was like, I almost left cause I was like, I'm tainting one of
the all time great movies by watching it in the shitty environment.
But, um, no, it's one I rewatch every year.
It's, it's a great, great, great, great movie.
And one that oddly a lot of people have not seen because it didn't make a lot
of money and it didn't make mangled into the big star everyone expected it to.
And then also the title, which at first you're like, it's kind of a goofy title.
Jeanine Graffo said she passed cause she heard the title and she's like,
right, I don't want to be in it, but, and then she went and watched
mangled first movie heavy and she called her agent the next day and was like,
I, I, whatever it is, I don't care.
I want to be in it.
This guy's really good.
Yeah.
I like a lot.
And his, his true Western three tender Yuma is fantastic.
But the way they justify that title with De Niro being like, when
he does that whole speech, kind of like you're the mayor of cop land.
You know?
Yeah.
Um, that's just an awesome movie.
God see it.
If you haven't seen it, couldn't agree more, couldn't agree more.
Um, and, and say, I don't know what I'm going to do for the second episode
because I just haven't seen much, but, um, what, what, what have I seen?
You know, nothing.
Cause I do these, uh, you know, I do my hour long rants as the bonus content
and that kind of gets at everything else.
I've walked.
Well, you've got one more for this one.
I know.
And I'm trying to
out.
It's fine.
We can stop at a two and keep it moving.
I, we, well, I got one more.
I want to do also, I'll, I'd like to shout out, uh, and I maybe did this on
the other pod too, but a great second season of the righteous gemstones,
which has really grown on me.
Um, as it's become sort of more action packed, they had these biker ninjas
with like, uh, Tron style, pink neon highlights on the motorcycles coming
after the gemstone family.
And, um, I don't know this, this is the mode that I love David Gordon green.
And I actually loved his early indie movies and he did movies that were
somehow even more indie than heavy.
That first mangled movie, like really artsy movies.
So now to see the path his career has taken is so nuts to me, but I don't
think you can get much better than his collaborations with Danny McBride.
I think obviously his Halloween movies are deeply flawed.
He's made some good stuff, some bad stuff, but when you got David
Gordon green and Danny McBride together, I think they make the, certainly the
best looking comedy that's happening right now and easily one of the only
funny shows on television of which there are two, so, uh, I don't know.
I feel like people do love gemstones and they should.
It's better than vice principles.
It's not as good as he's bounded down, but the little is, um, I'm a big fan
of the show and it's the, it's the most stacked comedy roster on TV with
McBride, Goggins, Goodman, Adam Devine, Edie Patterson.
Um, they got M .M.
at Walsh coming in and a pair of briefs playing the, uh, Alzheimer's Adolf father.
Oh, wow.
Um, it's just a great show.
And like either they bring in, Oh, uh, Eric Roberts was incredible this season.
They, they always bring back like great scuzzy seventies people.
Eric Roberts was great.
Um, yeah, it's a good, it's a good program.
And, you know, even when it's not slap your knee, funny, the plotting
in it is really interesting too.
I just, I think it's a well -written show and I'm a fan.
Oh, and with a movie I'd never seen, but we've touched on two of the actors here.
And I love three of the actors here from this movie.
And I loved it.
Uh, killing them softly, starring Brad Pitt in exactly the kind of role you
want to see Brad Pitt in a bad -ass hit man.
I got to give that another shot.
I saw it at a midnight show and I hated it because, and I think I hated it because
the cast was so great and I did not respond, but I own it.
I need to watch it again.
I loved it.
Uh, I get, you know, two low lives plan to knock over a, uh, an underground
co card game and try to get away with it under the nose of the mob card
games run by Bray Liotta.
Perfect.
Yep.
Two low lives are played by, I forget the one guy's name and the other
guy's Ben Mendelsohn, who also throughout this entire movie is drenched in sweat.
Uh, because he's a heroin addict, Ben Mendelsohn is great.
It's like scumbag, smart ass Ben Mendelsohn.
That's my favorite version of him.
He's always great.
And like, you never see him interviewed.
He just is like, I'm going to do my own thing and I will appear in many of
the best movies of every year.
And that's what I'm going to do with my life.
He's great.
Love that guy.
Um, the other guy's great.
I'm blanking on his name, but he's really great.
Liotta is great.
Liotta plays a strangely sympathetic character, which you don't see Liotta
do a lot, um, and it's great.
Um, Gandolfini now pit and pit and Gandolfini then swooping Richard
Jenkins, isn't it great?
Love him, but pit is awesome.
Gandolfini steals the show.
He comes in his first scene.
He drinks three martini straight down.
I believe he didn't know a movie was happening around him.
He drinks three martini straight down and then is yelling at the waiter.
He's like, what the fuck's the drink?
Hey, are you, he goes, uh, he goes, he goes, yeah.
Oh, you finally got back with the drinks.
I'm glad.
Sorry.
You had to go down the block to get the fucking things.
And the guy's like, I don't understand.
Sorry.
And he's like, it clearly took you so fucking long.
And, uh, he's like, how is it?
And he's like, how is it?
The thing's fucking evaporated by the time you brought it over here.
And Brad Pitt is like, are you okay?
What's going on with you?
Drinks can't wait for his drink to come.
Drinks Brad Pitt's beer while he's waiting.
And then, you know, the reveal is, is that Gandolfini's wife is leaving him
and he's, he's, he's on a spiral.
He's in the ad, uh, there's a scene with him with a prostitute where she goes,
no tip, and he goes, I got a tip for you, honey.
Stop acting like your anus is sacred fucking ground and put the condom
on with your mouth.
Whoa.
It's an insane, it's an insane character.
He's off the fucking rails.
Brad Pitt, who's a murderer is staring at him and every scene like, what the
fuck is going on with you, man?
Uh, I don't even remember it is they, they do like Ben, please don't spoil it.
I'm actually going to watch it tonight because I'm excited to now, but is it, is
it, uh, they do a robbery and Gandolfini's the Pesci, like the loose cannon?
No, they're brought in to take care of the guys that knocked the game over.
Okay.
Gotcha.
So I won't tell you anymore, but the backdrop of the entire film from this
first second of the movie is the presidential election of 2012 it's Bush
right, leaving office and Obama and McCain, one of them coming in and, you
know, at that time, there was this concept of a new beginning in the air.
Uh, and I think that this movie is, is a really interesting character study
that's put on top of that backdrop and has a lot to say about it's, it's
strange.
It was made so close to that time.
Right.
It almost feels like it was made now, looking back on it with, with some
distance and able to make a commentary on it, but it wasn't
it was made kind of in that time. Yeah. Anyway, give it a
watch. I really liked it. I'm actually thinking about buying
I well, I bought it and I don't like it, which means that it
must be $3 to buy because I do that sometimes if there's
something I feel deserves another shot. It's on Netflix
too. If you don't want to. Okay. This guy Andrew Dominic also
did an amazing movie called The Assassination of Jesse James by
coward Robert Ford. Have you seen that one? Never saw it. But
I love Casey F. It's great. But it's a it's a shut your phone
off and pay attention. It's a very slow mover. Okay. I saw it
at the now now ended. Beverly Center, you know, that giant
horrible mall in LA, the Beverly Center. They used to have a
movie. Yeah, the Beverly Center. Yeah, yeah, used to have a movie
theater. And it was as bad as it gets. Like somehow it wasn't a
dollar show, but it was shittier than every dollar theater I've
ever been to. And I was the only person in for a matinee of this
coward Robert Ford because everybody was like, you got to
see it on a big screen. It's it's Deakins, of course, one of
the all time great cinematographers. But finally,
10 minutes in this other guy comes in and I'm like, oh,
there's somebody else in here now. And he walks up, sits down
in a seat. And I see his entire head and body collapse and go
underneath the seats. He just falls to the ground. He stands
up and he's like, what the fuck? Sure enough, the usher comes in,
guides him to another seat and put some yellow police tape
around it. There was like three seats in this place that had
yellow police tape on it. Like, I guess the seats are just
collapsing. But that's a great movie. Chopper is a great movie
that he did his first movie that not a lot of people have seen
highly recommend that was an early Eric Bana, a fat Eric
Bana, actually. And then
now he's doing this movie called blonde, which is supposed to be
an X rated biography of Marilyn Monroe, starring Ana de Armas.
And he's just like, sorry, but it's X rated Netflix didn't
want to air it. They were like, this is too much. So I mean, God
only knows what we're gonna get with that one. But I'm a big fan
of the dude. He does his own shit, for sure. All right. Yeah,
but I'm gonna watch that one again tonight. Let's talk.
The Texas chainsaw massacre. Now, Joe, maybe you can speak a
little bit about the franchise, because I've only seen one and
two. I think one is, of course, one of the all time towering
achievements of horror. And I think two is pretty good, but I
don't ever want to see it again. I think it's because it fucked
me so so it fucked me up so much. It was the first extreme
movie that I saw when I was a kid at a slumber party. And I
was like, still the guy scratching that thing on his
head, even though it's such a mind, it's clearly just a little
makeup effect. Like it's when I saw it a second time recently,
it bothered me greatly. Because I just had this childhood shit
attached to it. I don't really like the movie. I love one. I
never saw three never saw the Zellweger one or the McConaughey
one. Walk us through.
Well, this is yet again, another attempt at doing a direct sequel
to the original. And I say yet again, in a very broad sense,
because not only is that something that horror
franchises are doing a lot of now, this is the second time
this franchise has done it. Right? Texas chainsaw 3d with
the great Alexandra didario was an attempt to do that it was all
that was terrible. But it was an attempt at a direct sequel. And
then that didn't work. And now this is supposed to be you know,
then they did the leather face prequel that nobody wanted or
gave a shit about.
Oh, yeah, didn't even watch that.
Um, and now there was the Jessica Beale, Texas chainsaw
massacre, right? That's a different one. Still, that's a
remake of the original, which is good. That's a good horror
movie. Okay, it's okay. They made a prequel to that called
the beginning. Yeah, which is not very good, but passable, I
guess. This newest one, again, direct sequel to the original,
the original, a great towering masterpiece in the top 10 horror
movies of all time, in my opinion, without question. And I
like the seat to the original, because Toby Hooper did the the
and I don't like gremlins to but he did the gremlins to
thing. He's like, okay, the first one was this documentary
feel. The most gritty disturbing thing ever. I got a budget now
for the second one, I'm going to grab big and self effacing and
self referential and have fun with it. And I thought it
really worked in its own way as a commentary on the first film
and as a commentary on horror movies. I love what he's doing
in two, I just for some reason, it's a movie that makes me feel
awful. And I don't disgusting. It's a disgusting film, but
it's great. And I actually like Leatherface, the Texas chainsaw
three, that's the most sort of product of its time of the
original series. It's you know, it's very much like an action
packed kind of wild, you know, right, big fight face off with
leather face kind of film. It's got none of the grid of the
original, it doesn't have any of the self awareness of the second
one. But but as far as late 80s, early 90s, whatever it was,
horror movies go, it's a solid horror movie. Next Generation
was the McConaughey Zellweger one. That's terror. I find that
one unwatchable. But still superior to the Leatherface
prequel. The Texas Chainsaw 3d film, and I will say this latest
entry. This latest entry is arguably the worst of the
horror movies. It makes no sense. The gore is great. There's
some great practical effects work in it, as least and if it's
not practical effects work, my hats off to the computer guys,
because it looks real. There's some great, great gore in it.
And that's, that's, that's far and away the selling point. I
mean, that it's a surprisingly great and surprisingly kind of
innovative at a time where I gotta say, even though we
discussed and really liked the new scream. Those kills were not
cool. They were not exciting, you know, they're in these
movies used to be, you know, they'd always say, okay, it's,
it's porn, basically, you're waiting for the next sex scene,
you're waiting for the next violence scene. But we have
really lost the art of like, amazing creative kills, where
you're like, ooh, that was a great one. These new
Halloween's I couldn't, I couldn't tell you one of them,
aside from when he kills the the old black lady in her kitchen,
because I was like, wow, that was really unpleasant to watch.
But it wasn't because the killing was good. This one really
does have good, cool, memorable killings that don't look CGI
fake. And that's, that's probably where the positives will
end in this discussion. But it's worth saying, it's got good gore
for sure.
Yeah, I agree. I think
you agree. I was just agreeing with you. Now you're agreeing
with yourself.
The so so why, why do I think let me elaborate, why do I think
this is the worst, potentially the worst of the series? It's
not. I don't know that it's worse than 3d. It is worse than
3d. I just it's just it's over. It's over. They keep trying to
keep this series going. And there's nothing left to get out
of it. Leatherface, if you're going as a sequel to the original
film is 70 years old. He's a man with severe mental disabilities.
There is no way he has survived on his own. It's absurd. It's
absurd. This this thing has you believing that he just survived
on his own somehow. Right? Or potentially with the help of this
lady in a wheelchair, I believe it's just it's just fucking
ridiculous, man. It's weird that you got that old lady, and then
the old lady from the original coming back, even though it's
not really her. But yeah, and then that's the second part.
Then the lady, the character, the one survivor from the
original comes back, it's a complete rip off of the horrible
thing they did with these Halloween sequels.
Where clearly somebody watched out the new Halloween. All right,
we'll just do this exact same thing.
Yeah, she's a stone cold warrior now. Yeah, by the way, she gets
killed in like three seconds. Um, it's like you mother, what's
her big line when she comes out?
I think you motherfucker. She's got a gun. There's a scene in
this. And then lastly, no, not lastly, third point. It makes no
sense. It's the laziest writing I've seen, you know, as I've
seen out there. There's a scene where the survivor lady who's
now the sheriff of the ghost town or some shit, I don't fucking
know. She's got her gun drawn on leather face in a room. And this
is her big chance to kill him. And she just lets him go with no
explanation. And then he ends up killing her. I don't understand
why that happens. And then finally, this week, confusing
semi commentary on the next the new generation of young people,
like going into this ghost town, because they're going to create
something to give back there. So they're doing some nonprofit
event there. I forget what the fuck they're they're going into
this band. It looks nothing like Texas, Texas. I think it was
filmed in Budapest. But it's supposed to be like an abandoned
ghost town or whatever in Austin that they are going to revitalize
and basically make a lot of money off it come in and it's
supposed to be making some sort of comment on millennials or
younger people who may on the surface have good intentions,
but they're really just going to like Starbucksify real
legitimate places and make them more corporate or something is
what I kind of got out of it. But honestly, and the movie's
short, it's it's 80 minutes, they don't even bother going into
that at all. So you even as Joe just proved, you don't even
really know what they're doing. It's like, so obviously, the
character development sucks, you know, the the characters have
always sucked in these movies. I mean, like, I don't mean Texas
Chainsaw, I mean, a lot of horror. But it's just what it
used to be was whether it was Beale or Dodario or whoever
else, it was the hottest woman you've ever seen getting
progressively more undressed as she gets chased around by
somebody, you know, sweaty, whatever it may be, maybe she's
in a bikini at one point or whatever it is. And then they
would get killed. Now, we've removed the sexuality from it,
we have boring, joyless asexual teenagers who get killed. So
it's like, sorry, I'd rather have the the hot cast, you
know, the cabin in the woods thing of the hot cast, you
know, getting naked and fucking or whatever, then this, if
you're going to do this, you have to at least then beef up
the commentary and make it mean something. But they just don't
they do nothing with the characters. And you feel it
because as they're all running from Leatherface, you're kind of
like, I guess I hope they get out of this. But I also don't
give a fuck. And that's where horror fails. It's where it
lives or dies. You care about the people or you don't.
Yeah, I didn't give a shit about one of these are
unlikable. They're not even good actors.
There's weird plot points that make no sense. Like like the
one young the younger sister character who's sort of the
outcast of the group. Who's like 19 fucking the 45 year old.
Yeah, guy that you think is a bad guy in the beginning and
then turns out to be a good guy, I guess. And it just none of it
makes any goddamn sense. It's just pointless. It's lazily
written. It's sloppy. It's it's poorly constructed. There's
nothing about the direction of it that makes it in any way
interesting. There's a beat at the end of the movie where
Leatherface is it's a post credit scene where Leatherface is
returning back to the original Sawyer house from the first
movie. It's like, why the fuck doesn't he living there now?
Yeah. So leather, let me get this straight. Leatherface, the
man who can't form a sentence literally can't speak, because
he's so mentally fucked up. He upped and moved. Yeah, he's
relocated, and then figured out a way to survive in this new
area. It's just a terrible, I'd imagine he's terrible. He lives
nearby the the Jeepers Creepers. Gentlemen, you know,
maybe they help each other out. They have sort of a meals on
type. Yeah, people that come by and help them and help them get
their driver's licenses and things of that nature. Yeah,
yeah, the vanity plates.
There's just no way this character survives. It's just
it's just stupid. It's just absolutely stupid and pointless.
And a waste of everybody's time. It's a franchise that is so old
at this point, that nobody cares anymore except people are
aged. Yeah. Yeah, no, like, like, like, I liked Ghostbusters
Afterlife. But Red, Red Letter Media hated it. I love Red
Letter Media. They're one of my favorite YouTube channels. They
hated it. But a point the guy made was when he was tragic. And
he was like, he's like, this is a conversation I feel like I
should have had 10 years ago. He's like, who cares at this
point? Okay, like, it's it's it's we're not even in the
sequel to anything. Well, you know, Ghostbusters was 40 years
ago, you know, like, and I feel that way, even more so about
Texas Chainsaw. This is a movie from 1976. Yeah, I think maybe
even 73. I mean, Jesus Christ, the last real sequel was from
fucking Well, the last real sequel was the McConaughey one
because the one of the original people was involved with that.
But even that is from like 92 or something. Yeah, you know,
like or 93. It's like way before McConaughey and Zellweger were
anybody knew who the fuck they were. In fact, it wasn't
released for years, because everybody was like, this sucks.
We're not putting it out. And then we're now it was a was
how eager and McConaughey got kind of famous. And they're
like, well, let's capitalize on this. They're both in it. Yeah,
Texas Chainsaw. So it was 1974. I just looked. But when I
searched Texas Chainsaw Massacre, I had to scroll down a
full page of Google to get to Tobey Hooper's original. And
that's sad. That's really sad. Because Google should always
default to the original, you know, that's what kind of sucks.
But like for me, and I did look, they used practical effects,
which is always good, happy when that happens. It looks better,
it feels better, it's more visceral. It also clearly this
guy, so Fede Alvarez and his partner did Don't Breathe, they
Evil Dead remake. And I think, you know, these guys that did
this? Well, they produce they didn't direct. Okay. And there
was a director fired. And also usually an 80 minute movie
indicates pretty big problems, because no, no script gets
turned in at 80 pages. It means big cuts. So they clearly love
this kind of gore where it's like, it's the that's why I
like them. I that's why I like their Evil Dead. It's why I
don't breathe the kills hurt, you know, they make you wince in
a way that that horror is kind of abandoned. It's usually now
just knife goes in the chest and you move on. But he they like
when like a fish hook gets in a the side of a mouth and like
rips through like, you know, gives you that Joker smile up
up the side. Or, you know, they like when something cuts into
your side or your arm and split your arm in two or something,
you know, but they find really cool ways to shoot gore. Again,
I don't know why I'm focusing on on. Like, I do know, it's the
one positive of the film. But for me, especially the stuff in
the bus at the end, when you know, it's got the shitty scene
from the trailer where they're like, you're canceled,
leather faced. But that scene where he kills a bunch of people
on the bus is awesome. If you watch it as a standalone, you'd
be like, this is cool. Everything after that is pretty
run of the mill. And it's also like, at some point, they're
just running around a cheap abandoned warehouse. You know,
like there's there's zero regional flavor, like the
original Texas chainsaw massacre has that kind of flavor for days,
you know. And since nothing is shot in its actual location
anymore, everything feels generic and kind of bad. And
you don't feel like these kids know each other, you don't feel
like they're friends, you don't feel like the town is real, the
people in it are real. And therefore, you don't give a shit
about what's happening on screen. It's a it's a lazy movie. So if
they had paid any attention to anything but the kills, it could
have been okay. There's some interesting shots and stuff when
leather face pops out of that poppy field or whatever. There's
a reason they use that in the trailer. It's a great shot. But
it's just not a good movie.
So I'm wrong. Kim Hankel, who wrote the original screenplay, I
along with Toby Hooper, or did Toby just direct the original?
Let me see. Yeah, Kim, Kim, Kim Hankel, co writer of the
original has stayed on the franchise. I'm wrong. He's been
involved in every one of these. Wow. That's why they keep
making them. But wait, who's he? He's the co writer of the
original movie.
Well, that he he might not be involved. They just know he's a
producer on the producer. Okay. Yeah, usually on IMDB, they
include you as a writer if you wrote the original film.
No, no, he did. He's included as a writer in the original. I'm
saying he stayed on the franchise and and either wrote
either co wrote or
or produced every sequel. His producer credits are the
original. He was well the original he's a co writer and
associate producer. Next Generation is when he
returned. Oh, this is interesting. He returns in the
original four. Okay, as a producer, and then he stays on
and continues to make shit sequels to and reboots or
whatever you want to call them. And I'll give him a pass on the
remake and the and the and the Texas Chainsaw the beginning.
But, but so he you know that I mean, you can get a producer
credit and literally have nothing to do with the film. I
mean, it might just be his agents for like you owe him a
credit or something.
I guess I do though think it's strange that
Hooper left after part two, I believe. Yeah, he did.
I just think it's strange that, you know, part three was like
the sort of the last attempt to keep this franchise going in a
timely fashion. Right.
And then all of a sudden you get this batch hits part four
that's like that doesn't even get released. It's so bad
initially. And that's where the original co writer steps back
in. I just smell a rat there, you know, like, but, you know,
like a guy coming back in and being like, Yeah, I'm gonna
cash in and maybe I'm wrong. I mean, you know, I don't know.
But he's, you know, he's also I'm looking at producer credits
here. He's also produced. He produced a short called head
cheese, which is a reference to Texas chain. So I'm asking for
two, right?
I don't know. We'll see. Anyway, hog way down. What are we gonna
see? What are we what you said? We'll see. I was like, you're
gonna kill this man? What?
No, I'm just saying what I'm saying. Like, we'll see. Like,
maybe we'll figure out why he's involved or if he's actually
involved. You know, but I don't know.
I thought you were like, we'll see if something happens to
this guy.
No, no, Jesus. Um,
that my hogs way down soft and low.
Look, my hog is not completely down. It's down. Don't get me
wrong. It's just kind of I think because it was 80 minutes
because I was surprised by how effective some of the kills were.
You know, I don't hate it as much as a lot of people. I follow
some of the hellions on letterboxed if I recognize the
name and you guys seem to really fucking hate this movie and I
can't say I blame you. I just feel like it's it wasn't a
complete abomination. But
yeah, not a good movie. We'll be back next time folks with
discussions of another late entry in a kind of long in the
tooth franchise jackass forever.
We are on see you in hell pod on Instagram. And look, our Twitter
account has never been something that we monitored. But I'm at
the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
At Jodorows a comedy Twitter and Instagram, please come see me
in Philadelphia this week. I'm at punchline Philly this coming
Thursday, Friday and Saturday five shows total and then please
come see me in South by Southwest. I get to Austin on
Sunday this coming Sunday. And I'll be there. One, two, three
days doing shows. I'm doing a sandwich summit with some
sandwich makers from around Texas or from around Austin,
Texas rather. I'm doing a bunch of comedy shows. Please come see
me please, please, please. And I hope to see you. We'll see you
next time. And we'll see you in hell.