I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the sound of your screams
beg I'm laughing on my dreams
and I'll say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I watched the cold open where he sells like the $1,200 golf club at the store, and he goes into his boss and he's like, I just sold one of them, but see this is what I'm your guy and you got it, and I'm like, it's just like, it's like, it's just, it's just the wedding crashers character, like, it's like, he, he, I'm like, what the fuck is going on man, like, where are we at, how did we get here, how did we get here?
Him and Mark Marren and a golf buddy comedy, it's just like, what are we, what's going on? And Owen Wilson, people forget this, try to kill himself. Yes, you know, I had probably 15 years ago, but he came close. And since then, as I can imagine, with somebody who went through something like that, the sparks gone, the lights out of his eyes, and it's not age.
You know, because Vaughn still gets the spark back sometimes, it's fun. He's, he's on autopilot, you know, that terrible Jennifer Lopez movie, and he's just, they'll just pop up and anything, and he's just.
Reliant on his old bag of tricks, there's very little trying, and he's almost never taking on a role that asks anything of him anymore.
Yeah, it's a real bummer. And look, I also get it.
If he's in a place where he's like, look guys, I don't give a fuck anymore. I tried my hardest. I did my best. I'm out here. I got kids. I'm taking checks.
Oh, you know, I get that too, because I mean, look, we can all sit here on our high horses and say, everybody should be creating art for the rest of their lives. But, you know, I do have sympathy and empathy for somebody that's only ever existed in the Hollywood system to say, this is what I know, this is how I know how to do it.
I'm not going out and, and, you know, shooting in 30 below weather. Yeah, for two months with no money, because I believe in art. Like this is how I think things get made.
And it's a disgusting business, and I'm done.
Countdown into it. I get it. It's the same little Jackson thing. I always talk about that letterman interview. I saw him years ago. Like, Dave, if somebody was going to pay you $10 million to spend three months in Hawaii, wouldn't you take it?
Yeah, you're absolutely right. Sam, I would.
And sometimes sometimes it takes a bit of a fall from grace. Like, look at, you know, I watched, I was watching Shia LaBuff's and he and mammoth were on bad friends that Bobby Lee Andrew Santino podcast. Yeah, that was on there.
They were on together. Okay, plug in the movie. And it was a very fun episode. But, um,
Shia had a really funny line where Santino's like, you're so funny, dude, everybody loves you. And Shia goes, not everybody.
Quite a few people don't love him.
But, but I was watching it. And I was like, you know, if I was there, what I would have asked him was, you know, despite the troubles that you've, that you've had, which I'm sure not pleasant to deal with and whatever.
For anybody involved, do you see a certain, uh, value in the fact that it has led you to doing more substantial projects now.
Yeah. Because had you not been yanked out of the Hollywood system, you wouldn't be sitting. You probably wouldn't be sitting here talking about the David Mammoth movie you just did. Right.
You'd probably be sitting here plugging Transformers 19. Yeah. Or whatever. And it's like, you kind of see that with some of these guys where
they have a misstep. They fuck up whatever it is. They kind of get yanked out of it. And because there's not the option of playing in the system they're familiar with, they then go and go, well, I guess I'll do some stuff over here.
Yeah. And then they actually do some of their best work because they go, oh, holy shit.
Well, they're hungry again. Yeah. Yeah. There's a whole other world over here where you can do stuff. You don't have to do it all like that.
No, no actor has ever been less hungry at this moment than Owen Wilson right now. You know, like, but Shia LaBuff has that again. So he's exciting to watch again. Right.
You know, that's, that's the problem is all these actors get so fat and happy and lazy and where is it filming? How long does it take?
There's a classic expression in Hollywood that we used to say all the time on cool kids. If you want to make an actor unhappy, give him a job.
Actors sit around and bitch about how there's no work. And then the second they have work, they complain incessantly.
That's even now where jobs are nearly impossible to find. I guarantee a lot of these people I listen to complain all day.
If you gave him a job by the end of that first week, they'd be bitching at you. Yeah.
It's life. I'm probably guilty of it myself. Um, what were we even talking about there? We were talking to Shia LaBuff. Yeah, we're doing the movie. Oh, I'm on my last
movie. You're on number two. We're still on number two. No, no, I did any haul is my number. Oh, you're right. You're right. You're on my number three. Then you have your number three. Yes.
Uh, another Woody Allen movie I watched, uh, rewatched. I'll just stay on the topic again of
uh, unchecked or overchecked people. Uh, uh, I rewatched Broadway Danny Rose. This is one I don't believe I've ever talked about on here.
I used to, I always had a fondness for Broadway Danny Rose given its subject matter. If you haven't seen it, it's about a
low rent talent manager that focuses mainly in in standup.
Uh, he's the character of Danny Rose is played by Woody Allen. He's the character is the it's he was a comic. He wasn't good. So he became a manager. I know that story.
All too well. Yeah, without the years that I've worked or whatever or some version of it. Uh, everybody's got a legendarily bad story about this guy that works in the business.
I, this all of this is very familiar to me and it was always why I liked the movie. Uh, but the plot of the movie is he starts repping the singer. The singer is having an affair with a woman played by me a
Farrow. He as a favor to his client has to go pick up this woman and bring her to his show that to the singer show that night.
And they get embroiled in this whole mafia scenario and have the wildest day ever and blah blah blah. And it goes from there.
This is the part of the movie that I that I didn't like because I was like I really like all the inside baseball of show business that they set this all up with.
But then it gets into this sort of, you know, paper and I was like, you know, I don't know, I wish that didn't get into the paper. I wish it stayed in the world of showbiz and it comes back to that at the very end.
Um, but now on this rewatch it's funny. I couldn't fucking stand the showbiz parts of it. Really? Because now that I'm 25 or 24 years into my career and very jaded about how much comedians love to stroke themselves and, you know, I got a, I got an even funnier story.
And they're always on and what our comedians most of the time make me sick.
Even though it's what I do. Yeah, I couldn't have less respect for modern comedy. Not all of it. There's some great comedians out there. Obviously. And I, you know, there's a handful of people I like and respect.
Um, but just overall, I just mean the overall like what you see on average when you turn on your streaming service or whatever, I couldn't have less respect for it. It has become to me a bunch of wedding bands.
Up there begging for a crowd of people to, to please enjoy them and, um, and doing anything for it. But, uh,
so, so sitting and watching this movie and watching the cold, you know, the, not the colder, but the opening where they're all the comics wrong cats is deli and being like, I got a Danny Rose story. Oh, you know, remember the time. And I was like, shut the fuck up, man. Like it just that fraternal horse shit. I couldn't fucking stand it. It was really making me angry. The Woody Allen scenes that had to do with showbiz and I found very funny.
Cause it's just him being funny and neurotic. Um, I still didn't really love the caper part, but me a Farrow is truly tremendous in the film. She's, she, she really disappears into the character. She is a, if you watch this movie and you go, that's the lady from Rosemary's baby. You'd be like, what? Like it's, it's wild. She's, it's, it feels like he found a woman randomly in the Bronx and just put her in the movie. Like it's, she's really good at it.
You know, people love it. Some people think this is one of his best films. It's definitely considered one of his classics. It's a beautifully shot film in black and white, which is also one of the reasons why it bums me out that it kind of devolves into this caper because it's got the visual aesthetic of Manhattan.
But given the way the story goes, it, I don't know. I feel like, I feel like if it was a, if it was a different story. If it was a more emotionally rooted story.
You'd get more out of that visual aspect of the film, but not to say it's not beautiful. It is, but.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't think I'm a big fan of the Broadway Danny Rose film. I thought I was, but I'm not.
But you, you might really enjoy it. So maybe check her out.
I always considered it, you know, second high second tier of Woody Allen.
I've been really hoping for a Woody Allen box. I had three DVD box sets of his giant.
And I sold each of them at a tremendous markup when his scandal happened because I was like, these might go out of print, but like they were really going for a lot of money.
And now, you know, I think Annie Hall is on 4K. Maybe match, actually, I should match point is not maybe I don't think Annie Hall is.
It's this weird thing where they don't want to like announce a big splash you release because of his name.
And yet we get a new plan ski release all the time. It doesn't make a lot of well, the bigger issue. I think the bigger issue with the Woody Allen movies is they're all distributed by and owned or whatever by different companies.
Okay, that makes sense. That's why you had all those. I had those box sets too, but there was like the Dreamworks one, which is only four. Yeah.
Then there's the earlier ones that are I forget I can't believe I can't remember what what studio those came out. It's United artists. Yeah, United artists, which doesn't exist. That's why you forgot it.
And now these ones he does now are all over the place because it's like this one's produced in England and this one was France and this one was Italy or whatever. So I think that's the biggest issue.
And also too, I don't think there was a huge physical media market for Woody Allen to begin with given his audience. Yeah, you know, I used to go see the premiere, not the premiere, but you know, I mean, like I'd go opening weekend.
In when I lived in New York to every one of his movies. You even though and this was this was before the shit hit the fan.
Even though it was Woody Allen, even though it was New York, even though it was, you know, all the pieces were in place.
There was like one theater that played them. It was an art house theater on the upper west side. You had to go to that theater. Yeah, the audience would be partially full.
And most of the audience was like blue hairs, right? Yeah, you know, so I don't think there was ever a big physical media demand for his stuff. So now I don't think there's, I think there's probably even less of a demand of we got to get these out in 4k or whatever, but, but I think a lot of more than you think are out on 4k, I believe. I think, I mean, I think I have the couple that are, but like his big ones.
By and large aren't.
I just feel like in a world where my next movie is available on 4k.
Should also have Annie Holland Manhattan and 4k. My next movie is called Body Parts.
And I like to quite a bit actually, but just the fact that we can we can own this and pristine 4k quality and we can't own 95% of one of our great filmmakers is a little troubling.
But and by the way, Eric Red, who made Body Parts has his own checkered history, which you can read about on Wikipedia, not anywhere near Woody Allen's allegations, but.
And very different.
Eric Red is a pretty great genre filmmaker and certainly screenwriter.
He did, you reminded me of like Larry Cohen, Body Parts, you know, reminds me very much of a Larry Cohen movie.
Pressing right up against camp, occasionally going for camp.
The performance by Jeff Fahy is good.
Jeff Fahy is an actor. I don't really know anything about like I feel like I've almost never seen a Jeff Fahy movie.
He was in, you know, he was below Van Dam, Segal, below Chuck Norris below ever. He's not even really an action guy.
He's in psycho three.
He's in psycho three and he's acted a lot, you know, he was in all kinds of like low budget stuff like this.
He's he's sporting some, I don't know if it's the 4k revealing at her not, but he's sporting some ludicrous hair plugs on a par with Steve Carell in the first season of the office before they fixed it.
But this is a fun movie. It feels intentionally a little silly at times, but for a movie with its plot, it takes itself pretty seriously.
In a cool way, it is a movie about a man.
Criminal psychologist who gets into a car crash. The car crash is insane. He goes flying out the front window. It's very graphic.
He loses his arm and he becomes one of three patients.
To receive a limb from a serial killer.
Who has been executed. So they give the legs and arms to these three men, one of whom is Brad Dorif, who shockingly is not the serial killer, probably because he had just played that in child's play.
But the great Brad Dorif, there's another guy in it. I was not familiar with the actor.
But he goes and hunts these men down and is like, hey, have you guys had any problems with your new limbs?
And they're like, yeah, I have no control over it and it's killing people. And he's like, interesting.
And then he investigates it, you know, and then he's got a, he goes and finds the killer who has, who wasn't executed when he was supposed to be. He instead has put a new head on his body.
So all this is going on, but it's played very straight and stone faced.
That's the only way you can play it or it becomes a Leslie Nielsen movie.
And I got to tell you what a great plot for a Leslie Nielsen movie, by the way, if this was just, you know, they could spoof this very easy.
Yeah.
Yeah, I really enjoyed it. And Eric Red makes a lot of movies like this.
He's, if he's not very familiar with the work of Larry Cohen, I'm going to at least say that they're very similar talents.
He wrote Blue Steel with Jamie Lee Curtis, which is great.
An early Catherine Bigelow James Cameron joint.
He wrote The Hitcher, which is obviously a classic. And I have the new 4K, which is supposed to be weirdly one of the best looking 4Ks out there. I haven't watched it yet.
I also wrote the, I mean, I had the Hitcher, I have the Hitcher on DVD.
Oh, yeah, yeah. I love the hit.
He also wrote Near Dark, one of the great little vampire flicks. He's directed a few bad moon, which I think I reviewed on the show, which is a.
A sea level werewolf movie, but fun, but amongst real quick, if I can interject amongst werewolf films, oh, he's in one of the areas looking werewolves.
I'll certainly take bad moon over the fucking wolf man that we talked about on here recently.
Yeah, great looking monster in that movie.
Yes.
And this movie looks great too. This, this, especially in 4K, it's like.
It feels very ramy, you know, not quite as absurd with the camera angles, but it feels like it might have been influenced by a ramy's camera work. It's inventive. It's fun.
The cast is like almost winking, but not quite.
And I understand my body parts is like this cult classic. I remember my dad renting it when I was 10 years old and telling me what it was about.
I was like, that sounds really stupid and he goes, yeah, but it kind of wasn't.
And that's exactly the review of it. And when you look on Wikipedia, they collect all the reviews and ever review says, boy, I tell you, I walked in thinking this was going to be a piece of shit.
And it wasn't a piece of shit. Nobody's like, but it was amazing.
But it's better than you'd expect and it's new to Kino 4K and there's good deals on it right now and Amazon.
And that's it.
Did you say Kino did it earlier? I'd missed it if you did.
Kino did the fork. I'm saying, I don't know if you already mentioned that until just now, if you did, I didn't hear you say it, but I'm shocked that Kino, I'm saying if Kino did it, yeah, you know, that's probably, you know, they put out quality shit like, you know, I agree.
That you know, they put up the, well, there is the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the