I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the sound of your screams
there comes a thing on my dreams.
And I'll say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
We're here to talk about those movies,
those sweet, sweet movies.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
And I'm Patrick Wall.
Hello, everybody.
And we're talking this week about Deep Cover,
the film 1992 film, New to the Criterion Collection.
Criterion, you know, they've stepped up.
Somebody called them out for being very white, which they are.
And they have been showcasing a lot of very interesting
films from Black filmmakers, some surprising ones.
I think a lot of people were like Deep Cover,
like some old Lawrence Fishburn action movie or something.
But I myself had it mixed up with Boiling Point,
which is Wesley Snipes with, yes, Snipes and Lithgow.
And I also had it mixed up with Ricochet with,
no, that's Denzel Washington and Lithgow.
Boiling Point is, isn't Boiling Point always better on Black?
Isn't that the one?
That's passenger 57 with some.
That's a great one.
You know, we're not mixing up these actors or something.
There was just so many of these crime thrillers.
And I wasn't allowed to see them.
They all come out in the early 90s.
The cover was always Snipes, Fishburn,
whoever, what Denzel pointing a gun at you from the cover of the box.
And then Bill is head in the background looking over him ominously.
Either that are a giant, giant photo of half their face
with like a plane exploding behind you or something.
Yeah.
And then like in the background like Ray Liotta laughing maniacally
or something.
But yeah, as we will discuss,
many of these movies are better than their reputation when
have you believe, but Deep Cover is certainly no exception.
Great, great movie.
And Deep Cover is definitely, I would even say not even,
not really in that ilk of what we're talking about.
It's when you, upon the rewatch,
it was the first time I realized like, oh, this is like a,
this is an indie.
This almost feels like a, like a, like an able Farara vehicle
or something like that, you know, 100%.
Yeah, we'll get to the, I mean, the tone of it.
It was directed by a character actor,
which is I think why you have a lot of great character actors going off the rails
and really wonderful ways in this movie, but we'll get to it.
What other, what other black directed movies do you think we might see pop up in
Criterion?
I'm going to make a few calls here and say,
do us a great red edition of Malcolm X.
There is a grave relationship with Spike Lee.
Like put it out.
You know, give us an hour of extra shit.
There's an amazing Blu -ray of Malcolm X that I almost,
that I own that I thought was Criterion for a minute because it's so well produced.
I have it.
You're right.
He brought up love and basketball, which I saw in theaters.
Don't remember it.
Bet you boys in the hood hops in there at some point.
Would love it.
I think somebody should shine a light on baby boy.
A later, right?
Singleton classic that didn't get the respective deserves baby boy.
But menace just got added.
Menace the society just got added.
Yeah, which hopefully means dead presidents isn't far behind, which I also love.
Right.
I bet you a rosewood pops in there at some point.
And what's the Oprah Winfrey movie that's like sort of a horror movie,
but it's not.
Beloved the Jonathan.
I love it.
I bet you beloved hops in there.
Those are my guesses for right now.
I got to be honest.
I said, I wouldn't be surprised if candy man popped up in there.
It could.
The dream.
Really.
And I think more deserving than or at least as deserving as any of these titles would be Friday.
You got cube and Tucker alive.
Do an interview with the two of them now.
I mean, why not?
I mean, it criterion doesn't usually put a comedy that zany.
I don't think.
But no, but I mean, hell, why not?
I mean, I just, I have lost an America from criterion.
And that's.
That's as goofy as as a Friday is or something like that.
So yeah, I mean, Friday would be, that'd be really cool to see.
I love it.
And the only version of Friday on, on Blu -ray is just bare bone shit.
Yeah.
It's talking with Joe the other day.
I mean, outside of criterion, shout factory, arrow, you know, the boutique places.
All your big movies that are coming out on Blu -ray have essentially no special features.
They'll have the EPK, the electronic press kit and the trailer.
But the studios are putting no money into it.
And I think four Ks not taken off the way they wanted.
So I think that's going to just slowly go away.
But I don't know.
My, my guess is it's always been about five years for the life of physical media.
Who these boutique places my, as soon as you see an arrow or a criteria and go under, that's it.
But criterion, at least, is, is being boosted by their streaming service.
I don't know, man.
It's a, it's a rough time.
But good on the pocketbook because I don't buy Blu -ray's near as much anymore.
I wanted to best buy the other day.
They had removed the Blu -ray section.
Like Blu -ray essentially is like dishwashers now.
I mean, sorry, best buy is essentially dishwashers now.
Yeah, I mean, it's, you know, and that's, that's the, the sad thing is, is the criterion.
Being one of the companies actually does special features.
Yeah.
My God, I texted you this the other night.
They do terrible special features.
I mean, it's just, it depends on the, I love the video drone one where they're interviewing all the great directors, you know, the.
Yeah.
I mean, look, that's a cool moment.
And sometimes it's something like that.
But, you know, it's a lot of like, we sat down with this film critic to discuss the importance of this movie.
It's like, I don't give a shit.
True.
What this critic thinks.
Like, you know, like, like as much, like on the Albert Brooks one I was texting, they got a fucking 20 minute interview with his manager.
And it's like, his manager's in lost in America for a very brief moment.
But, but the interview gets away from Brooks and starts to be like, and that's when I signed Stallone and Stallone and I produced Rocky, Rocky.
And it's like, why am I watching this on the, you know what I mean?
Like, you guys couldn't put a panel discussion together.
You got Julie Haggard in an interview.
You got Albert Brooks in a separate interview.
You can't get these two in the same place.
Like, come on, you know, like, I mean, yeah, I mean, it could some of it.
I've seen some of their COVID attempts, like where they do zoom.
Like the one I talked about with Olivia Wilde interviewing Cameron Crow and stuff.
And it's like, to me, you shouldn't be putting zoom anything on a criterion interview.
You go to their fucking place and do it.
You know, I don't know.
They do have amazing transfers of their movies.
The movies always look fantastic.
I watched a little bit of departed on Blu -ray.
I'm not not departed Irishman the other night.
Looks so much better on the Blu -ray than on streaming, which is a great example
because they're both 2020 movies are, you know, like a lot of times it's hard to gauge.
Like they'll make an old movie look amazing or whatever and you can't tell on streaming.
But back to back, Blu -ray has a huge edge over streaming.
You're always fighting against your phone's Wi -Fi signal, your neighbor's Wi -Fi signal.
You're just not getting the best picture in my opinion.
Yeah.
I like Blu -rays.
That's Pat Walsh for Blu -rays.
I enjoy a Blu -ray myself.
Yeah.
What's new in the world, Joe?
What's happening?
What's happening with you?
How's the sandwich shop?
Or is it thriving?
Well, it's going well.
I have no complaints.
So far so good.
All enjoyable.
I have a question for you, though, Pat.
Come down, by the way, if you're in New York, Joey Rose is 173 ribbing.
And I'm very touched by the people going out of the way to come.
Two women drove in from Ohio the other night.
Good Lord.
Yeah.
Wow.
So, thank you for the support.
Got some hellions coming through.
Got some taste buddies coming through.
It's a very nice, it's very nice to see.
And then we got some just people that don't know who the fuck I am coming through.
People that just want to send which exactly.
So thank you for that, everybody.
Come through if you can.
Joey Rose is NYC .com for all hours and info.
And you can order there as well.
What was I going to say?
Oh, I have a question for you.
I'm going to spin the tables on you.
Why did you tell Joss Whedon to do what he did?
Man, what a terrible interview.
Like, how do you.
Go through all that time and like, okay, this is going to be the interview.
I grant to get my career back on track.
And how do you say everything he said in that interview?
It's just so bad.
The me and Joe both picked out the same highlight, which was.
They said Gal Gadot.
It said something about him.
And he goes, well, look, English is not her first language.
There's just every single thing he said.
Yeah.
There was a better version of it.
Yes.
Like he, he was like on purpose.
Yeah.
He chose to say the worst version of it.
Like, even if with that, he had said, look, Galen,
I had a little bit of a language barrier.
I think maybe she didn't get what I said at one point.
That would be a thousand times better.
Still not great.
A thousand times better.
Yes.
It's like, it's like, you took a problematic thing to say.
Yeah.
And you, you said it in the worst way possible.
When they asked him about the affairs that he had with the younger actresses,
he was like, I was afraid not to sleep with them.
I felt that I had to do it.
Otherwise, I'd be letting myself down or something.
It's like, dude, what is the matter with you?
Yeah, I'm sure that's what you thought when you were 30
and actresses on set are throwing themselves at you.
It's like, I felt like if I didn't do it, I'd regret it later
because how often do you get, it's like, what dude?
I mean, that's anybody's reason for, for fucking.
You feel like, oh shit, I better fuck this person
because I might never see them again.
I might never get this opportunity.
But to cite it in an interview as like, I felt it's just so sloppy.
And again, just say, or something along the lines of like,
hey man, I was dumb, I was vain,
and I was very stupidly trying to make up for lost time.
I'm thinking back to when I was younger.
Again, not perfect, but a thousand times better.
So as you read all these quotes from Joss Whedon,
and then you couple them with, you know,
the accusations that he's a complete asshole,
you slowly start to realize like, oh, he is definitely an asshole.
Like, this is a guy that, this is how he talks.
Like he doesn't know how to talk.
He says, I use all this flowery language or whatever,
and he keeps talking about like what a great linguist he is.
Nothing he says sounds particularly smart or anything.
It actually all sounds pretty fucking stupid.
But then the, what's it called to the,
then like that firefly shit came out where like one of the writers was like,
look, you know, I remember him telling me once,
like the writer was like, I've worked for a bunch of horrible showrunners.
He takes the cake though.
Yeah.
And he was like bragging to us one day that he made like a female writer cry twice in the same meeting.
And the thing where they talked about how he put like the woman script up on the screen.
Yeah.
And was like reading it to, to like show how bad it was and humiliate her.
It's like Jesus Christ, man.
Yeah, I had a boss used to do that all the time all the time.
I know who you mean.
Yeah.
Call people into the room and, you know,
you'd make sure there were other people there to witness him going off on you
for like an hour at a time.
And then you felt like you couldn't leave.
And people would cry every day.
And you know, it's, it's miserable.
What were you guys still coasting?
No clue.
I truly have no clue.
But as I was reading about Whedon, as is always the case with the showrunner profiles,
I went, I'm experienced worse.
By the way, from multiple people, but, you know, he says at the end,
look, I'm way nicer than most showrunners.
I know I messed up sometimes when I'm way nicer than most showrunners.
It's like, no, you're not.
And like, what, why is that your, your, your,
what people don't understand.
Again, what he could have said better is the job of showrunner is impossible.
You want to kill yourself every day.
And it's impossible to please all these people at all times.
And sometimes you can lose your temper and so forth.
But, you know, the truth is no one on my writing staff ever,
ever felt my wrath.
And believe me, my wrath was, was barely under the surface the entire time I was running shows.
You just learn not to scream at somebody who's there to help you out.
And all writers are there to help you meet your vision, you know.
I don't know.
Yeah.
But I mean, that's the thing too.
Even if it was a situation of like, well,
there was, there was nothing in his explanations where he even said like,
hey, man, I shouldn't have done that.
And I handled it poorly, but that person wasn't doing their job.
And it was the 10th time we had the discussion.
And I lost my shit.
There was none of even that.
It's like, dude, you're just a asshole.
Like, you don't even have the, the, the, the excuse or justification here of like,
somebody was doing something wrong.
And I lost it.
And I shouldn't have done that.
Yeah.
Like because he is a guy that would use that.
So.
Well, he was calling with the guy Ray Fisher, Cyclops.
Yeah.
He said that guy.
That was one of another one of the more damning things.
He said he's a bad actor in both senses of the word, meaning what he was meaning was he's a bad actor,
but also his big performance about how mean and racist I am was also bad actor,
which is another crazy thing to say, especially at this time.
But and people have already responded like Ray Fisher was basically like,
fuck you, Joss Whedon.
I hate you.
No, like, that was pretty much his response.
But, um, and good doe said, no, I very much understood what he said and all the writers are like,
no, that's, that's not what happened.
And, you know, basically these people have so much power unchecked for so long.
And now that it's going away, it's like, if I was Joss Whedon, if I had done all this shit,
if everybody's coming far with a shit, I'd go, look, I have made a billion dollars.
You know, you don't direct the Avengers and not have roughly a billion dollars.
He probably gets a piece of all of those movies because you get character payments and stuff like that.
That's it.
Retire.
Done.
You know, the guy's 60 years old.
That's a, it's a reasonable career for anybody.
He's been doing this 30 years in a very difficult business.
No one is putting you in jail.
So shut your fucking mouth and be done with it.
Or, or write scripts, write the scripts you want to write.
Direct indie projects, whatever you got to do, but like you're not in this place now where.
I was going to say where we care what you have to say here.
We've been talking about it for five, 10 minutes, but.
I mean, I don't get people.
I don't get the hubris.
I don't get the, the guy jacking off on his work zoom and then the next day I'd be in like, I'm back, baby.
Well, what happened to shame in this country?
I don't know.
I might have shamed when I, when.
But this is enjoy your flight and I say you too.
Why do I think about that for four hours?
But just we didn't can release a profile.
This is because this is the backfire of, of no shaming culture.
This is where eventually it ends up, you know?
It's all, it's all a great idea initially.
It's a nice idea to say we shouldn't be shaming people because of their lifestyle.
Like, like, like slut shaming.
And we shouldn't be shaming people because they enjoy drugs or we should.
Right.
All these things that, that, you know, five, six years ago, seven years ago, we adamantly said, this needs to stop.
We need to stop shaming one another.
Well, fine.
Of course, that's a wonderful concept.
And I, and I agree with it.
But.
People take the ball and run with it.
And then that's it.
And you give somebody an inch and they'll take a mile.
And that's, that's the other cliche I'll use and I'll stop.
And then you end up now in this.
It, it eventually ends up at Trump's doorstep where it's like unapologetic.
Fuck you.
I don't give a shit.
I don't, I'm who I am.
And then that's when people start to go, well, wait a minute.
We need to be shaming certain things and say, well, you can't now.
You called the rule that we're not allowed to shame anything.
So now here we are.
Which by the way, do you see what truck?
I laughed.
So did you see the Trump thing about the Santas?
I laughed so hard.
No, I didn't.
He got, he goes in interview and they said, what do you, they said, what do you,
what do you think of the booster?
He goes, I'm boasted.
Mm hmm.
Good thing.
Vaccine saved millions lost around the globe.
They go, what do you think of these politicians that won't say whether they're boosted or not?
And it was clearly talking about the Santas and he goes, he goes, they're boosted.
But they won't say it because they're gutless.
Not wrong.
Not wrong at all.
I really laughed.
The term gutless is very funny to me.
Yeah.
But I mean, this is, you want to talk about a hyper weird reality we're living in.
I'm now watching Trump shame to Santas.
Uh -huh.
For not admitting that he's boosted.
Well, I don't know what's going on anymore.
But anyway, enjoy the show, folks.
It's wild out there.
Um, and I apologize for telling Jess Whedon to do what he did.
Um, I read a profile speaking of, of shaming and then are trying to adjust to this new world or whatever.
Allison Tolman, who was in the first season of Fargo.
She basically played the McDormand role.
Delightful actress.
She was actually on the effects of life thing.
She played, uh, Tudy.
But um, she said she came out with this big thing was just a Twitter ramp.
But of course, because of what we deal with now, it had to be broadcast as national news.
Um, but she said, hey screenwriters, don't ever put a fat joke in your script.
Don't ever describe a character as fat.
Donut, you know, and it goes on and on and on.
She's like, I assure you, even if you think it's okay now, it won't be okay in five years and on and on.
She's a, she's an overweight woman, you know, or whatever.
I don't even know what you're supposed to say.
I think you're supposed to say fat, which to me seems outrageous.
Like if I said, well, you know, she's fat.
I would, I would, uh, why is it outrageous?
It's scientific word.
It's no, I know.
I just mean in a world where everyone's sensitive.
I don't know how fat became the right one to choose.
This is the problem to, by the way, it sounds like, you know, this is the problem too, by the way, with, with the softening of language, which, you know, like, I don't mean to hack George Carlin.
But like, I had a health teacher in college tell us, he goes, everybody needs to stop saying overweight.
That's not what it is.
It's over fat.
He's like, technically, that's what it is.
It means you have too much fat on your body.
He's like, overweight could mean muscle.
A body builder is overweight.
Yes.
And he's like, they have to define it so we can take better care of ourselves.
And it's like, forget it.
It's just, you know, but whatever.
Anyway, so she said don't, so then, so what, what she said that, you know, many people, uh, of course, had her back, took her side.
But it's like what I'm, I'm right now, I've been trying to cast this movie with a fat female lead.
It has to be in my opinion.
So that doesn't leave a lot of actresses, it leaves very few bankable actresses, maybe one.
But the issue is, I don't understand how I can sit down and write a script about a fat woman and not say that she's fat.
And if a character in the movie says she's fat or makes a joke about her and hurts her feelings, that's what drama is.
That's what, that's what conflict is.
That's what makes a screenplay or makes a story.
So I think the reason we're getting all these movies and shows where you're like, what is even the, what is the conflict?
What's happening?
It's because people are scared to have conflict in their real lives and in television.
But to me, that was a bummer.
I've struggled with weight, you know, we talk about it on this show all the time, Joe and I.
It's not fun, of course.
But it's, it's something where, you know, glandular, et cetera, hereditary, yes.
But to some extent, it's something you do to yourself.
Alcoholism is a disease.
To some extent, it's something you do to yourself.
So like to say all this, it felt very odd to me that like,
you know, I'm sure she gets sent roles where it says an Katie comma overweight or Katie a few extra pounds or something like that.
But that's why she's working.
You know, like that, that's why she's getting parts.
There's a reason there are character actors.
It's like Charles Durning got the parts that said like Reggie comma fat.
You know, and I'm sure he was like, and by the way, just a clarify, just a clarify.
Not every part.
But that plays in every almost every part I've ever been sent to read for or that I've booked has had the word depressed in it.
Yeah.
It's had the word run down has had the word out of shape phrase out of shape.
You get misogynistic a lot as well.
Yeah.
So you get these things because they're descriptors now that doesn't mean everything I've ever done was described that way.
But you certainly get to play certain things or you're eligible to play certain things because you fit a certain physical type, certain personality type, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
Everybody is trying to read every descriptor and adjective that isn't glowingly positive.
You know, so it's like, I mean, honestly, I'm not exaggerating.
We now we now live in a climate where I could have when I did living biblically with you.
There was a joke in the script for my character when it's a give me a break my six pack has a six pack or my abs have abs or something like that.
Right.
About how much he works out.
We took it out.
Why?
Because it's me.
It didn't make any sense.
Right.
You made the joke in front of the cast and crew.
We have to get rid of that joke, Joe.
I mean, it's TV, but it's not a complete fantasy.
Or something along those.
Yeah, everybody laughed.
Right.
And I only would have said that to a friend.
I wouldn't say that.
But my point is, it was of course, but my point is is we literally live in a climate now where I could turn around and say,
I was devastated and embarrassed by that and how dare it's like, can everybody get a grip on themselves?
When somebody tells me my I don't have shoulders, I don't weep in the corner about it.
I go, I roll my eyes, I go, yeah, I know, my shoulders stink.
When somebody refers to me as having an extra chin, I don't weep in the corner about it.
I go, yeah, and I should probably work harder on that, but I don't, and until I do,
I don't care. I'm not being shunned from society for it. And neither is this person writing this
complaint. And I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're there? Is that bad? Sorry, I gotta, I thought my neck knocked out.
I'm just, I'm just, I'm just over it. I'm just tired of it. You know, we're not talking about
lepers being sent off to colonies here. You know, we're not talking about Asian Americans being
rounded up and put into camps during World War II. We're not talking about racial profiling here.
We're talking about using basic descriptors to describe characters in fucking movie and tv
scripts that don't matter at all to anybody and have no fucking purpose other than to entertain.
And not exploitative descriptors at that. It's not saying that slob. It's not saying, well,
you know, because this person is overweight, they're naturally lazy and they fall down a lot
because they're natural clutch because it doesn't say any of that. It just says in the general
appearance, let it overweight. Yeah. But I'm descriptor in my film. And of course, it has to be the
first line. You open on the lead character and it's like, I had written a little overweight or
something like that. We discussed it for a week between the producers and the director and everybody
what to put. And then everybody came to the conclusion that it should say she's insecure,
though it's not really clear why. And I said, well, that doesn't say overweight at all. And I was like,
do you want to say she's overweight, which causes her to be insecure? No, just don't say overweight.
And I said, well, if you don't, then they won't know. And I think it's almost worse to say it's not
clear why. And they're like, well, you're saying it's not clear why like she should be ashamed of
her body. And I'm like, no, I'm just trying to when they're casting the movie, they know what I want
for the part, you know, that's really all I'm trying to do. My wife works in medicine.
She had a full day lecture where she had to go and this woman said, you're no longer allowed
to tell people they need to lose weight in medicine. She's like, we don't, it's not fat,
like fat is not what's causing health problems. And then there's all these doctors there who are like,
well, of course it is. If they're having hard issues or they're out of breath, we have to tell them
they need to, they're like, if they come to you and they're overweight, they know they're overweight
and don't need to hear it from their doctor. It's like, no, that's who they do have to hear it from.
Like, we can't police language around doctors. That's insane. You're grabbing your, your
bulge and being like, oh, look at fatty here. That's insane. That's different. Two years ago,
right before lockdown, I had a joke where I already said I had a friend that went to
and I exaggerated this. Yeah. They were talking about their dog and their vet.
And they said the vet said my, the vet said my dog need to lose weight. I was like, don't fat
shame my dog. And I was like, it's not really fat shaming when it's a doctor. And she started laughing.
She's like, yeah, I guess you're right. Yeah. And I wrote a joke about it and I changed it to a
person and said the same thing. It's not fat shame when it's your doctor. Six doctors
and stand around you pointing and laughing like it's only stepped on the scale and the metal thing
shot across the room or whatever. You know, like, yeah. But it was, it was absurd. Yeah.
I can't believe what I'm hearing right now that this is a real, this is now seeped into real.
People really think if you deny it, it's not real. This was a day -long lecture.
Find another way to tell people that they're, that they're fat. And that's what's causing
their health problems without saying they're fat. And the doctors are like, we have to diagnose
and explain the problem to them in five minutes. Like sometimes you got to use words like
you need to lose some weight, you know? Like, I don't know. They're like, well, it's keeping fat people
from going to the doctor because they feel ashamed when they get. All right. Well, I'm sorry.
Standing up there, I'm always like, can I take my shoes off? You know, like, I get it.
It's uncomfortable and it's cold and it's, you know, especially if the nurse is a pretty gal and,
you know, it's uncomfortable. Let's shift gears. I'm going to start ranting and
saying things I don't want to, we're fine. I just don't. I feel, I feel way more comfortable
discussing this than race because I'm comfortable with a few extra pounds. I'm comfortable. I'm
saying, let's, but I want to bite my tongue now and I don't start down the road. Let's go to the
movie quarter. Okay. The movie corner. Yes. I, well, Joe, let's, let's start with one of your
favorites. I just completed season four of all in the family. I've been watching, you know,
something like six episodes a day. Basically, that's just because of this job I'm going to. It's like,
we're, you know, we're aiming for all in the family. We're aiming for all in the family. A lot of
shows say that. But I was like, you know, I really, I really have only seen the first season of this show.
It gets so much better like immediately after that first season. The first season is the ground
breaker. And it's, you know, but it's, uh, man, just every episode now is great. They go into huge
issues. They, they did one where it was like, they're worried about food poisoning coming from
mushrooms because they grow and shit. And I was like, this seems like kind of a random episode for all
in the family to do. And I looked it up and that's exactly what was happening in the world at that time.
It's just one of those shows where they opened the newspaper and managed to create beautifully
written human stories that feel real and relatable out of any issue that is going on in the world
at any time. You show you both sides equally. Evenly to some degree, there's a, there's a constant
tension in the people howling at Archie saying slurs and then applauding when somebody tells Archie
what a bigot he is. And that, all that stuff, all that gray area, all that kind of stuff that makes
you tense when you watch the show is what we have wiped away from our entertainment. And it's such a
bummer because I get that you don't want racist jokes, but to simply show a bigot and constantly
have him getting his comeuppance and making him the idiot in the room is so powerful. I realized that
some people's dads made Archie out to be a hero and, you know, toasted their beer to him. But,
you know, this is one of the all -time great sitcoms. Of course, the only thing you can really say bad
about it is that it's the worst -looking show I've ever made. It's a terrible -looking program,
but it's the 70s, you know. What a, what a, I mean, you watch the Dick Van Dyke show. It looks like
a fucking Hitchcock movie. It's like, yeah, where they did sitcoms on film and then they switched to video.
But yeah, and then they went back to film and then they went back to video. But like the, you know,
I think it's a shame because I think that we're due for an all -in -the -family style of show right now.
I think we need a show right now that's showing the commentary about everything going on from both sides
of the aisle. Yeah. They're just, it's the most ripe time since the original run of the show for it.
You know, I was talking to a fellow bar owner yesterday about his establishment. And he was telling me
in problems with employees. And I was like, you know, I go, listen, it's a tough time. You can't win
because you have Gen Z and Millennial kids that like think they know everything. And you can't tell
them anything because they've been pampered for too long. And then you, on the other side of the
aisle, you got the boomers that think they know everything because they had more pain or more
experience or the hard knocks or whatever. I go, boomers need to shut their fucking mouth and
go to bed. Everybody's alone. Yeah. You know what I mean? So like, it's well, not everybody,
you know what I mean? They took their swing at the world and we see how that worked out. So
but it's very on the family where it's like, where it's like, there's validity
to meet head and glory as arguments about what needs to change in the world. There's also great
validity to Archie's argument of if it wasn't for me working, you wouldn't have all the time to
sit around in this house and pontificate about what needs to change. I mean, that's happening literally
right now, again, between the mainly the Gen Z generation and the boomer generation or what's now
boomers now been bastardized and means anybody over 35 with an adverse opinion. But
but you put an atheist and a religious guy or an atheist and a religious husband in the same
house and a show and immediately it was like, we don't want to hear a single word from the atheist
character. I have talked to people about, look, I'm from Missouri and I live out here. I see the
ridiculousness of both. What if we do a modern day on the family with a trumpet and a non -trumper
who have been married for 20 years and they don't know how to deal with? It's such fertile,
easy ground for great one, you know, one act dramas. That's what these old, I mean, they're all
one act plays. These all in the families. They're they're they follow the structure of plays as opposed
to sitcoms really. But people just don't want to do it and I don't get why. I think they maybe because
they think people won't watch because they only want to hear their side and there's some truth to that.
But I do think a well written argument where you're not treating the trumpet like an idiot and you're
not treating the liberal like, you know, a complete character. I think you'd have a really
riveting interest in groundbreaking show and they won't do it. I think the shot was the Rosanne
reboot, which wasn't great, but I think that was the one shot. And yeah, that got screwed up.
And I said from the beginning, they're missing a major opportunity here to do something that people
could learn from by just cutting this character and getting rid of her. Have her come back and
deal with this situation on the show. Like you would have done in the original Rosanne show.
Right. Let's try to learn for a second. But again, it's like the weight thing. Well, if we don't
mention it and we don't look at it, it's not real. Right. Okay. Well, then great. So now, great. You
know, so it's just a waste then. The way Rosanne and Dan were always talking about their weight, I have,
you know, I have terrible genes, both sides of my family. Like when I think about uncles and aunts
and stuff, like you over there for Christmas and like the discussion turns to weight, like I've been
trying to get out there and walk every night and it's so hard. I would have to keep cutting off things
that we can't talk about. That's what people don't get. It's not
anytime you say anything about it. It's like, oh, he's Mr. Anti -Cancel Culture or whatever. And it's
it's all just so dumb. All anyone is saying is the only way to fix where we're at is through
conversation, not through shutting off venues of conversation. That's what people don't seem to get.
I watched along these lines, I finally sat down and watched kids in the hall, death comes to town,
the limited series they did, 10 years old solid, no brain candy, but it was solid. Yeah, which
they still themselves do not like brain, I don't understand. I think brain candy is awesome,
but well, they were in a miserable place at that time. Yeah. But anyway, I watched it and some of the
reviews I read, it's about 10 years old at this point said, like this is surely going to offend
every person under the sun. However, it's classic kids, it's funny, it's funny, it's funny, it takes
a while to get into it. It's because of the different sort of format of it. I admired it
more on a, you know, how good they are at disappearing into characters sort of vibe as opposed to laughing
out loud. But here's the thing and you could never do this now. But, you know, one of the characters
calling the question is the Bruce McCulloch character, he plays the kid who's massively overweight. Yes.
And I guess some people could find that as mocking or whatever. I never saw it like that. My heart
broke for this character. I felt so sorry for them. And I was so excited when this character
finally gets out of the house for the first time in 20 years or whatever it is and like is going to
go solve this murder mystery and is like, has a reason to live again. I thought it was beautiful.
I really did. Yeah. And the fact that somebody could look at that and condemn it and go, it can only
be this. It can only be interpreted as this is so crazy to me. I just don't get it like, you know,
so. But anyway, that aside, the show itself was fun. My hat's off to Scott Thompson. He's got no
hair through half of this fucking thing because he was doing like chemo. But he's still there and he
still does it. And it sent me on a, it's a fun show. It's worth watching. There's some, there's some
real standout classic. Hold on. Somebody's at my door. Give me a second. Yeah.
Back from the door. Sorry about that. But anyway, death comes to town. Check it out. It's worth
seeing. There's some new classic, newly made characters that I think could be classic kids in
the whole character. That lawyer that Bruce McCullough plays. Oh, yeah, yeah. When he comes in
and he's like, he's like, because I'm from the city, not like you dumb shits, you know, like that
was classic, classic, classic Bruce McCullough. When are we getting the Amazon, the new reboot of kids
in the whole? They're shooting right now. They shot the first season. And I have the same manager
of Scott Thompson. That's the only reason I know that they finished the first season. Yeah. I'm excited
for it. You know, that little lyric theater right by my house. Yeah. Scott Thompson does his,
the, the buddy character, the, the gay, not kind of nightclub guy. He does it there all the time.
I've seen him do it twice. It's hilarious. It's like five bucks. I'm excited to see this new show.
They, they released the entire series on Amazon Prime because it's an Amazon show, which has been
fun watching. And then I found out that spade had, or spade, not David spade, David, uh, just face
fully had another sitcom after news radio that took place and it was shot in Canada. It was never
released here. And there was an episode of that called the middle aged guys in the hall, which was an
episode where the entire kids in the hall cast is on it. And I sent it to him. I didn't watch.
It's great. You should watch it. The plot is is that they show up and they're all goth to like
Dave Foley's work. Uh -huh. And the plot is is that they made a suicide pact when they were kids.
Okay. That they would all kill themselves when the youngest turned 50. And it's his 50th birthday.
Okay. Okay. And uh, everybody's great in it. But McDonald really steals the
show. He plays like the leader that like entrances everybody. Uh -huh. And it's, it's, it's very funny.
It's very, very funny. But he's doing that classic like almost like, you know, he's just doing
classic Kevin McDonald's shit. Uh, Mark McKinney is doing like almost like the version of the
deriel character. Uh -huh. Uh, except the goth, Scott Thompson is doing like his dumb like,
oh, GZ, you know, like, except he's a god. Like, it's really, really funny.
I watch it. They're, they're funny men. They're very funny men. But, but anyway, I'm driving to the,
to the last point, which is death comes to town. I was also going down this rabbit hole and watching
interviews with them. And I watched an interview with Bruce McCullough and I thought it was interesting
because he talked about the character of cancer boy. And about from brain candy and he said, you
know, some people thought it was like a little much, whatever. He goes, I thought it was actually a very
beautiful character. I love the spirit of the character. Like, you know, and it's just like,
whether you agree with that or not is secondary. I'm just like, I feel like you couldn't even,
you can't even roll that die anymore. Like we're like, no, but look at it this way.
And maybe you'd, you'd convince standards and practices or whoever that it's, that it's okay.
Just wouldn't fly. Anyway, all right. I got a quick piece of, it's not really scary stuff. I don't
know what you'd call it. Screaming in. But Michael Mann is, well, A, he's doing a TV show for HBO Max,
an LA cop show, which I would be excited about if it didn't star. Anzal Elgort, the worst actor currently
working. But I will watch it. I love Michael Mann. He has written Heat 2 as a book, which I think
could very easily mean it becomes a movie. But here's what it is. It tells the stories. It's called
Heat 2, like me too. No, Heat, like the movie. Oh, Heat. Oh, I think he said Heat 2, like he's
going to have some big commentary on me too, as I got Jesus now. So the novel Heat 2, it starts
one day after the events of the film with a wounded Chris, the Val Kilmer character, desperate to escape LA.
The story moves to both the six years preceding the bank heist and the years immediately following it,
featuring new characters and new worlds of high -end professional crime with highly cinematic action
sequences. If we get a heat sequel, I mean the de -aging they'd have to do. They got a dub Kilmer's
voice in. Well, they got a de -age Pachino. What do they have? You're right. They'd have to recast.
I mean, yeah, they'd have to recast. 1995 is when that came out. That's 25 years ago. Is the Pachino
character in the book? Yeah, they're all in there. Wow. I mean, I'm going to read it. It sounds
interesting. It sounds like what a lot of directors did over the pandemic when they had a lot of time
in their hands is write books, I guess, but I'll check the thing out. Wow. All right, Heat in it
comes out August. It's called Heat, too. To call a book Heat, is insane. A sequel to not the book.
I mean, yeah, it's a weird move. Let's go to this movie, Corn. We're in it already, babe. I did
the kids in the hall. You did all in the fam. Okay. The boys from Brazil was recommended to me by
our dear friend, Matt McCarthy. I have to back up what he said, which is I would do everything
you can to watch this movie cold, easily one of the wildest premises to a movie I've ever seen.
I've always heard about the boys from Brazil. I was like, well, it's it's some sort of Holocaust
thing. I thought it was like an app pupil type deal. What it is, the one sentence plots and
nobs is Nazi hunter Ezra Lieberman discovers a sinister and bizarre plot to rekindle the third right.
Folks, I'm just going to tell you right now that plot involves multiple clones of Hitler.
And I don't know why this movie wouldn't lead by saying there are people trying to clone Hitler
because that is a amazing premise for a movie. And it's Gregory Peck, Lawrence Olivier, James Mason,
and Steve Gutenberg. Your three of the greatest actors of all time and Steve Gutenberg together at
last, the movie's nuts. It's kind of campy. It's very fun. I would check it out for sure. It sounds
like what that Pacino Nazi hunter show was supposed to be. But I always heard that it sucked. Did you ever
watch that? No, I just didn't care. Also, Peel, Peel's new movie is called Nope. It's called
Nope. Yeah. What is the plot of this thing? That's a terrible title, man. Alien, it's coming
to earth. It's got to be a comedy, right? It's, you know, it's like a get out type thing. But I think
that it's like my, my guess is the trailer is going to be they're running, running, running,
and then this giant spaceship appears in front of them and they look at each other go Nope. I mean,
that's how I think they're using the title. But I don't know that for sure. All right. Well, we'll see.
Anyway, um, go ahead. All right, movie. Uh, what was my next one? Oh, lost in America. I mentioned
it earlier, but I didn't watch it. What can I say? It's a wonderful Albert Brooks film. It's a
classic. My, I am of the opinion that real life is a solid effort from Albert Brooks, but not
one of the best. It starts great. And then it kind of gets a little boring. But I think Albert
Brooks's films from the, from Modern Romance, which is the second movie forward, um, go from best
to worst. That said, I enjoy all of them. But I think that modern romance is his masterpiece. I think
lost in America is second place. I think defending your life is third. I think mother is fourth. I
think them uses fifth and looking for comedy in the mother world is sixth. Yeah. Um, so in my opinion,
this is the second best, um, Albert Brooks movie. Um, stars him in Julie Haggardy. They play two, uh,
yuppies that want to drop out of society. Uh, that, that, that begins with one of the greatest
getting fired scenes of all time. Oh, no question. Albert Brooks getting fired from his job.
Uh, it's just, it's just, it's the movies filled with classic like Albert Brooks breakdowns,
uh, which there's nothing funnier. Um, great line that I never picked up before. She makes,
they're when they're first on the road, she makes them the melted cheese in the browning microwave.
Yeah. And he goes, how long does this take? And she goes, uh, 25 seconds. And he's like,
including the browning. And she goes start to finish 25 seconds. And he goes, hmm, great,
great browning element. Which is classic. Albert Brooks is like, there's nothing funny about that line.
There's no show there. Yeah. It's just for some reason. It's funny when he says it. Um,
they fall in hard times because they stop in Vegas, uh, and, and Julie Haggardy gambles away
their nest egg. And then the rest of the movie is them trying to figure things out. It's a great movie.
Albert Brooks said in the interview that they had to add, they said that Julie Haggardy
gambling away the money was so unforgivable. Uh -huh. They had to add a scene to get you back on her side
again. And that scene is when he's yelling at her in the camper about the nest egg.
Right. And the interviewer was like, that's like the most famous scene in the movie. And he's like,
yeah, we added that after test screenings because before he just accepted her back when she said,
sorry, yeah, we had to add that scene. And I was like, wow, talk about a lucky accident man like
Jesus. It's also like classic Albert Brooks that his solution to the Juliet, uh, Haggardy being too
unlikable problem is to make himself equally unlikable to balance it out. That's the beauty of
Albert Brooks. He didn't think, okay, so we got to write in a scene where she helps a sick kid or
something. He's like, no, I'll make myself an asshole so they like her more. It's perfect.
Yeah. He's, uh, he loses in that scene. Yeah. How do you use any part of the word nest egg?
If you're in the, if you're in the woods, you have to point and say that bird lives in a round stick
like, yeah, I'll have things over easy with toast today. Like it's just so fucking funny, man.
Did you go defending your life first? No, I think it went modern romance. I think modern romance is
the best. And I literally think they're a perfect descending order from that. Yeah, I know I agree with
you. Um, all right. I saw and need to give a shout out to one of the best TV shows of the past
five years. Joe, I know you know, the people who did it a bit, uh, search party. I know the creators.
Yeah. I've lost touch with them, but they're very nice people. Very talented.
Glad to hear search party is a completely insane show. And since they knew this was their last season,
they went so far off the rails. It actually becomes an end of the world zombie show in its home stretch
tying it to horror. The show has had zero horror elements up to this point.
Um, it's madness. I think they got in the writer's room and we're like, the world is ending.
Let's just treat it like the world is ending. And it's, there's something very dark about it.
Of course, the show's always very, very dark, but it's so funny. They do a really great job of
bringing in new and crazy and hilarious supporting characters each year. There was, and I wish I had
their name handy, but the, the black woman who played the lawyer last season was an all -time great
character. Um, they have John early who steals the show in a dual role this year. He's also undercover
as a old Jewish scientist. And they have them kind of look like Doc Brown, um, trying to get information
out of a lab, like literally, you know, wearing costumes. His name is Dr. Carpet, that, that character's
name. Um, it's just super funny and bleak. My one kind of criticism of the show is the lead,
a Leah Shaw cat. Shaw cat was nobody's favorite character on arrested development, but in, in typical
Hollywood fashion, it's like, oh, yeah, yeah, she should be the star of the show. Everybody
loved arrested development, but she was the 16th lead on arrested development and, and, and not
the high point of the show. So to me, all the Shaw cat stuff was kind of dull. And I think it's a big
part of the reason that they beefed up the supporting cast to such degree, and they have so many
murderers on that staff, like everybody that comes in kills. The Shaw cat stuff is rough. And in this
season, she's playing somebody who had a near death experience and becomes super enlightened and
super like, oh, like I, I know everything now. And I'm, I'm, I'm in a better place. And it's a great
satire as the show always is, but her playing manic is just, it feels like being around a manic
person. She's very annoying in the show. And it sucks when your lead is the weak link. It rarely
happens, but there are a lot of shows where the lead sucks and everybody around that person is great.
I don't think Shaw cat sucks. I just think she's got the least fun material and the show kind of
drags when she's on screen. That's it. If you've never seen it, I watched the fifth season in one
day, granted I had some COVID booster after effects, but it's a really funny, great show. It's a quick
watch. I urge you to check it out. It's very different than anything else on TV.
I'll close out quick with the Super Bob Einstein movie. Speaking of Albert Brooks, his brother,
Bob Einstein, sadly passed a couple of years ago. They've yet to address it on curb. I don't
understand why they're not mentioning it, but I hope they do at some point because he was a major
player on the show. Yeah, but anyway, this great documentary came out called the Super Bob Einstein
movie covers his career as Super Dave. It's got tons of great interviews in it with his brother,
Albert Brooks, with his other brother, who I didn't know, who works in advertising, I believe,
Larry David, Jeff Garland, you know, the list goes on. It's a great watch. It's a hilarious watch.
The interview clips with Bob Einstein in his own documentary in particular are some of the
funniest. The stories about him are tremendous. It never gets too modeling or sappy when it covers
the fact that he's gone. It really is a celebration of him, and I found it uplifting. It really
put a smile on my face. I suggest a watch. Yeah, I liked it too. It's a very pleasant way to pass
the time if you're a fan of the man, and it's full of laughs because who wouldn't want to watch all
that guys great moments, you know? He's a legend. And his funniest work might be in Modern Romance,
which is also included. Yes. Let's talk about the movie of the day, Deep Cove,
the 1992 American Action Thriller, Deep Cover, starring in three awesome performances.
Larry Fishburn, as he has called in this film, very, why did he change? Do we know? Not
only did he change, he demanded that he be called Lawrence. It was a hard line in the sand for him.
Interesting. Fascinating career on the kid. I mean, he was in Apocalypse Now,
and then just kind of, it's like, for a long time, he was like not really a presence in movies,
then he became a star, then he changed his name. Now he's in everything. He always pops up in a trailer,
you know? He's in a group. He's in a group. As Kristen Wiggs kind of like fuck buddy slash love
interest. He's very funny in the group, or just by kind of doing nothing. But this movie was written
by Michael. You didn't say the other cast members. I'm sorry. I'm scattering all over the place. Larry
Fishburn, Jeff Goldblum, to me in the perfect version of Goldblum, where he is still in the character
and playing a character, but also bringing enough of that weird Goldblum to it. Now when you see
Goldblum in a movie, he's just Jeff Goldblum. And he almost doesn't even try to pretend he's acting
anymore. In this movie, he plays a true like coke, death, disgusting scumbag slash family man.
He's got some amazing monologues in the thing, some bits that I wonder if they were improvised,
but we'll come back to that. And then almost stealing the damn movie Charles Martin Smith from American
Graffiti as the like racist police chief. Wow. Is he good? Yeah, we need more good guy and stuff.
I don't know why are we getting so little? He's still around. Where the hell is he?
68. Where's the where's the campaign to get him back in movies like like with Moranis? He's
another Moranis in my opinion. It's guys looking at a picture of him. He looks fantastic. He looks
better than Moranis. He's great. He's great. He's so good. So good in this movie. But
and then directed by the great Bill Duke, the great Bill Duke beloved character actor. If you don't
know him by name, look him up right now and you will. He is 78 at the moment and still kicking, you know,
from commando predator, menace society, Mandy, great, great, great, great, great scene in Mandy.
But this movie it opens in a flashback Cleveland 1972 and a young Larry Fishburn is the son of
this crack addicted guy who goes in to rob a liquor store and gets shot and his last words are
basically don't do this shit. Stay away from this life. Ed from there, it goes to
Coke. Not crack. Coke. That's important. Coke. Yeah. Sorry. Larry Fishburn looking phenomenal
who is a I don't drink. I don't do drugs. You know, straight up fly right cop and the force
and the movie opens with Charles Martin Smith chief character asking several black cops what is the
difference between a black man and an N word. This is like the opening of the movie. Yeah. The first
guy says I don't know and he's let go. It's almost like a joke. The second guy jumps up and wants to
kick the shit out of Charles Martin Smith reasonably so. And then Larry Fishburn says the N word is the
one who would answer that question. That is called back perfectly in the final scene of the film.
Yes. But man, I watched I watched this once when I got the Blu -ray about a month ago and I rewatched
it for this pod and you really admire the structure of this thing when you watch it. It's like a Swiss
watch. And you know, as you might imagine or guess Fishburn, given the title Fishburn is sent
into undercover work in the drug trade. Yes. And the deeper he gets the more he has to do to not
blow his cover, i .e. killing and selling drugs and whatever. And the deeper he gets the more that
line gets blurred between is he a good guy or a bad guy? Has he become what he's beheld as Elliott
said in the untouchables? And next to the untouchables, this is I would say this is the other one of the
other great films that examines that like how far are you willing to go? You know, there's the great
thing in the untouchables. You know, you go through this door and ask does no turn back. And you see how
crazy it gets. And this is that movie too where it's like or that type of story I mean where he just
keeps getting deeper and deeper. There's the part where he kills that one drug dealer who's obsessed
with Schwarzenegger. Who's awesome in this? Yeah. And the drug dealer when he shoots him in the chest
in the bathroom, the drug deal is going, you fucking bitch, you shot me, you fucking because he can't,
he doesn't always a cop, but he can see that he doesn't have it in him. Yeah. And then he does it.
And then eventually in the movie too, Fishburn starts to do drug. He starts to do blow because he's
like, fuck it. My department isn't behind me. They've left me on my own. Yeah, it's it's a classic
kind of film film noir thing of like the guy who with all these bright ideas goes up, you know, tries
to go up against the people he's trying to bring down, but learns that everyone is fucked. Everyone
is corrupt. And you know, it's a it's a it's a full circle. It's kind of like nightmare alley,
which we just discussed here. It's like, I'll never be that guy. And then by the end he's fully that guy.
But the way they do it though is just it's just beautifully done. It's beautifully done. He
becomes that guy. But he then in one of the great heroic movies, Mo movie moments in cinema, he
redeems himself and he gives me chills in the sequence at the end when the DEA agent or drug
agent whenever played by what's the third who's also awesome in this always awesome. Yeah.
He's he's basically stopping single -handedly the big bus to the end of the movie.
Jeff Goldblum shoots him. Fishburn finally breaks. And there's that awesome scene where he's going,
you shouldn't have done that, David. And then finally, he reveals that he's a cop and Goldblum goes,
I don't care, just get get in the fucking van. Yeah, yeah, you should he goes, you shouldn't have done
that like a perfect delivery and then it cuts to a tide of Goldblum's face because but I did it.
Okay, so what are we going to do now? It's just perfect. The awesome heroic moment, which is like the
it's like it's almost like when they when Hogan would fall asleep in the ring and then they on the
third time they raised his arm it would stay up and start pumping. Fishburn is holding Clarence Williams
as he's dying and he goes, you have the right to remain silent and you're like, he's back. I just
got chills talking about it. You're like, he he he kept he kept he kept his honor like he's he's
back. He's still a cop. You know, like because because there's a minute where you don't know, you're like,
I think this fucking guy's going to like, this is it. He's going to like sell these drugs and leave.
And but yeah, it was it's and you're almost rooting for it at that point because his his people let him
down so bad. Yeah, Charles Martin Smith, who as every bad guy in every movie made from 1980 to 1995, he has
to get punched in the stomach at the end by the hero, but it's very satisfying. And Charles Martin
Smith is actually the one pressing snipes to go deeper into this world, you know, he's like fishburn
big. What did I say? Snipes. Sorry, I was okay to world. But yeah, he's telling him like,
you got to you got to get out there or you got to like get new clothes, get a nicer apartment,
like start living the life, have some fun. And of course, when fishburn starts doing that, he gets
swept up in it. Well, who you never see his family pass the initial scene after that, he's just like
some scumbag out of the town. But he, oh, no, you see the wife in another amazing scene where
Goldblum, she's like, well, when is it going to be enough? You know, you've got a family that
loves you. Why do you need the respect of these people? And she walks away. I just don't know what you
want. And he sits alone and goes, I want my cake eat it too. Then I want my cake and need it too.
It's just insane. But perfect. That's up there with the scene with his daughter, where he's doing the
times tables, whether three times four, three times four. And then she keeps fucking it up. And he goes,
honey, she will get this. And he starts pounding the table. Yeah. Like it's the first that's how you
beat him. It's it's so I love when he and Snipes are walking back into the house. And my assumption,
as this was not in the script, and Bill Duke was like, just start improvising about something on the way
in and we'll pick it up. But Goldblum goes, what's the wildest sexual experience you've ever had?
Have you ever been with two women? And fishburn's like, yeah, you know, I have. And he goes up,
you know, it's interesting. Sometimes they get that discharge, you know, that big glob of discharge
when they get really excited. And they just go into a scene about drugs after that. But the movie is
full of those kind of moments. There's the crime boss with the mustache, the bald guy who's an amazing
character actor. He's he used to be on Sanford and son. He played the months for a recon friend
that Fred Sanford was outwardly racist towards because he didn't trust Puerto Rican people on the show.
But he's awesome. He's got my favorite line in the movie. Oh, he's growing balls now. I mean,
the guy is just so fucking sinister. Yeah. You got that great. A feminine heavy set guy that I've
seen. The guy from the biggest nest. Just the fact that that guy's in this movie is so weird.
Is he a lover of the mustache guy? Is he an instrument? Is he a fan of him? And they're like obsessed
with him. There's that crazy scene where they're doing the slap game. And he's trying to embarrass Goldblum
and Goldblum's hands are all red. And that guy's going, oh, it hurts. It hurts. There's the other
great character actor, the guy from Malcolm X. Yeah. Who's just fucking incredible in this?
Who plays another guy where I'm like, how is this guy not one Oscars? I don't understand.
Like, well, he played the, what Joe, what do you say now for mentally handicapped? What is the new?
He played the guy and do the right thing who was mentally handicapped. Yeah. Yeah. And then in Malcolm
X, he's the guy that they link up with. Yeah. He's half Italian and half black and he's bragging. And
that's the great scene in Malcolm X. Yeah. Where he's going, which side is this? Is he Italian side?
Is what he's putting the gun to his nose? Right. He is so good in this as a guy in a bar that you
would be like, I hope this guy doesn't speak to me. And then, you know, Fishburn's like, I knew it.
He was going to come over and you know, talk his shit, whatever. But like he's, he's that he's
everyone in it is perfectly cast. It is an assemblage of amazing characters put together by one of the
great character actors, Bill Duke. And I think my guess is he let the scenes get a little improvisatory.
He let the scenes kind of, you know, build like it's a movie that feels alive in a way most movies
don't where it feels like you can imagine everybody talking once they y 'all cut and they didn't just
shoot a scene. It feels like you're picking up actual spontaneous moments to shame. We didn't get more
directing work from Bill Duke. He did, he did the cemetery club with Danny Ayello and Olympia
Duke caucus and all those old white ladies after deep cover, which is very strange to me.
Because that's like a steel magnolias type. Yeah. Yeah. He's done some, he's got movies that
preceded this that I now want to see. I didn't even know. I didn't know until I got the criterion
that Bill Duke directed this. Yeah. As I was watching it, I was like, who directed this man?
And I was like, oh my god, it's Bill Duke. I didn't know that. And then when I was starting
watching the special features, I thought he had directed all these other movies. And I had no idea.
I thought he was strictly a character actor. And almost a bearing of the lead to have not
mentioned yet. This is the soundtrack. And I remember they plugged this in the commercial that played on
TV with new music from Dr. Dre featuring Snoop Dogg. This was, and I was such a rap fan,
and this was, this was, when this got announced, nobody was sure just yet if NWA had broken up or
they just had or whatever it was. And this is it. This is the song that launched Dre and Snoop Dogg as
the powerhouse team and death row records like the title track from this movie. It's crazy, you know,
like it's, it's just wild. Like this movie's groundbreaking in many, many ways. It's very, very good.
I'm so glad that criterion put a spotlight on it because it's definitely one. I never would have
watched again. It's, it's available right now on Hulu and actually it's not on criterion channel
which is kind of weird. It's on Hulu and HBO Max. Well, it's a new release. So they're probably waiting
to add it to the channel. Try to get people to buy it, right? I would imagine, I guess. Yeah.
I wonder if you put in the Schwarzenegger obsession because Duke is clearly friends with Schwarzenegger.
He's been in several movies. There's a lot of shit where I'm like, was that supposed to be in there?
With Goldblum gets him off on the in the courtroom and he goes out of 5 ,000. I'm like, so weird.
Like Goldblum is like these hip hop. It's almost like Jim Jarmushy like ghost dog. Yeah. Well,
I mean, Goldblum is playing a guy, which is what we didn't even really mention yet about the movie
is that in addition to all this stuff, it's an amazing commentary on capitalism and on cultural
appropriation. Goldblum is what we would have called at that time, W -I -G -G -A, at that time was the
term. But Fishburn is clearly very kind of annoyed and disgusted by the way he tries to sort of
appropriate black culture and he's always fucking black women and he's talking down to Fishburn in a
lot of ways. Remember that scene that's really amazing where he's calling him? He said, when I saw
you were like a panther, like a beast. Yeah, he's like, excuse me. But it plays real. Yeah,
because he's like, you're overstepping your boundaries now. That's a great scene. That's a great
commentary on what guys like that do. It's funny. Big J. Ogerson and I say that to each other
when we like, if one of us is following the other guy on the stage as we're passing, we'll be like,
you were like a magnificent jungle cat up there. We always quote that to each other.
Yeah, but yeah, it's just a great, great, great film from every angle. It's just really,
really well done. And my Michael Tolkien, who did the player of the same year and did the
rapture of the year before, which is an awesome movie I talked about on here with Mimi Rodgers
about the end of the world. But that was a great writer. Apparently did an uncredited rewrite
on the amazing Dawn of the Dead remake. Oh, well, that makes sense as it's one of
Zack Snyder's only good movies. Anyway, my hog's way up for deep cover. Super way up. It's going
to be a real treat for you when you check it out. It's just it's one of those movies where like the
thriller aspect works, but it does everything else beautifully as well. The character moments,
the commentary, the soundtrack kicks ass. It's just a great movie. My one grievance, I guess, would be
Bill Duke's constant that flashing zoom effect that he keeps doing, which is like show offy, but it
also doesn't look very good. It's like not his strong suit. You know how like whenever anybody's
getting out of a car, they do like four zoom -ins on them. Yeah, no. And you know, I wonder though
at the time if that was something a little more unique because that's something that you see a lot
of now or have seen a lot of since then. So I just not done well. It looks bad. Like it was done
in post or something. I don't know, but I feel like it's supposed to be idea is it's supposed to feel
like you're there. Right. I would news camera would get the shot. So, you know, dock you style or
whatever, but but I don't know. Anyway, folks, we'll be back next month with I don't know yet. We
might do Boba Fett. We've discussed it. And we'll see what comes down the pike. We'll think
where he's usually kind of a dumping ground, but it's also a time when a lot of horror movies usually
come out. So we'll let you know. Maybe some more criterians. You know, there's a lot of these horror
criterians that Pat and I haven't seen yet or Pat can revisit and I can watch for the first time.
So I don't know. We'll figure it out though. With all that. With me out of town and Joe working
at the sandwich shop, there may be a few instances like this where we get it up quote a little late,
but really all we've ever pledged you people is we'd give you two a month. So they like don't say you
people don't always expect the first and the 15th is all I'm saying. It might be a little later.
Yeah, we promise you this. You'll get you'll get four episodes every month regardless. And the
fans, by the way, Emily was nice enough to post. Please everybody be patient. It's coming and then I
wrote we're going to have these up by Wednesday at the latest and they will be. So we thank you
everybody for sticking with us. We love your support. You can follow me at Jota Rosa Comedy on Instagram
and Twitter. Please visit Joey roses NYC dot com for all hours and information regarding my new bar slash
sandwich shop and come visit us. Please. And oh, if you hear this when you hear this, I'm in I'm in
Buffalo at helium comedy club the last weekend of this month. And then the first week in a February
I'm at bananas in rather for New Jersey. And then in March, I'm at the punchline in Philadelphia. And
then in May, I'm at the Creek and Cave in Austin, Texas. Go to Jota Rosa info dot com for all ticket
links and show info. And I want to see you out there. Please.
I'm the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram. Not much else to plug. Love you all. Thank you, Emily.
Thank you to our Patreon fans and listeners. Tell your friends. Tell your wives. Tell your kids.
We love you. Happy New Year. Stay safe. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.