Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help
you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
There's a new podcast app that delivers chilling true crime stories straight to your mobile device every day.
They release a new episode that investigates the gruesome true acts of America's worst serial killers
and you can explore into the minds of psychopaths and murderers.
To get started, find and download Murder Minute from the App Store or visit murderminute .com.
That's M -U -R -D -E -R -M -I -N -U -T -E .com to get your daily dose of true crime creepiness delivered
straight to your mobile device.
It's a cool show!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
and as far as we're concerned.
And that's what she said.
Oh boy.
Oh!
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Joe.
All right, Pat.
I'm good.
Been ranting since I came in as Joe.
Sometimes we ran about things,
but we can't talk about them, the show.
It's what our relationship has been boiled down to.
I feel now Pat walks in here from work.
Rants to me about his day.
no dinner on the table. We do our business, which in married terms, this podcast is our sex time.
Sure. And then he leaves. And then he's gone again. He goes, he leaves right out the door. I got
shit to do. I said, I feel like I'm living with a ghost anymore. It's true. Joe listens to me,
rant until I stop talking. I listen to Joe rant until he stops talking. We record the podcast and
me go our separate way. And we're
ranting from different world. That's
right. Yours is a very business
related. Mine's very personal
related. You know, I'm around this
place all day alone. You think
this isn't a job for me. That kind
of stuff. And meanwhile, I'm out
doing a bunch of penthouse deals.
Hand shakes. You mean for the
magazine penthouse? Yes. That's
right. You're selling subscriptions
door to door. Some selling, some
posing. Uh, before we
We start here, folks.
I'd love, if I may, to get on with the show.
And in doing so, on with the don't change for you, don't change a thing for me.
What song is that?
It's called Don't Change by Inaccess.
And I heard it in the car.
It's the best inaccess song.
Wow.
That's not get carried away.
The best in excess song early early in their career. I believe it's on an album called like Hoochie Boochie or something
But it's a great song what you need yes, what you need is is wait. What's what you need you mean?
I need you to know that's I need you tonight. What you need is
Sure, yeah, that's a great song. That's an amazing song. I also like
Miss defa me
mystify is a good song I also like suicide blonde so I also like I get
white that's a hard I get that mixed up with the talking head song it's like
nothing can come between us
ruminum wannabe I like it next I like the slow one yeah I'm trying to never tear
part. That's it. Never tear us apart. Just down, down, down.
Gouraching saxophone. So I would never heard that much sax outside of a Bruce Lee, a
Bruce Springsteen song in my life or a Bruce Lee song. I watched a behind the music on it
and I learned that it was actually not a sax. Somebody was slowly stepping on and then releasing
the pressure from a goose. So it's just a goose going, and then kind of leaned back on it.
And you criticized my, what joke am I at the live show? Did you criticize about an animal?
It was way worse than this joke. I'm looking at a picture of some sort of aquatic bird.
It's what popped that into my head. That's a swan swan. That's the cover of Faith No Moreer's
Angel Dust, which is arguably their best album. Okay. I got the vinyl out the other night. I
I actually was playing it on Halloween,
getting geared up to dark album.
I was getting geared up for the, for a night on the town.
Where did you go on All Hallows Eve?
I met up with my friend, Julie McCullough.
Our friend, Julie McCullough.
He's an acquaintance.
He's my friend.
Sure.
And he's an old friend.
I've known him for, Christ, 13 years or something.
And his lovely, lovely fiance, Meg.
And he was engaged.
Maybe we cool it with a double loveless in a probe.
What do you say we make a comedy movie?
We bring back Ricky, who's the guy to place Hagrid in Hagrid?
Yeah Hagrid in a Robbie Coltrane.
Robbie Coltrane.
We get Robbie Coltrane back in a Pope role from the Pope must die at.
Yeah, and we call it inappropriate.
And it's about a, you know, sort of a low -class,
sort of gambler guy that has to pose as the Pope for a while.
And it's not a sequel to the Pope must die it?
No, it's just, it's just, I feel like investors
might not be intrigued by a sequel to that.
It's a spiritual sequel.
Okay, sure.
It's the same universe, but maybe not the same characters.
Like how the good son was a spiritual sequel to Home Alone.
Yeah, yeah, you see what I mean.
Anyway, we went out, Meg does, it makes a wonderful artist and she did our makeup and she did
Julian and her up like zombies and it was tremendous and then I had to wear my glasses
I was like, Meg, I can't do a zombie because I got to wear glasses all night and she said,
well, what if I just put a bullet hole in your head and she did and it looked really cool
and then we went out drinking and makeup and we had a blast, I had a wonderful time with
those two. They're very lovely people. Where did you go? Well, we went to a little place called
the Roost. Okay. A big surprise. I could have guessed. And then we trotted on down to another place
called the Bigfoot lot. Sure. Sure. It was the usual. We were about to go downtown to a bar called
I think it's called like little easier something. It's like it's like a New Orleans style bar. Uh -huh.
Yeah. But run by little people. Yes. Yes. Yes. Uh, and, uh, and they're all real easy.
You can have sex with anyone at the drop of a hat. That's nice. Uh, the, uh, it's a
New Orleans style bar in Julian and mentioned, like, we should go there. And I was like, okay,
but it's downtown. And my, the whole Uber ride to his house, I was like, uh, that's going
to be a fucking shit show down there. But I was like, you know what? I'm not going to be
that guy, I'm not going to show up and be like, you know, guys, you really want to go
now, you know, I was like, just go with the flow. So I showed up and in the 11th hour
as we were about to call an Uber, Julian was like, do you think we should just go to the
roost? It's always the better option. Yeah, Meg was like, oh, yeah, I told, and I was
like, guys, thank God you said that. Yeah, this whole time I've been dreading that that's
going to be a shit show down there tonight. Halloween at a New Orleans style bar downtown
town LA, forget it.
Not only do I not do that stuff anymore
and nobody asks me to do it.
I feel like everyone is just kind of staying in their home
are going to a place nearby.
Well, I texted you,
and said are you gonna be out at any point tonight?
You said you were working, but that's why it's us.
I had a great Halloween.
I worked till about 8 .45.
I came home, I made a bowl of grapes,
and then I fell asleep at the kitchen table.
Do you get any trick or treaters?
not a one, but it was 8 .45, but they don't, they don't come up. It's all hills in my neighborhood.
Oh, come up. And near the house, they stay away from them. They say, they say, old man,
wash lives up there. Sure. And, you know, rumor has it. I slipped a couple of razor blades
into an apple or two a few years back. Rumor has it. He was once married to the devil. That's
Shout out to my lovely wife, yeah anyway, she's wonderful. I love her.
It's going out town every weekend. I feel like I'm a single man.
It'd be nice if you hung out with me once. I'm here, you know.
Not for work. You're married to your goddamn job.
And speaking of which, I almost forgot to bring this up.
All right, I told you privately that I was gonna say something about this guy publicly on the podcast and I wasn't kidding
Okay, one of these one of the fans on the Facebook page. Oh, yeah, what's his name Bob Moskovitz? I think Ed Moskovitz. Yeah
I don't ever do this. I don't ever go after one person personally. I'm doing it. It's fucking guy writes
That were lazy and entitled yeah to have a patreon up
for this podcast because all it consists of is us getting together and just talking. Oh,
yeah, Ed, is it that easy? Is that all it is Ed? You just get, you just get together and talk
into a microphone aimlessly for an hour and somehow it's just magically entertaining. Is it
that easy Ed? Does it have nothing to do with the fact that both of us have worked for the last 15
fucking years to raise our profiles high enough to a point where we can even dare ask for a
Patreon contribution to something like this.
Does it have anything to do with the fact
that we put this thing out for three years
for fucking free and never made a dime
and never once complained?
By the way, still put it out for free.
Yeah, you're still asking for a bonus episode
if you want it.
Yeah, and if you don't contribute,
you still get four free episodes every month
and you're gonna fucking complain
that we have the nerve to try to make some cash.
What do you think we're raking in on this thing, dude?
What do you think we're making?
Okay?
It's, I'm a blue collar guy.
I carry debt.
I live paycheck to paycheck.
I pay rent.
I don't have a car.
What the fuck do you think we're making off of this thing?
Unbelievable, man.
Like, so, so I'm just gonna say this flat out.
Because I've seen a couple of these people pop up via via through the grapevine.
because I'm not on Facebook, but it gets back to me, people.
I don't know if you think I don't listen,
but I got ears in the streets.
So I hear about these things.
This was the one that I was most peved about.
If you feel this way, then don't listen to the fucking show.
It's that easy.
We got a million, not a million.
It was a million, Ed might have a point.
But we've got a bunch of great fans out there
that we cherish, that are wonderful supportive people.
We don't ask for anything out of line with them.
They don't ask for anything out of line with us.
It's a very, very even exchange here.
We enjoy doing the show for those people.
And anybody else that wants to sit around and fucking bitch
because of a $10 fucking contribution
that we're saying is, we're not even asking you for it.
We're saying if you feel like doing it great
and if you don't find, just beat it, man.
Just fucking beat it.
And we have not forgotten about having to make up
for the two miss months because I also saw a couple
of people griping about that.
Guys, can you give us a chance?
We're not sitting around all day just doing this podcast.
We do other things.
I travel a lot for work.
Pat works a lot at his show.
It's hard, okay?
Okay, we are doing our best and this is not aimed at the entire audience.
This is aimed at like five fucking people that are so entitled in this day and age of
the internet where they think everything should be free without cost or hassle at all and
delivered to them with a nice little fucking bow on it, exactly when and where they want
it.
I mean, it's telling us entitled is an interesting thing for somebody who's posting that to
Facebook.
Yeah.
Yeah, because he was also like,
it's just two guys talking to each other.
Well, sure, but I feel like people really enjoy listening
to us talk or we wouldn't have people come into our shows
and et cetera, but if it is that easy,
I certainly recommend you put together
the Ed Moskowitz hour and, you know,
you can charge your two listeners five bucks
and make yourself $10 and go buy a fuckin' life.
Yeah Ed, why don't you talk to a buddy
and do a tape recorder for an hour?
Let's see how entertaining it is.
As if, as if 16 years on the fucking road have nothing to do with the fact that I may be able to talk into a microphone for a while and keep an entertaining.
You know the amount of goddamn free radio I've done in my life before I ever even touched a podcast microphone.
It's, I'm so fucking appalled by that stance.
Unbelievable, man.
Anyway, we love the rest of you.
I got it right here.
I took a photo of it.
I know you sent me the photo.
That's how I heard about it.
Yeah, it's like criticizing the production of the shit.
Really just irritating shit.
Yeah, it's like, look, you get four episodes free of month.
If you can donate, great.
If you can't, we don't care.
Don't care.
If you've never given anybody shit about that.
We've never guilted you for not donating.
We've never pushed for donations.
We've simply said, here it is.
Here's what it is.
That's it.
it. Most of our merch money goes back into creating more merch. Okay, it's like, it's
like all this stuff is just here because we want to have a connection with the people
that care and are enjoying this because we love those people. I met a delightful young
couple the other night. They were dressed as Wayne and Garth at our live show. I don't
have their full names. I don't know if they want me to say them, but I wish I did because
They only remember the bad folks.
This guy was contributing twice a month,
made up an alias so he could contribute twice
because he wanted to.
It's outrageous.
Thank you, sir, whoever that is.
And it's unnecessary.
You don't have to do that.
I'll find out.
And also too.
You'll get your shadow.
Also too, why don't you go to Ed?
Why don't you go try to find another podcast
who tells their fans, please guys,
don't fly in to see this live show.
Please don't break your bank to do this.
We'll get to you eventually.
We please like let us let us accommodate you. It's best we can. We feel bad. Please don't do that I'm fucking real
I'm fucking real and then people go can you believe Trump is president? Yes
This is why because everybody's greedy
This is what happens. You want to be greedy? Then the greed pig becomes president. That's what happens
God damn it and now somebody else say I wish they didn't get political on the show
We didn't get political. I called him a greed pig.
I mean, even if you're pro -Trump, you can't argue. He's not a greed pig.
I mean, give me a break. I'm a greed pig.
Many people in the lame stream news media have referred to me as greed pig.
Recently, especially for a man who runs something called a hog house,
it seems an interesting claim to make that I am a greed pig.
All right, I'm done.
I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see
I watched
8th grade the Bo Burnham vehicle
folks
A really excellent movie again that I never want to see again as long as I live
But if you've seen welcome to the dollhouse
Todd solens's first film, which is a real warts and all portrayal of adolescence
And everybody was like, oh, it's too depressing.
It's too much.
I actually don't know that you can get depressing enough
if you're trying to accurately depict
like what most people's eighth grade experience is like.
Certainly mine was a hellish nightmare.
And eighth grade comes real close.
It's real rough to watch.
The lead actress is incredible.
Bo Burnham, as a stand up, I like more than I like
laugh really hard at, but he's clearly got
lot of talent and he's an excellent filmmaker and this is a pretty incredible first movie for a
guy. It felt like watching a young girl actually go through eighth grade and not a fun way to be
honest with you but a great movie. Now I have a question. I was going to start today's with Shocker.
Never saying it. Okay. My question is, if I lend it to you today, would you have time to watch it?
Sure. I think we should actually do an episode on Shocker. A couple of the fans when I mentioned
at the live show. We're like, Oh, yeah, man, please talk about shocker. All right.
We'll do a little. This is people out of the stairs today. So we'll do a couple West
Cravens in a row. Hold off on shocker. We'll call this month Craven for Craven month
with Pat and Joe. We're also going to do it and up coming up the nightmare before Christmas
as a little transition. Oh, that's right. Joe and I saw the film live with Danny Elfman,
and Catherine O 'Hara, Paul Rubens and others.
Yeah, we'll talk about it, though, another time.
I was intoxicated, but I remember most of them.
I saw a wonderful documentary called
Every Other Day is Halloween.
Okay, never heard of it again.
It's a documentary.
So you remember how the local TV stations
used to have those like Saturday night horror hosts?
Sure.
Elvira.
Yeah.
Well, she was sort of like a national one that kind of Joe Flaherty played a great one
on SFTV.
Anyway.
Floyd.
There's a documentary about one of these guys who played, what was his real name, I'm blanking
on his real name, because I didn't know who he was until I saw this.
is Dick Dysel, a television personality,
and he played a character called Count Gore -Vidal,
which is very funny to me.
On the same channel, he also played Bozo the clown,
kind of space guy named Captain 20,
but like it's basically like, it was UHF,
the movie UHF, like he had shows like that.
Yeah, like his Bozo show was like the Stanley janitor show.
Right.
Then he had like Stanley Spadowski.
Yeah, science fiction goofy kid show and then he had a horror show.
And but anyway, it was just an awesome love letter to this guy
and like the work he did and the influence he had on kids growing
up in the 70s and 80s that loved horror and even into the 90s.
And you know, they how they all grew up and how they remembered him
and now they made this movie about him and he's still alive
and he's still out there doing it.
He was one of the front runners or four fathers,
I should say, rather, of internet streaming.
Like he got on the internet thing before anybody
and like when he realized I can't do this on TV anymore,
they won't pay for it.
He set up a studio in his basement
and started doing it on the internet.
And now like his whole gig is,
you go to his website and he streams
like these old horror movies.
All right, awesome.
And he's also one of these guys that made the total flip
of like God damn it, why isn't the network behind me too now being like I would
never go back to a network. This is I am free. I do everything I want to do on
worldwide. It's just a great you know little low -budget documentary. The guy
that made it is named Jeff Krillick who also made heavy metal parking lot.
which is a famous, you know, underground documentary.
Say it.
And, you know, they interview a bunch of other, like,
local horror hosts, and it's endearing.
Even though these guys are horror -efficient autos
and host these horror movies,
there's a very, like, kid -friendly vibe to all of it,
you know, like, it's very fun and innocent,
and, you know, most of the movies are just goofy,
and, you know, it's like the thing from Planet Nine,
whatever the fuck you know. So it's just a really nice documentary. I really enjoyed it.
All right. I got a shout out probably my favorite thing in comedy all year thus far,
although admittedly there's not a lot of competition. The new Adam Sandler special on Netflix.
people, of course, have a lot of opinions about him. I have long said, the man's sense
of humor, I think it's clearly much more in line with his early, strange, really like
different comedically work. It's hard to call it work, but Billy Madison, happy Gilmore,
et cetera. Those movies are so much weirder and more interesting than even most comedy that's
It's not mainstream.
He kind of reached a big audience with it, but it's a very bizarre sort of comedy.
And there's touches of it in all of his movies, even the worst of them.
Ridiculous six has a very funny scene about the invention of baseball.
There's always like a few things that you're like, oh, wow, that was kind of cool or interesting
or funny.
But the man's clearly gotten lazy.
So this special is just like, I'm going to get back to my roots, do some 30 -second comedy songs.
I hate comedy songs, but usually it's because they're four minutes long.
Now, he did perfect comedy songs.
I saw this as well.
The thing about comedy songs is once you get the joke, get out.
And most of them go back to it five, six verses and you're like, stop.
he gives you the joke, he twists it in an interesting way, gets off.
Yeah.
The standup in terms of bits he was doing was also surprisingly strong for a guy who's never even been a great standup.
I think he was a good standup. I just think he got out so young.
Yeah, and I never saw him do that.
There wasn't a lot of documentation of it, but if you can catch, I used to have some DVDs that had old Chandler Clitch.
If you can catch his early, it's only early.
Yeah, but before he was on SNL, it's really fucking funny. Yeah, and it's all the shit
he brought to SNL and then brought into Billy Madison, which is why I was so disappointed
as a fan of the guy from his stand -up first when he started to do only stuff like Mr.
Deeds or whatever. Sure. You know, I was like, man, like Mr. Deeds though has those weird
bits too. It's got tutorial that the sneaky bit. It's got it's it's got it's moments. Big
Daddy has those moments for sure, but you know what I mean like I just
There's less and less with each passing movie. Yeah, I missed him being weird
Like his early stuff was like truly what you would have called alternative comedy in the early 90s
And this is too. There's still people being snobby about it
But I mean it's called a hundred percent fresh. I think it has done very well in terms of
Reviews and stuff. I see a lot of positive feedback on Twitter
And it's like the negative reviews that I've read are so hilariously snobby where it's like there's nothing deep here and etc
etc. Deep
Comedy does not have to be deep, and I don't know when this changed, but it is so frustrating
It changed when what's it called came out and nothing against her, but it changed when
Well, it was a long time called Eleanor
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
She was so far from the first.
I mean, like this move to every best comedy spot
at the Emmys is always up for, it's always dramas.
It's like marvelous mismasal, transparent.
These are dramas and they're being pushed as comedies.
And I'm not even saying they're bad shows.
But -
Oh, they're wonderful shows.
They're just, you know, just don't say that they're comedies.
Right.
And Silly is this bad word in comedy.
I get that note at work the often they're like you know it just seems a little silly or something
It's like yeah comedy a huge part of comedy should be silly. I like silly
It's my problem with so much of modern horror
It's the same thing happens with modern horror and we are gonna do an episode about haunting of Hill House
But I will say this about the show
Right now
That is not a horror show
It's a family drama that has some horror stuff in it.
That's what it is.
You watch a movie, for instance, crimes and misdemeanors.
You would never say, that movie is a comedy.
Now you would.
You wouldn't have them, but now you would.
People take these dramas and they say they're gut bustingly funny
and they're not.
No, people take these horror movies and say this is an exercise and terror and they're not
their
dramas that have little elements of this other genre you like in them and
There's a big fucking difference. I'm sorry. There's just a big difference and uh, I
I agree with you. You know, I'm kind of tired of people saying only this heavy stuff is like
Especially now, do you need more heaviness in your life now?
Are you crazy?
I just, I mean, this is a guy who obviously has a billion dollars
and it's like, maybe people wanted to get a little deeper.
We saw that with like funny people, you know?
A three hour movie, like nobody wants to watch a rich guy
complain about his life.
It's got, this is a guy just like, I'm gonna make people laugh.
And he does.
he's 51 he looks 30 he just kind of came out and slapped everybody around at
their own game and it's kind of awesome. I always watch these new specials on
Netflix and stuff and I'm like okay I didn't laugh once and here's the thing
nobody saying nobody saying heavy can't be funny but the point is is if if you're
gonna go heavy you got to make it funny why can't there be different kinds of
comedy. Well, there can't be. But the cat Williams, I know you know, the last cat Williams
special was incredible. Yeah. He slaughters from front to back half of the goddamn thing that's
him talking about Trump. Yeah. And complaining about Trump. But it's funny. Yeah. Make it funny.
You giving a dissertation is not funny. I'm sorry. Words have meanings. Yeah. You never hear anything
about that cat Williams special either. No, because because you're crazy. Well, he gets written off
because he, you know, he's, he's nuts.
Yeah.
But I think you know, you can't do that hour and be nuts.
That's the, an hour of a very smart guy who's just choosing to talk about things in a
way that makes him seem a little nuts.
Um, yeah, so I just, I agree with you.
I think the sandwich special was fantastic.
I think it was nice to see a guy just coming out and having fun.
Here's what I really liked about it.
Having fun and being himself.
Yeah.
It's the same thing I love about Reagan.
It's the same thing I love about Maria Bamford.
It's, there are comics that go out there
and are so true, while I love Cat Williams.
and they're so true to themselves.
That to me is important.
You know, a lot of these specials I watch,
it's somebody trying to make a point
and it's painfully fucking obvious.
Yeah.
It's somebody trying to be cute
Or trying to be weird, or trying to be any one of a dozen things that people do in comedy right now except for
Being themselves and being just normally organically funny. Yeah, and it's it's boring
It's like this is a pose. I don't believe this. I don't think you're really this person
But you watch something like the sandwich special you go
This is that I think this is who this guy is like he's a good weird guy the other thing
I saw in reviews is like he he it's lazy because he'll bring up a topic
and then move on to another topic.
That's not lazy, that's his style of comedy,
and there can be different styles.
He brings up and it like, okay, my kids,
I have to go to school three times a week.
It's thirsty Thursday, so I have to go in
and pour them a drink or whatever.
And he's like, I saw my dad at school once.
That was my favorite stand -up bit,
where his dad comes into class
and asks him where the rake is.
Then he's like, where's the rake?
It wasn't on the nail.
And then he's like, well dad, it's all right.
It's not all right, where's the rake?
I was dying laughing at that.
that it felt very specific, it felt very personal.
And I saw like a young Adam Sandler and his dad
have painted this quick immediate picture
of their relationship for me.
As did the bit about when his dad shaved.
And it was the only time he saw his dad be vulnerable
because he shaved and realized he had made a mistake
and shaving off his beard.
That's like really cool character sketches
that he pops out and then moves on to an interpole song
about peeing in the shower, which was also very funny.
Yes, but like that can be comedy too
That's that's honestly what I loved about it is that it's not like if he does bring up a topic
I'm not interested in I got to listen to him talk about it for 30 minutes. Yes. I had a blast with it
And then at the end by the way he sings incredibly sincere hard felt song about Chris Farley that everyone
I know has everyone I know has got an emotional watching and then he sings a song about his wife
And how much he loves his wife? I could do without the emotional songs. I'm not saying they're touching
It's the wife song sure but I think he felt like if I'm gonna talk about anal with my wife who I love
I need to give her a little something. No, no, it's comedy. It's comedy. It's a joke
But he created an evening where like a husband and wife could watch this thing
You get you never see romance and a comedy special you can turn off before you get to the heartfelt stuff if you want
But it just kind of had it all and I was very impressed by it
I think I I will stand by this I think comedy should be
funny. And no argument here. And if there's a thing that's not funny, then that's not comedy.
Sure. It can be something appreciated. The song can be heartfelt and beautiful,
then net can be moving and touching. But don't say it's comedy when it's not funny. Comedy
means funny. Drama means not funny. That's my take. So if you're going to do a comedy special,
I don't want to see the love song about Chris Farley in it. I love Chris Farley.
Right.
I'm a huge fan.
But I don't think Samler really cares what your opinion of that would be clearly.
Well, I don't think anybody does.
I'm just saying while we're on the subject, keep it funny, I could do without the heartfelt
stuff at the end.
I mean, you turn it off.
You turn it off.
You know, I used to love the buddy -hacket stuff, but like that he closes special with like,
I have a song for my daughter.
And he'd be like, a flower grows in a dirt patch.
It's beauty in the wilderness and it would like get all serious. I hated that. I hated when like
Like lamp and Ellie would walk around the end to be like you took a joke because we're all equal. You see I hate the lesson part
You know, I'm like, I don't I don't need this just give me the fucking jokes and leave
Right, yeah, that's me. I don't know
But I largely feel the same. I just kind of felt like it was a cool. It was all cool coming from him
a guy who you just sort of feel like kind of is checked out at this point coming
through and very casually throwing up just a great hour 15 minutes. I thought
it was awesome. That's kind of number two for both of us. I feel like on the movie
corner yeah yeah. I'll do a third one and then you do a third one. All right or you
can do a third one. No, go ahead. No, go ahead because you weren't first. Well, I've
been talking about this the whole time. I watched. This will be quick because I feel like
we're running long RBG, a documentary about Ruth Bader Ginsburg. Didn't know much about
about the woman. I found it relatively interesting. You know, it's a fairly dull documentary about
a fascinating woman, kind of how I felt about Quincy as well. Like, there's just something
about a documentary that's just ticking off a biography where I feel like, you know, if
I don't really love the person, you know, why didn't I just read the Wikipedia page? It's
I didn't dig deep enough that the raves about it. I don't quite understand. She's an interesting lady, but you know, there it is.
Didn't do much for me.
I watched her classic fade to black.
I believe it's from 1980, maybe 83 somewhere in there.
Stars the kid that plays Eddie Caspernick in the original IT TV miniseries.
He plays a guy obsessed with movies.
He gets let down by a woman that he's in love with,
who looks like Marilyn Monroe.
And he snaps, goes crazy, starts murdering people,
dressed as his favorite movie characters.
Fun flick, well shot, well directed, pretty well written,
drags after a while once you kind of get the first couple kills
and you're like all right like I get it now he's going to dress up like a
fucking mummy and do it or whatever right but but overall worth watching you
know tragic ending you know a pretty fun little piece of early 80s horror it's
gritty it's dark I enjoyed it so I would say check it out all right I probably
won't. Got something for the screen and end news psycho quickly. Sure. And just because
I think you'll be interested in this, I wanted to bring it up. They apparently are making
a sequel to labyrinth. I had heard this. I didn't know it was a sequel, but yeah, I thought
it was a remake. Labyrinth is doing a sequel or they are doing a sequel. No, they said it's
going to be a direct sequel picking up 20, 30 years after the first film, whatever, just with nobody
from the original in it.
I'm sure it's gonna be like Connolly's daughter.
Uh huh, you know, it's like, mom, I believe in elves.
Right.
And then Connolly's gonna be like, you know,
or maybe the brother gets sucked back in.
The baby brother.
He's probably only like 22 right now, right?
Yeah, they'll have Zach Efron as the baby grown up.
But it's gonna be directed by Fred.
Is it Fred?
Fred Alvarez, Freddie Alvarez.
The guy that, don't breathe.
Yes, got it a don't breathe. Yes, which I hated, but he also did the evil dead remake which I really liked. I thought you liked don't breathe. I hated don't breathe. It shit on it on here. Pretty bad. We talked about it, and I felt like you were pro. No, he co -wrote the script with Jay Bazoo. I don't really know who that is, but they're saying that, you know, it's going to be its own thing and it's going to be a true sequel. Not a remake, not a reboot.
boot. All right, but a sequel. So we'll see. Jay Bazoo was a screenwriter.
Obviously, he wrote, looks like he wrote monsters, dark continent. He wrote the
new Charlie's Angels girl in the spider's web. Yeah, what was the deal with that?
They just throw out another girl in a dragon tattoo movie. It gets no promotion.
and dies made like $5.
Why do they abandon that franchise?
I mean, the Dan O 'Creg one did pretty well.
They threw it out with a different actor playing.
Different actor?
Yeah.
Confused me.
I was like, is this a sequel to the other one?
Or are they not connected?
Or like, what is this?
I think everyone was confused and they did not get out ahead of it.
They just kind of threw it out and abandoned it.
But I liked the Dan O 'Creg, David Fincher one.
I never saw either of those movies, I strayed from it because I know there's like apparently
a pretty harsh like rape sequence and I was like, I don't like seeing that stuff.
But it's, you know, it's fincher, it's shot amazingly well and it's a cool movie.
I just, I mean, those movies, those books were so massive, it just seemed so weird that
they were just abandoned it.
Because it was like a reboot, but it wasn't, but yeah, but people didn't go see the German
originals. It's like they're ready for an American version. It's weird. All right, let's get
to our movie today. Oh wait, real quick though, do you think Labyrinth sequels a good idea
or a bad idea? I mean, I'm interested. I'm curious. I feel like just make a different
movie. I mean, it sounds like it's going to have nothing really to do with Labyrinth.
It's not going to have muppets in it, isn't it? Why wouldn't it? Yeah, it's going to be
a sequel to Labyrinth. I don't know. Why would it not have muppets in it? The guy that
Don't breathe is putting together a puppet movie. I feel like it's gonna be CGI
No, I think like the dark they're doing the dark crystal series on Netflix. It's all puppets. All right. All right. I know. I'm curious
Is that start? I?
Don't know they said they're getting I think they're in editing now
And they have a lot of editing to do they said but you know, they're they're getting there
So all right, hopefully it's good some of the stuff they've they've done some prequel comics and stuff which
start really cool and then seemed to always go off the track so I'm a little
nervous about that show I hope it's good I'm very excited about it but I
mean that that that original movie to me is I'm fucking masterpiece like I you
know that's that's a tough tough thing to follow up. I'm gonna have to do a rewatch
I mean it was it was just not a part of my childhood at all. Labyrinth definitely
was. And when you get halfway through the movie and then you suddenly realize
Again, like every single thing I have watched has been a puppet, right? It's insane. Yeah, it's an insane work of art
Anyway
All right
What are we doing people under the stairs West Craven's
He had been in a real kind of shitty period of movies.
Did people on the stairs?
It was a surprise, huge hit, made a ton of money on a small budget.
And then I believe he went directly into shocker.
Or this followed shocker, but regardless, the man has was always,
I should say, because RIP just an incredibly uneven director for his entire career.
Fun fact.
Yeah, the last project he was supposedly working on was a TV series adaptation of the people under the stairs, which is still coming
It's like close to release. I believe all right on sci fi. I think don't hold me to that. I don't understand how that will be a series, but
Could be down with it. It could be down. Not against it
I've just I you definitely don't feel when it's over like I want to spend more time in this house
And hang out with these people so that it's a little unusual
But the picture, which I didn't realize until the movie started, it stars the two people
who play a married couple in Twin Peaks, which I was unaware of and I don't have the
actor's names because Joe's internet is shit.
It's not shit.
There's Wi -Fi.
Sign on to it.
It's not being a fucking moron.
I'd also stars the the woman that was in who's a name I'm also blanking on was in a she was a nightmare and I'm street five
And she's popped up in a bunch of other stuff. I want to say Mary Joe something
Shocker was 89 people one of the stairs was 91 and then he went into new nightmare
So he had a little bit of a run and then killed it immediately with vampire and Brooklyn, but
People on of the stairs stars
you guys. Everett McGill and Wendy Robie and their characters are named man and woman,
but they were both in Twin Peaks as a married couple. She had the blind subplot where she
was putting in Venetian blinds in her apartment. The worst subplot in all of Twin Peaks, a show
that had a lot of bad subplot in all of television. Maybe in all television. It was just her trying
to get the blinds tour. And to me, really, Trigger is kind of
the end.
And was that the gag, like the half -blind lady once blinds?
I don't think so. I think they just felt, hey, this woman
is obsessed with Venetian blinds. Let's give her an eye patch
to make her seem weirder.
This movie is about a young kid from the Projects.
very good act, who is in a weird sort of way mentored by Ving Rames. Correct. And Ving Rames kind
of coaxes this kid into going and robbing the house of the landlords of their building
that has just become like this rat -infested tenement and neglected and everything else
because they don't. And the kid has a sick mom. They need money. They're in a hopeless position.
And so the kid agrees to help Ving Rames.
They go into the house to rob it.
Of course, it's a spooky old mansion.
And then when they get inside,
things, there's more to the place that meets the eye
and there are people under the stairs.
But what is the motive of those people?
Right.
Basically, this couple has kidnapped a bunch of children
and whenever they disappoint them in some way,
they remove whatever part of their body did the disappointing. There's a kid with no tongue,
which is very disgusting. And they just kind of keep them as pets or prisoners. The performances by
the lead to are incredible. They're like really original feeling horror movie villains. The movie
has a lot to say. It's got a lot of social commentary to it. At the end, the house kind of explodes,
giving, you know, shooting a bunch of money into the streets and the people of the town
coming to get it.
But it's about kind of like class warfare, it's about greed.
These people own a bunch of slums, but don't keep them up, they just keep getting richer
and richer off them.
It's an oddly very timely movie for having come out 30 years ago, and wouldn't say it was
particularly scared by it, but it was very, very original and strange, and I really enjoyed
it.
I think the performances are great.
I think the script is pretty strong.
I think the commentaries are spot on,
but I think the movie sucks.
Interesting.
It's a boring watch.
It's a terribly boring watch.
Would you do a rewatch or you're gonna say no?
I know I did a rewatch.
Because I thought, this is a movie I've seen many times.
I've gone back to it many times going.
I'm missing something.
Right.
But I rewatched it again, I bought it to rewatch it again, I must be wrong, that's how
I got shocker too, came with it.
It's not a good movie and I'll tell you why, you hear that title of the people under
the stairs, you see these kids with the intentions of ripping off the bad guys, they break into
the house and and the notion or the assumption is they will now have to go up against an enemy
that will treat them unfairly. Again, you know what I mean? It's you're looking for a sort of
a layered plot where where it keeps sort of descending down. Like these people got fucked over. So
now they're going to rip off these people. But then when they get into the bad people's house,
They get fucked over again because there's this other secret in there and once you kind of find out
That everybody under the stairs who are supposed to be these creepy monsters and everything are just nice kids that like want to help them
Yeah, I'm I'm checked out at that point like the the couple themselves aren't crazy
Or interesting enough for me to carry a movie as villains
Mm -hmm and
I just don't I don't know I'm just like yeah, and then I I'll grant you that once the kids are not
Threaten anymore and they they have that reveal way too early in the movie way fucking early and alley larders like almost like an angel
You know who's she the good kid. Yeah, the good kid
You know her name
She's been in tons of shit. She has. Yeah, who is she? I don't even know. She is. I thought there was the one thing she was everywhere. No
It just kind of, yeah, it takes a lot of the scares out of it.
It's not a scary movie, but for me, I just sort of felt like in a genre where almost every
horror movie or like I've seen this a billion times, this felt very weird and unusual and
interesting to me.
And I have some respect for that.
I agree with that.
I don't disagree with that.
I'm sorry.
AJ Langer.
Not.
Not Ali Larder.
A .J. Langer was the girl and she was in, well look, episodes of Coach, she was on, she
was a regular on my soul called life. She was one of the main cast and maybe that's
as far as it went. I thought she had kind of had a bigger career, but I guess not.
I think it is an absolutely original film for this genre particularly and I think that
I don't know, maybe I'm just too caught up on, maybe I have to rewatch it yet another
time and not look at it as a horror film, but sort of as this strange caper movie.
But at the point in my life and in West Craven's career when this film came out, I was absolutely
and capable of seeing him in any way,
right, besides a horror creator.
The movie was marketed that way.
And it has since not been, there has been no revisionist
history with it, you know, it has not been retconned
in any way to say like, actually, this really isn't a horror
film, it's actually more of a strange thriller or whatever.
And, you know, like I said, or like you said,
they make that reveal of, they're not monsters down there.
Yeah, so early the kid is one of the McPoyles the kid with no tongue
He is yeah, is that them is that the guy from
Is that the kids the other not the one in Westworld not Jimmy Simpson is the other McPoyle okay, yeah no shit
I didn't realize that I
Would have been more scared to have the McPoyles down there. Yeah, it's I think
Clearly, to me, the fact that that reveal happens so early in the movie and takes a lot
of the threat out means to me, Wes Craven wanted to say something more than he wanted
to scare.
Also, there's like some comedy in it that's a little awkward, a lot of like kind of post
home alone trap, like when he sends the dog down and stuff, because it was a year after
home alone.
Yeah, there's a lot of ving rames is scared of the dog bits. Right. Um, I felt like this was not intended to be super scary
Even though I've always heard it described by friends as being terrifying. No, um, it's not and times change, but I
Like that I went back and watched the ebert and wrote a Cisco neighbor review of it
which you can find almost any old movie reviewed on YouTube by Cisco neighbor and
Ebert loved it
Cisco kind of was a little down on it, but I
I thought, for instance, I would have liked to have seen a rogue monster in the basement.
Maybe one of them is evil.
You've got one that's helping them and being nice to them.
Have an evil one that poses a threat because that's the thing.
Once the people are out of the house, once the husband and wife are out of the house,
which they are frequently, there's no threat.
They're just in a big, and by the way, there's no real threat if they're in the house.
It's like it's like get a gun go downstairs kill them and leave and nobody will know what the fuck happened here
Right, you know, so I you know, it's it's kind of I would have liked to and then I was like okay if you're not gonna
Go that route. I would have liked to have seen a more gruesome ending for the husband and wife
I
Thought because I didn't really remember what happened at the end
I thought for certain one of them would be eaten alive by these cannibal people in the basement
That never happens, you know, and it's just there's not a lot of big good scares and when it's a kid in jeopardy and kind of a wise -cracking kid to boot
It did have more of a home alone feel honestly, but
Tarantino a
Big fan of people on of the stairs casting Rams and Pulp Fiction a few years later and also that Gimp costume
Which oh, yeah seemed a little familiar now after that first season of American horror story and Pulp Fiction and etc
I imagine that was a lot more disturbing in 1991.
Yes, I would think so too.
But Tarantino was in spot, like based the Gimp costume off that.
And the reveal that their brother and sister is weird.
Yeah.
You know, that's a nice little creepy twist.
Yes.
But, you know, I shouldn't say it's a bad movie.
I'd give it a C minus.
Right.
And I always like, I mean, Poltergeist is the best example of this.
I like when a movie appears to end and you'd kind of be okay.
with it ending and then they have like a sort of more action -packed climax.
Poltergeist is the best example of that. It's a perfectly satisfying 90 -minute horror
movie and then they give you the true thrills and chills in the last 20.
People on the stairs does that to some extent. The kid goes home and then he's like,
no, fuck it, I gotta go back and save this girl. I thought that was kind of cool.
I had a good time with it. I'm not crazy about the house blowing up and
raining money at the end. That to me shows that they're going for more of a
fable time. And then they play like a new Jack swing beat. Yeah. It's a little
too. It's a little too happy. That people. My other stay is, you know, but but
anyway, that's the people under the stairs. I'm gonna give it a hog sideways. My
hog is, you know, it's pointing to about two to a clock. You know, it's it's a
a B for me, but I really enjoyed it.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram.
I will be in Philadelphia at the Punchline Thanksgiving Weekend,
Two Shows Friday, Two Shows Saturday.
My new album is Out.
It came out, it dropped on Halloween on Series XM,
Raw Dog Comedy, exclusively.
It's the only place you can hear it.
It's called I Go To Atlanta All the Time.
And it's, what if I don't have serious accent?
Well then, tough shit for right now.
We'll see.
But anyway, that's all I got folks. Thanks for listening. I am the Patrick Walsh
Instagram and Twitter cool kids is on Friday nights at Fox
73830 Central whenever 83730 Central. It's on Hulu as well. I
Would look out for the Thanksgiving episode coming up in two weeks, which is something special. I just finished editing it and
And that's all I got.
We have coming up on the show Nightmare Before Christmas,
oft requested, and we'll see what else.
Maybe we'll take a few more requests.
Shocker.
I've also recently saw upgrade in the first purge.
I think those would be good ones to do.
I'll watch upgrade.
I don't want to watch the first purge.
Yeah, first purge.
OK, well, I'll take you out the movie corner.
And we also should do underlord
or overlord. Yeah we'll go see overlord when that comes out all right and a lot of people have
been asking about the new Halloween that will be the second bonus episode which will drop next month.
This month November. Oh yeah it's November that's right and I gotta tell you folks Patreon
or not as we long discussed at the beginning of this episode but I listened to that live show.
I thought it was one of our best works. I really enjoyed it. Check it out.
I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next