I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's Will See You In Hell, your favorite show, reviewing movies.
And today we are reviewing a movie with the worst name since Hotel for Dogs.
Now, I know I've said that many times about many films, but the latest contender for
champion and worst named movie in the worst name movie department is Heart Eyes.
It is a terrible, terrible, terrible title.
I can usually fall right in line with you here, Joe, but Heart Eyes wouldn't crack my top
thousand.
It doesn't bother me at all.
Really?
Especially because the villains' eyes are hearts that light up.
But that's not a thing.
But yeah, the Heart Eyes emoji has, you never, you never, you never been sent that?
How was that what it is?
It's the emoji.
Oh God.
God damn it.
All right.
Now I'm upset.
I mean, you can't call a movie Heart Eyes emoji, but it's upsetting me now that I'm like,
oh, they used an emoji as part of the inspiration for this.
Everything gets ruined, folks.
We'll get to Heart Eyes.
I don't know.
It's like saying like, it's like calling a movie like Dick knows or something.
And like it doesn't, like it's not, I don't know.
Well, Dick knows is a thing, but you know what I mean.
You know what you mean?
And I go see the girls too.
Yeah.
Teeth fingers or it's like two words just don't match.
Anyway, whatever.
We'll get to Heart Eyes.
Let's know what you, Joe.
What's know what you quit?
Quit hiding behind shields and tell us what's really going on.
I got back together with my girlfriend.
We patched it up.
So that's good.
OK.
So that's the newest thing.
There was a regular Jim and Pam over there.
You're a regular big and carry over there.
Yes, it is very big and carry, especially given the fact that I am 17 years old, older than she is.
So it does feel big and carry.
And oddly, I feel like the carry, which folks,
oh, you got a bigger, you got a bigger age gap than me and my lady friend.
I don't feel bad anymore.
What is your age gap?
Oh, we're about 13, 14 years.
Oh, all right.
Well, that makes me feel better.
I thought you were going to say like five, six.
No, it's my biggest gap by far.
And I'm enjoying the hell out of filling it up.
I like it.
Yeah, no, no, we're 14.
Yeah, it's a big gap.
And I know people have a lot of thoughts about that these days.
Nobody's like stopped us in the street at least and stone dust or anything.
So that's good.
No, I think, uh, yeah, strangely, it doesn't, it doesn't seem that odd, I guess.
I don't know.
And I like it because now I feel ready to date a woman with maybe a 22 year old, uh,
your gap.
I feel like I could really move now into some bigger numbers.
Well, as Matthew McConaughey said, you get older and they stay the same age.
You can just keep dating the same age of woman and let that gap get larger and larger.
And anytime, uh, anytime she complains about my age, I say, Hey, good luck.
Tuts.
You want to go date a moron in his 30s with no cash.
Sheesh.
Yeah.
Or do you want to ride?
That's what I say.
Rev up the old, uh, the chopper.
Uh, no, it's been she's, she's an incredible person.
And, uh, I would, I would go as far as to say she's wise beyond her years, uh,
given her don't say that, Joe.
That's what every guy dating a younger girl says.
Don't say that.
Well, she's 31.
I mean, she's not a child.
You know, definitely don't say she's an old soul.
Definitely don't say she's an old soul.
Um, no, she just feels old.
She smells weird.
Uh, very wrinkled, uh, terrible attitude.
Yells at people in public all the time.
You know, it's, she's like an racist.
Yeah.
So anyway, that's the newest thing we, we made up and, uh, she came up here for a week.
And we, we really, it's been really, really lovely thing.
She's not here now anymore, but, but, uh, that was good.
That's the newest thing.
Matt, a bunch of hellians and DC at my DC show, which was a borderline disaster of a show,
given the venue and, because the venue sucked and they, and they didn't promote it.
And there was, we, there should have been more people there.
And then they sat it poorly.
The show was fine.
Like me and the audience were fine.
It was just everything around that kind of sucked, but I do think the hellians and, and the
other fans that came out for that show.
But, uh, but so that was interesting.
Uh, and that's, you ever have, do you ever have like a beautiful woman after a show
come up to you and like say, hey, I just want to shake your hand.
And then you look down and they're palming you a piece of paper.
And she leans in and goes, please give my number to Pat.
No, no, sort of.
No.
Ah, okay.
I can take that.
No, but women have DM me about you.
I mean, in all seriousness, I've told you when it's happened, but you know, there's been
women that have DM me, you know, and said like, please tell Pat, I'm in love with him or
whatever.
And, you know, I've messaged him, but I haven't heard back kind of thing.
No, I don't know that.
I don't know that you have told me that.
Um, you just took these women for yourselves.
You probably said he's not interested, but I'm a veil.
And I said, yeah, go, you know, he's gay, right?
No, I didn't know that.
You know, who's only by me, Joe.
Um, yeah, I have.
I have, I don't know.
I feel about something specific.
I don't know.
No, we, I mean, I talked to Kermont.
Kermont said I text roughly once a week, but what, what's that?
Not nothing.
He was going to call you.
I was talking to him.
It was just like I was going to call him, but maybe he didn't.
Oh, he's in, he's in London playing Supergirl's dad.
Are you allowed to say that publicly?
Yeah, it was announced.
Oh, it wasn't.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I knew about that.
He told me though when it was like off the record, then I was like, well, what is
America going to do at this moment in time to learn that Supergirl has a Jewish
dad?
Aren't they going to go insane?
And he was like, superman, uh, this new Superman is Jewish.
Wow, really?
And the new Supergirl is Jewish and I was like, well, I love that.
We will, we will see how America reacts as we spiral further into the toilet.
So why a wild time going on right now?
Wild every day.
I, I, I guess it, well, it's, it's privileges what it is, but I am able to watch it
as if watching an episode of V for the West Wing and be like, boy, there's some crazy
shit going down in that country and not just not, I don't have the full panic yet.
I'm, I'm observing it, but not feeling it, I guess, because it doesn't feel quite real.
Um, I'm dejected completely with everything.
Um, yeah, you know, me.
I'm not a big political guy.
You know, I'm not heartbroken or elated by either party, you know, being in
prominence or whatever.
Um, but I will say that, uh, these last, which, at the end of this term of Trump
will be 12 years.
It is just exhausting.
I said to a friend the other day, you know, I said, everybody I know is having
some sort of existential crisis or not really being able to kickstart back into
the new year and everybody's going through something.
Yeah.
And she said, yeah, me too.
And I said, um, I think it is the fact that whether you are a Trump fan or not,
him getting reelected is a reminder of not a great time in the country.
We were very divided.
We were at each other's throats.
There was a lot going on socially.
It was very turbulent.
And I said, whether you like him or not, his, his stepping back in feels like we're
stepping back towards a time on a subconscious level at the very least towards a
time we don't want to revisit pandemic, all this stuff.
And, um, she said, well, that might be true.
And I said, so there's that just kind of looming.
And then you got to deal with your personal shit.
And it's just, you know, and then not to mention the fires in, in Los Angeles and,
and in all the stuff happening overseas and it's a lot.
And she said, yeah, no, it's terrible.
But you know, she goes, I have young kids and I don't watch any of the news or anything.
I, I don't have the bandwidth to let it in.
And I said, even that is, is exhausting and causing doom.
The fact I avoided too.
And the fact that I have to avoid it because I know if I don't avoid it, it'll be too much.
That in and of itself is, is a terrible burden.
So it's just terrible.
It's just a terrible, terrible, terrible time.
And then entertainment on top of it, helping the state of entertainment.
It's not helping.
It's not taking us all anymore.
Well, you're, there was always this promise, you know, like, well, back in, in the
depression days, you know,
America went to the movies to, to feel good again.
And we don't have that anymore.
There's no distraction.
And the distractions make you feel worse.
Like TikTok is the ultimate distraction.
I, I realized I had an addiction to fucking Instagram reels.
I go to bed, I lie down and then it's like my brain either drives me to the
brain.
Bear and I don't sleep or I watch it.
I'm against the way we apologize that we're having a few audio hiccups here and
they're pets in an Airbnb in Atlanta.
We're, you know, and when we're out of our own element, it can have an effect
sometimes do the internet.
But that's why once in a while, Pat cuts out, we apologize.
But say again, it brings you to the brink of despair.
Sorry.
Also, I will say you cut out occasionally and I, it doesn't show up in the recording.
Oh, really?
Oh, okay.
Great.
It's just like, it's a weird thing between us, I think.
And I'll be in a better Airbnb next week on the mainland.
I'm on a weird lake right now.
I brought my girl back here.
She came to visit and she was like, Oh, you're going to murder me.
And I mean, it looks any movie if you're driving down this like mile to
wear this house is in the woods.
The audience is like, Oh, fuck, this girl's about to die.
So I'm probably the problem.
But the Instagram Reels, an hour before bed, I would go right to sleep.
I'd have a big goofy smile on my face, but it was affecting me.
I was waking up, ragged, haggard in a bad mood, no attention span.
If you wake up and watch a half hour of Instagram Reels, when you go sit down to
start your job, you can't do it.
You don't have the attention span to do your job.
If you sit and watch a bunch of Instagram Reels, it's destroying our brains.
I meet, I just turned 44 and it almost destroyed mine.
I had to delete it off my phone and start reading.
Reading people.
Can you believe that?
So what are we doing with these kids who are handed an iPod at eight or earlier?
All my friends, kids are five and staring at the iPads all day.
And then the parents are like, well, I mean, obviously it'd be easy to just let them be on the iPad,
but we can't do that.
And I'm like, the kids have been on the iPad for 16 hours.
Yeah, these parents ain't shit.
These modern parents ain't shit.
Yeah, like taking them off the iPad for when they go to sleep is not exactly being a great parent.
These kids are going to have major social and mental disorders.
I find it fascinating.
You know, my barber was telling me he was like, yeah, he's like my oldest daughter is really pissed at me.
I took her phone away from her.
Yeah.
And I was like, wow, that's, you know, that's interesting.
Let's talk about that.
I go, that's one of the reasons I don't want to have a kid is because I feel like you have to give
them all these like devices and things that I don't think kids should have.
And then if you take it away from the kid, you're like a bad parent or something.
I go, so are you getting grief from like the school, like pressure from the school to let her have the phone?
And he was like, no, quite the opposite.
The schools are now emailing us and saying, please keep your kids phones at home, which they were not doing before.
And they're like, it's become a distraction.
It's become this.
It's like, oh, do you think this finally might have barreled out of fucking control that nobody's
disciplining their children at all?
You're giving them every fucking possible allowance.
Yeah.
He told me too.
He goes, he goes, he goes, my daughter is an honor student and she doesn't, he goes, it doesn't matter though.
He goes, you can just, if you just show up, they will pass you now.
And I was like, that's so fucked up.
Like I go, what motivation does she have to keep trying then?
Why would you keep working hard if the kid next to you not doing anything gets the same
reward of and progress?
Like it's, it's, it is not good, man.
It is not good.
Yeah.
Some, some schools issue an iPad, you know, like I, one of my friends kids had two and I was like,
what are they doing with two is one for school, one for, like one for learning and one for whatever.
And they're like, no, every student is issued an iPad in addition to their like home iPad.
So that means school, which should be your time to not stare at a screen all day.
You're doing it there too.
And it's, I'd never call a teacher lazy or a parent lazy.
They have miserable lives.
Why are you, it seems like you're, you're just giving over your job as a parent and as a teacher to kids
when they're on the iPad all day.
Like that's your job is to intervene and get them off that.
And yet at the same time, I get here, take this and leave me alone for four hours.
So I can breathe.
I get that too.
There's no real right answer.
I don't think it's the teachers doing.
I, I think it is the parents, you know, it's a weird contradiction with, with, with a lot of modern parents.
It's like they want to be helicopter parents, but they also don't want to really be parents at all.
I mean, yeah, it is, it's just a given now that part of raising your child will include a budget for a nanny.
Yeah.
Like that's just part of life.
Like when I was growing up, I mean, I'm not trying to do the whole in my day thing, but it's like Jesus Christ, guys.
Like when I was a kid, a nanny was like a thing that like the fresh prints of Bel-Air had.
You know what I mean?
Like that was not a common thing.
And it's just part of it now.
And I think that people, you know, they don't, they don't want to deal with the kid in the way that you really have to.
But then they also want to be helicopter parents.
So it's a very weird contradiction.
And I think a lot of the, you know, it started more with the teachers.
It started more with teachers I knew talking about how hard it was to be a teacher because you couldn't discipline the kids anymore.
Because anything you did to reprimand a kid, the parent would come in and try and it could cost you your job.
So it starts to become this thing where it's like, all right guys, good luck.
I guess, you know?
Yeah.
It's kind of like, it's like, it's kind of like being like a cop now.
I'm not saying there are problems with cops.
There were plenty of problems with cops.
There were some awful things happening that need to be rectified, obviously.
But at the same time, there are also cops that are just trying to do their job and every time they do anything.
So he's got an iPhone in their face.
I'd be like, hey guys, I'm going home.
I'm just going to leave this alone.
I'm going to sit in the car and eat some donuts.
And I know.
Hey, care.
I'm not like, I feel like it's saying that with teachers, like, what do you want me to do guys?
Every time I try to discipline a kid, some parent is coming in here telling me that I am traumatizing their child.
I'm not going to get run out of town over this.
There you go.
I can't stand the police.
I've lived my entire life in unnecessary fear of them.
But if there's one behind me, I can't drive.
I like need to pull over.
I just hate them.
I hate everything they represent.
They're bullies.
They're going to get it.
But there's so many things.
I'm surprised you feel that strong.
I get that some of them are very fucked up.
But you think that, you know, are you an anti-cop guy?
I never knew that about you.
It's not something I'd go to rallies over.
I'm just used to every fucking dick from my high school immediately becoming a policeman.
Right.
There's so many of these guys who were just racist, miserable bullies who'd come up,
take your knees out from underneath you, hit you in the head with a book.
And then one year after graduation, they're, you know, monitoring the local target in a police uniform.
Yeah, that's the hell.
You know, I just, it brings about a personality type that I don't like, that agro-masculine type,
that I grew up around and hated.
So when I sympathize with them entirely, like when I watch enough of these videos, I can't
help but sympathize with these people.
I don't even like.
They're like, hey, you know, your left tail lights out and you made a weird lane switch
and you're going about 65 and a 35.
Can I just get your license, please?
So many Instagram reels and TikToks start with the person on the other end of that
go, um, no, actually you can't.
Because I don't need a driver's license to drive a car and I'm surprised you don't know
the way the law works.
Can you get your supervisor down here?
The amount of people now that are asking to see a supervisor in traffic stops.
It's, it's constant.
I, I pulled you over because you're speeding.
You need to get your supervisor out here immediately.
They're filming the cop as they come up.
No, call your boss.
Get him out here.
I've never seen anything like it.
I, I don't know how a cop doesn't just shoot them in the face.
I, I, I just thought of a bit.
I just turned my camera off and shoot you in the face.
I just thought of a bit and I, I honestly, I thought of it before you just said the
shoot you in the face thing.
I don't know what do you think I'm taking the idea.
No, no.
But can I do this?
I just thought of a bit.
It's a funny.
Joe, of course, I don't care.
It's a funny premise.
I was going to say I'm not against police brutality.
I just want to see it switched.
Yeah.
Exactly.
It's a very funny idea.
I, I love to see this person get the shit out of them.
Yeah, for sure.
All right.
I'm going to write that down.
Um, anyway, what's new with you, Pat?
Besides, uh, you asked me what's new with me.
I told you I want my breakup and all that stuff and then we digressed into police.
Yeah.
Well, I'm, I'm working, uh, in Atlanta, I'm doing eight episodes and eight weeks.
So it's, it's balls to the wall Friday morning, which is when we're recording now is my
one kind of, uh, relaxing time because we do two live shows on Friday, two live crew,
one at one, one at six.
If you're in Atlanta, come to a taping.
They're super fun.
Um, but it is really busy.
That's great for me.
I like being busy because it shuts my brain off.
I had my lady friend come out for the four day weekend.
We had an amazing time in Atlanta.
Um, I'm enjoying that situation ship for what it is quite a bit.
Having a really good time.
And, uh, other than that, I got to say I enjoyed the hell out of the SNL stuff this weekend.
I thought the concert was great.
I only skipped one performer in three hours, which is amazing.
You can probably guess who it was.
A jelly roll.
I talked, I talked, I know I'm sure he is.
I've talked at length about him on the solo pod.
I know you know jelly roll, but I can't stand him.
I thought the concert was fantastic.
I love the, you know, David burn and Robin and the different people from different generations
performing and, uh, you know, I'm not a big pro gem guy.
Eddie Vetter doing the waiting Tom Petty's song.
I thought was awesome.
The highlights without question, B 52s, who I saw in Vegas last year, who are in their
70s and fucking destroy and even better and even older looking, Devo.
Oh, wow.
That I'd be interested in.
Devo did uncontrollable urge.
These men are at least 70.
They look like real estate agents.
I saw a Devo concert a couple years back and it was in the deserts called desert days,
which is basically a drug festival.
And I just saw hundreds and hundreds of heads just like slowly turn towards the stage.
Like, oh, I wasn't even going to pay attention to Devo.
Are you kidding me with how fucking tight they are?
It was so good.
And I hope they tour again because they still got it.
They had Fred Armiston drumming for both Devo and the B 52s, which was fun.
And then to see people in the crowd going nuts, you know, it was like Pedro Pascal, Paul
Rudd, the whale himself, Brendan Fraser, to see them rocking out to Devo.
It makes you like him more, you know, I wish more people would talk about what they like.
I like knowing what celebrities like.
I don't.
I'm depleted of all joy.
The Saturday night live thing did nothing but piss me off from start to finish.
I'm done.
The concert and the special.
I didn't watch.
I didn't watch either.
And I've got friends involved with both.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do the hashtag best life.
Look at the big party.
You're not invited to thing anymore.
I just can't do it.
It's too much.
Every fucking sketch on that thing that I at least saw, it's like celebrity after celebrity
after celebrity.
And they're doing jokes about SNL in the sketches.
And I'm just like, guys, what is happening right now?
What is going on?
And I'm getting clips about Ryan Reynolds.
The fact that Ryan Reynolds even was fucking part of that was disgusting.
That was disgusting.
Quick pause.
I've been following this shit so much.
Him to stand up and joke about his wife's alleged, which I don't believe, persistent sexual
harassment from this guy.
And then he stands up and makes a crack.
And you see her look at him like, what the fuck are you doing?
Blake lively looks at him like, are you kidding me?
Well, but please, like she didn't know that was happening.
The whole thing is fake.
The whole thing.
Now Blake, we want you to look like this.
So then the press says, was this what you're probably right.
And yet, immediately Baldoni's lawyer did exactly what he's supposed to do.
I've seen a lot of cases of sexual harassment and sexual assault in my time.
And generally the husband of the victim is not cracking jokes, especially in a public
forum.
And I'm like, yeah, you lost the case there, Reynolds.
And you should have, you can't spend five seconds out of the fucking public eye.
You disgusting narcissists.
Yeah.
You can't go, hey, we ought to lay low for a month while I have a $400 million lawsuit
going on.
Nope, I got to get out there and wink at everybody about it and make us sarcastic with
about it.
Not only should you see costner's reaction.
No, that's a, get out, get online.
I'm telling you to watch Instagram, Reels, while criticizing.
Well, wasn't costner sitting behind him with that next to share?
You was.
What's going on?
Shares performance was incredible vocally and she looked so good.
Great.
I mean, just, but I'm just saying the whole thing, it's, it's, it's like when I pitch
about these largo lineups, it's like for God's sake, can one normal person be injected
into the mix of this thing?
Like dear God, it is overload.
It's like an Avengers of fame.
It's crazy, man.
I hear you.
Google, Kevin Costner reaction to Ryan Reynolds went, you know, after, after we get off here.
And then when Reynolds stands up and starts doing his bit, Costner has given him the
biggest, like Clint Eastwood grand terino get off my lawn.
Look, he's like, is this fucking clown serious?
He's doing bits.
So that's why I liked the audience.
Porses of the show was to see people's genuine reaction to things.
I would recommend strongly watching the live special because the sketches were good.
Eddie Murphy doing Tracy Morgan on Jeopardy was really fucking funny.
Eddie Murphy was in quite a few of the sketches.
They were, they were good.
Laugh out loud.
They had Mulaney doing some bit with David Spade where he does this New York musical.
And it had been going on for like 10 minutes.
And I'm like, this isn't really hidden.
And it cuts back.
It's, it's Pete Davidson and Mulaney and they're like, well, where are we going next?
And then Mulaney goes, well, what happened to David?
What happened to David Spade?
He was a part of the sketch for like 10 minutes.
And Pete Davidson goes, I think he actually sat down in the audience and they cut over to
Spade and he goes, you know, I got the gist of it.
It seemed improvised.
It was like, no, no, I'm bored with this fucking layman sketch.
I'm going to sit down.
There was a lot of big laughs.
Steve Martin's monologue was great.
I was surprised because I still watch SNL, but I rarely LOL and I laughed a lot and I
really enjoyed the concert as well.
I thought they did a great job.
I don't ever need to hear anything about SNL again, but I'm glad they didn't resort to
another Samurai delicatessen clip show where it's like, and who could forget this moment?
And you're like, none of us because we've seen this sketch of billions on.
I didn't laugh when I was five.
I know, I'm not laughing now.
They dropped that.
They just had new, written material and I thought it was great.
That's my take.
Yeah, I just, I feel like the show just did this 10 years ago for the 40th.
I guess they're going to just do it every 10 years.
Yeah.
But the fact that they did it for the 40th and the fact that they did it, I think for
the 25th or something.
It just doesn't feel quite as significant to me.
It would have felt more significant if those hadn't happened and then it was just the 50th.
Maybe there wasn't a 25th.
I believe there was though.
It was a great, I owned the 25th.
They released it on DVD.
So look, I'm not going to say that there's nothing funny in there.
I'm not going to say that there weren't great musical performances.
I did not watch.
But I just couldn't bring my, and again, I've got friends and
involved heavily with both productions.
I just can't do another, I just can't do it anymore.
I can't do this flooding of social media with look at our selfies from the big event
that we were fancy enough to get invited to.
I just, I can't fucking do it anymore.
There's also been such exposure and reveal that everything we fucking load and
everything we love is an absolute fucking cahoots with one another.
That it's like this to me would be like watching a political thing and getting excited
that I'm seeing Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton appear in a sketch together.
Like I'm just like, it's just gross to me, man.
I'm just like, you people are over there.
I'm over here.
You're all part of this machine that I'm not a part of clearly.
Yeah.
You know, that I don't even understand.
There's an orchestration at play here that I don't even understand.
And Ryan Reynolds being the epitome of that.
Like he's the epitome.
It is only 30 seconds of the show.
I get it.
You got personal grievance.
You know, Crumel's when he, he lived in LA for a while and he was like, you're going
to get a point.
He was telling me, yeah, to get out of LA as you tell me always as well.
He's like, you're going to get to a point where every billboard you pass in the street
will enrage you.
And you'll be like, this motherfucker, how does he get a fucking shot?
And he's like, you won't even notice.
It'll just like slowly overtake your brain that you hate every person on earth because
there's somewhere that you're not or whatever.
And it does happen.
I get it.
I'm saying despite all that.
And even though I win in arms folded, I had some good laughs.
And I thought the musical performances were really solid too.
I don't know.
Well, let's, let's, if you don't mind, let's count that as the first movie corner.
And I'll do a second one or I'll do my first.
I watched, well, I'll just, these are, these are movies we've talked about at length.
So these will be easy.
But I, my girlfriend had never seen any of them.
So I showed her all three of the naked gun movies.
Yeah.
We started with two.
So I'll start with two.
Two front bars.
Quick pause.
I'm sorry.
You know you're going to watch all three.
Why the fuck are you starting with two?
I didn't know we were going to watch all three.
We were going to skip.
My buddy Scott was over and we were hanging out.
It was like a sudden.
It was a Monday after Super Bowl the day after.
We were all kind of hungover.
Scott had the day off.
We had the day off.
I was like, come on over.
We'll eat some pizza.
Have some day drinks.
lick our wounds.
Whatever.
He's like, let's watch something funny.
So we put on naked guns.
She had never seen it.
And I was like, do we show her one or two?
And he's like, my favorite's two.
And I was like, me too.
And also, you're not going to be like lost.
You see the first one.
No.
So we showed her two.
You can do a quick pause and say, oh, by the way, driven and Priscilla Presley have a romantic
history.
That's really all you need to know.
That's literally what I said to her.
I go, all you need to know is as they used to date in the first movie.
So anyway, we watched it.
It was front to back laughs, man.
It delivered on all fronts.
I was like, this is the best naked gun movie.
She got it in spades.
She loved it.
I'm trying to think of the standout bits that she laughed hardest at.
The entire, of course, the entire sequence in the singles bar when he's depressed and
whenever every, the hardest she probably laughed is when he grabs both her hands and the
third hand comes up and slaps him in the face.
In the trailer, yeah.
Yeah.
That really got her and.
And in this much sex, since I was a boy scout leader, I mean, at the time, I was dating
a lot.
Yeah.
But then the, I love it bit really got her.
I've been swimming in love.
I love it.
Yep.
It's real good.
Also, if I may, because I, I've seen one more.
I love one and two about equally.
I think the heights are so high in both.
And there's not a lot of lows.
But I'll take Goulet over Motelbond.
That's the difference.
Goulet makes me laugh right out loud every time I see him.
Huh.
That's interesting.
You know what?
I'll do, I'll just do both of them back to back and, and I'll save the third one.
We watched one second.
I enjoyed rewatching one, but it reinforced my opinion that two, one is a better movie,
one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie,
one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie,
one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie, one is a better movie
another than Gosling, we don't got any movie stars, we don't got any comedy stars, we don't got nothing, our comedy actors are John Cena and the Rock and Dave Batista and I think that's a goddamn shim
but when you look at like female leads in a movie, romantic comedy
let's say six out of ten guys these days, who's the hottest woman in Hollywood, you know, they're gonna, let's say they say Sydney Swini, okay?
the star power between like Sydney Swini and anyone but you and Julia Roberts in pretty woman, there are miles and miles and miles and miles between these points, I mean, Julia Roberts is so like dad
and you cannot, I didn't, I dropped my phone not because I was so into the plot mechanics of pretty woman but because I just wanted to look at Julia Roberts for two hours
and the difference is it's not in that Sydney Swini way of like, excuse the craftness but look at them titties
Julia Roberts is unquestionably hot and she never dressed more sexual than in pretty woman obviously, she's playing a sex worker
but you just want to look at Julia Roberts because she is an unattainable standard of perfection
a true natural stunning beauty that a movie star, male or female, used to have to be, you have to have, you used to have to have the looks but also this huge inner light and this world of charm
and then we also knew how to light them and how to write for them and how to make them shine
it was a reminder and I don't think pretty woman is a masterpiece but it is a reminder of just everything we have lost
and we may not be getting back, we don't have these kinds of stars, we don't have these people you'll follow anywhere
you know, she bounces off the screen in this that's the reason that scene so famous where he slaps her with the little jewelry box and she does the big horse laugh
is A because it's real and B because you're like that's the most perfect beautiful feminine laugh I've ever heard of my life
who is this enchantress there was just we looked for these people and I guarantee they exist it's a big world full of millions and millions and millions of people
we have stopped even trying to find these these movie stars in my opinion I it's hard to believe that the last time we had movie stars was like
10 15 years ago pretty woman itself is a very entertaining romcom way darker than most the script started out super dark it was called three thousand dollars
and it was much more about the cd underbelly of prostitution I don't think the movie is showing you the reality of being a sex worker by any means
but also it's a romantic comedy it's not supposed to be leave in Las Vegas and people's criticism of it feels a little weird
I remembered it that Julia Roberts had done like one blowjob before she met Richard gear and then gave it up but no she had she says I had some regulars you know that it's kind of
balsy especially for its time and that this woman was a true sex worker she got around before she met Richard gear and the movie while not being pro that life
it's respectful of it when Jason Alexander tries to rape the Julia Roberts character
his his it's gross to say but his motivation for doing so feels disgustingly real his his motivation is she's a hooker
she's gonna be fucking guys anyway who cares like at least let it be me you know he just tries to
get on or and do it because he's like you're a sex worker you you're supposed to love this right
and that's which is a great commentary for them to explore that problematic perspective that men have towards sex workers that's a great
and in a progressive commentary for them to explore at that time very much absolutely
and and Jason Alexander immediately loses respect for her and starts talking shit and talking
and crafts about her the second he learns that information so
people want movies especially movies that are of their time they want them to be a million things at once
you can't be one of the most famous and beloved romantic comedies of all time and be a realistic expose
of the sex worker lifestyle you can't but this movie I think uneasy though it may be at times
does a really good job of blending and balancing them and it feels real and it feels legit
and to compare it again to this anyone but you anywhere whatever that movie's called it's not
fucked up stupid high-jinks you know it's not like
Julia Roberts comes into the bedroom with a giant dildo and gears like whoa I'm not quite ready for all
that you know like stupid hooker high-jinks that have no basis in reality the movie feels like what
a real love story might look like between an extremely attractive wealthy and powerful man
and a stunningly beautiful sex worker it actually in my opinion did a great job of making
it feel real Carrie Fisher apparently did a very big rewrite and my guess is that helped a lot
because it feels like a movie that was written through a female lens and it is really good it's
also fun frankly to see Jason Alexander in character actor villain mode you know before
Costanza kind of made him type cast I like pretty woman a lot I think it kind of loses its way
by the end but I really enjoy the movie it's a good rom-com for sure Ken Russell was critical of it
because it was around the time he put out horror I saw horror and horror too yeah and he was like
my movie is a real movie about a hooker
not this look pretty woman shit look he's he's right but they don't go they don't go so far
into the fantasy with it that you forget and her character Laura San jacamos character
is experiencing kind of the rougher side of the sex worker lifestyle at the same time
I commend them for at least trying you know of course it's yeah I get it it's like analyze this
versus the sopranos I get it sure yes yes I I would just I will quickly say naked gun 33 and a third
I did not watch with my lady and thank God I didn't it is a terrible fucking movie I thought time
would have done it some justice there are zero laughs in that thing it is so hoki really oh dumb
it's terrible it's terrible it is so not funny it doesn't have any of the tenants of the other two
you damn I knew I knew way worse but I didn't remember that much worse dude you get 25 minutes into
this thing uh and then all of a sudden he's doing the Frank Dreb and voiceover and you're like oh
yeah I forgot they do that in the movie yeah like like none of the tenants are there like uh like
it doesn't feel like a play on on a crime noir in any way shape or form it doesn't feel like a
police procedural in any way shape or form the the the the really sharp jokes and if you read
about the production of the movie you know it's because it's like written and directed by the guy
that came in to help out with the second movie you know it starts to become diminishing returns
right the original players just aren't really that involved at this point um
you you you're off to a terrible start it starts with a sort of funny spoof of the of the
train station scene from the untouchables and then Frank wakes up and he's having a nightmare
and uh uh uh uh Jane says don't worry everything will be okay in the morning
and he goes you're right let's go back to sleep and he takes the remote control for their
adjustable bed and throws it onto the nightstand and it lands in a glass of water
and that causes the bed to jerk back and forth and throw them out the window it's terrible yeah
yeah like those are like that's your big opening joke so um I'm not going to say it has not one laugh
but I mean you know the big set piece and it is when he has to go to the the sperm-donning clinic
oh yeah and like even that's you know like I guess there's it's just it's just sucks it was it's a shame
it's a shame I had always had a fantasy that uh I was you know a year into comedy at the time I had
no hope of ever trying to pursue it but I was at a fantasy of making another one called naked gun
negative one that would have been a prequel to the first three where it would still star Kennedy
and and Nielsen but you would just dye their hair black and that was like them being 30 years younger
whatever yeah and like that's sort of what the wet hot reboot was yeah exactly so yeah I don't know
I'm excited to see what they do with this new one only because and this is the only reason the
fact that they have Liam Neeson playing the part I'm like they're doing what they did with Leslie
Nielsen like they're they got a serious actor who can be very dry and when he's very dry it can be
very funny let's see let's see you know um I'm curious yeah I read 20 pages of the script and just
closed it up I will watch it when it comes out I hope for the best but I don't I don't have good
feelings is it same tone though like the script is it slapsticky or is it it's slapsticky I mean
I'll tell you the opening is a is a bank robbery going on and in comes a girl scout and the cops
are like what the fuck is this girl scout won't get out of here little girl and then the girl scout
reveals itself to be Liam Neeson in disguise and the little girl beats the shit out of these people
and to me that sounds so bad and so dumb and I read it you know with an open mind it's it's the
whole opening set piece it's like she whips her pig tails around and and slaps the guy in the face
and I'm like what am I even looking at you know a girl scout is gonna be four feet tall Liam Neeson
is six two so what do you do I tell you what they're doing a CGI Liam Neeson face on a girl scout's
body and if you think that's funny then you're eight or you're mentally handicapped it would be
funny if Liam Neeson just came in and a girl scout wig and they were like get out of here little
girl and they were it was a terrible disguise but they were falling for it that's kind of funny
that's not how it's written maybe that's how they shoot it but that's not what's written so
all right I I stopped reading it and it's from the writers of chip and Dale rescue rangers the
movie that was on Disney plus you know I don't have high hopes Joe Christ Jesus Christ
why are why are you not getting like these three guys from SNL you know what I mean or whoever
it's like why are you right the rescue range this is like when they hired the Lego movie guys to do
the Han Solo movie and they had to fire them it's like no shit guys they weren't they weren't
hitting the tone of the Han Solo movie the Lego movie guys didn't get it like Jesus God man
yeah um I don't here here's why I feel sort of good about it is that it was directed by
Akiva Schaefer who is one of the lonely island guys okay the lonely island guys are the only
people from the last 10 20 years who are still trying to keep this kind of comedy alive pop star
is the vast version of like a major of a modern naked gun type movie so with him at the helm
maybe I don't know but the script wasn't showing me things and I personally don't have faith in
Liam Neeson because I think uh Leslie Neelson how weird is that that Liam Neeson and Leslie
Neelson but uh Leslie Neelson always had that twinkle in his eye and you knew that there might be
a funny guy behind him I don't see that in Liam Neeson at all I've never known him to have like a
barely suppressed sense of humor that's not what comes across from him at all um well if you watch
I I would disagree if you watch the earlier like Leslie Neelson in airplane and in the police squad series
he's he very much is a very heavy dramatic actor playing it that way that twinkle comes out more
and more as he starts to realize like it's fun to be funny so that's true that's true we'll see
um anyway that's all I got for this week's uh movie corner excellent um my other one
was the movie that Gary Marshall made the following year right after pretty woman Frankie and Johnny
starring the great al Pacino and the incredible Michelle Fyfer
Frankie and Johnny is currently on the criterion channel um as part of a New York romantic comedies
uh block that they have they have Arthur and you know Annie Hall and a lot of things you'd expect classic
New York romp coms and I had seen Frankie and Johnny I think I originally watched it on CBS you know
they used to look the Saturday night premiere of a movie that happens now on HBO they used to do that on
network TV you know tonight's the network premiere of doc Hollywood or whatever it would be on NBC um
and I watched Frankie and Johnny and enjoyed it and I still enjoy it it's an adult romantic comedy
it's pretty woman aged up and without the sex worker thing obviously but it's uh have you seen
this movie Joe no I really like it it's based on a play and the play starred Kathy Bates in the
Michelle Fyfer role which tells you everything you need to know about Hollywood but it was supposed
to be and in play form as like a female Marty the Ernest Borg-9 movie that is such a great movie
and one best picture about this like heavy set douty dumpy on a law flower who meets this guy
who just got released from prison has his own damage but is much more charming and kind of a fast
talker and a cool guy um so that was on Broadway Kathy Bates like discovering this secret you know
sexuality in herself and coming out of her shell but then when the movie was happened and they were
like sorry nobody's gonna buy this nobody's gonna buy a pichino fucking Kathy Bates not happening
so she was devastated that she lost out on this great part that she originated but it led to
her getting the part in misery so we have to all be thankful for that um but how tough must
that have been for Kathy Bates you can't be no one buys you as a love interest we'll only buy you as
this murderous wench who lives in a cabin in the woods and kills people um anyway
the movie is great it is a testament to how great Michelle Fyfe is that you do believe that even
though she is stunningly beautiful one of the most beautiful women that ever lived you do believe
that she is so broken and damaged that she is not gonna be good for a relationship you believe
that she's lonely it's a lot of the same energy she brings to Selena Kyle before she becomes catwoman
she's so good that even somebody that gaga gougu sexy can believably be like an outcast of society
in a movie she's that good of an actress and I think an underrated actress because of her looks
but Chino is Pacino he's funnier than normal maybe he's more romantic than normal maybe but
I love him in this mode he's not going over the top at all he's just kind of a clueless uh I love
you is that so crazy I just all I want to do is make love is that a proud he's always like
open your robe and let me see your pussy he's saying stuff like that to her all the time it's
a lot more hard-edged than your average rom com Pacino his most memorable scene is he's been
jacking off and coming in prison for so long that he doesn't know how to let his come sounds out
so when he fucks michelle feifers she's like let it out and he has this scene where he's
screaming in her face like uh funny and also kind of sweet
you know getting back in the sex game in your forties it's wild it's absolutely wild everybody's got
their own shit everybody's got their own fetishes and sometimes they match with yours and sometimes
they don't some people come quiet some people come loud some people come not at all some people come
eight times per session that's kind of what this movie is about two lost souls in their forties
who thought they were maybe never gonna find love and happiness again who find love and happiness
in each other in the most unlikely of places the diner they both work at I've found it very sweet
and funny and charming I like the supporting cast a lot um and look before Gary Marshall
flipped and started doing Valentine's Day New Year's Eve you know like an ultra mega romantic comedy
movies where there's 20 different stories I think he did a really nice job that movie exit to
Eden killed his career if memory serves but I like Gary Marshall as a he's not the hack he's made
out to me I like his series of like adult romances they're not up to the sleepers and Seattle you got
male mode but they're close they're really really good strong rom coms with great characters
and great performances all right all right and that brings us to a rom com murder or
we're yeah sort of a movie that combines horror with the rom com and a touch of the naked gun feel
because there's an element of like parody tongue and sheet uh we're in on the joke about this movie
as well yeah this to inject injected quite a bit of the scream yep thing uh hard eyes a movie about
a Valentine's Day murder or mass murder or serial killer whatever you want to call it um who
attacks every year on Valentine's Day in a different city and murders people in love uh that's the
premise uh we land on the third year it's happening that's where we open uh in this film um
it's really great the the cold open is extraordinarily funny where the guy is proposing to his
fiance or soon to be fiance and they're hitting every cliche of like an Instagram proposal where
they're trying to videotape it and all this stuff and it's so funny and they make the both of them
so unlikable that when they are both murdered by hard eyes you're you're almost happy you know like
yeah these two people are terrible um yeah um and then so I saw this with my girlfriend and
was funny that sequence happened and then the credits started and it started and they I love that
use happy Valentine's Day by outcast that's a great opening song for a movie and it's on she turned
to me and she goes so wait so is this guy like this is like a serial killer that that attacks
couples in love I guess and I was like I think so and then right after that there's this sequence of
news clips that tell you exactly what's going on exactly who the killer is exactly why the killer's
doing what he's doing and brings you completely up to speed and I started laughing and I was like
that's so funny you asked the question literally they're like this that's good filmmaking they're like
we know you're wondering what's going on here's exactly what's going on so we can just get into the
story um and then from there you get a you it's two people that have a meet cute um
um they amidst this meet cute encounter uh the heart eyes killer who is now in their city uh
and it's the cat and mouse of the killer trying to kill them throughout the movie and you know
they go through all the motions that you'd expect is the is this guy the killer uh you know uh
why are the police so suspicious of him when he seems like a good guy blah blah blah they go
through the whole thing and they hit every single traditional rom com trope it is very funny
until it's not and then it gets quite serious like you you are in fear for them when they are
being pursued by the killer uh the murders are brutal uh and then those are butted up right up
against very funny moments they somehow pull off the balancing act of these two things tonally
very well this is something that could have gone horribly wrong if it was too ticks to the left
or the right of of the mark and they in my opinion hit the mark dead on uh in the way that
screamed it it is absolutely brutal and then it is terribly funny like and enjoyable um i i really
really really like the movie i don't i don't i won't say much more about the details because
there are things that you kind of have to see uh you know it's it's not going to do me much good
or to try to explain why the spoofing of a rom com sequence is funny or not you have to see it
and obviously there's not much i can do to to illustrate why there's great tension
uh in suspense and and whatever in in the in the more violent and uh and and horror sequences
but i i just think since since thank not since thanksgiving was the one where we were kind of saying
not since scream have we seen something kind of nail the the horror comedy thing with a wink to
camera so well and thanksgiving is pretty recent but i'll say not since Thanksgiving have we seen
something do it like this and uh i think it was i think it was very very well done and i look
forward to a sequel and uh and i enjoyed it very much yeah it was directed by Josh Rubin who
i have actually known very very casually for years he plays some of the villains in the pete homes
batman videos uh oh yeah he's he's like an impressionist and uh a funny kind of improv guy
and yeah he's clearly a very talented director it i i like i liked it less than you i liked it
less than thanksgiving i would compare it more to this tier of of comedy horror movies that's
been coming out and doing well i think it's it's of a piece with freaky with Vince Vaughn
it's of a piece with um there's been a couple other movies in that camp that kind of like comedy horror
did not not terrifying not hilarious i didn't quite have the laugh riot that you did with this one
but i thought it was really clever i liked the nian's i liked the the hard eyes how his eyes would
glow when he'd kill it's that kind of seemed influenced by my bloody valentine uh yeah or yeah
i thought the movie was sort of exceptionally clever and well written i just never got in
in a suspense horror way the way i did in and i was never slapping my knee laughing out loud a lot of
that's my mood lately which is pretty hit and missed depending on how i wake up but uh i i liked it
without loving it i'd see a sequel and i thought it was well done i did enjoy it um i guess
the kills are what really kind of sold me they were big fun like gross out head exploding kills
and there does seem to be kind of a market nowadays for the fun slasher i'll always take the fun
tongue and cheek slasher over the terrifier three and i've had a lot of people both of my personal
instagram and on the patreon lately asking us about the terrifiers when are we gonna do them what
we can do them i've seen one and two um it's just to me they're too much at the the the only thing
that bothers me i'm like i don't need this experience this feeling in my life i already have enough
dread you know i already uh sort of live in enough fear that i don't need to see the most depraved
aspects of humanity played out for over two hours i felt the same about in a lonely place or whatever
that one was with the guy walking around at a certain point it's like nature in a violent nature
yeah they're they're cut this kind of movie now that is just about how fucked up into brave
humanity is sure that that is hard for me to take at this moment in time something like hard eyes
almost goes down like a romp comp it's it's uh for me in and out of my brain almost as i leave the
theater that's why i'm kind of having a hard time joining you in a serious discussion of it because
i only saw it a month ago and i don't have a great memory of what went on but it was fun and i had a
good time um mason gooding i didn't know that he's the male lead uh that's cuba gooding junior's
son i didn't know that and mason good more relevantly is in the new screen movies which i also didn't
realize when i was watching this i was like i know this guy from somewhere and i wasn't placing it
he's in these new screen movies uh Olivia halter's the female lead i was unfamiliar with her
she's she's a disney kid it looks like um and uh you know they were both very good they were very
charming i believe they great chemistry i believed uh them as you know romantic interests
of one another um i thought that uh mckella walkins kind of stole the show she was really funny
as that boss i like her i really really enjoyed her she was very very very funny um
um you know i'm not going to ruin the end i'm not going to give away what happens um but they did a
great job of keeping you guessing and even in placing things right in front of you that seemed
a bit obvious making you still question whether or not those things or what you thought they were
or or if you were being fooled that to me is usually the mark of a good slash movie when they're
presenting things to you and you're going well that's too obvious well wait but is it no maybe
that's why and you're you're doing that whole guessing game in your head this movie had me doing that
and uh the reveal at the end was enough of a reveal that uh that uh that i was still invested
uh and uh i look forward to seeing if something else uh comes after this a sequel or whatever i
would i would gladly go see it um but uh my hog is up for hard eyes
uh my hog is barely up we didn't actually talk on the last one but in case you couldn't tell the hogs
were in the dirt for a wolf man ripped ripped from my body by a wolf man and thrown into the dirt
it couldn't have been more down and off yes uh and and as for hard eyes you know i just looked up
Josh Rubin uh just because he's a guy i've i've met a few times around the comedy scene in l.a. and
tragically this man lost his home uh that's sorry he fires so on January 7th before him and his wife
were slated to move into their dream home in all to dina they watched along and horror as the
eaten fire headed straight for their new neighborhood so it was a brand new house that they hadn't
even moved into yet um so i'm glad that he's got a movie that is well received and might lead to
a sequel and it seems like his career up but uh yeah a lot of people affected congrats to Josh
Rubin congrats to all congrats to the listeners for supporting us for all these years and thank you
i am on the Patrick Walsh at instagram we are on c when help pod on instagram where you can see
kind of funny audio clips and fan art and thank you to all of you as always for the wonderful fan
art uh i see it when you tag me sometimes you know i'm at work and can't engage but we always see it
and we appreciate uh your guys love and support of the pod thank you absolutely jota rosa comedy on
instagram uh jota rosa.com for tour dates again please come check me out live and uh johi roses
and nyc if you're uh in town go get a sandwich have a drink uh folks we'll see you next time
and we'll see you at hell