Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber, offer not available in all states,
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
Hello everybody and welcome to another scintillating episode of We'll See You in Hell.
On this week's episode we'll be talking about the finale of the Twin Peaks reboot but
also the entire rebooted series at large.
And don't you worry because I know very few people watch the reboot.
We'll be talking about many other things as well and now
Well, that guy suppose we should go ahead and get on with the show and and in doing so get on
With the Joe
I like that one my that might be my favorite a whispered
Yeah, I like it all right
It's it's it shows it shows I don't need to come to you. You'll come to me. I
Set the tone here. That's right. I like that quite a bit
John, I'm gonna I'm gonna just shout out a little a little tension in the room that you're probably not even aware of
I'm sitting here with a
extreme amount of hair cut off of my head about
45 minutes ago. I haven't gotten a nice haircut. I'd take a did you get a haircut?
You think I haven't noticed it. I've noticed it, but you just don't give those sort of maybe I was waiting for the podcast to start to say something.
I mean, you don't pick me up at my house. We were driving along. I'm like, well, you know, I took off, you know, probably a foot of hair.
Your hair looks great. Thanks, Joe. And I think this style of hair suits you better.
You know, I think so too. I was just not getting it cut out of busyness and you know, like
You work a bunch it's like things like a haircut and stuff you're like that. That's it's a luxury
I don't have time for sure, and then one day you look in the mirror and you look like cousin god damn it
Sure from the Adams family sure
And I I like to fancy myself, you know when that back in the day when I should have done it I
Never rock that grungy
Cobain look I
i had the same hair cut literally for about thirty two years
by the way how was somebody not done of like some sort of youtube mashup where
it's the it trailer but it's cousin it instead of pennywise how's that i think
is nobody gives the fuck about the adam's family yeah i guess so it's mean it's
not a funny joke but i just i don't know i'm surprised it hasn't happened anyway
uh... your cut looks good i like it thanks shows off more that delicious face i'd
call it high and tight baby
Yeah, I truly, I had, I would say the exact same haircut for 90 % of my life, and then I like the long at times, but, you know, you can't control it, it gets into your hair, it gets in your face, you know.
You ever have a long hair? You don't seem like that would work for you.
like it's more like Afro -ey.
Okay, because it's curly.
But you know, you with the long hair,
it didn't look bad but it did times
make you look like some kind of card shark.
You know, or something like that.
Yeah.
I like you with the cleaner cut to be honest.
Sure.
I had an old roommate who really loved
when I started growing it out
and would just like praise me all the time.
You gotta go longer, crazier, wilder.
And it got in my head, you know.
Especially when you get your hair cut,
Looking all nice and your dear friend Joe can't say so much as two words about it. I said it
I was waiting for the thing to start all right. I saw I also don't copy I got to tell you something
I was a little sad about oh
We went to that Emmys party the other week bad party right not a great party, but an okay party had a bad time
I thought that I really put people put the whole suit together tremendously you did and you didn't say anything and it kind of bothered me
I had a black shirt, gray suit, black shoes.
I mean, it came together.
It was sharp.
And I thought you would say, like, hey, dude,
you're looking snazzy.
Did he have to tell you, like, nah,
she's good about that kind of.
No, and I was, and then when she didn't say it,
I was like, I must look terrible.
No, I, I mean, we had had some cocktails.
I'll blame it on that.
But that was just the whole party.
I would say from the second I walked in the door,
I said, god damn, I wish I had stayed home.
And that's not always the case. I'm not hugely social. I don't love a party
But that one the vibe was immediately off
It was a comedy central
Now I will say this just last year that party was popping and swinging and I had a blast
And this year was dead and weird and awkward and it was a very
Because this year they had it after the creative Emmys. Yes
us. Um, and also to it was, there was something there was not a party vibe this year.
No, nobody, everybody I was running into at that party, I was like, well, this guy doesn't
really drink. Like I was desperately trying to find people that were ready to throw them
back. And nobody was really, it's like, there's like four open bars in the place. It's like,
come on, it's got some fun, man. Like, I know. And it just didn't have that vibe. Even my
buddy Jonas who works over his name is Jonas, yes, not my name, his name. My name is Weep Hill.
He baffling lyrics. I mean, of course, that's one of the best albums ever made. The Weaser Blue
album. But what does any of that mean on my name is Jonas? The other ones, the other songs are very
clear. Are they Bible references, I think? Well, Jonas in the whale, yes, but not a deep pill.
Jonah and the whale.
Yeah, so not Jonas and it's not whale. It's wheel. My name is Jonas. I'm carrying the wheel.
I don't know. Thanks for all you've shown us. This is how we feel.
I mean, talk about a group that went from having a little mystery in the lyrics to just
lane it all of the table. They got a new song. I love rock and roll music and glasses on my face.
Their new song is like a tribute to the beach boys. They're literally that's what it's about.
It's about like I love the beach boys. I always say no one in my life
Has ever let me down like weezer and I'm a guy who ever when I know disappoints me in a huge way at some point
Weezer
You go blue you go Pinkerton anybody wants to argue which one of those is better. I'm happy to side
Depending on the day. I'll side with blue being better or Pinkerton being better
I was like, these songs all follow a very specific formula.
It's a little corny, but it's still very catchy and good.
Maladroid underrated, but we're dipping into some problem areas.
I feel like everything beyond that was a fucking train, right?
You take Maladroid and the green album and you can
piece together a decent album between the two.
The best of Maladroid and the best of green is a great album.
Yeah, possibilities. The punk song on Maledroid. Yeah, it's great.
Gone Fish in is awesome. Gone Fish in is great. The one that's like, wow, wow, wow,
whatever that song is on Maledroid, it's the second song. Here in my head. Yeah,
that's classic like fun weezer, you know. Yeah, they are great songs on both. When you get into
the one with Hurley from Lost, don't even bring it up. There's a song on that called
peace and love with like a sitar in the background that is arguably the worst
song ever written but then every time a weasery album comes out all these fucking
nerds come out of their coffins and they're like hey this one's a real return to
form well you know what okay I'll give it a spin and it's terrible I will say this
not the new one that's coming out now but the last one that came out was
I know you liked it. It was dog shit. I didn't look I wouldn't say like I it was as close to a weezer album as you
Were gonna get what was your favorite song on it? You're right. No, of course you couldn't but I remember the first song sort
It was like tired of sex and
It had moments it had redeeming moments, and I was like, you know what if this album would have came after the green album
I would have given him I would have given it a shot. Yeah, it was that it was that kind of thing
But I mean it was certainly a step in the right direction from fucking Beverly Hills
That's where I want to be and I can't even tell these being sarcastic or not
I can't tell I don't even think he knows
Yet and there's always one song where he's like I
Fucked a 13 -year -old Asian girl you're like wait, what was that line?
What would you say rivers?
Yeah, I love so much but here's my question Joe and it's a question. I'm sure I've posted this podcast because the question I asked myself every day
If the Weezer Blue album, and we don't know anything about Weezer, that album drops today.
Is it the success it was back then? The answer to that, I'm just going to go ahead and say
it's no. But would I love it as much now? And I think sadly, tragically, the answer is also no.
I just agree. I know chance I would listen to that every time I got in the car for three years
as I did for Blue and Pinkerton. Well, I didn't listen to it every day, so it didn't hit me like that.
But I did like the complete obsession with me and my friends are always saying every
Lyrics every time we drove around. I didn't get into weasier till Pinkerton
When I love that when Pinkerton came out, I was like, oh, yeah, the new weasers. I was like
Yeah, I guess that's sort of it. Maybe I'll check it out. Yeah, and my RA and my dorm Chris played it for me
And I just remember being like
Holy shit man. This is really dark. Yeah, but it still sounds like weasers. This is really fucking cool
And then that, then I retroactively got more into the blue album, even though I was
fairly familiar with it. But if the blue album and picker wax America for Christ's sake,
yeah, what do you want? In the garage. In the garage, yeah, amazing song in dreams.
I always play only in dreams on the jukebox because it's like getting three songs for one.
It's a nine minute song. So you get, but here's the thing, if the blue, if those albums came out today,
Okay, commercial successes, I can't speak to, probably not.
But I still think if I heard those for the first time today, I'd be, I'd be pretty blown
away.
I'd be like, wow, this is an amazing, I remember when that blue album came out, Pinkstone
playing it for me and going, this band sounds like if Nirvana and the Beastie Boys did an
album together.
And I was like, oh yeah, you're right.
It's, I'm sorry, the Beast Boys, right?
Beach Boys, excuse me.
Oh, okay.
Sorry, I said Beastie Boys.
He was like, this sounds like if the Beach Boys and Nirvana got mixed together.
And it was like, yeah, you're right, I buy that.
You know, so it was a good, a very good assessment.
I was going to tell another Pinkstone story.
What were we talking about earlier?
Pink or Stone.
What were we telling about talking about earlier though?
Before this.
Weezer, and then my hair cut, I think, is all we've covered.
Your hair cut?
God damn it.
It's just really slipping for you, isn't it?
You're seeing the pattern, right?
You're seeing the pattern from...
I'm regularly forgetting things.
I can't remember words anymore.
Well, I am the one who listens to our podcast each week.
Joe does, and I think it's a,
I think you'd be really pleasantly surprised,
because sometimes even when I let's do it the next day,
I'm like laughing at our own banter,
you know, which is really smelling your own shit.
It's very narcissistic, but sick.
I have to listen to it and make sure there's no weird pops
or whistles or anything, that somebody has to listen to it.
And, uh, you know, Joe really more and more each week will start a sentence and then
be like, what was I talking about?
It happens a lot.
And this past week you were kind of angry at yourself about it.
I feel I struggle with my short -term memory as well.
We know the reason.
It's marijuana.
But...
No.
I don't smoke marijuana.
Maybe I got a wet brain.
Do you think I got wet brain?
I don't know.
But more and more.
I mean, we've only talked about two things.
and now you're trying to figure out what we're talking about.
No, I'm not gonna figure out, I'm not lost.
I'm not wandering around the room as we podcast.
All right, I'm just trying to remember,
there was a pinkstone thing I wanted to say to you
that was a rough, that was that had to do
with something you were talking about.
And it's not.
We only talked about we, you know,
with a weasier has an album called Ratitude, right?
It makes me sick, yeah.
It makes me sick.
Actually, peace and love might be on Rattitude,
but that was the last one I listened to all the way through
and it shook me to my goddamn core.
Rattitude, hurly, yeah.
As we already mentioned,
with the guy from Lost on the Cover.
Yeah, yeah.
That red album is the,
album I believe that is the Beverly Hills song on it.
Well, it also has pork and beans
and pork and beans is really catchy.
Look, Beverly Hills is catchy.
Doesn't mean I want to fucking listen to it.
It actually feels like a limb biscuit to me.
Okay, pork and beans is lip biscuit.
That's what I said.
No, what?
So there's nothing like lip biscuit.
It's douche rock to me.
But it's like a pop song.
It doesn't sound like lip biscuit.
Babbily hell.
Lip biscuit would be like,
Babbily hells on your forehead.
All right, well, it sounds like sugar rate, man.
There you go.
All right, we'll say the right reference the first time.
Stop it.
You know, uh, one of the greatest concerts I've ever been to, sir, I mean,
certainly not 90, but it was a 90s show at the Greek theater.
And I went with a bunch of co -workers about, yeah, God, at this point, five, six years ago.
And it was Marcy playground, one of those 90s reunion tours.
Yeah, I like that song.
Then it was
Jen Blossoms, who I consider one of the most underrated band.
You talk about their first album.
You know what, Walsh?
I've been waiting for a while first to harshly disagree with you.
Their first album is a
classic.
I will throw this fucking drink at you.
And here's why.
Here's how wrong you are.
There isn't a bad song on that first album.
I ate a joke where the punchline was Jen Blossoms.
and it got a laugh, because people were like,
oh yeah, that they suck.
Yeah, because they're unfairly aligned
with your smash mouth, your hoobist night,
and everybody else on the field.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I put them in a different shitty category.
I put them in a different,
I'm putting Jim Blossom's below smash mouth.
I'll listen to Walker out of your
fucking frayless and do.
You're not about you.
Well, I'm talking about their first album.
Find out if I use an amazing song, by the way.
Oh, right.
They also have one of my favorite songs
ever about addiction called hold me down okay brilliant lyrics to this song and the story of
the gin blossoms is so tragic it makes me like I'm even more okay what's the story they're actually
went forward as a band and released their music their guitarist well they're either first albums
called new miserable experience yeah I know and their second one is called congratulations I'm sorry
Yeah, congratulations. I'm sorry is a dream album title
How many times have I said I'm sorry to somebody where the subtext is congratulations? All right, I'll give you your I'm sorry
I'll give you the album title, but tell me why this first album is so brilliant
Well, I mean to me they're like a big star, you know big star. What did big star sing?
Big star is a is a lost kind of it's a it's a very like you know
Alex Chilton 70s 60s band I know a few other songs, but they're they're pretty lost to
History unfortunately, and they made great music and Jim Blossoms was kind of ripping them off
I put Jim Blossoms six to candle box. That's that's that's get it. You're out of your fucking mind
You're out of your fuck. I'm like who sang you know what band I did like although the eastbound and down where they played
Far behind at the funeral of the Jason Sudakus character, right? I ruined that about who's the band that's saying so let's gel
Oh, bear near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near near
That's not that's not collect the you're right. That's collective soul Joe is in collective soul.
Joe don't think so. Wait, bear now, bear now, bear now. Let's mingle. Yeah. Make it well.
I don't know who that is. But they sound nothing like the Jim Blossom. I know they don't.
That's why I like them. Uh, and then local H was born up. It's collective soul. Okay. Yeah.
They collect some awesome great songs too. Yeah. The gin blossoms. Here's their story.
their guitarist wrote all their best songs right not their lead singer and the
guitarist was a extreme alcoholic the lyrics to the song hold me down and by
the way if I were to if I were to present you the poem of hold me down and you
didn't know it was a gin blossom song you'd be like this is the best description of
being addicted it's nothing I've ever heard right because the guy had some
fucking demons fair enough he also you know he did your hey jealousy he did all the
big gym blossoms hits all the all the big ones all the hits now as the as the
time comes where they're getting ready to go out for their second album he can't
stop drinking he's showing up to practice his drunk still by all accounts playing
beautifully and still writing the bet clearly the best songs in the band because
they never had a hit again but the band finally had an intervention and we're like
I'm sorry. You're drinking. It's been graduation. I'm sorry. We're throwing you out of the band, right?
You can't stop drinking and we don't we don't like it. We don't like that you're showing up a show's drunk. Whatever
he leaves and
Kills himself right like almost immediately for what he had inflicted on the world with these two what show?
The man couldn't live with himself folks. Please take record of how I am not laughing at this at all
Because the man was a great fucking songwriter.
And they were in the wrong time.
They were abandoned the wrong time.
They should have been contemporaries of a big star.
There are some fantastic pop rock songs
on their first album.
They seem like Matchbox 20.
No, they didn't.
They're like very much in that same thing.
They didn't, but Matchbox 20 knew
how to craft a pop song as well.
Jim Blossoms are far superior band.
When you're a great thing that'll make you like
the guy from Matchbox, by the way.
I'm nowhere near even even the first part of talking about this concert.
We've become so side track the gin blossoms concert. Oh, wait, that's right.
Now the gin blossom or are you going to say?
How about he play? He wrote a great Arctic. What's that guy's name again?
Rob Thomas. All right, I almost tell my the article where he said he was the first guy
who ever got fat being addicted to cocaine. No, no, that's hilarious.
I love him. Yeah, he wrote an article about how everybody hates him
because he's Rob Thomas and he's just like, yeah, I'm like a cool guy.
Like I just I'm sorry that you don't like my bad, but like yeah, we just do what we do like it doesn't mean
I'm an asshole. Oh god bless them. They they probably have he probably has 40 million dollars. He tells this story at the
end of the article where he was hanging out with David Cross. Yeah, and then and everything and like they were
In a great time until David Cross figured out who he was and like and then was like shitty dorm and he's like what the fuck man?
And he goes and then you know to add insult injury
I think he did, of course, thought I was Scott's step.
And he goes, Scott's, this is the last line of the article,
Scott's step, he's my Rob Thomas.
That's great.
Yeah, I really like that guy a lot.
I don't like his music, but I think that's the musical area.
I hated Rob Thomas.
But when smooth first hit the airwaves,
when it first hit the airwaves,
before everyone got sick of it,
I was like, you can't deny this song.
It's the greatest selling record of all time.
It is catchy as fuck.
And the catchy song is not an easy thing to do.
It makes me, when I hear it now, I see the red.
Oh, no, it's a blind rage.
I just pictured Angela Bassett getting her groove back to it
and some outdoor cabana bar.
It's not the song sucks.
But yeah, this show was,
Mark's a player who I had no interest in.
But they did sex and candy and they of course they play sex and can tell
he better than Ezra showed up and it was a great song. I love that song. Now
better than Ezra are the slightly shittier gin blossoms. You're a fucking idiot
that well they are. You're an idiot. And here's why the guy from better than
Ezra said when I wrote good I was trying to write a pixie song and when you
listen to it through that filter you go yeah that's kind of sound like a pixie
song. Good is a great song but I have never heard one gin blossom song but
It sounds like that.
Also, one of the most perfect Northern McDonald's weekend update jokes.
One of my all time favorite Northern McDonald's weekend update jokes was number two on the
adult alternative charts this week, better than Ezra, number three, Ezra, really a truly
perfect one.
And I bet you had bombed, right?
of course yeah so this show was at the Greek theater very fun it was as I said
Marcy Playground. It was the gin blossom lit. What did lits sing again? You make me come. You make me complete.
You make me completely miserable. I don't even remember this song. Do you remember
Did you forget about the things I said? Yeah, they had a good album too. Please tell me why. We're singing
and beautifully tonight.
Yeah.
But miserable is a really great song to this day.
Remember to hit you with my favorite 90s song
when you're done?
I'd love it.
But for some reason, maybe it was weed and fluencer.
I don't know, but we got a real kick this night
out of me saying, you make me palm,
you make me palm freights.
You make me palm freightsly miserable.
They were selling palm freights at the venue.
Clearly we were high doesn't make any sense Pat. I'll tell you we loved it sure you do I tweeted it
And the people of Twitter loved it as well. I don't know why it just captured the zeitgeist
Then it was the gin blossoms who killed it?
Then it was sugar ray now
I have always hated sugar ray except for their one kind of more rock and song which is called answer the phone
Which is a great pop punk song and I have a not a fan certainly in those days
I had some affection for the pop punk genre, but Sugar Ray fully embraced how
washed up they were and it was a funny fun time. Then outcomes Joe the headliner ever clear.
Ever clear who wrote the same song 500 times, but I'm listening.
I love Santa Monica, their first big hit.
Beyond that, I can give her take almost interchangeable with the TOTE's backwater.
Now, the TOTE is one of my favorite.
Listen, I like the TOTE's quite a bit, but I'm saying those two songs, you could do like
a mega mix thing.
The TOTE's first two albums, I mean, I consider them a really fantastic TOTE's or a great
band.
They're on that, they're not, but they're first 12.
But the Tudys are one of those bands like Faith No More,
where they got popular and are only known for the one song
and you were like, no, there's so much, yes.
There's so much more.
Correct.
Good.
But Everclear was very like self -important and kind of sucky.
And at some point, I was very into Twitter,
at this point, probably five years ago.
I tweeted something derogatory about Everclear.
Within 10 minutes of Everclear leaving the stage,
I had a hateful tweet from the drummer of Everclear, where he was like, I'd like to see you write some of the best fucking songs of an that defined an entire decade you mother fucker.
And then that was really the first time, because I had almost no followers at this point, where I was like, yeah, words can hurt.
Yeah.
Words can hurt.
You're drumming an Everclear, you think you're cool, you go back.
What what what what what people thought of the show?
What would you have done if he went and killed himself after that?
No, don't bring that. I'm just saying. I'm asking. What would you have done?
Probably nothing I mean to be honest
He was also like a late addition. He wasn't even like original ever clear member. Yeah, well then fuck him. I agree
That's lame. That's like one of the roadies firing back at you. Right. Now. What is your favorite 90 song? You're going to it's quite arguably
We went through the ride, we sat a hermosa, we bumped the one to zero on that day.
Oh fastball the way.
Yeah.
It's a fantastic.
Which to me, it's almost, and this is a pinkstone thing we've talked about this.
It's almost a prototype for a modern spoon song.
It sounds like shoun.
It's got that Spanish guitar in it.
It's got the super catchy hook that's all great that's all ripping off Elvis Costello. Yes, which which I was my favorite artist of all time
That's also had a great song. You're an ocean. Remember that song. I only know the way around ocean. Yeah, I only know the way
But I love that song makes me happy and ways that I can't even I mean, I just I love that fucking song
Everybody knows this once and it had that song. Sure. It had
Toadies backwater. It had Everclear, Santa Monica. It had
Stars by
Humm. Oh
That's a great song. It had
Well, fuck me and this this sound garden song
I don't know what the song is called.
I, uh, sound garden, I love their early stuff, but really they hit a real, I mean, down
on the upside is arguably better than super unknown.
Down on the upside, I finally, finally got it on vinyl.
They re -released it finally.
It's a double vinyl.
Yep.
I've got something to equate a bit blow up the outside world is is
One of my favorite songs is that the one that's like no
No, no, that's not blow up the outside world the song when the lyrics are blow up the outside
It's actually a different song, but that's that one make that's the one right. Yeah. Yeah, that's a fucking awesome song
That's a real like
It goes for a lot of changes throughout it's a great song pretty news is my favorite
sound guard and song next to
outshine the worst ever
performance I've ever seen on
Saturday night. Yeah, I know what
you can garden. His voice was
shot. Yeah, when the care was
hosting. They're doing pretty
news. He can't hit the notes.
It's like I was like, oh my god
Jim Carrey and sound garden in
their primes. What a killer
night. And he was just like, like
voice going out every note. Yeah,
he couldn't he couldn't do it, but
it was clear that it just
I'll tell you what was beautiful and heartbreaking is the when Whitney Houston died.
He does that.
It was a Chris Cornell concert and he comes out for the encore and he does an acoustic
version of I will always love you and he dedicates to it and it's and I mean he wails at the
fuck out like yeah.
That guy was awesome man.
I'm sad that he died.
Same here.
Yeah.
I watched and you know I certainly don't wish death on Eddie Vetter absolutely not.
He's a very talented man in a songwriter.
Where are you going with this one?
I'm saying my least favorite of those pro jam, you know, pro jam,
Nirvana sound guard in your big three.
My least favorite by like one billion percent is pro jam.
That's nuts.
One billion percent.
You're nuts.
I've never really gotten into a pro jam song or album.
I think they're decent.
I had a friend in high school.
My curry who was obsessed with them.
Mike, I think you might be listening.
Hello, he would play them.
Incessantly and like you got to hear this song. You got to hear this live cut. Yeah, remember they at least they released like
5 ,000 live out. I don't give a shit about any of that stuff, but I'll tell you this man. I'm not my thing. I've made many a Pearl Jam mix
Where every song sweeps me away? I heard do the evolution in the car today, and I was I was jumping out of the seat
I like that. The, uh, hell hell
Fucking animal even flow that I go Nirvana Pearl Jam sound garden and then in fourth place
So I'm gonna put your old STP because I feel like they were the fourth. I'll take SCP over progeny shut up
Absolutely shut your fuck absolutely shut your dirty mouth the first
Number four is weak. The first three stone -to -one pilots albums are better than the first three pro gym albums. You are a crazy man. Sorry
You think I know I know stone temple pilots purple is better than her versus purple is phenomenal
I don't say I didn't like the tiny tiny music is a is a master music is let's not get carried away here
It's not a masterpiece. It's a good album very under a album. I would tell you about when I saw some double pilots
Yeah, I'm a hundred times the guys wife puked on her tits and he gave you the tickets to the Vegas show and you went in and you watched it
It was I'm sorry. You sat in the front row and it was great
Yeah, that's basically the story right that's it
I don't even like Allison Chains, I might take him over progen.
I would give you Allison Chains over progen.
Even though I don't agree with you.
I'll take some over Allison Chains and progen.
You're, you're pet, you're talking like an asshole.
They got better songs.
No, they don't.
What are you talking about right now?
Sorry.
They got better songs.
You think dude, fucking them bones.
Uh, rain when I die, man in the box, I stay away, unblood, no exchanges, interstate love song.
I love interstate love song, that was on my 90s mix.
It's a killer song.
That was on my 90s mix.
I didn't say they didn't have good songs.
I'll take the totes over project.
I would give you the totes, but you can't say stone temple pilots.
I am.
That's an insane.
They were just not my thing.
It's just a matter of taste.
Well, bad taste actually, it's a matter of bad taste.
All right, so all of you remember when you were feeling,
you wanted to support Pat during his gin blossoms argument,
saying this guy just likes to bet.
Can I say something?
He just said Stone Table pilots was better than Pearl Jam.
Even though I know gin blossoms only have one and a quarter
good albums, I'll take gin blossoms over Pearl Jam.
You know, you make me sick.
And I won't hesitate to do so.
You're just saying this to make me angry.
I'm not.
I won't hesitate to do so.
Let me stick to my stomach.
Have you heard the entire first dungeon bust up?
You come out here to Holly when you become a pig.
Have you heard the first gym bust up?
No, why would I hear it?
I urge you all to check it out.
It's, I just don't care enough.
I don't, I've never liked one song.
I've never wanted to do it.
You didn't enjoy hate jealousy.
No.
Then we're different.
We're different.
We're different people.
I hate that song.
I hope that song kills itself.
All right, how about that?
How about that?
I hope it's never played ever again. Now I'm gonna get a hate tweet from the replacement guitarist in the gin blossoms
I had a friend who I made made fun of for years the guitarist and Jim loss was dead
But I know the replacement like like how you got the replacement drug replacement's over project the replacement drum
That was a callback. No, I got I got my friend for years thought that
The song hey jealousy was about a woman named jealousy and
And we all made fun of them for that.
Pat, I got to tell you, as negligent as we are on this podcast about not talking about
the movie.
Yeah.
PR.
We are 34 minutes in.
We haven't touched a segment.
We haven't touched the review.
I mean, this is truly incredible.
But I got to tell you, Joe, people, when I look at the Facebook page, I know you don't have
Facebook and I envy you for it.
They're always citing shit that generally is completely all right. I'm happy to talk about other things
Well, I mean we're just to tell you where we're at right now
We're recording this episode two days after we we recorded the last episode
Because of some scheduling problems we had
So there is really nothing to talk about for Pat's movie corner
There is nothing to talk about I did see a movie and you did yeah, and that's short period of time movie last night
Would you say I saw Kingsman two? How was it? Do you see Kingsman one? No, you still have it and I told you you should I know
I'm not against it. I just haven't seen it yet
So I hate superhero movies. I have said a million times. I find them lazy and boring
I
Went into Kingsman like all right. Let's see what this is and was blown away by it and
And the final scene of the first Kingsman is still one of the most shocking things I have ever seen in a mainstream movie, and I could not believe that it happened, and I urge you to watch it. I think it's great.
So I was moderately excited about Kingsman 2, but as I know Heather, my girlfriend loved the first one.
We both got our movie passes by the way you can now get movie pass which Joe and I both have for $10 a month
They have zero customer service. It's an atrocious company, but you can see a movie a day
For a month so 30 30 movies a month if you want for $10. Yeah, we we're not getting money from them either, but it's an amazing deal
I used to do this when it was $40 and thought it was an amazing deal. Yeah
So we go into Kingsman 2 and I'm kind of dreading it because as we walk in I see that it's like
145 minutes
Which is every movie now two and a half hours and
It starts out
I'm like I don't even they're kind of a it's it's a big thing of sequels nowadays where they assume that you love the movie a lot
More than you do sure so they'll start alluding to things that you're like I don't even remember what that was
I tried to Heather. I'm like, is this the same girl at the end of the first one? She had no idea. Right, but you know, it's entertaining. It's entertaining. It's entertaining.
Julianne Moore in the movie has her own almost like a universal city walk.
You ever been up there? Yeah, like her own like little world with all these restaurants and things. And she, her whole goal is to legalize drugs
And have them tax and everything and try to make money off them.
And once this sub plot starts up, I'm like, this movie's got a lot of shit going on.
And as my buddy pointed out to me, he saw it as kind of a Paul Verhoeven kind of satire.
And I did as well.
The president of this movie gets impeached.
He's nothing like Trump, but clearly like there's something going on here.
He's like fuck these drug addicts will kill them all anyone who's ever used drugs
Their their veins turn blue in their face and they get all weird or whatever and then he learns like some of his advisors have used drugs and
Stuff I don't know if I'm explaining this well, but why are there veins turning blue?
You know you'll find out if you see the movie but anyone anyone who's done drugs this shows up
They make a new drug to where it's called like jazz.
Oh, these kids are doing jazz.
They have an anecdote, yes.
But he learns that his advisors do drugs too
and the hypocrisy of it, but he wants them all killed anyway.
They're like, but what about the person who works
the 20 hour workday and wants to have a puff of a join
to whatever the president's like, fuck them all, kill them?
Like the satire in this movie is off the charts.
It's an insane movie visually at Spectacular.
The fight scenes are the best I've seen in ages.
maybe since the first Kingsman and there's a subplot.
I won't even say who it is, but it's a big pop star.
No, but you're gonna like it.
Okay.
A big all -time classic pop star.
I'm not talking about cold play or something.
And where they go with this is nuts.
This is a movie that probably costs $200 million.
And it's taken some of the biggest swings I've seen in ages.
So is it good or bad?
I was entertained for the entire two and a half hours
didn't check my watch once.
And then at the end, I turned to Heather,
and I was like, I fucking loved that.
She was like, I did as well.
That's good, all right.
It's nuts.
They're very inventive, crazy, like anarchic movies
at a time when every movie is the same.
Okay.
And I really, really loved it.
I loved both of them.
I probably preferred the first one,
even though I'm raving about the second one.
but I just admire that they're getting made.
They're nuts, and this one really had something to say.
I loved it.
Great, I loved it.
Oh good, I didn't think that's where you're going with it.
I think we're gonna say it was like a match
and you hated it.
It's a mess, and I loved it.
All right, great.
And it has currently, I think, like a 40%.
Really?
That's why you can't trust Ron Tomatoes, it's stupid.
Yeah.
I'll say the weakest link of it, sadly, is Jeff Bridges.
And he comes on the scene Channing Tatum and him are doing like a Kentucky they're running like a bourbon
I don't even understand anymore. I tweeted the other day. I mean I look forward to being part of what will become to be known as the Jeff
Bridges only did weird Southern characters face. It's like why is everything he's in now? He's got a cowboy hat and he's like
Oh, I think they're good to be here. Why is that all he's really hated it and when he turns around at first like I mean
I mean, we're talking one of my favorite actors, yeah.
When he turns around and they give him the reveal
and he's like, you all want a ship of bourbon?
You know, I'm like, oh, Christ, every time he came on,
I was waiting for the moment he would be off.
I wanted more Joel Egerton and Jeff Bridges.
And I know how you feel about Joel Egerton.
You're not a fan.
I also think Joel Egerton, even though he's only like
30 years old, I think he has hair plugs and that.
Speaking of what you know to look at this and see if you agree with it of a sip of bourbon
Baby needs a refill go ahead jump because because it's 10 of 11 on a Wednesday night and why not
Why not by the way I'm too in I've had two bourbons already you're still in that one tequila. Yeah, please tell me it was a pretty hopped up tequila though
I'll take another splash okay good. I'm just nursing it talk to the people because I do have something for Pat's movie corner
I'll talk to them, but folks if you've seen Kingsming you know what I'm talking about if you haven't watch it the final scene of Kingsman is the
I would say for me in terms of mainstream cinema
One of the craziest things I've ever seen in a big movie like that. I really I really do think so to end a movie like that
I can't believe anyone signed off on it. I'm not gonna spoil it for Joe or if you haven't seen it
Kingsman 2 kind of tries to do a similar thing
where
He has to put a tiny condom on his finger and he's got to put a tracking device in a woman
So he meets her and these two guys are competing to see who's going to be the one to do it
but they have to finger her to get the tracking device into her vagina.
And it was again, like you watch this whole scene, it goes on for like 20 minutes.
You kind of can't believe what's happening. Like I'm so glad that these movies were greenlit.
Matthew Vaughan
Did them both and I guess he did what the he did layer cake, which is awesome, and then maybe X -Men 3
No X -Men 3 is
Brad oh, Brad right
He did X -Men something right?
Matthew Vaughn, I believe did a
Future pass, which was yes, it was great and
He did one of the worst movies I've ever seen which is star dust starring Robert De Niro
dog shit. I would say an F -minus. When I say one of the worst ones I've ever seen I'm not exaggerating
but but Vaughn is a guy to watch I mean he's uh I I don't know to go to see a two -and -a -half
hour movie and not be bored is a special thing but that's all I've seen and now I've talked about it
for a long time. Well I've got something can anyone hear you I would imagine no. Well the mic is like
Pointing at me they can probably hear me like in a I can go ahead and keep talking if you need me, too. All right
Speaking of talking folks
Talking that's what I was about to say I just had a quick flash to sing look who's talking at the dollar show when I was a kid
I had to wait for every movie to come to the dollar show. It's always nice when your friends are all enjoying Batman
And you see it three years later at the dollar show these let movies be in the theater for a long time
But the first look who's talking,
what do you think that's like watching that now?
I remember loving it.
Look who's talking too was terrible.
And then look who's talking now where it's dogs
with the voices of Danny DeBito and Diane Keaton.
Even as a child, when they came out with the sequels,
I was like, why don't you fuck get the fuck out of my face?
Yeah.
But I, man, did I love that first one?
I think I saw the drive in.
Well, we accelerated our sex talk with my parents
Because they show you that sperm thing at the beginning. Yeah. I was like, what was that man?
Did I love that look who's talking? Sure. And that was the that was sort of a comeback for Travolta.
It was and Kirstie L .A. as well. But then and then he faded away and then and then Pulp
Tiction was the real comeback. So here's the thing. Are you gonna tell a story? I would consider the
the comeback Michael. Speaking of comebacks. Yeah. And Travolta. This is what I have for Pat's movie
We recorded some movie we've both seen several times, but I had a new revelation.
I watched with my friend the other night, Jackie Brown once again.
I don't think we've ever talked about a movie more on this podcast.
A phenomenal piece of work.
Can I just say this?
I'm prepared now as an adult man to place it in my top 10 of all time.
It's not in my top 10 of all time, but I love it very much.
But I will say this.
first time I ever realized the true tragedy of the Max Cherry character. His whole
thing is he does for other people never for himself and this whole movie is
literally him bailing Jackie Brown out of the situation. Yeah. And I never fully
realized that it always made me sad at the end. Yes. But I never fully realized the
the metaphor of it all. I am a very, very, very difficult cry. I don't cry. I've, I recently,
I always, Jackie Brown's always on like cinematics or it's on my favorite cable channel, Stars Black.
Right. My most watch cable channel is Stars Black. Now, when did they play it on Stars Black?
They play movies with Black Leads. Okay. And for whatever reason, they're always playing
exactly what I want to be watching okay I just I'm just shocked that it exists
stars black and that and the name is that bull but I watch Jackie Brown or I
watched like the last half hour of Jackie Brown on cable and I'm not this guy
because I don't like to come into movies late I like to see the whole thing sure but
I watch the end of Jackie Brown once a month probably on cable and I stay up if I
if I'm tired, I'm going to bed at three and it's on.
I'll watch the end of Jackie Brown.
That's my one movie.
But I've seen it again and again and again and again
for whatever reason, a couple months back, it was on.
And when she kisses in that tight close -up,
kisses Max Cherry, Jackie Brown,
that goes and gets in her car
and then Max Cherry fades into like hazy in the background
and then she's driving and singing while she's driving
out there.
I was crying.
Yeah, I couldn't stop crying. It's a beautiful film. It's a movie that gets better and better and better and
Certainly like high school. I watched Pulp Fiction a hundred times
But over the course of the back half of my life. I've seen Jackie Brown way more and I'd have to watch him back to back to true
would decide which is better.
Every, and I never dreamed I'd even be making a comparison.
Because every single person hits a grand slam.
Yeah.
Samuel Jackson.
I think it's his best performance.
It is Jackson's best performance.
Keaton off the charts, we were hysterical watching the scene
where Pam Greer's like, she came into the room
and took the bag or whatever she had Keaton's going.
Keaton's interrogating her and he's going,
he's going, you got no idea.
You got no you got no idea and he starts to actually do it like a weird deniro
And they got it with a gum and everything it's yeah, that's shot of him walking down the hall with the motorcycle helmet under his
He's awesome and his partner's awesome whoever that he's fantastic
But I feel like even the hardcore film fans I I and I think I told you this and you didn't know that he plays the same role and out of sight
Yeah, he that's the same character. It's the same character. Yes. I'm never seen out of sight
But what I've never seen outside I never saw it. I'm sorry. I never saw how to say out of sight is a is a lighter
You know, it's a lighter Jackie Brown now that you see like I don't know we watched life of crime together
Which was pretty good. It wasn't terrible, but I thought it was okay. I thought it worked
I enjoyed seeing most definitely that other guy play the younger versions of the characters
I like that. I thought that was cool and I thought that it was that was very early in our friendship
Yes, I would like to say folks out of sight
It's no Jackie Brown, but out of sight is like
It's one of the it's one of the better movies there is all right, and if you need to watch it
I'll watch it out of sight is phenomenal. It's the best clue. He's ever been. It's the best low pes obviously. I'll watch it
No, I saw it's also got a massive laugh of
Violent massive laugh along the lines of Pulp Fiction with Marvin. I saw
Jackie Brown on Christmas night when it opened I did too
West all I get once again pink stone myself a couple other friends my cousin
One of my cousins and we smoked a weed that was called silver pearl
Which now this was a time when you couldn't get weed in every dime store pharmacy on every corner
This was it was exceptional. You had a dealer and he was like this is called silver pearl
Well when I when I was coming up at you had two kinds of weed you a swag weed and kind bud
And if you found a guy that had kind bud that man he had something that was pure that wasn't treated with anything and then
That it and that we said a name right so we gave us this weed
We bought this we called silver pearl and we smoked it at my buddy's house and we got
Crazy high and then went to see Jackie Brown. What a drain and
I do remember moments in the theater
Standout moments in the viewing because it was a pack theater because it was before the movie house industry was completely failing
Right, and but I do remember one of the one of the standout moments in the theater at least like as far as audience reactions go was when
De Niro finally turns into De Niro because he's like this sort of burnout guy through the whole movie. Yeah, and then
There's that scene where they're getting Bridget fond of just grand slam. I clearly so much to Bridget fond of in that moment. Clearly Tarantino
was just like be really annoying. Yeah. And the way she's following him going Lewis. Yeah,
the West. And when he turns and he goes, just fucking, just fucking stop. Just I need you to stop.
I'm serious. I'd say another fucking word. I remember the audience getting so excited. Like,
yeah. Oh, he's about to go crazy to Nero. Yeah. And then of course, he shoots her two seconds later.
Right. But like Jackson shoots him. Jackson shoots him. I needed you to be beautiful. You used to be
Used to be beautiful. Fuck happened to you.
Used to be beautiful, man.
Yeah.
Heart breaking.
Pain, greed, or best.
Everybody's at their bed, rapper.
Forcer in his best.
Everybody's at their best in that film.
Forcer to me, and you're talking about a cast
of big time heavy hitters.
Forcer to me just kills me in that movie.
And I was that, I think that was the same year.
I guess he would have lost to Bert Reynolds.
That to me was the best supporting actor year of all time it was Bert Ryan olds and boogie nights
Mm -hmm. It was William H. Macy and Fargo. Wow, and I like look. I'm probably wrong with this
But it was a great year for supporting actors
But he does this thing throughout Tarantino does this thing throughout checking brown where
He has the character. He has the actors. Excuse me
Break into moments where it's an homage to their greatest character.
Yeah.
When you first meet Keaton, he's not Keaton.
And then later the Keaton comes out and it's great.
When you first meet the Nero, he's not the Nero.
Then the Nero comes out.
It's great.
When you first meet Pam Greer, she's not doing like the Foxy Brown thing.
Right.
And then there's that fucking tremendous scene where she's like, sit yo raggedy ass down.
And she starts doing like the whole fucking Foxy Brown thing.
Yeah, he just there are just such fantastic payoffs with the characters and then to me
Well, he lets everybody just like talk and hang out
Like easily 45 minutes that movie has nothing to do with the plot, which is what makes it so special to me. Yeah, but
Even though they didn't fuck that scene of forced or sitting at
Pangry is breakfast table with her hairs like down or whatever
that felt to me the most realistic of like sitting with somebody that you
fucked the night before. And she when she told he goes you know I bet aside from
an afro you look about exactly how you looked back in 1970 and she goes well
my ass is bigger and he goes nothing wrong with that yeah that's my favorite line
delivery maybe of all time and this was in an age when the big ass wasn't as
day regor as it is today. I'm sure I mispronounced. That's another huge laugh in the theater.
Yeah. Huge laugh wrong with that. Huge laugh in the theater when she goes, I don't have any,
oh she goes, oh my milk, when she's going to get bring coffee, she goes, my milk went bad,
while I was in jail and he goes, black spine. Yeah. Huge laugh in the theater. Huge laugh. Yeah,
Well, I saw it, you know, St. I'm from St. Louis ish, but the suburbs, so like if I wanted to see
an art movie or something that wasn't home alone, I had to go into the city. Right.
So my big theater was the West out of 16. Every year the day after Christmas, I would see five
movies for the price of none. Sneak in. It's kind of a big, dirty bastard. And one of those years was
of course, Jackie Brown. But to see Jackie Brown with a predominantly black audience, sure,
was an absolute dream in a way that once I moved to LA, especially when I was reviewing movies,
if I was seeing a saw movie, you go to the Magic Johnson. I mean, you just got to be honest
here. I mean, it's a more fun viewing experience. Frank, I saw saw for with a predominantly black
audience who man had and people were like, there was an energy in there that almost made
me like the movie because I didn't really like the movie that much. The song movies are
all terrible, but, but it was a great energy. Judd Nelson, yeah, a co -star of New
New Jack City. Yeah. Which I always thought Judd or breakfast club. I always thought Judd
Hirsch should have co -started New Jack City. We got a new Jack City way. We need to get
these cracks off the streets. These donuts are superior. Judd, Judd Nelson said when
New Jack City came out, he would go to like movie theaters and Compton to watch it and he said
it was like an unbelievable experience because it was so much, it was just so much more fun
and cool and whatever it 100 % is I mean a big comedy or a horror movie it just is right you know
I don't know what I'm saying the uh uh I know it does seem very strange to me that I saw Jackie
Brown in the very very very suburban world and uh that I grew up in in Pennsylvania when Christmas night
And it was still sold out and there were still like a very like there was a very strong reaction with it
That's very odd to me to think that that just wouldn't happen now, you know
I mean we live in a world now where it's like you know god damn you know the next Star Wars could come out on Christmas day
It's gonna be a quarter full. Yeah
You know what I mean like it's just not that's just not a thing that happens anymore
Well, and everybody was like it's not it's not pull fiction and whatever else
We've talked about Jacob Brown a bunch on this, but I remember seeing the clip on Letterman and Letterman was so
Pity about Jackie Brown, right, and they showed the clip that Letterman wanted to show not the studio clip and it was
Sam Lo Jackson going like don't focus my levels now
Yeah, and the car and he goes now you click this button. You're gonna hear a little yeah
It's great. No plot nothing and Letterman was like this moment. He's like, I love this so much. Yeah, it's great was the clip this show
Apparently on the set
They did a joke where they did a big dildo that they would take pictures of Billy if you fell asleep
And you know when you're on a break, they would take a picture of you with the dildo
But apparently through the whole production Tarantino kept saying like this is gonna be the funniest movie ever
I think he very much saw it's a comedy and I got to say when I watch it
I laugh a lot. It's very very funny. It really really makes me laugh and to me and
And you know, you can't fuck with Pulp Fiction.
It's an all -time classic.
That's my favorite Taranty.
I think it's probably barely mine.
It always would have been number one with a bullet.
Now it's getting a little more murky.
But Pulp Fiction's dialogue feels a lot more dialoggy.
And it's jokes feel a lot more joky than Jackie Brown.
Jackie Brown, and he never found it again after that.
just feels very natural and real and just fucking awesome.
It's a tremendous film and speaking of which, we're at 57 minutes we haven't.
And we've said this before. I don't know that we've ever gone this far
without talking about the subject. Never ever. So Pat, in closing,
did you like the Twin Peaks finale? I thought Twin Peaks
This fell apart for at least 10 episodes.
The final episode, I liked the final minute of the final episode with the quick flash of
her outside of the house.
I'll remember that forever.
I thought it was awesome.
Did I need the 50 minutes of them driving in silence that preceded it?
Fuck no, I didn't.
Okay.
But when I look back on the season at large, I go, you know, I liked less of it.
of it than I liked. Okay. Did that make sense? It does. I didn't like much of it, but when
I look back on it as a whole, I gotta admit, there's a lot of moments and images and sounds
and shit that will probably stay with me forever, and that's linched to it, see? Absolutely.
I thought it was a disaster, frankly, but I'm glad I watched all of it. I felt like I was
I was very glad to hung in there for the certain payoffs that came throughout the season,
the biggest of which of course was Cooper waking up and then him turning to Cameron
going, I am the FBI as the Twin Peaks music plays.
I was disappointed there was not more of a payoff with Audrey Horne's storyline.
Uh, uh, you know, there were, there were a lot of things that were left.
Well, I would argue that Audrey Horne and this new version was one of the worst television
characters of all time.
Well, but then she did the dance and then she woke up in that weird white room, and I thought,
oh, okay, something's going on here and they never explained it. And of course, Twin Peaks
were David Lynch in general. It's not the kind of thing where they're going to go.
Here's the meaning of the box where the alien appeared. I get that, but I would have liked a
little more closure. That all being said, and given the reviews and
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
the original series up through this.
Okay, there's probably a lot more going on
that I didn't tune into.
But I think Lynch sort of misstepped
because I think we mentioned this in the podcast
when he went to Showtime and said like,
look, I'm gonna shoot like 70 hours
and I'll just deliver a show.
Yeah, they should have kept him to the initial 10
or whatever it was.
Yeah, so, you know, he, I don't know. I mean, there were whole episodes. It was, it was building
up on my DVR and I didn't want to watch it. I never dreamed that could happen with Twin Peaks.
It was like, you know what? I don't care. I don't want to watch this, but there were great moments.
As far as the finale goes, yeah. I loved the reveal of Cooper is going to try to assure
or the murder never happened.
I thought that was so fucking cool.
I love that in the last episode,
they start showing clips from the first episode, right?
There were such cool moments.
I love the ending, which is basically like,
he thinks he saved her, but he hasn't.
And in the last moment, she realizes she is Lara Palmer,
and she is gonna be tortured,
and they are never gonna escape this hell.
The last moment is an A fucking plus.
Yeah, and all that stuff was awesome.
made it worthwhile.
Yeah, all that stuff was awesome.
So you're left with this sort of strange
perplexing question, which is should it have been shorter,
should it have been tighter, should it have been neither,
or because it was laborious in certain,
in many places, did that make the payoffs much more worthwhile?
And that's the answer is no.
Well, I'm confused there.
For me, but I think that Lynch was fucking with clearly,
he was like if you want to give me this money and you all want this show I'm going to make a
sit through some art shit and it's not always going to be entertaining I think there was clearly an
element of fucking with you and the ultimate proof of that to me was when Dale Cooper finally pops
out of his coma the first thing the character says is because everyone is like finally of course I
I mean, he knew what he was doing
and I don't think he needed to do it.
I don't know why he felt he needed to punish
the fans of Twin Peaks.
But in a way, he was punished.
I will say this, had Cooper come out
when I thought he was gonna come out,
I would have been like, oh cool, Cooper's awake.
When he came out, when he did, I was giddy.
I was giddy.
I was like, he's awake.
So I was like, okay, is that kind of the thing?
Where he's like, I think you would have had the same reveal
I mean, six episodes of this thing drop away.
Nothing changes.
Yeah, that's true.
That's fair.
I don't know.
All right.
There was an element of me being kind of pissed off
by the whole thing.
And yet, I watched it every week.
I had a great time, you know?
I've been watching Lynch interviews and they're just,
I know.
Well, I'm going to get that new criterion of like,
it's like a documentary about him.
But he's, he's an awesome guy.
But like him telling the story of like going to going with George Lucas to like yeah to interview to direct return to the Jedi
And he's like he's like I go to meet George Lucas
And he says I want you to direct the next star wars and at this point. I'm sweating and I'm feeling I'm gonna have a panic attack
He's like then he takes me to a restaurant. You know, you go to a restaurant. Sometimes in your order salad
All this place served was salad
And it's like literally just the whole story's like George Lucas is like offering him like a gazillion dollars
I would he's like calling his agent to be like you got to get me out of this
I can't do it like I would have there's no one with more integrity than David Lynch
I would I would have killed to see David Lynch's take a return to the Jedi if it was dune
Then I'm glad he didn't do it because of a boom. Doon is a monstrosity
Harlan Ellison claims and I love Harlan Ellison claims the movie is fantastic and claims
that everybody in the movie is impeccable except for Kyle McLaughlin.
Yeah, you know who he goes he did a fine job. He puts sting above cut that the audacity yeah
I love I love Harlan Ellison but come on. No, I mean, I don't apparently they're open to doing more of these Twin Peaks
But I mean are yeah, it just I feel like did you get the I got the feeling that
they were not saying this is over. I got the feeling that they were saying we're slowly building
to bringing these people back to Twin Peaks and we're probably going to do another season where
it's way more, we're back in Twin Peaks now. Because I certainly didn't tie up all the loose ends.
Almost none really. At all. What I heard was that out the gate showtime subscription rates went up
drastically, like before the premiere, but by the end almost nobody was watching Twin Peaks.
That's why, you know, hopefully you're thankful that for the large majority of this podcast,
we didn't talk to Twin Peaks, there's probably a lot of you didn't watch it, but apparently
it was one of their lowest rated shows by the end. Everybody was just like, I'm not watching
this. And I get that. I mean, it's certainly a lot to ask of your average person. And by the
And it was a lot to ask of your average Twin Peaks fan.
Well, that's what I would say.
And that's a person who's got a pretty open mind.
That's what I would say.
I would say in this day and age, I get it if you don't want
a cater to the sort of YouTube generation
or people that want instant gratification and instant pay
off within three minutes or whatever.
I get that if you don't want a cater to that.
But this went so, so far against that.
That it was like, yeah, it was like, dude,
This is even like tough as like somebody who was like excited about this.
I know.
But overall, I liked it.
I liked more than I disliked and I, again, I feel like if I had the patience, not even
the patience, just the time to sit down and rewatch all this again in a very comprehensive
session, I feel like I would feel very differently about it.
I feel like I would like it much more.
I just unfortunately don't have that kind of time.
So now God bless Lynch for doing that kind of thing for the people that have that time and at his age to be churning out this
Challenging of shit. Yeah, and impressive and there are Lynch fans out there that will take that kind of time with it. So
That's it
Beautiful an hour and seven minutes, buddy. This is a long one. Whoo. It was
folks
I'm at Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh
Joe, go.
I'm on a mainly Instagram, I'm only posting to Twitter
through Instagram right now, come follow me on Instagram.
If you could please, at Joe DeRosa Comedy.
And I will be coming to the Pittsburgh improv
the weekend of the October 21st to do shows.
So come on out if you're out there.
And we're hidden in near Halloween time.
I guess it was two years ago that you and I did that
Columbine Horror Film Festival.
two years. Two at least two years. The what? It was in Columbine. You and I. Oh, the mile high
fest. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You know, bring us to your fucking festivals. We'd love to tour. We'd
love to do whatever. Yes. Pat and I are available. What we would like to do is come in and we will
just do a live commentary to a movie. Yeah. That you guys want to see. We did Mania Cup 2 at the
mile high fest, we were not prior to that huge fans of maniac up to we we have been
since. But the festival asks us to do that once we did it. So we'll gladly do that
again at any festival and with the movie of your choosing. Bring us out. We'll see you
next week. We don't we don't have something picked out yet. But I know that if it's not
next week, I don't know when it comes out. But we'll definitely be doing the new Blade Runner.
Oh yeah, Joe and I are gonna go see that together and discuss it early reviews
I'll tell you this early reviews of Blade Runner and Justice League are through the roof. All right people are saying these are fucking match
Blade Runner, they're saying it is darker. It is like crazier
It's you know, I can't wait to see it and it's all because of
Villanue the guy who did prisoners which we discussed. Yes, and I'm always a fantasy and Ford come back into like one of his iconic roles
so all right we'll see you next time folks and we'll see you that was a hit
Thank you.