You are welcome to will see you and how the you
one more time. Sorry. Welcome to, you know what, you can keep that. Welcome to, we'll see you
in hell, your favorite podcast covering your favorite or not so favorite genre films in the
horror sci -fi action adventure spectrum. My name is Joe DeRosa. My name is Patrick Walsh. We let
you behind the curtain here at, uh, we'll see you in hell. You hear the flubs and all.
The mess ups, the jerkemarounds, and listen to that sweet rich sound of Mr. Walsh's voice. We have
fixed the audio issue. We are now able to bring you this quality from two separate coasts.
What, what will they think of next? It's crazy. Really just America is operating at, at its top,
at its peak, in only podcast recording, everything else, an absolute toilet.
But podcast recording is really hitting a new stride. I would agree with you, Walsh, and your state
currently just, it's on fire. It's on fire. Yeah. Somebody, uh, somebody sneezes next to a candle
in Berkeley. No, uh, I texted Joe yesterday. We, Joe and I like to kind of try to out dark each
other with our lives. Um, but I hadn't eaten at a restaurant and I went up to venture and saw a couple
friends and it was more lax that we were on the beach. So I, you know, you sat outside, but yesterday,
I was just like, I need to feel like a human again. I need to sit at a restaurant and have a meal.
So at lunch, I go up to this Italian restaurant in my neighborhood, sit way, way off to the side,
I'm outside, waiter comes up with the big storm trooper mask. Like immediately, you just feel like,
you know, he's got the big glass helmet mask. I'm not talking about the little, uh,
and it's, it's, it's almost offensive. It's almost like, like when you're about to have sex with
somebody and they go, you're, you're clean, right? Yeah. It's really just, if offensive or,
or if you're a lady, like imagine you were going to hook up with me and I draped a, uh, dental
dam across your neathers. You, you might take offense, right? Even though I'm just being safe.
I'm just, but so the guy comes up, uh, he lays out some bread for the table. And I was like,
oh, bread for the table. I remember that from the old, the old life, the before time.
Mm hmm. Uh, immediately the bread is swarmed by hundreds of flaws. I'm going to say hundreds of
flaws. They are all over me in my hair, uh, in my mask, I'm covered in flaws. He brings out my food.
And I, as he sets it down on the table, I see that it's, it's a plate of no key, but it's not going to
do the trick. And I go, can I get a second lunch order to go for my wife, who by the way is not home?
So he goes, yeah, sure. So he brings it to me. And I'm like, this is bad. I know I'm going to eat
the second lunch, the second I leave. I pay, I leave, I drive directly across the street to the park
and a lot of the e rustic, a bar in the neighborhood. I park and I eat that second lunch special.
Now in the car, at any point during this, did you realize you were inadvertently following a
script from Kevin can wait? I was actually, yes, reading a script and, and sort of acting it out.
Right. Uh, you were telling me about your king of queens, uh, rewatch and how he, he eats three
meals in one day or whatever. And I guess something stuck with me. And I was like, I'm going to do that
today. Uh, I, I have been rewatching king of queens and I texted you last night that the,
every food thing is played as a gag. None of it is, none of it is ever serious. None of it is ever
like, you know, your emotional eating is speaking to something greater. You should, it's never that.
It was the late 90s. It was all a goof. And I texted you the other day saying like some of these
food gags are, are down right upsetting. Like they're, they're depressing. Uh, and the one that I would
cite is in season two, there's a plot, uh, a storyline about, he falls in love with this Italian
restaurant. Uh, he, he, he's so excited to take carry there. He takes her, she gets into like a
thing with the waiter. And then she bans him from going to the restaurant and then they get in this
big fight. And he's like, you have to make such a big deal out of everything. Like who cares? And he's,
and she's like, you're banned. You can't go. And then of course, because he's fat and addicted to food,
he goes back without her. Uh, and he, he's sitting at the table. He's eating ziti. Yeah.
At a pace that is, it's disturbing. It's disturbing. To the point where Deacon, his best friend character
says, Hey, man, would you slow down? And, uh, and you're like, yes, slow down, dude. This is upsetting.
And then he goes, I got three days to catch up on. I haven't been here. And then he yells at a waiter
and he goes, whatever his Monday, whatever Monday special was, bring it, you know, classic
Kevin James, and it's just so sad. And then it cuts to him. And by the way, this is like probably
the fourth time in two seasons they've done this gag. It then hard cuts to him on the couch,
moaning and holding himself because he's so sick from food. Uh -huh. And you're just like,
this is upsetting me. Like this man has a hole in his life that he's
sure, desperately trying to film. And it's sad. It makes me sad sometimes.
They never really treated it seriously. And then all of a sudden in like season seven,
there's a very serious miscarriage storyline that you're coming to. So that's when, for me,
the King of Queens took a real wild turn. It's like a three episode arc where they have a miscarriage.
Oh, Jesus, don't give me that. Sorry, but it's coming up. That would be like doing that
on Seinfeld. It's the plot lines of this thing. You're so absurd. And the first season,
they're pretty grounded in like, this is what husbands and wives go through when they're newly married.
By season two, you know, uh, Jerry Steelers coming out of the basement, talking to how he wants to
launch like a slip -in -slide company downstairs. Like it's absurd. I mean, to me though, that's when
the show shines, as it gets weirder and weirder and weirder. Yeah. Yeah. Except for the
loop. The loop or ignore stuff I don't need. Uh, for igno's in and out by season three, he's already
in there like pretty. He he adds nothing to the show. I think he's a terrible addition. And like,
for them to think that that that would be a joke that keeps on giving that loop or ignore lives
next door is crazy. Yeah, it's kind of a weird. It's kind of a weird thing. By season three,
you're seeing quite a bit of that by the way, in the opening credits, you see that Kevin James is
now elevated to EP by season three. Of course. And you can see, you can see the influence of the talent.
Yeah. You know, like him just being like, I want to have loop or ignore on the show as a neighbor.
I want to do it. And then they just they're like, okay, he's a boss. We'll do it. I guess.
Um, I didn't mention that when I took my to go launch special. Oh, yeah.
In the bag, they had included a boxed up bread basket. There was a soup. Yeah. The boxed up bread
and then the pasta itself. And I also need the bread. I didn't get the bread. A container of flies too.
So you could bring home. Yeah, you open it up like one of those peanut cans that the snakes come out
of and I've just was swarmed by. Look, look across the street. And there's the waiter giving me a
wave. Yeah. It's just like when you go home, is it is like when you were here?
Actually, the waiter at this Italian restaurant was like Nordic. He had a thick,
like Viking accent. It was very strange. Anyway, I guess they take whatever employees they can get.
What was the second entree by the way that you ate in the car? It was uh, our party.
Penny, a ribbyata spicy pasta. The first time around, I had no key. Now, I will say this place only
gives you like six no key. I mean, it's probably a portion size, but it's like I was there to
work off some issues. You know, I've eaten at the place you're talking about. Yeah. And every time
I've been there, it's been with a couple other people and it's very actually, wait a minute,
Walsh. We've went there and had a drink one day. We're burying the lead. The place you're talking
about is the place is the place we met. The first night we ever hung out and we split the pork
on tray. No, that's uh, that's little doms. Oh, I thought you were talking about little doms.
No, La Pergoleta is like a, it's a giant two room place by the in the drawing room plaza.
Oh, that place. You and I have had a drink there. I miss, I miss, we had lunch there too.
Didn't we or no? I miss remembering. Yeah. They make delicious homemade pasta. It's a great place.
It's not their fault. It was covered in flies and the sky was made of
fat. I was picturing, I was misremembering the location of little doms. I was picturing it across
from you rustic. But I, Pergoleta is directly across from you rustic in the same plaza as the drawing room.
Yeah. Yeah. They got to just be dead. But I think drawing room, my, my theory is that
something's going on in there, even though they're closed. I drawing room people seem like they,
they still know how to make money in the pandemic. They're, they're running whores or something's going on.
I feel like you cracked the door to that drawing room. Yeah.
Oh, wait, you're talking, I'm getting my places all mixed up. Christ. Yeah. The drawing room,
I feel like you cracked the door to the drawing room. You're going to see about eight cops in there
drinking having a good time. Absolutely. I think you cracked the door to the scum on them.
Yeah. I feel like you cracked the door that you rustic. You're going to see, you know, John Ham,
a few choice people, maybe Niles from Frazier, just a couple people in there having a good time.
For sure. The, the he rustic since I was in their parking lot. I noticed somebody, maybe
sadder than I, it was one gentleman with two beers sitting on the outdoor patio at he rustic.
And they were bringing him out a dish of something that was not wings. And if you're not
getting wings at he rustic, I don't know what the hell you're getting. But he was dining there on a
weekday at 2 p .m. Have you seen our old Haunt, the roost, Vince Avril sent me pictures of the outdoor
parking lot tables? I've never seen anyone there. It's so sad. If I live there, buddy, we'd be there.
You got my, you got my word on that. But there's a point where if you're going to be drinking in a
parking lot, why not drink on somebody's porch or something and just you're not going to a bar.
It's not the vibe. It's there's something romantic about sitting in that
ruse parking lot and just get a shit face for the story. There's something. No, I would do it today.
So your, your air is not poison in New York right now? Compared to yours. No, compared to yours
with breathing, you know, sunshine, but it's, no, it's not, I mean, you know, it's New York air.
With New York air is always going to be New York air. But no, it's not, it's not like what you're
breathing. Yeah, that really added to the lunch. It was it's apocalyptic and the air tastes like
heavy. There's a grit to it. It's terrible for you. When you look at one of those maps,
like what a meteorologist puts it up, anytime they've shown the country in the last like month,
the entire West Coast is glowing red and and drawn like hell. Like there's flames coming off of it.
Sometimes on on a local news, they'll add the little devil dancing with the pitch fork
and the shaking, but are you serious? They will. No, I don't know. But they might as well. I mean,
it's, it's a, it's a living nightmare. And by the way, I almost forgot. Happy 9 -11.
I actually woke up realized it was September 11th and laughed because I was just like, yep,
you know, what they say, you forgive and you almost forget. Yeah. I completely blanked. I did the,
I did the thing you're not supposed to do. Holy shit, it's 9 -11. I watched Biden this morning. He walks
over to this giant group of reporters and he's like, hey, we're not going to be doing any talking
about anything today except September 11th. It's, it's all going to be about 9 -11. It's a very
solemn day and we'd like to keep it that way. And I'm like, but you're making a full public
announcement about it. You know, like that's also part of your stick. Do everything drives me nuts.
I have a friend who told me that their mother just sent them a video explaining how Joe Biden is
the actual devil. Well, that seems extreme. They were troubled by it themselves.
So that's one thing. So they really thought they really think he is. The parent really thinks that,
yeah, Biden is the actual debt, the actual biblical devil, which I hadn't heard yet, but I'm going to
look up some, yeah, look, I'm open -minded. I'll read everything. But no, that's pretty wild. And then
we were trashing Trump on without a country the other night. And then an hour later, laughing
hysterically at his tweets about Pelosi and Biden, like, because we're like, as much as you hate him.
Yeah, Joe Hyden is funny. Him saying, Pelosi, if you're getting out smarted by a salon owner,
how are you going to deal with North Korea? I mean, these are really funny tweets regardless of
my opinion on the man. No, he's been oddly getting funnier in a way as he nears that kind of end of
scarface period that he seems to be heading into. Yeah, I think he's got the election
sewn up. I mean, they're dumping mail in Los Angeles behind hair salons here. They have footage of
a big truck dumping a bunch of mail into a parking lot. I mean, he's got the plan. He's ahead of you.
He's, they've already figured it out. Russia is involved. You all know it. They know you know
everybody knows. And it's just going to happen. We don't really everybody knows the dice alluded.
Yeah, I mean, the democracy is at an end. And maybe it's time, you know.
Yeah, yeah, this is a wild rodeo these days. I love it. I tweet something negative about Trump.
You know, sometimes I do it. Now I do it like once every six months just to be like,
yeah, I still know that the world's in a bad place because I try to just make the occasional joke.
I don't think people want you to joke on Twitter anymore. But I wrote something about him. I
pretty light criticism. First, first comment I get, have fun working in the gulags.
Like that, that's really the discourse now is like, you say anything and it's
enjoy sucking the cock of Hitler's ghost. Right. Right. Now it's like, whoa, okay, that picked up quickly.
I mean, the, the, the, the, the most recent statement, or I don't even know if it's the most recent.
He's churning him out. I mean, you know, one, at least one a day. But the thing that he said about
when they wanted him to go to the graveyard of the soldiers and he's like, why would I go to that
place? A bunch of losers buried there. It's like, Jesus Christ, man. And it doesn't appear to have made
a dent, which is, which is great. Yeah. Have fun, Don. Like even the, the, the soldiers are like,
look, I mean, I was kind of a loser when I went to that war. It's like they're just like, yeah,
I mean, I could have maybe done something better with my life. Like they disagree with him.
Some, yeah, some of the other soldiers would he out? And I was in fact,
a loser. Yeah. Oh boy. What's interesting with him though is that he, he denies saying it.
And like, of course, I love our troops or whatever. But he's been on record many times.
He'd been like, well, Vietnam was a stupid war. You know, like I didn't approve of that war.
I shouldn't have had to go. That's the kind of thing when he's talking where I'm like,
well, that I do agree with. Well, here's the thing. I, my, a friend of mine pointed out
he's a draft Dodger and I said, I don't care that he's a draft Dodger. I have a problem with
the draft. I would be, I also respect the hell out of the troops. I know it's not for everybody. Yeah.
Um, but, but you'd think he'd find some sort of tactful discourse, but I guess it just doesn't matter
to say nothing matter. I didn't approve of this war. But God bless these troops or whatever,
either the phrase is. Sure. Uh, it's just odd, man. It's just, it's wild. It is scarfics. That
is a great analogy. He's got the tiger from the cage in his bedroom. Melania's hope for it.
Yeah. Cokes out the mountain of coke. He's ready to go to that balcony with that fucking grenade
launcher. Absolutely. Um, all right. Well, speaking of other dystopian news, I got a new psycho.
Actually, you brought it up yesterday. Uh, and we said we wanted to talk about it. I was familiar
with this, uh, but I'm glad you mentioned it because I didn't even think to talk about it until
you said that. Um, but there's a new, uh, Robocop TV show on the horizon. This thing also made me laugh
out loud. It's, it's a prequel. I read Pat's text to me. Uh, where is it here? Give me a second.
It's a prequel series to Robocop. Okay, here it is. Pat text me last night, 1008, my time.
Did you hear? They're going to do a Robocop prequel show dot, dot, dot, all caps where he is not a Robocop
yet. Like the interesting thing about Robocop, question mark, it's the Robo part, sweetie.
Yeah. It's, uh, he's just going to be a cop.
So I guess the end of the show then because he becomes a Robocop at the beginning of Robocop.
Very beginning. Like every Batman story, right? At the beginning, he becomes Batman. So
which is just good storytelling. So obviously in the prequel, we're just never going to see the
robotic part. It's insane. But here's, here's the, it's worse than you're describing.
It's centered not on the cop character. The series is focused on the old man that runs
oscorp or whatever the fuck that place was called OCP. Good Lord. That's what it's about.
It's about that guy. Yeah. Who gives a shit? Who would ever care about that?
To, uh, I guess, you know, they're like, well, we already rebooted it and nobody cared about that.
So they're making a sequel with Peter Weller.
Where for theatrical release, they're making, they're doing a new Robocop with Peter Weller coming
back. Oh boy. Which I'm fine with. Who was it? Oh, it was Joel Kiniman. Yeah, that's sucked.
But they thought that like, they thought that like, oh, well, because, you know, like Gotham was
you had the Joker and the Riddler and the Penguin and the scarecrow and Catwoman and a million other
amazing characters that have been IP out in the general world for fucking 70 years. Who the
fuck ever thought about Robocop pre Robocop? Nobody cares. When you watch the movie Robocop, you're like,
thank God, I'm not watching this movie kicking off before right now. Right. Thank God, I'm not watching
a generic police procedural procedural. I'm getting a sweet Robo action. Yeah. And I mean,
yeah, what are they going to have? Like a D age dad from that 70 show as like the young version
of that criminal. Who gives a shit? And he's like, we're at a time where they're not even supposed
to be doing anything about cops or anything positive about cops. So there'll definitely be all this
political shit in it, which you don't really want either. Like it's just, it's going to be a God
damn mess. I also announced a doogie cameo Loha MD. Yeah, I saw that. I guess a female Hawaiian doogie
house is where we're at. At that point, why are you even calling it doogie doogie?
Kamia Loha with some like, I don't. You're so removed from the IEP original IP at this point.
Yeah. Just call it something else about a kid doctor. Yeah. Why? Who do you think is going to go,
oh, doogie house. I wouldn't if you were rebooting actual doogie house or I wouldn't be excited.
And I loved that show when I was a kid. Who gives a shit? Same. And certainly the people who are
watching Disney Plus, which is where the show's going to be, have no idea what the fuck doogie has.
Yeah. I was told, yes, I had a zoom with Anna Perna yesterday, who's, you know, they're kind of like
a 24, a very cool movie TV studio. And they flat out said they were great, but they flat out said
at this time, you pretty much to sell something have to have IP meaning an existing book or an
existing source or the reboot rights to something. Anything else, you know, maybe post pandemic,
but they're only taking chances on the surest of bets. So it's like they need to have a book to
point to or something else, which just means there won't be any original ideas. So like doogie house
Yeah, that's a sure bet. Mike sent us a message. The episode of King of Queens was called
restaurant row. Okay, so 23 of season two, thank you, Mike. I mean, episode 23, you're, you're,
you're spent. Usually that like on broke girls, we'd, we'd be done with our 20 second and be like,
thank God, and they'd go, hey, yeah, to get us a little more syndication money, you guys might
work in another couple weeks and doing a couple more, and they always suck. Yeah, but maybe this
was good. It sounds funny. It is funny. It's just upsetting. Yeah. Okay.
The, and I mentioned to you in this Robocop exchange that this is so similar to me to this ratchet
series coming out. Nobody gives a rat's ass about the nurse and how she became the mean nurse.
No, you like one flu over the kukus nest because of the the Nicholson character. That's what makes
the play interesting. That's what makes the movie interesting. That's it. That's it. She's a good
villain, you know, the other issue is that, you know, Castle Rock, they took us behind Annie Wilks,
whatever they just did this, but Annie Wilks is a way more interesting character. Annie Wilks is
fascinating because she's the lead, the focus. I mean, and in kukus nest, that woman is there to
just represent, you know, bureaucracy, government bullshit. She's a villain. It's a fantastic
performance. It's a good character, but nobody wants to know how nurse ratchet became a bitch.
There are just people in the world who are bitches and assholes. And sometimes that's enough.
I agree. In fact, where are they now to do one flu or the kukus nest to TV show with a female,
you know, I forget Nick. What's the Nicholson character? Like Randall P. McMurphy with a female
McMurphy. Yeah. All right. I'm listening. I'd watch that. Yeah. That would be interesting. I don't
give a shit about nurse ratchet. And you pointed out. Tiffany Haddish as a as Randy P. McMurphy. Yeah.
Haddish in there. Maybe you get a, you know, Eliza's what's your face for broad city.
Glazer. Glazer. Glazer. Glazer. Excuse me. Yeah. She could play the, like, the
Davido character. Sure. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. I had watched it be like girl and erupted. I'd
watch that. But you pointed out when they first announced the show two years ago, they had billboards
up for this fucking thing in LA. And that's how long it's taken to get off the ground. That clearly,
it was when the word ratchet was like a hot word on Instagram. Absolutely. And they were like,
oh, let's do a show about this. Yeah. Now you never hear ratchet. It's already feels dated. But
when I, when I started on cool kids, which at this point is two plus years ago,
they had the writing offices across from us. And they had been there for some time. So I did 22
episodes of a show that's come gone, been canceled, moved on with my life. And ratchet has
still not seen the light of day. So clearly it went through major problems. This is a 10 episode
series. But here it comes. And it's Sarah Paulson. I've never met anyone who loves Sarah Paulson. No
one. She's fine. She's fine. Everything. She's in, it's disgusting to me. It's gross. I'm sorry,
people. But for all of the open -hearted, open -minded, we need to help each other. Bullshit that
comes out of Hollywood. I swear to Christ, if I see Sarah Paulson or Oscar Isaac or Idris Elba and
one more fucking thing. Guys, spread the wealth kind of, kind of every fucking thing. It's like
Jesus Christ almighty, guys. Like, I get it. You have one shot. You're very lucky to get that shot.
It's over -saturation. I won't name further names, but we're kicking around, you know,
talent and stuff for this movie that I'm trying to get made with producers and directors now. And
we're, you know, talent that we'd like to reach out to and stuff. And there are a few names on it
where I said, guys, this person is great. He's in too much shit. I don't, yeah, I don't, it's going to
take away from any mystique the movie could have. Possibly. He's in everything. It's too much.
Guys, take a fucking breath. My God almighty man. And this was Emo Phillips, right?
It was Emo Phillips. Now, Judy Tanuda, I did, I did push for. But what was the commercial I saw
the other day now with, or was you and I texting once again where I said the middle class of this
industry is, is, oh, it was the thing with now, you got Ryan Reynolds,
hocking this third rate fucking mint wireless. Yeah, like Ryan Reynolds needs to represent
mint wireless. The guy is in eight movies a year. They're all theatrical blockbusters. He's got his
pick and choose anything he wants to do. And he's, and he's representing mint wireless. And then
into the commercial walks fucking Rick Moranis who turned down ghost busters after life.
It was a real heartbreak, a real heartbreak when he walked into frame. And it's just like, dude,
and you know, they overpaid Moranis for the goof of that. Moranis got a million dollars for them.
Easily because he's, he's turned down way more money. But they were probably like, they offered,
I bet they came back to him five different times. And finally, he was like, look, I'd do it for
a million dollars one day of work. And they probably said, yep. Yeah. And like, I literally get to walk out
and be like, this is stupid, which is what he does. And they go, okay. And it's just like, oh my god,
man. Like, it's just insane to me. It's so gluttonous. And these, these a lot of the time,
I'm not speaking to Ryan Reynolds politics or Idris Elbas. I don't know them. But I mean,
I certainly can speak to Sarah Paulson's and didn't Oscar Isaac show up in one or two of those
black and white apology videos. Or am I mispeak? I think you're thinking of rammy malloc, but Isaac
might have been in there. But maybe Isaac isn't. I'm just saying, like, you know, the general tone at
every award show now is, you know, capitalism has run a muck and we need to think of the less fortunate.
And it's like, guys, you're taking up all of the fucking on camera real estate. Like, Jesus Christ
almighty. Does every three line part now need to go to like William Hurt? Or you know what I mean?
Can any new actor get something? Every, you know, car commercial narration is John Hamm or,
you know, somebody who doesn't need it, who you don't even really know, it's their voice.
It just goes on and on. I got to scary stuff for us.
Yes. And on the, on the next slide, we're going to discuss all the new trailers that dropped your
dune, your, et cetera, because I just watched them all last night. Making it, maybe I may not ever
see the lot of day. All right. I'm going to make a note. New psycho new trailers. Yeah.
This is a great scary stuff, actually. There's a little game that has been ported over to the Nintendo
Switch. It's called Little Nightmares. It's on sale as of the recording of this podcast. I
believe for $8, which is a steal. You can get it on the other platforms to other systems.
I like it on the Switch because you can play the Switch in bed. And it's a great game to play in
bed because it's a very dark and strange sort of horror fantasy game. Very Tim Burton -esque.
Good Tim Burton. Of course, I'm talking about the dark shadows Tim Burton.
Now, but very classic Tim Burton -esque. It's got all the action of big eyes.
Yeah. Very strange, spooky, legitimately creepy, and scary at times.
I don't know that fun is the right word, but it's a super, super indulgent and enjoyable experience.
So I implore you, if you enjoy a spooky horror game that is atmospheric and not action -based,
this isn't like the Resident Evil later installments. This is way more along the lines of sort of
slowly stepping through a haunted house. It's just a lot of, I just really liked it a lot.
So I'm playing it now. I look forward to one of those things I look forward to going to bed
for a while to get to play through a few more levels of it. And that's it. That's your scary stuff.
I would also recommend, while we're on the topic, in a different vein, Resident Evil revelations,
if you haven't played that. I also got part one and part two of that for my Switch. They were eight
bucks each. I don't know if they're still on sale, but that's a little... Those are still atmospheric
and scary, but you're getting a little more into, obviously, some action territory, shooting
of zombies, that sort of thing. But both games, a lot of fun. I prefer one to two. One takes place on
an old boat that has a very old haunted mansion quality kind of like Resident Evil one. The original
did. But they're fun. And the monsters are gross and disgusting. And it's a great time. So check out those
games. All right. Do they have them for PS4? Yeah. They're all out for every platform that's
current right now. In fact, they're probably even cheaper. I bet you they're dirt cheap on PS4 right
now. Every whatever video game platform you have, if you want to... If it's kind of something that's
been sitting there collecting dust and you've been meaning to, hey, let me try to jump in at some point
and stock up some games and get going. Now is a great time to do it. Since the pandemic started,
they've run crazy sales left and right on every platform in their digital stores. I spent $20,
$21, the other night on my switch. And I got, I think, six full games that are all very quality.
So you can really clean up right now. And then Halloween's coming up. Everybody always does a big
Halloween sale. That's a great time to stock up on your horror games. PS PlayStation does a really
good one. So check it out folks. All right. Let me take you down to Pat's movie corner. I'd like to
start this week with a new documentary on Netflix. I think it's probably about a year old, but it seems
new to Netflix called Tread. I recommended this to Joe. It's a documentary about a man who
for the first half hour, you're just rooting for this guy. He is being persecuted by the people
of his town. They keep changing zoning regulations and it all seems like they're just trying to
fuck with him. He thinks he pissed this guy off when he bit on some property at a local auction.
And this guy came over and gotten his face, but it's all like small town politics and zoning laws
and stuff. And it's kind of dull at first, but he's getting matter and matter that these guys keep
persecuting him. And about the half hour mark, you start to think maybe these guys aren't persecuting
him and he's insane and just thinks that everyone hates him, which is a bit of a disorder I have.
I always think everyone hates me whether they do or not, but you see where it just starts going
wrong for him. And at some point he decides to start fashioning a bulldozer slash killing machine.
He orders online a $50 ,000 giant bulldozer and he spends over a year in his little garage
turning it into a tank. And he just keeps saying, I keep waiting for God to give me a sign not to kill
everyone with this bulldozer and it doesn't come. Then he brings it into it. When he starts getting
it too big to work on, he realizes it exactly fits into the door of his business. So like he was like
there was an inch on either side. I was able to bring it inside and continue working on it. And he
takes all this as signs from God that he is supposed to destroy his town and all the people in it
with this bulldozer and killing machine. If that sounds like something that you might want to watch,
check it out because it was pretty damn fun.
The town's right up my alley. Yeah, the end is just footage of this man driving a bulldozer through
town and destroying buildings of people he feels wronged him. And you don't really know if these people
did fuck with him or not in the end, which makes it all the more disturbing.
All right, I'll stick to the documentary theme for today. I'll start with high score since I was
just talking about video games. High score is the new docu series on Netflix about video games
and about the evolution of video games. It starts basically with the dawn of space invaders
and carries all the way up through modern day gaming. It was a lot of fun. I think it's six episodes.
Each one is like 40 minutes or something. They get into some stuff that hasn't been covered in every
single other typical movie or video game documentary. But there was just some really, really
interesting fun stuff in there. I actually discovered some games I'd never heard of that I wanted to
explore. The most interesting part to me was seeing how diverse the video game business was
in the 80s. I guess still is, but I mean this was much more focused on the 80s than modern day stuff.
But it was inspiring to see because I think when we think back to that time period we think it was
literally just all men being pigs all the time and awful and whatever. And there were a lot of really
strong women. You know what, that sounds even that's derogatory. There were a lot of women that were
in the business that did really great things in the business and left major marks. The inventor of the
first role -playing game that actually had graphics and wasn't just text was a woman. The person
who oversaw the launch of Nintendo power which was huge was a woman. The inventor of the first
video game console that took cartridges at home that was eventually kind of smothered by Atari
was a black guy. It was interesting hearing these stories for the first time. Not that the
docuseries is focused on that. It's not like a diversity driven series or anything. It's just a series
that captures what happened and when it happened and how it happened. And I really, really, really
enjoyed it. And my favorite thing that I saw the whole thing though was they interview at length.
There's an episode about the Nintendo and Sega Genesis Wars in the late 80s, early 90s. And they
screaming them in America. And watching him go through his five -step plan was so enjoyable because
one of the things literally in the marketing plan was make fun of Nintendo. And that was what ended up
sinking the ball into the net for them was that they came out and really was like, we're basically like,
oh, you have a little Nintendo, you little pussy, like, you know, come play with the big boy,
Sega Genesis. It's violent. Yeah. It was just funny to watch, man. It was funny. But I like
the show quite a bit. If you're a video game, you know, I would say even if you're not into that
video game, you'd probably just like the docuseries. It was done by Netflix very well done.
Six half hours, six hours? Six, under six hours. I think they're like 40 to 50 minutes each or
something. It's a good one to put on when you're like, cooking and shit, you know, you know,
like, you don't have to sit there with your eyes glued to it except for the subtitles.
Joe, have you seen the film pop star? Never stop, never stop. Yeah, it's great. My lord,
it's funny. So I saw it in theaters. I was the only person in the theater. And I just thought,
boy, that's a pretty funny movie, you know, but, you know, especially for the state of comedy,
I was like, that's pretty fun. Then, you know, it's reputation keeps growing much like McGroober.
People keep discovering it and loving it. Popstar is actually way funnier than McGroober. I mean,
McGroober has some huge highlights. Don't get me wrong, but pop star from start to finish is just
amazing jokes beautifully done. One of my least favorite trends in comedy is the celebrity cameo.
And this movie is the only one where it actually makes sense, you know, it's kind of making fun of
that celebrity culture. So they got these celebrities who are hilarious in it. I mean, they really
give them all really funny stuff to do. People you don't think are going to be funny or funny.
The song parodies are hilarious. I want to fuck you like the USA fuck bin Laden. I mean, that song
had me out. There's just an abundance of great jokes. The extra feature shows you that there's,
you know, much like Ankerman, a whole other movie they could have done that's pretty much just as funny.
So those guys are great. I love them. They're song parodies. You always want to hate them and then
you laugh your ass off. One of the things they've ever done is Sacks Man with Jack Black on their first
album in Credit Bad. If you haven't heard Sacks Man, please check it out. I don't want to spoil the
joke for you. But you know, I'm not, I don't even love Andy Sandberg. I can't watch Brooklyn 9 .9,
et cetera, et cetera. Something about this movie and the stuff that they do as their little comedy unit,
just really fucking kills. I love pop star. If you haven't seen it, check it out. If you saw it once,
check it out again. It's a good way to get your smile back. And the right way to do it. Yes.
I watched a doc called Greetings from Tromaville. It is a soup tenets account of the birth of the
trauma films up through the modern day company and what they do now, which is basically make films.
What a great documentary. It's just a lot of fun to watch. Everybody involved is so passionate
about being part of the cause of making movies that they want to make independently on the budgets
that they're able to make them on. Story after story of like, when we shot this one, it was 17 of us
sleeping on a church basement floor with no air conditioning in August. It was growing. It was
horrible, but we got it done. And the fans loved it. It's just very inspiring that
there is a will. When there's a will, there's a way not to be cliche. My buddy, Zach Amico was in there.
It was fun seeing him as one of the later Tromaville family members. It's just an inspiring tale
about a guy. And what's his name that runs Troma? Blanket on his name. The little guy.
I've been sitting here trying to think about him, too, because he annoys the hell out of me.
Hold on. Christ. He was on the joe Bob. He was, you know, he's a maniac.
He's a nutty. He's kind of a nutty guy. But what's interesting, Lloyd Kaufman. Lloyd Kaufman. He's like
Harvard grader. This whole time, I thought he was just like some wacky guy that like, you know,
that, you know, that didn't, you know, that just kind of stumbled into some shit and kind of
did what he wanted to do, whatever. Right. He's like actually a very brilliant guy and kind of
knows how to ham it up for camera. And then like when they actually get him talking, and he does
give legitimate interview commentary throughout the entire thing. But when they really get him
like down to earth and talking, it's like staunch vegetarian. He's politically sound. He's a
progressive guy. Like it's just like, oh, that's, that's pretty cool that he's of sound mind and body.
And not sort of the cuck that you kind of assume he is because of a sense of humor or whatever.
But I find him charming and funny, even though at times a little much. But he, it's just a great,
it's a great thing. It made me add a bunch of trauma movies to my, to my wish list on Amazon.
I got to pick pick up some because I, I like trauma. And I always admired trauma. I never had
much of an interest in the movies because of the comedic aspect. But going back and seeing footage from
the original toxic Avenger from the original class of Newcomhuy,
Tromeo and Juliet, things like that. I was like, oh, I get it. Like the Gore effects and practical effects
and these are great. The stories are outlandish. This is a fun, exploitative watch. And similarly,
to the way like the, the best of John Waters would be. So that's good stuff. And I recommend watching
the doc, whether you're a fan of Tromer or not, just to see what you can do when you put your head
down to it. I think I have only seen Troma's war, which was done on Joe Bob show and was absolutely
terrible. That's the one they had him on. But yeah, not a big fan of that one either. It's
suck. But I've actually never even seen toxic Avenger. So it's a blind spot for me. But I always just
felt like it wasn't going to be my cup of tea. But maybe I'm wrong. All those companies, you know,
it's like they have the things you can enjoy. And then they have the things that are a little too much
for me. Yeah. So full moon's another one, you know, uh, full moon made some terrible shit. But full moon
also made puppet master and you know, like they, they have things that are that I think, and again,
like John Waters, I think you're better off the further back you go. Because a lot of it has to
do with that gritty, grainy, yeah, early 80s, you know, uh, indie cinema, grind house, whatever you
want to call it, vibe. When that goes away and things start to look glossy and shiny and have CG effects
or whatever, those kinds of movies don't hold up as well, obviously. Yeah.
My third is disobedience came out a couple years ago. This movie was very much on my radar because
it stars Rachel Vise and Rachel McAdams to great actresses to beautiful ladies. And all I knew about
this movie was that it had a sex scene where Rachel Vise spits repeatedly into Rachel McAdams' mouth.
Is this a diploma? No. That one was a compulsion or something like that. But I know I had that
somewhere on my shelf. I just haven't watched it. It wasn't great. But uh, no, disobedience is a movie,
basically it was the subject matter was too similar to On Orthodox, which is a Netflix show that I
raved about on my little solo movie corner. But On Orthodox is an amazing exploration of a girl who
is sort of reaching adulthood and it's very conflicted about living an Orthodox life.
I thought it was one of the best things I watched last year. I really loved it. And this could not
help but pale in comparison. Basically it is a lesbian love story about this. These girls who were
falling in love with each other. The elders of the Orthodox community found out essentially black
listed or almost excommunicated the Rachel Vise character. She left the Orthodox community. Now she
has come back because her father has died and immediately this kind of hot lesbian action gets
rekindled. So it was nowhere near as fun as that sounds like it's going to be. There's a few scenes of
this were like I never thought I'd see Rachel McCatum's in the nude. You know, there's a couple scenes
of this where they have her like stepping out of the shower and like badly lit and she's towering
her left breast or whatever and you see a quick glimpse. These are beautiful women. I just want to say
what happened to sex in movies? Sexuality, nudity, what happened? I'm sitting here watching it when
they eventually start to fuck. I mean, it is the most PG sex scene ever. The reason that everyone
was talking about the spitting in the mouth is because it's like, oh, I actually haven't seen that in
a mainstream movie. That's kind of crazy. But it's surrounded in the most chased love scene with no
nudity and just these two women kind of kissing and then there's just that one act that goes a little
too far or a little farther than you normally see. There's no reason to pick on this movie for not
being sexy enough. I'm just saying as an overall question, isn't it a little sad that we can have a
movie about Orthodox Jews hooking up in secret for a lesbian sexual relationship and you can't even get
half a chub anymore. Isn't it a little sad? Yeah. Like why is sex bad now? At any time on this show,
I'm like, oh yeah, that actress is beautiful or that sex scene was hot or whatever. I always feel like
a purve now. It's sex used to be a part of movies and now it just isn't. It's like saying, why can't
I get, you know, a good book at Walmart. This is what it is. This is what Hollywood has become. It is
an international production plan at this point. It's got to keep the brand safe and they're just not.
Which is why it's so shocking and impressive when a movie like, for instance, Dr. Sleep comes out
and you get this disturbing scene where a cult murders a child, you know, it's like
area seen in recent years. Yeah. And you're like, this isn't something I enjoy watching, but at the same
time, I'm impressed that this made it into a theatrical Hollywood studio release. But I mean,
it's all Walmart at this point. It's like, it is what it is. It can only, it has to remain so
significantly benign or they can't make their money or they might get letters or whatever, you know.
Yeah. I mean, emails, tweets, whatever you get now. For me, I'm just kind of watching this like, okay,
these are two very big, very popular actresses. I guess they didn't want to do nudity. But then
McCatams is also willing to be nude in other scenes of the movies that aren't sexual. And it's like,
well, why? I just, it makes no sense. But that sounds like studio stepping in and watering.
Yeah. There's a, there's a Rod Sirling TV film. I'm blanking on the name of it. Again, it's
something I have on my shelf that I've got to watch. But he talked about that in an interview in the,
I guess it was in the late 60s when he did the interview. And he said, you know, this was supposed
to be about racial injustice involving a black man in Mississippi. And by the time it hit television,
it was about a Hispanic man that lived in Connecticut or so. He was like, they, they
removed it so far from the original source concept because they were like, it's too disturbing,
it's too close to home, it's too real. And they just kept taking it away, taking away,
taking away until finally, it was about, you know, and I just said Hispanic because I just as an example,
it might even be about like a white guy of some kind in Connecticut, you know. But like,
the point is is, that's, you know, that's, that's what they do. Unfortunately, um,
it's just, you know, pop, pop star is three, four, five years old at this point. But like,
what, they're all sitting in the car like outside of the concert and then they're, they're being mob
by fans. And this woman comes up and shows them her giant breasts. She's like, would you sign my
chest? Whatever. And he's like, oh boy, you know, and it's this, it's, it's kind of funny scene.
Then for about a full minute, at least in the unrated version, somebody puts their dick up on
the glass. Yeah, I remember that. That's very fun. They ever tries to roll it up. Then finally,
the guy hands him a pen. He's like awkwardly signing the guy's dick. It's actually putting pen to
dick. And it's like, we can still do nudity. Uh, if you want to make it an equal opportunity,
thing, great. But all they've really done is add dicks to comedies and subtracted all other nudity.
So I don't know. I don't, I don't understand it. I'm not that upset about it. I mean, there's a,
I think what people think now is we have porn. So who needs to see it? But I need to see it.
I need to say needy. And by the way, show me triple the cock. I don't care. But bring, bring back a
boob or two. My final film is a little documentary called Dennis Rodman, Big Bang in Pying.
What? Is it about it? It's North Korea trip. Oh, yeah. What channel? Uh, we watched it on Amazon Prime.
Uh, this thing is just souped and nuts. That shit.
Now here's the thing. Uh, at the top of this doc, Rodman is doing an interview about why he is going
to North Korea to put on this exhibition game with American basketball players, retired NBA players,
versus North Korean basketball, professional basketball players.
And his statement is sound. He says, why am I doing it? Sorry that I want to try to make things a little
bit better and improve relations. And you go, yeah, right on, man, that is a pretty good reason.
Then he starts crying uncontrollably. And you realize this whole thing is in the hands of a potential
mad man. Uh, from there, he assembles the team. They go overseas. What he fails to tell the rest of the
team is that this isn't just an exhibition game. It's an exhibition game being presented to Ken Jong -un
for his birthday. Little different. Uh, American press, of course, gets wind of this. Uh -huh. Uh,
they now are questioning guys, why would you give this guy a birthday present? They're going,
we're not here for the politics. We're just here to play a game, which is what they have to say
because they didn't know that this was happening. And now they're on North Korean soil, where North Korea
during the time of this documentary currently has an American hostage. Okay. They're clearly like,
I just want to play the game and go home. Yeah. If I say the wrong thing, I'm going to be in a cell.
So we're just here. Um, the icing on this glorious cake is that Rodman from the second they put
foot set foot in North Korea is drinking non -stop. What's his poison? Vodka. Okay. Mixer? Nope. Okay. So
they'll be like, it'll be like, you know, the narrator will be like, it's 10 o 'clock in the morning.
The players have arrived for the exhibition practice. And Dennis is already drinking. Uh -huh.
He's just getting barreled at one point. He screams at a reporter that he invited to come there to
cover the story. Yeah. Uh, about what what what what his right was to be there as part of this trip.
Uh, he is, uh, my friend, Jay Okerson pointed out to me, Rodman is bowing constantly to everybody.
It's not a bowing culture, uh, which I'm glad he pointed out. I never would have picked up on that.
I just would have been like, I guess they bow there. Right. This thing is a fucking wild ride, man.
I highly recommend it to anybody. Well, if you'll remember when we went to the Bruce Willis,
Comedy Central roast, Rodman will out crazyed everyone in the house. And it was a crazy
dayus. It was a crazy dayus. He cried during that thing too, but cried about his love for Bruce Willis.
Yeah. Uh, and that was that was when you argued with my favorite thing you've ever said was halfway
through his dead silent roast presentation, uh, at the table that we were sitting at. You just hear
Pat very quietly go. All right. That's wrap it up. Yeah. I got a nice laugh. I recall, uh,
yeah, including from some Comedy Central execs that were at the table. That was a scene, man.
And he did this by the way, as you said, out crazyed, this was the night where at the end when Bruce
Willis got on stage. Yeah. Uh, said, if you remember, he was reading prompter so poorly
I think I turned to you and I said, Bruce Willis, I know how to read because it was I've never seen
anything like it. Yeah. It made no sense. He was reciting. They had written a speech for him where he
was reciting lines from his movies. Yeah. And it made no sense. He was like, yeah, come out to the
roast. Well, have a good time. Would you be surprised at all of his wills didn't know how to read?
Would it would it surprise you in any way? At this point, no. At this point, no. There was a time
when it would have. Yeah. Uh, anyway, I feel like we're at least an hour in. We are. So let's get
to the picture. The picture is host. Um, I, I don't understand how movies are titled anymore. Like
if you name a movie host, let alone a horror movie, there's got to be 10 horror movies called host.
There's an Asian one called the host about the monster. Yeah. Um, like there's no reason for this
movie to be called host. It doesn't make any sense. It's a minor quibble, but like it's like when a band
calls themselves like the letter A and you're like, okay, so no one will ever be able to Google you.
You fuck your career right out of the gate. I don't get people anyway. I don't know why it came in
so negative because host is a lot of fun. I keep calling it zoomed by accident. Yeah. Well,
zoom is a better name. Yeah. Uh, so yeah, there's the movie centers around a zoom meeting, uh, where
the five members or so are doing a, uh, sayons. And it's an hour long. It runs literally the
exact duration of his actual zoom meeting front to back. Uh, I'm sure there are edits, but it is
presented in a way where there are no edits. It's all done in real time. Um, and, uh, I hate found footage
as I have made very clear on the show repeatedly. And I loved this movie. I think it was arguably the best
or one of the best found footage films I've ever seen. Um, yeah, it's, it's a low bar. I mean, there
haven't been a lot of great found footage stuff. I thought, I thought Chronicle was kind of cool.
I liked Blair Witch at the time. But, um, the big, the big selling point of host is that it's under an
hour. You're absolutely right. The, the, the problem with found footage is that it's always a shaky camera.
It's always kind of wonky storytelling because you're only able to see what they see, you know? So
an hour is just the perfect running time for something like this. Good on them for doing that.
Awesome. The shutter picked it up. This guy Rob Savage just signed a three -picture deal with
Bloomhouse because I'm sure they recognized, okay, here's another guy we can have do, you know,
half -million dollar movies for us that make a hundred million dollars. But, um, it makes a great
double feature with one cut from the dead, which we talked about a couple weeks back because they
are movies that when you watch them, you're like, fuck, I'm wasting my life, basically. You know,
like I watched this and I was like, I could, I could put this together with friends, you know,
shoot a horror, but I won't. You know, um, I always admire people who do this kind of thing. It seems
like a young man's game, you know? I might have done this kind of thing when I was 25. But, um, it's an
admirable movie. It's actually very suspenseful. There are good jump scares in it that work.
The shaky cam thing is never that big of an issue. It doesn't make you sick or it didn't make me sick.
Well, yeah, because it's all being shot. They're doing it from their computer. So it's not like
you're running around with, you know, um, when they're banging the girl's face on her desk, you know,
that's just a great scare. There were some effects that wound up looking better than some of your big
action movies that must have been done for five bucks. You know, this thing didn't have any sort of
budget. Yeah, I was so apparently the way the director did this was he had everybody shoot their
thing independently and then he cut it all together. Okay, I have no idea how he was able to do that
because it cuts together perfectly. Yeah, and then there are the director is the director male female
what's his name? Do we drop savage? Okay, so then also too, there are effects in this thing where I'm
like, I don't even understand how he just did that. No clue. Um, so it's impressive. Uh, it stars new
comers, uh, hailey bishop, redena, drandova, saline, backster, and jema more, jema more plays my hats off
tour. One of the most unlikeable characters I've ever seen in a horror movie, which is perfect. Yeah.
Because you need one of those and she nails it. She was probably the standout for me because
she's so convincingly played this person that was so shitty and selfish. And uh, I really loved her
in this. I thought everybody was great, but she really was my, my, my fave. Alan Emre's is also in it.
He also plays quite an unlikeable dildo, but a little more indirectly, I guess you could say.
Yeah. Um, hailey bishop is sort of the lead, I guess. Uh, and she's, everybody's great. Nobody's,
nobody's bad at it. Um, their bridge, which I was not expecting. Um, except hailey, hailey's
American. Oh, okay. I assume they, the audition for this as opposed to just having his friends
set it up. I mean, I think part of the reason I was so impressed by it is that I thought it was
literally some kind of, you know, things some guy did at his house. You know, like I thought I was
going to look even worse than Blair Witch and, and feature non actors and so forth. But um,
it seems that shutter gave him a little money to do it and trusted them and, and, um, while I can't say
I loved the movie. It sounds like you liked it a little more than I did. I certainly admired it.
It's definitely worth watching. And I think, uh, it should inspire you, especially if this last
another year or something, if you, if you've been wanting to do something creative, you know,
you can do it pretty cheap. I'm on her, I'm on hailey bishops Twitter right now. She's got some
behind the scenes footage of how they did the stunts. Okay. Because she's the one that gets thrown
around like drug across the floor and stuff. So she was actually in a harness. And there was a guy
there. They're doing it all safely. But uh, there's a guy there with a rope and stuff. So I guess they
just managed to have her harnessed up and paint the harness out in the, that's crazy. I mean it's,
it's pretty pretty fucking incredible, man. Yeah. Um, you know, so this is, uh, this was a really,
really impressive piece of work. And again, Likens back to the, uh, Harkens back rather to the stuff I
was saying about trauma where, you know, what I loved about that documentary was showing, look man,
anything's possible if you really want to do it. Right. But you got to really want to do it.
I mean, that's the thing. They didn't do this with any, as far as I know, with any deal in place with
shutter or anything. It wasn't like, hey, if we do this, they're going to pay us this money and bubble,
what they just did it. And then I got, it got acquired by shutter. And then now this guy's got a
three -picture deal under his belt, you know, and I'm sure these actors will all go on to do more things
too. They've all been in other things, but it's very impressive, very impressive. It was very
cool little movie. Um, I wish shutter would have more than one of these things a month that I was
like really excited about. I was kind of complaining to Joe last night about shutter's latest offerings,
but they always have at least one thing to get excited about. They're getting better. They're adding
a lot more stuff more frequently. Yeah. The original stuff will get better and better, but they've
really been adding some bangers in the, in like, the old school department. I'm excited to see
fade to black, which I've heard is a very good underrated movie. I've never seen it. A lot of fun. Yeah.
A lot of fun. And then also, too, the other thing I loved about this movie is,
this is one of the scariest demons I've seen in a long time. Like this, the monster in this got me
a few times. And it's one of those things with, they did such a quick flash of it that, you know,
if you, if you stayed on it for five seconds instead of four, you'd be like, oh my god, that's
so stupid looking, but they, they, he really knows like how many frames to stay on something. And
he's a, obviously a guy with a big future. Yeah. Hopefully he doesn't, you know, get a big budget
and then loses his creativity, like so many do, but we'll see. Yeah. So two hogs up for host.
Go watch it. So now we're your time. Two hogs up for host. I'm the Patrick Wall should Instagram
and Twitter. I'm on the letter box as well. If you want a real time, look at what I am watching.
I also do the Pat Solo movie corner. Check those out if you haven't. We are doing four episodes a
month now. You can join us on the Patreon at the two episode a month tier or the four episode a
month tier. We thank those of you, no matter what, you know, spot you're coming in at. We really
appreciate you making this Patreon journey with us. It is what's keeping us doing the show. So thank
you so much. Joe plugs. Uh, Joderosa comedy on Instagram on Twitter. The accounts are activated again.
Joderosa comedian on Facebook. It is active again. I am not handling it. Our dear friend Emily
Simpson is handling it for me. And she has been given stern instructions by me to not
supply me with the passwords. So that's what it is for now. But look, you know, I'm not going to be
doing much chatting or anything on there. But if you're following me, you'll see updates for this show
and my other projects I'm working on. Uh, as I've said before in the past, there should be an announcement
coming very soon from Salvolcano and Christopher Stefano and myself about something new and fun,
including a show that Sal and I will be doing a podcast. I will be still doing obviously without a
country on the gas digital network or in Fisher and myself trying to find some middle ground sanity
in the polarizing news. Come check us out. If you want a free 14 day trial for gas and all their
content, you use promo code WAC. That helps us out helps you out. And that is it for now, I think.
promo code WAP to see my only fans. Um, that's a wet ass pussy. Joe, Joe, you familiar with,
oh, I'm sorry, WAC, not P. Sorry. Can I say P? I said WAP. Oh, okay. Sorry. No, it was, it was a joke.
Uh, it didn't work. I like to end with a with a dud. But, um, thank you all. And I'm also to
remind you to download the apps off our Patreon, not just stream if you want to have them for good and
not worry about any sort of glitch taking them away. But as of right now, all episodes should be
available to you if you're a Patreon user. Thank you so much. We will see you next time where we
are talking the Bill and Ted trilogy. And we'll see you in hell.