Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Reward subject to expiry, gambling problem called 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go learn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app
Hey everyone and welcome to the We'll See You In Hell podcast now a part of the
Fangoria podcast network for more information about the network including
other programs how to follow the show and find past episodes of We'll See You
In Hell please visit Fangoria .com now on with the Joe how'd that feel do you like
that felt great that's my first time doing it yeah they say you never forget
your first time. I've already forgotten it, but you like being in the driver's seat though.
I do. I think I have kind of an announcer voice. Not good enough to announce like tonight's
show or something, but maybe like a local car sale. You know, October, Honda days or something.
Yeah, I think I could do that pretty well. I always pictured you being the voice they play at like
festivals before the shows where they'll be like, please remember, no flash photography.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, they'll have that stock recording and then like one bad joke at the end. I could see you doing something like that
Yeah, yeah, you know, think bigger is my point. All right
Look, no little voice over work. Have you seen MTV's popzilla?
Haven't so very short -lived it was like TMZ, but animated. It's very funny. It was on MTV
I only I was a big fan of Blink Kong
What that is it's I'm joking. It's just another shitty monster
I was the pop -zilla announcer and I played a lot of voices, Sean Penn, a bunch of other
people.
Nothing on Blink Kong?
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Blink.
King Kong, Blink Kong.
That doesn't sound like an MTV thing.
Oh, pop -zilla.
Yeah.
Didn't even make the connection.
Or to Pop Carson, as you would refer to him for our last discussion.
Call back to last week.
Look.
It's our Christmas holiday, Hanukkah episode here, Patty.
and Kwanza and Kwanza sorry well you know I read recently I looked at the dates
of Kwanza recently it's it's I think it's way farther away from Christmas in
Hanukkah than I thought it was. It was maybe I looked at the wrong thing but it was
far enough away because I never knew when it was yeah so I looked it up and I was
like it's so far away like I don't I guess because it's the same concept but I
was like it's almost like not even in the same time frame or whatever I feel like
I think it was way closer to Thanksgiving or
on the 2016, well, you're right as always, Joe, Monday, December 26th.
Oh, really?
All right.
Well, and how was Sunday, January 1st?
So basically the exact same holidays that we all have.
Wow.
Well, all right.
Glad I looked that up so I could really dunk on you with that one.
Apologies.
Well, it wasn't really a dunk.
That was like having somebody come in and dunk the ball for you, and then you being like faced
It was kind of a dunk
Sorry, you looked it up on a computer
My point is since this is our Christmas episode and we spent so much time last week
tangenting
If you will
Maybe we just get right into the movie this week unless there's something else you want to talk about first
If you want to do any
Yeah, I'm ready. What do you want for Christmas this year though, Joe? Maybe we'll do that real quick. Well, I asked for some some cool stuff
What's your number one? I don't need the whole list. I'd actually Santa Claus
You know, I thought you were because folks you can't see Pat these days
But really shagging it out. Yeah hairs growing long beards getting bushy. I've gone completely white
And for some reason he's wearing red pants and black boots everywhere
Which I don't get what's your number one because I'm looking at my number one right now because I can't remember what the box it is actually called you know
This is gonna sound corny for somebody
This miserable day in and day out. I have pretty much everything I want. I don't I don't know what to say
When people ask what I want I'm I'm doing for an electric guitar
My I'm with stolen years ago and I missed it so much that I just never bought another I've had a variety of acoustics
And now I got a really nice one.
I want an electric guitar between you and me.
I'll tell you a post Christmas.
I think that's what my girlfriend got me.
I didn't even tell her that's what I want.
But I smell it in the air.
I think she knows that's what I want.
My two topics that I asked my mommy for both of these.
All right.
The actress is three collectors edition as we've discussed
many times because we're friendly going
to see that director's cut.
And the Herschel Gordon Lewis, the feast is the name
of the box set.
Oh, excuse me, the Herschel Gordon Lewis Feast is named, it is the 17 -disc limited -edition
box set of every Herschel Gordon Lewis film I believe.
He did what like basket case?
He did, uh, well, he did Blood Diner, which was his big one. He's sort of the guy that broke.
He kind of, he kind of was the first across the frontier into Extreme Gore in the 60s.
Okay. So a lot of really crazy bloody gory shit. I think in Blood Diner,
He ripped the woman gets her tongue ripped out of her mouth, okay, and they do the effect with like a cow's tongue
Sure, but you know he's one of these guys
Extreme whatever band and 16 states, you know those kind of exploitation horror movies
You can't find a better title than blood diner
Yeah, they remade it recently, but then the remake look to I don't know it didn't look right to me anyway
So I'm that's that's really the big one
it's a 17 disc box set and as you can see from my unopened Werner Hortzog and John Casavetti's
and Honeymooners and midnight special box sets over there, I get them and then I just let them sit
there. I do the same fucking thing and I think it's just not having enough time but I have that same
Werner Herzog box set also unopened and I've seen only like two of his movies. I want to see so
many more and I haven't done it. There's something about opening a box set and not digging into it.
Yeah. Because what would I'll do sometimes I'll open it and I'll get through one disc or two
discs. Yeah. And then it's just open. There's something about keeping it new until you have a week to
really. Yeah. With the thought that you're going to do the whole thing at once. I just got I talked
about it last week. This Oliver Stone book by Matt Zoller Sites. So a fantastic writer, New York Times
in various other places. He did an amazing Wes Anderson book and I went through Wes Anderson's movies
reading it. I read each chapter and then watch the movie or vice versa. It was fantastic.
I talked about his interviews, you know, interviews as influences. They showed you side -by -side
comparisons of the movies that interviewed him and you know what Anderson did with those influences.
It was amazing. Now he released one with Oliver Stone. It's a bigger, even more in -depth book with
all these insane interviews.
I opened it to one page, Oliver Stone's talking about
like getting ripped with Woody Harrelson and Juliet Lewis.
It gets stone and shooting natural born killers.
So I have an Oliver Stone box that I've had for years.
I've seen him maybe only half his movies.
I'm gonna go through it, read each article,
over Christmas break, I can't wait to do it.
And I recommend that book highly.
I have that same box set, I went through about half of it.
Yeah, gets a little, it wears on you after a while.
He's he's a very overpowering filmmaker. Yeah, and the movies just get longer and longer they do. I'll tell you though my favorite
I've seen probably most of that box that even though I didn't watch all of it when I you know
I've seen some of the movies that I haven't watched it since I purchased it or whatever but I
Think my favorite and people go people scoff at this. I think my favorite Oliver Stone movie is talk radio
I love it. It's his most simple film. I could see you in that play playing that lead role
I swear to you, Patti, it's a dream role in mine.
I always wanted to play that, and I always felt that.
I'll direct you up at the Burbank Playhouse.
I always felt that I had it.
After David Arquette's Sherlock Holmes waves up.
Yeah.
Well, when I do Tinder in the dating websites,
I put a begozy in type.
I'll get the Patti's in moist.
That's my one sentence thing.
Two least favorite words of every woman in a man.
So anyway, let's get to the film.
Yeah, but I had I had one other thing
What are we talking we're talking. Oh, I know Woody Harrelson. Sorry. I wanted to clear up
I it's funny that I sometimes want to clear up something from a previous podcast because really most of what we do is give
Wrong information but in particular I panicked last week when I left I've managed to meet Woody Harrelson
Like three or four times the show I write for he I guess he knows all the access somehow and I talked a few weeks ago about how
I was at this Halloween party and he was there with this and I said I said kind of coldly middle -aged Asian woman
Or age -appropriate Asian woman and he was you know drinking out of the ball of vodka and grinding on this woman
And you were like, why are you blowing up a spot? I didn't say why I just said blowing up a spot
Right, so then I left and I was like fuck cuz I was like well
He's a single man then I thought shit
What if he's married and he was there cheating on his wife?
It's just got a long -term girlfriend
right and I don't think what he else is listening to the podcast obviously but
things get to people so I kind of panic and I looked it up sure enough he's
been married to this woman since the cheers days and it made me love them all
the more he's just a monogamous happy man grinding with his wife of like 35 years
at a Halloween party I love it I love what he else and he steals the movie I
talked about last week the edge of 17 which I'm gonna recommend again because I
loved it so much he's great in that movie I like him when he plays just a real
person when he's when they waste him in a hunger games as they did with Philip
Simmer, Phil Simmer Hoffman, his last role I think is the third hunger games movie.
No, his last was miserable to me. His last role. Oh, wait, his, well, his last
starring role was that one where he's like the Russian. Yeah, that was an
interesting movie. It was depressing. He was great. I couldn't handle it. It was
too much for me. It wasn't great, but he was really great in it. As he always,
Did you ever see God's pocket with him in John Turro interesting movie?
I liked it. I loved it and you I never heard a thing about it. Yeah
And that was right towards the same with the owning Mahoney and love Liza and all those he did
Yeah, the one where the gambling one. I think that's owning Mahoney. That's a rough fucking movie. I don't think love lies
Is any no love lies? It's not funny either and he's smoother of a sale, but
All right. The movie we're talking about this week is Silent Night, Deadly Night. This
was my first time viewing it, Joe Yours. This was my first time viewing it as well. It
was one of those movies. I was on the road and I saw the double feature DVD of it with
both parts one and two. And it just hit me. I was like, why have I never seen this movie?
Yeah, and then I was sitting in the store and I started looking it up on wikipedia and reading all this really interesting stuff about the film and
Then I went on Amazon and bought it instead of supporting the store because it was like $9 cheaper brand new on Amazon
It was used in the store for like $20. See so and I hate that I do that too
You know, I'll be at a mebos or use record store and look something up and I'm like I could save $20 getting on Amazon
But it eats at you I'll say this when you and I are all pissed that I'm he was closing and maybe we contribute
It's been a ton of fuck. I did some intel. They're not closing. All right
They said they'll be there for at least another like six years and then probably longer
All right, it's fine. Here's the thing too though. I feel a little bad if I do it on a real mom and pop yeah
I give a meba plenty of my money and I don't feel bad when I do it in there also because I mean I've seen grocery stores
there's less crowded than a Meeb erectors.
That's true, that's true.
You go in there to 11 a .m., the place is fucking packed.
And they're overpriced, too.
I love them, but they're a little overpriced.
They are.
Anyway, and for you shit, Franklin.
Yeah, but then some of the stuff is they're just giving it to you.
It doesn't make any damn sense.
I've made some finds there where I bring it up,
and I'm like, surely they're gonna say,
you switched a price tag or something.
That's me, too.
They'll look at it kind of skeptically, like what?
But it works out.
Are I'm like the record will be scratched and you get home and it sounds amazing. So
Let's get to the synopsis. Yeah of Silent Night Deadly night. I'm just gonna read this straight up the DVD box
Actually, this is the first thing on the if you flip the DVD over. This is the first thing it says
It's not the synopsis. It says
Community leaders tried to suppress them the PTA fought to ban them now one of the most controversial slasher films of all time and
It's sicko sequel
are back. Why not sickle? I don't know. Both of these gore -hound holiday favorites have been
restored from the original Vault Materials, chock full of gratuitous nudity and grizzly violence
then stuffed with jolly extras for the absolute ultimate in season's bleeding. Nice. I think the
crypt keeper wrote this. Crypt keeper. Silent Night Deadly Night is the heartwarming story
of Little Billy who was traumatized by his parents.
Christmas Eve, rape and murder.
His parents, I think they probably could have specified that the mom got raped, not
both of them.
Yeah, the dad didn't just just got murdered, not that it's any less horrific, but that
sounds like they both were.
He is then brutalized by sadistic orphanage nuns, but when a grown -up Billy is forced to dress
is Jolly St. Nick. He goes on a ULTI'd rampage to punish the naughty in quotes. Santa Claus is
coming to town dot dot dot. And this time he's got an axe. Robert Brian Wilson and Lena Quigley
starring this jaw -dropping horror hit that a nation of angry mothers still can't stop. That's true.
And I consider myself an expert now on the backstory of the controversy surrounding
sound at Dylan.
I'd like to go into that after we discuss the movie a bit.
The movie itself, you know, it's just like what they said, you're watching this thing.
There's a very unsettling scene where, which I didn't even really get why they needed it,
but they take, a young couple takes their son
to visit their grandpa, who's like an Alzheimer's patient
in the hospital, and he's sitting like catatonic,
then the parents leave the room for unexplained reasons.
I guess they both need to go to the bathroom together.
Right.
And the grandpa turns to him and he's like,
Santa's gonna kill ya.
Basically.
And it's a terrifying scene, but also beyond ludicrous.
That the whole set up, you're like, nothing about,
But all it took was a slight tweak to make this a realistic scene, but it was ludicrously
handled.
Now, here's the thing.
Here's the thing, too.
They, before the grandpa starts speaking, they go out of their way to establish several
times over.
This man hasn't talked in 15 years or something like that.
So then we start talking to the kid.
Of course, as soon as the parents go back, come back into the room, the guy goes kind of
tonic again.
Right. So you don't know, is this in the kids head?
Yes. Is this their way of saying this kid's always been a little off?
Right. But the point is, is the grandfather tells him Santa Claus is going to murder him
for some reason. Yeah. So, and then they're in the car and the kid goes,
grandpa told me Santa Claus is going to murder me. And instead of the parents going,
that's crazy. And that's not true. And whatever. They go, but grandpa doesn't talk.
And the mom just goes, well, he's got no reason to lie. And the dad goes, okay.
Yeah, so this so there over it father who's been
Catatonic for 15 years the dad doesn't even give a shit that a Christmas miracle has literally happened
Maybe like let's turn this car around you know, we got dad talking. Yeah, let's go talk to him
So this movie currently holds a 31 % on rotten tomatoes way better than that. I agree
It's a 39 % audience score which is also not right it seems like something I should have seen at the new Beverly
I know that's an L .A. reference, but it's got a real grindhouse sleazy feel to it that I love like what we're talking about as
Strikes against it are are not somehow lights out last week had huge problems and logic and we were ranting and complaining about them
The problems with this one are just sort of part of its charm, you know, like it's just like let's get to the killings
You don't really care about this shit. The kid is honestly a great little actor. He was adorable and
and there's a Santa, a man posing a Santa,
he robs a convenient store, shoots the guy.
Then he's pretending to be broken down
on the middle of the street.
He attacks them both.
He lays the mother down, rips her blouse open,
and rapes her on the side of the road,
which was like insane to me.
Yeah, disturbing, the kids watching it all,
he goes into this nunnery where they're forcing in nudity.
By the way, by the way, don't leave this out.
The kid watches from the side of the road as the baby is just in the back seat
Yeah, and they never come back to that. They never talk about the baby now. I know in the sequel
Yeah, well no isn't the baby in at the end of this one or did I dream that? No, I thought the baby's like kind of grown up at
The end of this one. I mean unless that kid at the very end is supposed no, no
I thought that was supposed to be the baby no and the sequel
Let's not we'll get to this we'll get to the sequel
but the point is is there's a baby in the back seat and they never even bothered to say,
hey, what the hell happened to this baby out? So you don't know if the guy killed the baby too.
It's an upsetting scene. It is. So then the kid gets shuffled off to this orphanage where
nuns are fucking in it for some reason. Yeah, it's a very strict nunnery and then the kid
starts hearing some moaning and I'm like, well, this has got to be something really thought
was it can't be people having sex in a nunnery right and he opens the door and
sure enough it's like real gratuitous fucking going on already I'm on board I'm
comfortable with this movie I'm loving it I'll tell you and you know this might
be TMI but I like I believe our listeners want the truth that scene aroused me
so much I had to go masturbate to nun porn afterwards I had to google nun porn the
there was so much great nudity and it particularly the girl that he's
banging on his pool table.
And then she gets hung from deer antlers on the wall.
Well, that was, and that was like, off the charts.
She looked like a Barbie.
And that was an odd scene which comes later in the film.
Let's, before we get to that.
All right.
So what happens now is the kid grows up
into being, they cut, it just jumps like 18 years later.
He's like a scrapping young man.
For some reason, still living in the orphanage.
Yeah.
And for some reason, like, Hunky.
Real Hunky.
Like why not, I guess, you know, it wasn't a great actor.
Why not make him kind of a Anthony Perkins type?
That's what I was wondering myself.
And I'll tell you this, I guess because you had to believe
that he was strong, yeah, which we will also get to.
But the thing for me was this was the twist in the film
where I was like, because I didn't read
the back of the box.
I just bought the damn movie, right.
I thought for sure the psychosana at the beginning
was gonna be the psychosana.
I was like, man, they're really getting into this thing.
Yeah.
This kid's gonna have to get to the cops
and convince them that Santa's killing people.
They don't want to hear it.
They don't believe them.
Yeah.
You know, but no.
And I honestly thought it was actually gonna be Santa.
But when I started the movie, I thought that Santa
was actually homicidal this year or something.
Really?
Yeah.
That would have been great.
Like not even a crampus, just a crazy Santa.
Right.
That's what I was expecting.
I think that's what that Goldberg,
the wrestler Santa Claus movie is.
Okay.
I won't see that, but fun.
But anyway, so the kid now gets a job at a they've established by the way at this point that anytime the word Christmas
Even comes up. It's a trigger. Yeah, it's a trigger. He starts having flashbacks. He starts screaming naughty or nice. Yeah
He starts working on a Walgreens where the the boss is the guy from every single sitcom
That it's pretty be looking dude. Yeah, it's it's it's it's Anthony Michael Hall's dad from weird science. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and he's
Just he's the boss of the store guzzling alcohol
Kind of making passes at his staff
It's really uncomfortable and though that whole scene was so weird and so not based on any kind of reality that I of course loved it
It was an insane scene and
Then one of the guys like we're gonna the stock room brings the cute girl that our hero likes as well
You skipped something here. He's working in the he's working in the
the store and it's all going swimmingly until talk of the big Christmas party comes up.
Yes.
And the boss says, I'm going to need you to do me a favor.
The all -shocks kid is like, anything for you, Mr. Wilson, whatever the fuck is needed.
I need you to be sent.
He needs him to dress up as Santa.
Now the kid is in the skin of the holiday that makes him have fucking like Vietnam flashbacks
essentially.
So now they're having the party.
They're all getting wasted 10 feet away from the party where the co -workers, by which
Which I mean, three people are sitting in like downing shots of bourbon at 5 p .m. on
Christmas Eve.
And it's Christmas Eve, which I love.
Nobody's got a family to get to.
They're all just like, let's get blasted.
Let's stay at this Walgreens and drink together, then 10 feet away from his three co -workers.
This guy tries to rape the cute girl who works like in the in the stock room or the co -worker.
who are hero likes, lays her down in the back room and he's gonna rape her and then our hero comes
back and just starts going a town and the killing begins because he sees the raping happened or the
attempt at raping happened. He's insane. The girl. Yeah. Now, this is where the flash is back. They
do a flash as her blouse gets open and her tits fall out. They do it. This is how tasteless this
movie is. They do a flash to his mom's blouse being ripped open and her tits fall out. Yeah. Now,
Now, this is where the movie starts to get not just disturbing, but a little confusing.
Because here's what happens.
The woman he's in love with secretly is about to be raped by this asshole guy that he
works with.
The guy comes in in the Santa Claus suit, sees it, it triggers him, he starts screaming naughty.
He takes, I believe, some Christmas lights, throws them around the guy's neck, hangs him.
This is where the strapping young lad stuff comes in.
The guy has like super hero strength through the whole movie
Just like literally just police system style hangs the guy with Christmas lights
Then the woman goes
That was not crazy get the fuck away from me to hint the guy who just saved her
She's like what the fuck's the matter with you? She turns on a dime. Yeah, there's literally no like hey
Thanks for that, but what the fuck it's just you're fucking great
So any murders are wrong with you. He saved you from being right. That's what's wrong with that any murders are immediately
He murdered why this is where I'm going which but she wasn't doing anything wrong. What is she getting murdered, right?
I just assume because the nudity brought back
That is what I thought then he goes to murders the boss the drunk boss and the other co -worker
I don't know what the hell they did nothing
He's saying punish I you know what looking back. That's probably why they had him chugging so much alcohol
Is that he was punishing him for being a drunk probably okay?
But what about the old lady, but this isn't like seven where these people had legitimate crimes drinking a little bourbon on
Christmas Eve is no crime. They really it was folks. I'd be in jail
They really do play it up though the second the store locks the guy is repeatedly going let's get drunk
Yeah, so that I didn't occur to me at the time
But probably they were trying to set him up as a guy who needs to be punished as well
And there is there was a little handsy with this co -worker. I was there is and there is there is some sort of hinting that maybe the older woman that works there and
He have some kind of they might fuck now
Let me ask you this because here's where I thought it was going when he's like we're not hiring anybody
I don't that the old guys like I don't want to hire anybody
We don't need anybody at the store and the nuns like maybe you should meet him first and he comes in and it's this hunky kid
And then the guys like oh
Oh, we, I guess we could always use a little help.
Was he supposed to be a perv?
No, no, I think it was, no.
That scene felt very sexualized to me.
I didn't get that at all.
What I got from it was he was saying like,
because he goes, it's a job for a man, not a boy.
And then she's like, well, look at him.
Despite his age, he can do the job.
And he was just like, and then later they talk about the boss
being kind of like a cheap skater or something.
Right, right.
I think that was supposed to be like,
his dollar signs going off.
Like, oh, I can pay a man -sized boy shit money
to do all this crazy work for me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which, by the way, again, it's like a Walgreens.
What the fuck are they doing?
They're grit, by the way,
they're almost gratuitously showing Star Wars toys
in the background of every scene in this thing
is the job of the Hut play set from 1983.
And I'm sitting there going, how the fuck did Lucas okay?
The Star Wars products to be in these in this film probably didn't yeah
I guess maybe it was before you weren't you just couldn't do that or whatever
Yeah, I mean you could sample music for free. It was a different time. So anyway, he then leaves and he leaves the store
I wanted to go be the linear about it. I don't think but he goes on a killing rampage from that goes on a killing
Here's where I'd like to be linear. Yeah, because he goes and he starts on this killing rampage
He attacks the couple that you said
are that are fucking on a pool table.
Now the crazy part about that is it's a babysitter,
fucking her boyfriend or the pool table
of the house where she's babysitting.
The kids right there.
The kids there, it's like 11 p .m. on Christmas Eve.
Where the fuck are this kids parents at?
Whose parents are out at 11 .30 on a Christmas Eve?
Very valid.
And then also how to think of it but very valid question.
How does he find them?
It's not like he gets tipped off in some way
or hears moaning.
He just walks into a house and happens to find two people fucking. Yeah, and they didn't it's not like they bullied him
When he had no ties to them at all he just walks into a house and kills people who are fucking as he walks into their house
Yeah, yeah, but I will say the best scene in the movie is
The kid sledding the little kid the little the little girl finds him and
She says she thinks he's really Santa, and he's of course looks
He's horrific, he's got like blood in his beard and shit and he's all dirty and she's like,
are you saying?
And he's like, yes.
And she and he goes, nodding or nice.
And she goes, I've been nice.
Yeah.
And he's got a knife and he goes, well, I brought you a special present and he has a knife.
And you think, this is horrible, he's going to kill a little girl.
Then he hands her the knife as her present like the blood -stained knife.
I thought that was a fucking brilliant, it was very intense and then he goes and kids
are sledding.
I don't know what their crime was.
Well, he beheads the kid that steals the sleds.
This guy's really looking out, finding assholes just out and about doing shitty stuff on Christmas Eve.
Not even that shitty, though.
Like, Dexter was killing people who did terrible crimes.
Really, this movie is Dexter Santa Claus.
Yeah, but if Dexter killed people for like, you know, stealing like a pack of chewing gum or something like that.
Yeah, I went to Six Flags yesterday, I had a blast, and there's a water park next to it, and my buddy Ian that I went with was like,
telling me about this story about how at this water park a little kid got so
tangled and mangled in the slide on the way down that he was decapitated. Oh
God. And I was like, can you imagine being down in the pool like waiting for
your kid and his head rolls out? Jesus Christ sure enough in this movie he
cuts them off and the friends are all waiting for him for the sled to come down and
down rolls his head and it was disturbing but of course it looked very fake. Now
Now did your version have the added footage?
I taped it and you can tape it too off of showtime.
I think it's on all month.
Actually, I had recorded it months and months ago,
so maybe it's not still on.
OK, so that's probably I'm assuming the edited version.
The version I have is the uncut.
And there's actually a card that comes up
before the movie starts that says, please excuse the quality
of some of the footage in the film.
Okay, but it was the best we could do to put the film back into its original state
Okay, and whatever so there's there's a lot
You know every every so often it would go to that sort of grainy VHS looking yeah film and you go, okay
This was just added back in a lot of extra Gore okay like knife when he kills the girl
He's in love with like they show the knife dragging up like her chest. Yeah that decapitation scene had a lot more
had a lot more gore in it. So I would recommend if you're gonna you're a fan of
this sort of thing you should you should watch the uncut. I mean by today's
standards it's not that crazy but all right well then take us to the ending and I'm
gonna go into the backstory of the film. Well the ending is he finally makes his
way well this is why I wanted to go through it linearly. You're a good hour
in 10 into this movie, going, man, they really just streamline this fucking thing.
There's no protagonist, there's nobody trying to save the day, the cops haven't been
nothing.
Then finally, somebody goes to the cops in the last 15 minutes.
Now they got to find them.
They say he's on the way to the orphanage, I forget how they figure that out.
The inevitable happens, which you know is going to happen.
And there's a Santa Claus at the orphanage.
The cops show up.
They're yelling freeze.
The guy's in stopping.
He's just moving slowly towards the kids.
The cops saying stopper will shoot.
Right.
They shoot the guy and kill him.
I love the reveal after that where the nun goes.
That was father, backster.
He's deaf.
They didn't hear them.
You know, it's just very, very convenient right now, of course.
And then finally, Billy makes it to the orphanage.
He meets his maker at the hands of the abusive none, I believe, kills him, who's supposed
to be a bad guy, but then actually does redeem him through death or something.
So it's a very odd, odd ending, and then the last thing is, as you see, like another little
kid going, naughty or nice, and you realize, oh, now that kid's been affected.
And this will happen again.
And I thought because it was a younger kid
that it must be the baby grown up now.
But I think the age difference is probably too great
for that to be the case.
Yes.
In the second film, would you have not seen?
I have not seen, but I have read the synopsis.
And here's the synopsis of part two.
And I do need to watch this.
In Silent Night Deadly Night Part Two,
Billy's younger brother, Ricky,
follows the family tradition of Christmas carnage.
Psychosana is back to deck the halls with chunks of bodies.
That's good.
That is good and I
What are the controversies about the movie was the poster?
Yeah, this poster really I'm getting to that. Okay. What do you do? I want to talk about the poster for the second one
so Charles E. Celier Jr. Directed this movie and
the man is
brought on to do this movie and
Was so uncomfortable directing the rape scenes the sex scenes and the gores scenes the entire movie?
I don't know if he didn't read the script or not or what, but he was like
Passing out like so uncomfortable with having to do these movies that the editor had to step up and direct any scene with gore
Right or rape so the director the editor essentially directed the movie. Okay, then this guy Charles E. Celier
Was riddled with guilt because America not just the PTA but critics and everybody else turn it on the movie in a huge way
The movie comes out and they're advertising it in prime time with Santa Claus running around with an axe killing people and kids are
Of course, shit in their pants because now this thing that they're told is gonna come down their chimney. They're now scared of so
Charles he's cellular. Let me close out his story and then get back to that the controversy
He is so traumatized, but whatever he's saying about his movie and that maybe he fucked these kids up
He only does religious movies for the next like 30 years
he goes strictly like born again.
Any of note?
No, well he invents Grizzly Adams.
He created that character and did that.
Okay.
Yeah, I was looking at his director's list
and like nothing is highlighted to Link on Wikipedia.
Yeah, they're all these like straight to video,
like beyond straight to video.
Yeah.
And he was, he did like George W. Bush,
Faith in the White House, a documentary in 2004.
Okay.
Like the evidence for heaven, you know.
He fully went into this shit
But was always riddled with guilt about it and then not I think 2011
I'm not saying it's related to his guilt from this movie
But who knows why people do things the man killed himself. Yeah, boy
How he has this fruitful career where he's like, you know doing all this religious stuff then he kills himself
How do you kill himself? It's not that cause is not listed
But just a terrible story hung himself with Christmas lights. Maybe that would be quite poetic
It really kind of bummed me out but the movie
The poster of it is Santa coming out of a chimney with an axe or going down the chimney
I believe or yeah going down the chimney with an axe.
And so I get swept up and reading about the controversy about this thing.
People are furious they try to ban it.
And it's first week it comes out the same weekend as Nightmare on Elm Street and it made more
money than Nightmare on Elm Street and it's first weekend and it was pulled from theaters
right after.
Yeah.
People really flipped about this poster.
Which is crazy.
I mean, you cut to now.
Right.
All right.
I remember as you can see now at a PG movie are disturbing.
I remember when in glorious bastards came out, they had posters for the characters.
And the Christopher Waltz character, I think that it said the Jew finder.
Like on the poster.
Yeah, that seems right.
And I was like, I get that he's the bad guy and like they're not saying that's cool but I'm
like, Jesus Christ, you could just put that on a poster, I guess, yeah, you can.
can.
Speaking of posters, I like the poster.
I actually kind of prefer, they're both really cool.
I think I prefer a little bit, the sound in the Deadly Night 2 poster, which I have here
for you to see if you haven't seen it yet, but it's a red Christmas ball and in the Christmas
This ball reflection is the hand of a Santa Claus with a gun, which is very, that's
great.
And it says, prayers won't save you in the silent part of this night.
What the hell does that mean?
That means absolutely nothing.
And the silent part of this night is some of the worst riding I've ever heard in my life.
And they didn't put the, it's all in italics.
Just this should have been an italic.
Yeah.
This night.
I went back and watched because I read about it on Wikipedia, the Cisco and Ebert review which you can watch online of
Silent Night, Deadly Night. Good. It is so awesome. So Cisco, and these guys were all about all about not censoring things, free speech, et cetera.
Cisco talks about the movie and then he goes, so yeah, that's that's the premise of the movie.
Anyway, I just wanted to say a few things right now and the whole tone's like different than any other Cisco neighbor.
He goes, this movie was put out by try star pictures.
Shame on you.
He looks at the camera and goes shame on you.
And he goes directed by Charles E. Celier Jr.
Shame on you.
Written by Michael Hickey.
He goes through the cast and crew and says shame on you.
How could it have been this controversial?
I don't know understand different time and but here's the thing it was not controversial for the right reasons nobody was saying
It depicts rape too passively or whatever now it would be all about the right people were literally mad that Santa Claus was being evil
That's what they were mad about that was it and the ads for this I think Eric and Pramkin was a big part of it
So they cut to ebert who's like you know, you know, he wrote movies for Russ Meyer
Like he wrote fucking beyond the value of the dollars and I he's he's literally doing one of those things
I always knew something great was coming when he'd be like shifting in his seat, right and like
Adjusting his too small
Carderoy Blazer, you know, I'm like, oh, he's gonna tell Jean like what an asshole he is right and he bird goes and I'll tell you something else
You liberal Hollywood fat cats or you know, he's going on. He's going on and on and on and he goes
May I'm gonna try to remember the exact wording, but he goes
Because I'm glad you made a little money and now as you slink back to your Beverly Hills
mansions, like the scum that you are.
This is Ebert now?
Yeah.
As you slink back to your Beverly Hills mansions, he goes, I'm glad you got your money
because I just want you to think about the little kid who now has Santa Claus ruined for
him forever.
Think about the moms who have to tell their kid, it's not real because Santa Claus is not
real.
Five years too early think about what you've done. They're they're literally so furious and they're like trembling
Well, this is this is a great way to segue into the movie review section because I just wanted to read
reviews of this movie from
Rotten Tomatoes, please do
This and there's no top critic section for Silent Night definitely night on Rotten Tomatoes believe it or not
So Scott Weinberg in a review my buddy, it's time I look up at old horror movies Scott Weinberg's got a review
These are I haven't used a great follow on Twitter if your fans are horror. I have got Weinberg. He's the best
I haven't got I haven't gotten all the way down the list yet because he's really good
This one's from Rob Vogue or Vox, however you say it at mania .com. It had its moments
It had its moment and then vanished like all garbage does
John A. Nezbit from Old School Reviews, a brutal reminder that Christmas can have negative
connotations for some.
Okay.
Yeah, I'd say rape and murder would cost me to have negative connotations.
Rob Nelson from city pages in Minneapolis says, among the dozen or so victims of Santa's
sleigh ride is a man who's choked to death with a string of Christmas lights and a young
woman who's impaled, topless, of course, on a pair of moose antlers.
So it almost sounds like this guy's condemning the brutality in which the way the rapist
was murdered.
Yes, exactly.
Right?
I think he's the one that gets hung with the lights.
Unless it's the guy she's fucking on the pool table.
No, well, all I remember is that the antlers was the topless girl who's -
Yes, that part -
I understand that -
And that was consensual, so I know that much.
Uh, here's Dean King, Super Reviewer.
Hard to see what all the fuss was about by today's standards, but suppose it was
a bit shocking for 84, the film does look really dated, and now it's just unintentionally
funny to row than scary or gruesome, a very poor film with cheap effects, bad acting and
little plot.
I don't agree with that.
Couple of one -liners from the time Leonard Malton.
What's next?
The Easter Bunny as a child molester?
Oh, boy.
L .A.
Times.
It's safe to predict Silent at Deli Knight will start making worst movie of all time lists
immediately. I don't agree with that either. And then my favorite one positive notice came from Kirk
Ellis at the Hollywood Reporter who complimented director celliers, quote, workman -like competence.
That's the only good review they have. Workman -like competence. Oh boy. Oh man, I love it. And it's just
it's not that bad a movie. It was never released in the United Kingdom because they they couldn't
get it down to an 18 rating? Like, I don't get this shit.
Well, I guess it's like that review that I read where it's like, you know,
I guess imagining it's 1984, this was, yeah, you know,
it was a much different time, but it seems almost more quaint than
Nightmare on Elm Street, really, which was released the same weekend
apparently, except for the Santa thing. I think I'm willing to bet
that the plate, the weird this movie went wrong at least for the
times. And why Nightmare on Elm Street got more of a pass was there's
There's a lot of implication in Nightmare on Home Street
without showing it.
You get an idea that he's a child molester,
but they don't show it.
They don't show him ever murdering kids.
So I think that's probably enough for most people.
I would agree.
I don't need to see brutal rape scenes,
or anything other than like.
But I'm assuming that's why Nightmare on Home Street got,
because Nightmare on Home Street's a really dark movie too.
That's no fucking pick me up of a film.
Well, the sick thing about these kind of grind house movies
that Terrence, you know, shows all the time at his theater in town, the New Beverly,
is that rape is part of the fun, of the violence, and everything else, that these movies usually involve a rape or two.
I'm not talking about his movie grind house, I'm talking about grind house cinema.
Yeah, and it becomes troublesome because it's never really a man rape.
No, except deliverance, but, you know.
I understand why there's some, there's backlash about that.
But my favorite little detail, and I think we probably need to wrap up my favorite little detail about this is that
Mickey Rooney
You all know Mickey Rooney. Love him. Was one of the most outspoken and vocal critics of Silent Night, Deadly Night
And he wrote a letter to the producers where he referred to them as quote, scumbags
You've ruined Christmas and if you picture Mickey Rooney doing it or better yet Dana Carvey's impression of Mickey Rooney doing it
Yeah, you can you can imagine how upset he was about it ruined in Christmas for all these people
Cut to years later silent night deadly night five
Is being released and who is in it?
But Mickey fucking runie. What a son of a bitch the money has run out and
Runies in the very movie he can do what a son of a bitch
That's like Linda Lovelace when she did porn again right at the end. It's yeah, what are you doing?
Well, I think, you know, and there was speculation online, even though I think people were just got great if you've ever read you want a real troublesome read
Look up. I don't remember what magazine put it out
But there's an article about Mickey Rooney's kids and how they abuse and exploited him like constantly
Yeah, I've heard that so maybe they wanted him to get some money and force him to do it
They also said maybe the movie was called something different and he didn't know
Well, that's possible that does happen. I think the fact is he probably just needed some money
But that's our how they know what I want you to look up a clip of this movie online where the guy
I don't I've not seen it, but there are toys come to life
There's like a nutcracker type thing and there's another rape scene the nutcracker type. This is shout -out night
Definitely night five five. It's like a living doll like this creepy like it's a man in a suit like he's a doll
That sounds cool and he takes down his pants to rape this woman and he's got doesn't sound cool
He's got the Kendall no genital thing and advances on her to rape her and the scene cuts out and I'm like
I
Don't want to know what happens next and yet. I'm very fascinated by whatever was gonna happen there
So it gets a little supernatural down the line with the sequel
I think you and I should maybe
Some some Saturday watch all four of the rest of them and just give a good do one episode
I'm not accomplishing the rest. I'm not against it
The first one, I think we can both confidently say, is a fun, sleazy time at the movies.
Folks, that's our episode.
I had a great time here.
I had a great time too. I'm supposed to read this final thing.
Well, at the end, hold on. Watch out.
Watch out. Learn from the way I did it.
Would it have mattered if I did it sooner?
Some severe situations.
My short fiction column available at fangoria .com.
Follow me on Twitter and Instagram, Joe DeRosa, comedy on both.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Vine Twitter Instagram and I guess most importantly folks married Christmas and happy
Honey, if you're home with your family, they're driving you know unhappy ones family's driving you know
It's bust out some old archives. We had a lot of great stuff last year's Christmas episode. We talked about black Christmas
We're just we're thankful for you guys. We're thankful for your tweets. We're thankful for your love your five star reviews
We are.
It's great.
We're getting a lot of great feedback, and we love it.
Thank you all.
You've been listening to We'll See You In Hell, a presentation of the Fangoria Podcast
Network, produced by Thomas DeFail, and executive produced by the great Ken Hanley of Fangoria
Entertainment.
For press opportunities, advertising inquiries, we are looking to advertise, and information
about We'll See You In Hell, contact kenatfangoria .com or Joe and I at our Twitter profiles.
Merry Christmas, everybody. Be safe and happy New Year. We'll see you in the New Year.
You