I'll see you when you hear some discussion about movies.
My name is Joe DeRosa. My name is Patrick Walsh. And on today's show, we'll be discussing the
2007 Brian Robbins classic Norbert. It's starring Eddie Murphy. Eddie Murphy and Eddie Murphy.
Oh, it's been a long time coming. We've discussed the show many times on here. We've referenced it
many times. We've argued about it many times because Pat changed his opinion seemingly over the years
of the film. And we thought, let's give it a real review and see if my staunch opinion how
hell is up or if he's right for having strayed from the path. Yeah, I saw Norbert theatrically
alone, haven't seen it since, but I saw it last night again. And I'm prepared to discuss
in the meantime, what's new, Joe? What's happening? I texted Joe yesterday thinking I had some
juicy news. Robert England, Freddie Krueger himself added to the cast of Stranger Things. Joe
writes back, I don't give a fuck. I said, who gives a shit anymore? Just meaning about anything.
About England. But also about Stranger Things. I mean, I feel like that show, I think that show
at this point should have been a movie, maybe a movie in a sequel, but the fact that we're going into
like the 40 hours of this and they clearly have no story to tell is starting to lose me a little bit.
I do think it's a very well -made and entertaining show, but they're going through the motions a little
bit. Stranger Things. I heard the new season was going to be about the relationship between Drake
and Millie Bobby Brown. Folk. Yeah, I could care less. I'm over it. They're grown, man. They're grown.
They're like 17, 18 year old kids now. It's like not fun anymore. It was fun when they were
little kids, like, yeah, endearing and fun and charming. It's going to be like the kid with the
tooth is going to be like when Screech was in the college years, trying to make his voice crack,
you know? Yeah, nobody wanted to actually think about Zach Morris having six.
Got to that point. You were like, I'm out, guys. I don't want to. Yeah.
And we're going to get to that point with this. To me, the way it was shot, too, where they're really
they're showing you like all of his balls, taint, and asshole when he's fucking Kelly Kapowski.
To me, for a kid's show was just needlessly graphic, you know, and to point the camera at the
undercarriage of Mark Paul Gosler, you know, I think that in porn when, you know, you're watching
really any angle is fine except the angle where the camera is positioned behind the man's balls
and taint. And they always go there. They always go there for you're watching. I haven't seen
that in years. It's, look, it's mostly the point I came up with, you know, you're that you mean
you created? Yes, exactly. You're 80s, 90s, whatever. But yeah, they would always go to a shot and it
just be like three minutes of like you're looking at a man's asshole in the noise. You'd be like,
I'm like, guys, I need a different shot here. I want everybody to remember back to the last
episode where I made a joke about checking box and Pat said gross. And he's now making the sound
effects of squish push. Jesus Christ, wash. I didn't say what the sound was. We all knew what it was.
Well, I used to watch porn where they would be in a marsh or swamp land. Right. That was the
noise I was doing was their bodies in the muck. The uh, I have a news. I think, right in the mud.
Who is it hot in here? That's like an old golden girl's joke. Yeah.
Right. And oh, who is anybody else need some water? It was sprays herself. Yeah.
I never made love in a swamp. Uh, no, no. The one place swamp acid is is the norm. You know,
you're going to get swamp ass making love in a swamp. I did get caught jacking off in a bog once
on a troll. No less. Yeah. Joe, you ever stood up from a chair and looked down and there's a,
there's the crack line of sweat left on the chair or seen someone leave that behind.
I've never seen the crack line of sweat left behind by me or somebody else, but I have stood up
and the feeling in my pants is so outrageous that I can't believe the seat is not soaked.
I hear you. I hear you. Yeah. You're lucky. You got both, both denim and boxer materials,
protecting you. I had it one time. I went to a friend's, um, sader. And he's letting me into this
very like private Jewish religious ceremony. And I was like, I feel a little uncomfortable,
but I'd love to experience one and it was, it was lovely. A great night, great conversation.
Easily a hundred degrees in the man's apartment. And I asked politely a couple of times. And then
finally, I was like, I guess it's just going to be super hot in here. And we finished this big long,
like dinner and discussion. I get up to use the bathroom. I look back and I've left, left the snail
trail. Wow. Really? Mortifying. Mortifying. Do you think that smelled like? Look, not great,
but I keep it clean and I keep it tied. I mean, I think odds are it just smelled like sweat,
but I didn't get down there and do it. I see my wife sometimes on her exercise bike. She'll go over
there and be sniffing the seat. And I'm like, could you not do that? You just assume that the seat
always could use a quick spray. She sniffs the seat. It's, it's, it's, it's so gross to me. And
I've asked her to please not do it. But it's like, if you're going to go over there and it takes
one second to give it a spray and wipe it down, just do that. Eliminate the sniff test. It's always
going to smell like asshole. It's a bike seat. You know what you should do is the next time she does
that you sneak up behind her and press her face and the seat is a mash it in there. Yeah. I noticed
this is a pattern of that we have on this show lately. The first episode of the pair
each every two weeks will be a lot of just somber, we're, we're done, we're circling the drain,
everything is horrible. And in the second episode, it's very jovial and a lot of laughs. And I think
people like the, the, the, the drama and comedy faces aspect of this. Tell us that program.
We've always represented both the comedy and tragedy masks. And when Joe's around also the
V for Vendetta mask, which he wears at all times because, you know, he took a lot of that movie's
beliefs to heart. And to this day talks about how much he loved the, the political path set forth
by V for Vendetta. Did you see that film? I saw it in the theater. I remember liking it.
I do too. And yet I don't remember one thing about it, except that stupid mask.
Yeah. I remember the only partner remember is like, she gets it. She escapes from that like weird
prison. And she realizes it was her mentor that did it to her to train her. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Stronger or whatever. I remember that part. Yeah. And I also remember for years
when Wakowski's would come up in a conversation saying, all right, I'll give you Matrix and V for
Vendetta. And then realizing like a week ago, they didn't direct it. It's like, I saw articles
as recently as this week where they were referring to it as a Wakowski's directed movie. And it
wasn't. It was a very big director, Louis Mateig. You ever see V for Velvita? No. What was that?
Good movie. Little cheesy. Oh, God. How was there not a porn movie called V for Vagina? Like a spoof
of V for Vendetta. I bet there was. Yeah. There had to be. I would almost guarantee there was.
And then I could I could see the cover. It was the mask, but the guys holding up the two fingers
with the tongue through. And honestly, if it hasn't been made, let's get $10 ,000 together. You
know some AVN people and we'll get it going. I got a quick news psycho. I texted you just the
other night, but the fans need to know. Flatliners. The musical has been made. I mean, Jesus.
And no, and it's not a comedy. Yeah. Oh, it isn't that I didn't know. I didn't look like a comedy
to me. Did you see the remake of Flatliners? I did not. I didn't see it. I heard it was like
unwatchable. Yeah. The original is not great. It's not great. It's fine. You know, it's you're kind
of there for seeing all those stars at a young age being hot and young. The remake I had heard
was almost not released. Who's in the remake? I don't think anybody. It's there's also I always
confuse it too with the Lazarus effect. Sure. Which is that shitty movie with. Who's the lady that's the
book smart with Olivia Wilde. Olivia Wilde. Yeah. Some some me and Joe Wilde's the one that, wait,
who's Mulaney Dayton? Mon. Oh, that's right. Okay. Sorry. No, something Joe and I have been talking
about doing is looking at him a random month like April 2002 and going through every movie that was
released and and our recollections of it. That's a new segment. I'd like to try. I think that's
I think it would have to be a whole episode the more I think about it. I mean, I don't know how you
get through. I mean, the amount of movies you forget about, I got the idea when I was talking about
Freddie got fingered with the friend of mine and hit the the whole overhated podcast that he does
is one quick little segment as you go through movies released the week before and after and in
the case of Freddie got fingered, you're like, oh, wow, there's several movies released within a
week of Freddie got fingered that are significantly worse. And you're
geez, I wish it's on the podcast and he wants you to do it, by the way, if you want to do it. Yeah,
I'll do it. Yeah, he was I'm like, oh, wow, that's a way worse movie. I think I've analyzed that
maybe or something like that. And you know, it's just how these movies get like Ishtar, Freddie got
fingered, they get this stamp on them as being like one of the worst ever. But when you really
look at them and put them amongst other movies at their time, they don't really stand out at all as
being terrible. There's just certain titles that stick with the public and their branded flops. But
like Norbert, to be honest with you, Norbert is one of them for sure.
Norbert is one of those punchline movies where like you, you wouldn't be surprised if you're watching
an old tonight's show and Jay Leno's like, no, you know, I haven't seen something this bad since
not a bit. No, I'll be. And then I'm in the back row going, have you watched your own show,
you giant chinned denim fuck. Oh, look, look, look who's got balls now that he's off the air.
You'll trash him. Oh, I always couldn't. It was off the air too. Yeah, he's off the air.
Anyway, it was great at the Emmys. I didn't see the Emmys because I let him know. No, Conan apparently
killed at the Emmys, but I didn't watch him. I'm sure he did. He's good at that kind of stuff.
Yeah, where they do the Emmys this year, the parking lot or something gives a shit. I mean,
the fact that it's even something anybody even takes seriously anyway, it's ridiculous. Yeah,
I agree until I get nominated for one and then another greatest thing ever. By the way, Emmys folks,
stop using the term snubbed, please. Yeah, it's outrageous. She was snubbed for seconds after the
award is mentioned, like the second the announce it snubs snubs snubs. It's not spikedfully done.
It's not done out of hatred. You lost. That's not a snub. Yeah, a snub is like you go to shake
somebody's hand and they ignore you. That's a snub. Oh God, everybody's so dumb. All right,
let's keep it light. Let's go to the movie corner, Walsh. Let's go to the movie. You know what I would
like to say in our screaming in is the trailer dropped for a picture called Licorice Pizza, the new
Paul Thomas Anderson. And as I consider him one of the best working directors, I was very excited to
see it. It's the worst title I've ever heard ever. It's a very bad title. Apparently it was a chain
of record stores in LA in the 70s when the movie is set. I think also in thematically, it's supposed
to be like two things that may taste great on their own. Doesn't mean they taste great together.
But it stars much like how I'm this new sopranos movie stars Gandalfini's son, this movie stars
Philip Seymour Hoffman's son, who gave many of his best performances in Paul Thomas Anderson movies.
And it stars a Lana Heim from the band Heim, which is a great group, great pop group if you'd
ever heard him. But and then Sean Penn and Bradley Cooper and other folks, I can't quite tell what
it's about. It looks like a young love story. It looks like it's got kind of an almost famous days
to confuse vibe to it. Trailer looks awesome. Can't wait to see it. In looking at the release dates for
this year, I do think there are movies to look forward to, which is exciting. It's been a while.
That's it. All right. I haven't seen it. I didn't even know it was out. I mean Paul Thomas Anderson
has kind of lost me over the last however many years. I thought, you know, we talked about it. I
thought that Aaron vice was painfully boring. I thought that master was a disgrace. The phantom thread
I couldn't have cared less outside of Daniel Davie in there. He hasn't intrigued me in a while.
I've loved everything he's ever done except inherent vice, which I liked a lot more on a second
viewing. But this looks to be a return to his boogie nights kind of style. I don't know if that'll
be the case, but I'm curious to see it. I hope so. I'll watch the trailer. Anyway, in the movie corn,
I watched a picture called Cray Machu. Cray Machu. Starting Clint Eastwood, who is 91 years old.
He plays Mike Milo, a one -time rodeo star and washed up horse breeder, who takes a job from an
ex -boss, played by Dwight Yokem, to bring the man's young son home from Mexico. Cray Machu is
like all recent Clint Eastwood movies, kind of nuts. Dwight, so Clint's whole thing is he does one
take of each scene. Apparently Sean Penn was calling people back on the shoot of Mystic River saying,
like, get me out of this movie. I'm like warming up and he's moving on to the next take. I'm going
to be terrible in this. But he wound up being great. The one -take thing can really work for some.
When you're 91 and you have a hard time closing your mouth to make words, you can't do one take.
Because you see Clint in this and he looks 10 years older than he did in the mule. The mule he
looked like a mummy. The mule is also a movie where Clint Eastwood had two on -screen threesomes.
And he continues that in this. He's 91 and there's like a gorgeous 30 -year -old Hispanic woman
who's like writhing on a bed trying to get Clint to fuck her. He's 91. He's not Clint anymore.
He's a dottering old man. He's got the Biden thing where his eyes are like sunken into his actual
skull. And he looks sort of half dead. So he's got these exposition scenes with Yoke him where like
Yoke him will miss a word or two. They cut over to Clint Eastwood and he's like, I need you to
tell me where we're going on the, on the highway. And you're like, are you fucking kidding me?
Like somebody had to step in and go Clint. We can't use this take and nobody was willing to do it.
So it comes off very shoddy in that regard. He's clearly not firing at 100%. The story is it's not
enough that he's got to go down and get this kid and bring him back. They add in this thing where
the kid's mom is selling his asshole to cowboys and friends in Mexico. They add in this thing where
Clint's going to not only get him and bring him back to Yoke him, but he's rescuing him from getting
fucked. It's like a 13 -year -old boy. All right. Then you go down there and then they're on the road.
And even though that kind of horrible thing is hanging over the story, Clint says to him,
you're got to come with me, boy. You got to learn to listen to me. You got to learn to listen.
And he goes, if you keep talking to me like that, I'm going to tell somebody that you
put your finger in my butt, that you're an old man who put your finger on my butt and he goes,
yeah, you know how they would test it is the doctor would have to reach around in your butt.
Is that something you want to have happen? Like these are discussions in the mood. It's nuts.
Okay. They're using this boy getting fucked and the boy actually gets fucked according to
the movie. They're using it as comedy at times. Yoke him is good as always, but he seems kind of like,
is this going to cut together as a movie? Like everyone seems confused. The kid is the worst child
actor I've ever seen. And a lot of the movie is him and Clint talking about what it means to be
macho. So it's not good. I mean, it's it's like sub after school special dialogue between a guy
who has a hard time speaking and a kid who can't act. All right. It's a bad movie.
I watched a friend David Kremholz's new short film that he stars in called class. You can
check it out at omeletto .com. Omeletto is a curation site of short films. I believe Hank is
area produced this. It's about a move. It's about an acting class run by a borderline sadistic teacher
or megalomaniacal teacher. I should say played by David. The news the newest student is coming into
the class for his first night and quickly realizes things are a little out of place here and this is
functioning more like a cult than a class. I don't want to ruin anything because I want you to go watch
this movie. I want you to enjoy it. I know usually we throw spoilers out on this thing, but this is a
grassroots art project. And I want people to go watch it. Not say I already know what's going to happen.
Kremholz gives in my opinion an a word worthy appearance in this film. He's amazing. Everybody
in the entire thing is fantastic. It's very well directed. It's dark. It's funny. It's insane.
It's so worth a watch. I think it's like 11 minutes or something, 12 minutes. It is so, so worth it.
And it's one of those things you watch and realize how good something can be. And why is nothing good?
It's able to be great. So it's great. Go check it out. Class. Can't wait to see it.
Excited. The only guest we've ever had on the show, Mr. Dave Kremholz. Very excited to watch.
I saw Copshop. I was going to say we could do this eventually for the show, but we probably won't.
All right. Good. Copshop stars Gerard Butler, who makes eight to 12 movies a year.
That originally, yeah, there was originally his Gerard day part do was the original star of this.
I didn't know that. He's a guy who gets accused of rape every six months and then has a movie
every year. I haven't seen him since the Me Too stuff. I didn't know he's still out there.
Copshop is it's Joe Karnahan, which I didn't know until the credits rolled. I remember when
NART came out, everybody was like, Joe Karnahan is going to be the next score, Sazy.
I hated that movie. I thought it was fine, but it was really overhyped. And then Karnahan went on
to do like Smokin' Aces, GI Joe, etc. He's a good director of action with a sense of humor that
is not like off -putting. He's good at getting funny guys being funny without it being super joky.
This movie felt a lot to me like Wrath of Man, very similar tone. And in a very similar way,
I and you could tell that everybody else in the theater was delighted by how much better
than expected it was. I thought it was really entertaining. It's just as entertaining as Wrath of
Man. If you took our recommendation, if you thought that was a cool little ice movie, I think you're
going to like this too. But it's basically a hitman who sucker punches a cop, a female cop,
to get arrested and put in this small town police station, but he's in there to kill a guy.
Great little kind of simple action movie premise. It's mostly on that set. It seems like it's
mostly set in prison. And they really do a fantastic job. You're noticing a lot of these kind of
movies now where they're like in one location, or they feel a little more like sets than normal.
And I think that's COVID restrictions, but it's causing these directors to be more creative and more
inventive with their storytelling and also the way they're shooting action. And I think that's
great. I think of anything positive came out of it. It's that these directors are doing kind of
more interesting work. Like what's his face? Guy Richie had been in my mind in a slump for 20
fucking years till Wrath of Man. It's like going low budget sometimes is the thing to do for these
guys because they do better work. And I loved cop shop way more than I love fucking GI Joe.
I imagine it's going to be on Hulu or something shortly. Check it out. I think you like it.
I want to see it. I look forward to it. I love Toby Huss. And uh, oh, yeah. He lets Toby Huss go
fucking nuts. I mean, he's that he is over the top, but he's playing a crazy killer. And he
is right when the movie you're starting to kind of figure it out. Huss comes in and steals the show.
He's awesome in it. I watched hacks. Uh, I haven't finished the season yet, but it's an HBO show
starting the great gene smart. The mighty gene smart and thinking of Emmys and newcomer.
Uh, uh, for God's sakes and I are beginning. Yeah, I follow on Twitter. And she follows me back.
Thank you very much. Oh, I'm Newman's daughter. Yes. They're both I'm the sucker for gene smart.
I've been a sucker for gene smart for years. She's playing. I like when she plays an abrasive
sort of boozy, brassy broad. And she's doing that in this as she did on Frazier. So brilliantly.
I think she might have gotten an Emmy for Frazier too. She did too. Um,
you know, look, it's about stand up comedy. How could I not initially be intrigued by the premise
of an old stand -up comedian who is sort of being put out to pasture, uh, being joined by a new
stand -up comedian who thinks they're more important than they are and them learning from one
another kind of breaks my heart to be honest. I always wanted to sell a show called Bridges
that was about that was a similar premise about, uh, a produce, uh, an old producer
and a young producer taking Hollywood by storm. And, uh, it was one of, I guess, seven projects
that my manager at the time told me, had no legs and would never get made that I've now seen made
into one way or the other into something. Um, it's a great business. But anyway, that's what
I like about this show is that it gets into all this about the business. It gets into how cruel it
is. It gets, I love that Gene Smart is as politically incorrect the character as you're probably going
to see on TV these days. I like that they don't pull any punches. I like that they make her unapologetic
and inappropriate. I like that they make Hannah's character very woke. Uh, and I like those two things
clash a lot. It's, it's the sort of all in the family dynamic. I've been waiting to see on TV again.
It's of course not that extreme. They actually make her wokeness unlikable at times, which is
the point of view you do not see anymore on. Oh, it's great. In fact, Gene Smart gets the upper hand
more often. Right. Like there's the scene. I, I mean, I really like cackled when she's like,
are you a lesbian? Uh, and, uh, like Hannah goes on that whole thing about like I'm more attracted
emotionally to women, but sometimes I need a penis in order to come properly. She goes on this
like three minute tirade. Yeah. And then, uh, Gene Smart just goes, Jesus Christ. I only ask
because you dress like Rachel Maddo's mechanic. Yeah. And that's it. That's the end of it. There's no
like, you know, you shouldn't say that or whatever. It's just right. It's very, very funny. Um,
uh, I enjoy the both of them. I think they're both in real like beast mode in this thing.
It's a good, it's a really good show. It's a great. Donald always great to see, uh,
in an acting role, Shooter McGavin. You got. Oh, yeah, that's right. He's in it. Yeah.
You got the great Caitlin Olson. You know, it's a good supporting cast too. That's right.
Caitlin Olson's great. Uh, it's a great, it's a great show. Uh, I look forward to finishing the season.
I'm, uh, I'm friendly with Jen Statsky, who is one of the creators. Um, but yeah, it's just one of
those things that makes you jealous. It's a bits of big success right out the gate.
And it's a town where no matter when you pitch something, if it's got anything to do with Hollywood,
they tell you, we don't, no one likes shows about Hollywood. We don't do them.
And every time one comes out, it's decorated with Emmys and everybody loves it. And the business just
doesn't, they just don't get it, you know. They never are interested in the entertainment industry.
That's why there's a billion subscriptions to fucking us weekly. And why they're all on TMZ and
everything else. Uh -huh. Don't give me the light, Joe. Don't you give me the fucking, well,
you said you got to hard out here. You got to go to therapy. I'm trying to therapy. Don't give me
the fucking light. Well, no, we got to, we got to move here. I know how much we, I know. I'm watching.
I'm watching the time. I watched NYC epicenters 9 11 to 2021 and a half.
The new documentary from Spike Lee, Spike Lee joint, if you will.
I, we've, look, we've talked at length about how much we love Spike Lee on this show.
What he is almost entirely overlooked on is his amazing documentary work. His documentary on
Hurricane Katrina is, in my opinion, one of the best long form documentaries ever made. I remember
sobbing watching that thing. I couldn't believe how good it was. And he takes his time. This thing is
464 minutes. That totals up to be something like seven, eight hours long. So, you know, it's really more
like watching a season of a show. The first half of it is all about the last year and a half.
You do not want to relive that or you want some more time from it. I get it. I think that's why this
isn't super popular. Nobody's talking about it. Is that for four hours of this thing? It's telling us
about the insurrection, about COVID, about Trump. And it's just too soon. You know, you're watching it.
What I did really was go holy shit, that was one year because the documentary feels like watching
the history of Earth. And it happened in one year. It's crazy. And then the second half of the
documentary is about September 11th, the event's leading up to it, etc. And he makes some interesting
parallels. As always, he has hilarious, great, awesome New Yorkers speak. Some of them are famous,
like John Tertoro, etc., you know, Rosie Perez, people you associate with him, but he also has all
kinds of just like blue collar guys, cops, NYC, firefighters, etc., who talk about their experiences
on that day. He keeps it as light as he can considering the subject matter spike is very funny throughout
but in my opinion, it's a must see. It really helps make sense of the last couple of years and the
September 11th stuff. I didn't know a lot of it. I didn't know they did see escapes from down there
that they took like boat full of people off the island. All kinds of really interesting shit
and great interviews. Check it out. It's on HBO Max. Is that it? That's it.
All right. Can I talk? Can you talk? I'm giving you shit. Just see you know what happened folks. Pat told
me he had a hard out. So I was generously being like, Hey, dude, we got to move a little faster. And
then he threw me right under the bus and said, I know the time I'm watching the time coming from a man
who has never once been on time in the eight years I've known him. All right. I was just trying to help
you so you can get to your little therapy session and talk to talk to 23 minutes. Yeah. I haven't
done my third movie yet. Maybe I don't I just don't get to do one today, I guess. Let's hear it.
How much do we talk about in orbit? A lot. We call it a special episode. A league of their own folks.
I rewatched it. I'll go fast. I have nothing more to say about this movie. Other than it is a
masterpiece. It is certainly in my opinion, Penny Marshall's finest hour. Certainly in my opinion,
Madonna's finest hour. Certainly in my opinion, Rosie OD's finest hour.
But in particular, it's Tom Hanks. It's the best. It's almost as if Tom Hanks knew, I will never
give you a comedy ever again. It is all HIV and box of chocolates and guy with an accent stuck in
an airport from here on out. The very next year was Philadelphia. And then he was like, see you.
And he does every Tom Hanks trick in this thing. Like he does, like he gathers every Tom Hanks
trope from every Tom Hanks comedy and he gives them all to you in this. He does the like Tom Hanks freak
out like that we saw in money pit. He does angry head shake Tom Hanks that he did like it. All
of his movies back then screaming Tom Hanks, the like high pitch like when he does all that,
he just gives it all to you. He pisses for 90 seconds.
This is for 90 seconds. Great scene. And you know, you know, you know they begged them to cut down
that piss. I bet they did cut it down. And they they never get things like that where the joke is
the length. That's something studio executives never get because to them it's just time, time is money.
Yeah. But it's hilarious. It's the funny scene in the movie. So the it's just it's worth watching.
Um, you know, when he wakes up like kissing the old lady that drives the bus like way he loses his
mind and he's like weeping and spitting. Yeah. So nuts. He's really nuts. And I got to give a
shout out to Johnny Lovitz who is also hilarious in this movie. I remember when they get attached.
I saw it in the theater at the dollar show and Lovitz to Lovitz was scoring more than
Hanks like the audience for whatever reason loved Lovitz. But you see the way it works is the train moves,
not the station. Just each each line just chewing it. Gary Marshall comes in with his cartoonish
New York accent. Yeah. Gary Marshall's accent is so ridiculous. You're like come on, Gary.
Was this real? He's funny though. He is funny. He's very funny. But you know what? Like lost in
America, he's super funny. And he's not he doesn't really have that accent, which makes me think he
does turn it up. Yeah, he's great, isn't it? You give the money back. That is one of the all -time
great scenes. And we'll be me in probably five years talking to it. You know, man. All right.
Yeah, but you're very funny, man. You made me laugh. And I thank you for covering it tonight.
Folks. Norbert. The movie is called Norbert. The reason Norbert's been on our mind really on
everybody's mind lately is because the film's director was just named the president of Paramount Pictures,
which is a lot of peas. It's a iteration. I know. But they are making a full pivot to Paramount
Plus, even more peas. And they're essentially abandoning the movie business. And this is a big
announcement. They ousted a lot of their management. And they brought in a guy from Nickelodeon who
directed Norbert. It's certainly not a directorial triumph, the film. I think Joe, even if you do still
love Norbert after rewatch, you'd admit it's imperfect. Well, most most comedies are. I mean, how many
comedies out there could you say are perfect? But I'm curious to hear because for me, I remember I
watched it the first time I looked back on it as kind of a last raw of that big stupid comedy that I
usually enjoyed. Eddie Murphy had been in life a few years prior, which I remember liking, but
it just also felt kind of subdued or something. This was him really going crazy.
Watching it last night, my issue was entirely with Norbert himself. I think it's one of the
worst characters Eddie Murphy's ever played. I do think that some of the movie is funny. And yes,
some of the horrifically racist stuff in it kind of shocks you into laughter. But I do, I think that
Norbert is a way less funny and way less charming version of Eddie Murphy's character in both
finger. And a few thousand times funnier of a movie than both finger. Oh, I disagree there in a big
way. I want you to tell me a few funny, I don't mean to challenge, but I do tell me four funny parts
in both finger. I have watched this movie so many times since I thought it was good and the hopes
that it would be good again. It is a terrible, terrible, laughless film. Well, no, I mean, it's
an imperfect movie, as we said, but I watched it recently with my wife and we both laughed throughout.
I mean, the big trailer scene is him trying to get his way across the highway that he thinks is fake,
but it's real funny. That's funny. That's funny. Eddie Murphy's first scene where he shoots the
symbol is funny. When Eddie Murphy is in Eddie Murphy mode, barking orders about what he wants to do on his
next movie. He's hilarious. And when he's the nerd, like when Heather Graham seduces him is
really funny. He's got some very funny scenes with Steve Martin, Downey Jr's funny as the agent,
the Scientology stuff doesn't quite work, but I think both fingers of B plus B plus. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, stop it. Sorry, I do. We haven't disagreed like this. So, so Kingpin is an A plus. You think, you
think, uh, both finger is a B plus. Absolutely. Oh, my God. That's a range. It's one of the better
comedies of, of its year. I mean, it's, I think it's a really well written funny comedy. Steve Martin
wrote it. It's a good Hollywood satire. It's a good character comedy. It gives Eddie Murphy too.
It's about, it's about a C film at best. At best. All right. A B plus is like, you know, um,
I don't know what comedies, what are the comedies are there? Like Groundhog Day is a B plus. You
know what I mean? It's like rage. It's all right. But we're going to get to sidetrack. Norbit.
I think this is an unsung masterpiece. Whoa. I think it's the funniest Eddie Murphy has been
in ye or was at the time had been in years. I think it is leagues above the sequel to coming to
America. Oh, yeah. I think it is, it is, I think it's funnier overall as a whole than nutty
professor. Notty professor is not funny. Once you get past, that's outrageous. No, it's not,
once you get past the revenge scene and then nutty professor, it's not funny anymore. There's nothing
funny anymore in it. He's great in it. But you do that first. He's, he's so good as Sherman Clump and
the asshole. He's amazing in both parks. And the movie is so funny and touching and sweet and so
many classic scenes. The Clump scenes themselves. I thought this was touching and sweet. I thought
this was, I thought he was amazing in all three parts in this. I think, I think Norbit is better than
the Clumps or my memory of the Clumps. I think Norbit is better than certainly a couple of his movie,
you know, Meet Dave and like that really bleak period. But I think Norbit is one of his worst movies.
I think the problem is with Tandy Newton who they have for some reason 10 pounds in this movie.
She's always 10 pounds. She looks ill and she has no chemistry with Norbit because he's a
repugnant man. I hate Norbit. I don't like him or think he's funny. I find him endearing. I don't,
I don't hate the character. I think any Murphy is equally as good in all three roles in this movie
as he is in the Clumps. 100%. I love Rasputin. If you didn't know, if you didn't know that he was
playing the Asian man, you would think he was an Asian man, just like you thought he was a Jewish man
in coming to America originally before the big reveal at the end. So I think he's, I think he's
equally as good in this. I think the supporting cast in this, the prominent nutty professor is you've
got a great lead and then nothing else. Shepelle is funny and if brief cameo and that is it.
This has an amazing supporting cast. Terry Cruz is hilarious in this. Fucking cat Williams
every line he says is a fucking home run, dude. I'll give you Williams and Griffin. I didn't think
Terry Cruz or anybody else was even supposed to be funny. I thought Terry Cruz was funny. Williams
and Griffin are great in it. Even Cuba Gooding Jr. gets a laugh when he goes, I'm out.
Like the way he yells that. I'm like, guys took a line that was nothing and just made it really
fucking funny. Oh shit. Whoops, sorry. Hit the table again. Tanny Newton, not funny at all, but she's
not supposed to be rough. And I would dare say the first half of this film is loaded. I'll be it
sometimes very uncomfortable humor for this day and age. Very, very funny, funny shit.
Like dude, Marlon Wayne's is funny in this.
Well, Wayne's is funny in it. I mean, it's all, you know, broad kind of rough caricature stuff.
It's, I think it's weirdly way less questionable when a black guy plays another race, but it is
certainly weird. But you didn't say it was weird when he played the Jewish guy in coming to America.
No, and I'm saying there's something that didn't seem weird about it then. And sort of seems
fine now in a way that a white guy. You know what I think it is? Black guy says a history in an
American policy. Right. But I'm saying, I'm saying I think the people took issue with Eddie Murphy
when this one, because there are a lot of Asian jokes. There are. I mean, they think that's the
far away from it. But when he's just riffing, when it's clearly just Eddie Murphy doing
bits as that old Asian man, it's really funny. Like when he's talking about the, what's the line
about the whole? Because they, they kicked his ass and he's like, I'm talking like the whole.
I like this. Yeah. It's something where he specified the whole that really got a right in whole.
Yeah. I mean, but again, it's, it's a guy talking in broken English and it's, and it's, I don't know,
it's, it's odd that Mickey Rooney is considered the one of the worst things to ever happen to the
cinema. And I don't disagree. But you never hear about this. But then again, when you look up
Norbit, the word racist comes up many, many times. I think people kind of look at it. I thought,
well, he killed his chances of getting the supporting actor award for Dream Girls. Everyone thought
that the trailer for Norbit came out and everybody was like, he's not going to win the Oscar anymore.
Because it was this big kind of offensive thing. People would take issue in this these days with
the fat jokes. They would take issues with all of that. That all said, I think we're sprue shift
flying down the water. I think going through the fence is funny. I think the, of course,
I'm wearing bottoms gag. It's hilarious at the point. He's getting in the car and her tits hitting
the horn repeatedly. Yes. Destroyed me. I love the movie. I love the movie. And I've said to you
before, I think there should be a box set called Eddie Murphy's Overlooked Masterpieces. And it
should be this. I spy. Oh, come on. Life. Well, I spy is really funny. You told me, I'll have to
rewatch and I'll have to rewatch. And, and you know, you want to put tower eyes down there, Jim.
You know what? I'll leave it out to be fair. I'll put, I'll put those three. But I think those are
like, look, dude, for what we talk about and you, and you need, you, you must understand this.
As a guy that defended Zack and Mikey need wedding dates or whatever the fuck that movie was,
and your defense was, if I get three good hard laughs out of a comedy, I'm happy,
then this is a, is more than passable comedy. I mean, it completely agrees on more than passable
comedy. It's a, it's a, the, the, you know, the taste level of it, you know, is it dated, sure,
of course, there's some questionable stuff in it. Slow, brown stuff. It's, you know,
it's low, brown, down and dirty comedy, you know, it didn't make me feel anywhere near as dirty as
like sole plane, which I watched recently. But, um, I, dirty, you mean sexy, right? You felt sick.
I mean, gross, just like I shouldn't be watching the, I know, I'm putting,
for me, this movie's strength is not the bottom's gag is funny. I'll grant you and we've all seen
that lady. But the, the, the gags that made me laugh were not the four scenes of
Rasputya tackling Norbert into the bed and the bed collapsing. All the funny with Rasputya is in
the, the little details that Eddie Murphy brings to it. That's what people tend to overlook. And
that's what his genius is. Sure. Is that he finds the heart and soul of every clump at the table.
And every clump at the table is a relatable probably because he has to spend so much time and
makeup, he fully gets into these characters in a way that no one else can do. And that there's,
there's no comparison to you. No one is doing what he does at that level at all. You hate her. Yes.
You hate her and you are afraid of her for him. Yeah. Which is why I say as much as you could say,
you don't like the Norbert character, which again, I don't mind it. But if you don't like it, you don't
like it. But you got to tip your hat to a guy that's like, he's playing both roles and you're feeling
a certain way about both people because of the way they are interacting. Yeah. And whatever,
it's, it's, it's wild. It's so crazy. Like it's so, so, and like there are scenes between Norbert
and the Asian man who was like the, you know, he owned the orphanage or Norbert Grapid.
We're like, there's like this fatherly love between like, and father and son love. It's like
endearing. And you're just like, these guys acting against the tennis ball right now.
Yeah. The fact that the touching elements work that well between a man dressed as a cartoon level
nerd and the same man dressed as an offensive old Asian man character. And the heart of the scene
is playing between this exchange. Yeah. That's, that's pretty crazy. And it's very impressive.
But I do, I did hate Norbert. I, I think Norbert is maybe the worst character Eddie Murphy has played.
Respuesha, I wish he would have dialed it back a bit. And I wish he would have dialed the nerdiness
on Norbert back a bit. Just so you'd buy him as a viable romantic lead in this thing, which you don't.
I think, I think it obviously has, I don't think it's poorly directed. Now, do I think it's,
anything earth shattering or game changing absolutely not. But I do think that one of the things,
what's his name Brian Brian Robbins jokes get landed comedies today. Can't land jokes. They land jokes.
He knows how to direct comedy. I will say this too. He puts a strange scene. And look, he gives
the movie a very interesting look. It does have a sort of fairy tale -esque quality to it. Well, it does
feel a little bit like the, like a little red riding hood in a big evil witch. And you know,
there is, it was on the Warner Brothers lot, like the street where I worked for many,
many years. And to me, it all just looked very fake. But, but I wondered for somebody who didn't
know that lot, would it seem kind of like cool and like that was a choice? And clearly, it did for
you kind of a Tim Burton kind of thing. Yeah. And as me, it just looked kind of fake. But I hear
yes. In fact, when I was watching it, I was wondering, I was like, I wonder if this is based on some
old, you know, shit, because rest few, just sounds Shakespearean. Right. Abend on the Shakespearean.
I was like, I wonder if this is based on some Greek tale or some Shakespeare player or something like
that. Of course, I didn't look it up because where would you look up such a thing? Well, I mean,
it was written by Charlie Murphy and Eddie Murphy. And I don't think they had based it on anything.
They added in a couple of the writers too, but this movie also got a lot of stuff for being
misogynistic. And that's always something I find weird that having a gold digger character,
a mean woman character, a crazy woman character in your movie is now and then thought of as misogynistic.
It always, but who was it misogynistic towards? The woman is mean that Cuba,
good in junior is the gold digger. So it's not a female goal. Every female character in the
movie is likable, except the wife, except respuesha. But I think it's like they must hate women if they
made and they must hate that with fat people, it's hard to argue. There's a lot of fat jokes in the movie.
But it's the misogynist of Eddie Murphy shines through or whatever. And I was kind of like,
you have to be able to have a negative female character in a movie and not have that be called misogynistic.
They used to call Elvis Costello misogynistic. And he was like, I was singing about one girl,
not women, you know, like. Right. So I don't know. I think the Tandy Newton character is underwritten
to the point of insulting. I mean, she has less to do than almost anybody I've ever seen in a romantic
comedy. But I don't know. I didn't feel misogynistic to me. It just feels like a comedy from a different
time. But there are laughs. And I have to on my own grading system say that it's a successful comedy
because there are laughs in them. And I'll say this. I'll say, and perhaps my, I have a filter
over, you know, on my viewing of this, maybe some rose colored glasses because I'll say this in a world
in a current cultural climate that kicked up, you know, look, when this movie came out, this whole
like, oh, everybody being at odds thing was just starting to brew. And then you think about how long
ago that was. And now we're here. And it's like, it is only amplified day by day by day by day by day,
not great or great or great or great. So in a climate like that, to watch something this stupid
and this escapist. Yeah. I'm just I was I was beside myself. I was elated. I just was so happy
to be watching something that wasn't hitting me over the head with why I'm a bad person or
or what I need to be doing with my life or what I need to be taking more seriously or
challenging me in any way or whatever the fuck. I was just like, no, this is just dumb fun. I felt
like I was watching a cartoon. I was watching loony tunes like I actually agree. I agree with
that totally. And I think I think though that by the time you and I are very old men that like
somebody doing a podcast will find Norbert watch it and speak about it how I talked about the
where's Papa movie with the gang rape use for comedic effect. Like it's it's one of those movies
that is so extreme and it's comedy that already a woke 15 year old watching it would be traumatized
by it. So if this continues for another 50 years, I'm curious to see if Norbert like really
stands the test of time as it really was kind of the last line in the sand of just
comedies where anything goes in terms of that sort of material. Right. Because there were rumblings even
on shallow hell, but not many. You know, like, I don't remember it being that controversial.
There were maybe an article or two, but it got a good amount of shit. You know, look, they make fat jokes
in this. But the fact, at least the fat jokes are just like her being in denial about like, right?
Why'd you move my seat? And he's like, I didn't move your seat. It's because you're a little big.
And you know what I mean? The fat jokes and shallow how we're literally like, how could you like this
fat person? What is it? There's a little bit different. So anyway, folks, my hog is up for Norbert.
Yeah, my hog is straight out in front. My hog is straight out there. There are laughs here. I can't
deny that that it was fun to watch Norbert and that it's rare to find anything fun these days.
And that's our show, folks. We hope to see you again. Follow us. Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and
Twitter. The Patrick Walsh and Instagram and Twitter check us both out in the coming weeks on the
We Love Val Kilmer podcast. I did Tombstone, Joe did Spartan. And I'm not sure when they're
airing, but it'll probably or whatever you call it, not airing, but you get what I'm saying.
My solo movie corner is dropping just in time before the end of the month. I'll probably get it out on
Wednesday. That's all I got. We'll see you next time. We'll be back with Dune, Joe.
That's not commit to that just yet. The empty man definitely will be one next time. We talked
well, we talked about doing trick or treat because it'll be October 15th and that's a Halloween movie.
I think we should do that. And then maybe do Dune next month. I think we should do a Halloween film.
So are you a bond man? Are you going to do no time to die even though it's three hours long? No,
I couldn't give two shits. All right. Well, I'm going to see what I'll talk to you folks about.
All right. So trick or we'll be back with trick or treat an empty man in the middle of the month.
Empty man and both of those are streaming right now on max is empty man trick or treat. I think
also might be on max or HBO max. Anyway, folks, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.