I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
Your favorite podcast covering horror, sci -fi, fantasy, action, sometimes drama, sometimes
even comedy.
What are you?
What are you going to say folks?
We cover all types of movies.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh and I'm here visiting Joe in New York.
I flew here, walked in and Joe just starts the intro.
We've not spoken.
He just starts in with that intro.
I'm kidding folks.
We've been catching up.
I haven't seen each other in a while.
How you been, Joseph?
Good.
We haven't had a proper catch up yet, but I feel like it's good.
We do it and then sure.
But we're going to spend a lot of this weekend together, so that's true and a lot of it podcasting.
Wow.
Which is fun.
We're doing a podcasting.
We're doing a big live show tomorrow.
You guys occasionally hear these out of order, but we're starting to straighten that out.
We had kind of a, we didn't know what was going to happen.
Yeah.
Now we know they'll be in order.
Well, also the live show will be weeks before this air show.
Yes, exactly.
I should have worn the listeners that I have not been to sleep.
So I've been up at this point, you know, with the time changes, hard to say, but about 36
hours.
So I don't sleep on plans I never have.
And on this flight, it was a 1230 flight and I was like, okay, I'm going to have like
three drinks.
I'm going to pass out, I've been going to bed earlier and earlier like training for this
thing on the plane.
I got a window seat in the back, I think everything's going to be fine.
I finally doze off, it's like around 3 a .m. and I do the arm whip.
My arm whips really hard, jolting.
I punch this Asian girl next to me in the head.
Oh boy.
She sound asleep.
That's not good.
So I'm out of it.
I go, you almost hear the knuckle connect with her skull and I go, oh my god, I'm so
sorry.
I'm so sorry.
And she looks at me and it's like, it's okay.
It's okay.
I don't know that she even spoke English.
I think this poor girl is sound asleep on a plane, gets punched in the head, wakes up and doesn't
know where she was.
Welcome to America.
And then I stayed awake until we landed.
That sucks, man.
I fly so much.
I've mastered, man, I can sleep anywhere on the plane any time of day.
How jealous.
I'm going to take a pill or something, all over on my, I sleep so much in one position, like
I'm in absolute pain when I wake up, like that's like almost dangerous.
Okay.
Probably cutting off circulation for, well, I never like doing the, the flight to New York
like at 5 p .m.
Because then you get here at 11, it's got, you know, the whole push forward, three hours
and all that.
Yeah, that sucks.
What are we doing away with this fucking time zones and, and daylight savings?
It's all horse shit.
It's nuts.
Well, the time zone thing I get just because of the sun, that fuck it.
And frankly, I've been sitting on that too long.
Fuck the sun.
Yeah, I mean, I'm not a huge fan of it, which is why I move back here.
It's my favorite Rolling Stone lyrics.
The sunshine, boars, the day lights out of me.
Ooh.
Rocks off, which is my favorite stone song.
I, I will do a sort of a stones related thing in the movie corner today.
Okay.
But I'm very excited to talk about one of the things I saw because it was, I would almost
say life changing.
I'm excited.
And I feel like you've seen it already, but I'll, I'll hold off.
What's, what's new in your life?
Hey, I mean, we folks, I know you listen to this podcast, you think these guys must
pal around all the time, having, having these big jerk off fun hangs.
It's really just become a business relationship at this point.
It's staying saying it's been a while, you know, Joe move, we're, we're by coastal now.
We, we text, we're not, we've never been big phone guys.
No.
There's texting.
Usually the texting is either bitching about something in the business, or some sort of
weird mile, mild insult.
I hit play in a voicemail and Joe's, you know, two minutes deep into a rant and then it just
drains the entire battery of my phone, listening to it, but I always enjoy it.
And you'll send me posts, you'll, you'll screenshot something and send it to me.
Sure.
I always worry about that.
You remember there was a brief period where, and I think it still happens, if you screenshot
a DM on Twitter, it tells the person, it does.
I read that one day and I was like, that seems like a huge violation.
So when I screen grab somebody's Instagram and I've got one, I want to talk to you about
what's wrong.
Mike, by the way, that's what I'm talking about.
You know, I send them over to you and I'm always just like, did it tell them it, it panics
me, but they don't tell me, you know, I never get a note of it.
I don't get a notification that that happens.
I think maybe nobody cares enough to screen grab my shit.
I think the reason for that on the Twitter thing is so if somebody's privately maybe sending
you nudes, you can't like blow up their spot, which is a nice protective thing.
But like all security measures, it's greatly violating the, of course, the measure itself
is violating your privacy in some way.
I was entering my phone number into an app that will supposed to diminish your spam because
my phone's ringing with spam now at 3 a .m.
6 a .m.
Yeah.
So I'm like, God, damn it.
I download this app and I'm entering my phone number into the app to tell it like, okay,
protect me.
And then I'm like, why would I trust these folks?
Right.
Then, you know, the other day, it's like, hey, chowhound, which you use to order from some
pizza place you wanted in 2017, we've had a massive data breach.
Your security code is known by everyone, burn the car, I'm like, God, damn it.
Now do you leave the ringer on while you sleep?
By the way, I'm not looking at my phone.
I'm trying to find a story that I just realized would be great for the new psycho.
I leave it on vibrate.
Why don't you go do not disturb it night?
I didn't know that was an option, but I will do it.
You didn't know, do not disturb was an option?
No.
Do not disturb just means what you'll, you'll get it, but it won't vibrate.
It won't ring.
Okay.
When you put it, that's like, so when you go into a movie, you put it on do not disturb it,
then your phone doesn't buzz in your pocket to distract you.
Okay.
I like it.
That's literally been a feature for 10 years.
Well, if they don't tell you, how do you know, what do you read the instruction book?
It's, it's almost like saying I didn't know texting was an option.
Like it said, that's, that's a pretty, every phone is, it's what that little moon symbol is.
When you pull down like the control panel, all right, I'll start doing it.
Yeah, that's a do not disturb.
I, yeah, I'm never like waiting for an important morning call.
Well, the one thing that sucks, and I, I, I like this apartment.
I'm in quite a bit and I like the location quite a bit.
The one thing that sucks is this is an old tenement building.
So it's a very, you know, no frills isn't the term for it.
I mean, there are just, there's nothing at all fancy about this building.
Right.
Including it doesn't have a buzzer system.
Okay.
So he, AC, what's that?
He, AC, but window, I'm going to have to do window AC, but that's most of New York apartments.
I feel like unless you're in a really new spot.
But, but actually pretty advanced heating system for, for New York.
Not that old, like, hissing metal radiator, right?
But burn yourself on it going to the bathroom.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what I have when I lift it.
But the one thing that sucks about the no buzzer system,
it's not that big of a deal when you, like, have somebody coming over
because a lot of places you have to go let them in or whatever.
And then also to the no buzzer means nobody weird ever can ring your buzzer.
Right.
And try to get into the building like it's never a disturbance.
Yeah.
So that part of it is nice.
The part that sucks is whenever I get something delivered,
I have to put in the instructions.
You have to call me because there's no way to
free to be buzzed into the building and how often do they pay attention on that?
They always do.
But it really fucks up what I'm getting at is they do not disturb
feature on the phone.
I mean, when you go down for a nap sometimes in the afternoon,
which I often need because I work crazy night hours,
you can't, you can't do it because you gotta,
you gotta leave your phone on because you're like,
oh, my, you know, my fucking order,
my resident evil seven is coming in the mail today that I ordered.
So that sucks.
But, you know, what are you going to do?
I, uh, we were ordering the other day on Amazon.
Heather was ordering like a 15 pound sack of cat food.
And then like we just, as I picked it up to like bring it inside,
I was like, this Amazon is the sickest fucking thing.
The guy who delivers Amazon,
just whatever you decide you want, like a king,
whatever you push, he's got to carry it.
Yeah, whatever you say you want to deliver to, he's got to take it to.
Yeah, he doesn't make a dollar more,
whether he's delivering a cotton ball or a brick wall.
Well, they do use different services, which sucks,
yeah, depending on the size and weight.
Okay, uh, which often sucks because sometimes you'll get
one thing that was delivered and like they,
like they kept saying we attempted delivery, but it didn't show up.
And I'm like, what do you mean you attempt to deliver?
I was here. What are you talking about?
And I looked in the delivery service was called like laser guys.
And I called Amazon and I go, what is this company you're using?
They're like, I don't do that again.
You don't ever send anything to me through them.
Yeah, and they're like, we have no, that's not how it works.
Right? Strangely, I had no sway over the Amazon.
Yeah, nice to see him at the Oscars, by the way.
Oh, was he there?
Our favorite filmmakers, Jeff Bezos.
He was there. Chris Rock gave him a little shit.
What, uh, how did I didn't see it this year?
Because I was on a plane.
I read the Joaquin.
Well, you know what?
Let's save the Oscar talk for the live shows.
Fair enough. Fair enough.
And by the way, those are going to be released as episodes on here.
So don't think you're missing out if you can't make it.
I saw our last night at the airport.
A hellion.
12, 30 a .m.
I'm, uh, sitting there, zonked out and, uh, up he came.
And, uh, how was the interaction?
The interaction was delightful.
Good. It was brief.
I was up front.
I said, I'm, uh, very close to falling asleep just so you know.
And, uh, yeah, I guess, let me think.
I don't want to give out his name.
Remember that guy that didn't want us to give out his name?
Yeah.
You know, was it him?
Maybe he doesn't want to.
Well, his name is Phil.
I'm not going to say as well.
I thought you meant it was the guy that actually.
Okay.
But, uh, yeah, well, I'll call him out of the live show because I have some questions for him.
I met a, yeah, it was super nice.
I met a couple hellians.
I was in a Cincinnati, Ohio, doing a show.
And after the show, I met some hellians throughout that entire tour, which was nice,
including some kids in, I think it was Pittsburgh.
And they were like, we'll see you in New York.
And I was like, God bless you guys, man.
That's nice commit.
Thank you.
That's the same commitment to me.
But I love it.
But anyway, I met a very nice couple, uh, after the Cincinnati show.
And I was at the bar having a drink with the other comics.
And they came up and said, we love this podcast and the standup show and all that stuff.
And, uh, and then the female said, uh, despite your take on mid -summer,
I'm still a big fan.
And then I, it's like a, it's like an organic response.
I then relaunched into my 20 -minute review of why I hated mid -summer.
I'm sure she was glad you brought it on.
She was laughing inside.
And then like, finally I go, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry I'm doing this.
I hate the movie.
And, uh, her husband understood a little more where I was coming from.
But I get that a lot.
You, I find that people are more often disagree with me than they do.
I don't want to ever get people going, Pat was wrong about this.
That it's usually Joe, you were wrong about this.
But maybe that's because I'm the one standing there.
I tend to be right.
It's a blessing and a curse.
It is.
Like 50 cent said.
Yeah.
Hater to love it.
That's this whole thing, I guess.
Oh, that was the game.
Hater to love it.
Kater to love is a game.
The blessing and the curse was 50 cent.
I think it was the third record was called like something something
called in the blessing and the curse.
Okay.
And it was about as dick, right?
It was about as dick.
Yeah.
That's actually how it was called snake dick.
The blessing and the curse.
He had an apple on the head of his dick on the cover.
Did you know that 50 or 50 cent
jerked off on his show, his stars show and showed his hard dick on power?
Yeah.
No.
And then wound up like getting mad at them for showing it.
But I'm like, dude, if you had your dick heart,
hey, what are you doing in this day and age?
What's also a scripted show?
It's not right.
This was like, hey, I didn't know it was going to be on TV or whatever.
Crazy.
But it's a scripted show.
That he's in.
But still, I mean, you're never watching, no matter what the show or movie,
you're never watching it and you see a hard dick.
That's the last taboo.
What was the premise of the scene?
I don't watch power, Joe, but he was in a car like
jacking off for some girl.
Don't watch power.
No.
It's a little too close to home for me.
Yeah.
So that was a joke that I always loved.
See it?
I lived.
Yeah.
That joke never got old to me.
Has there, can you think of a hard dick in a movie that's real?
Like the Jonah Hills and Wolf Wall Street's clearly fake.
Yeah, Walburks is, well, not, it's not hard,
but Walburks is fake at the end of the bookie nights.
I think you're not allowed to show it because it's an aggressor.
But it started being okay if it was fake.
I've definitely seen real Dixon movies.
Real Dixon planning.
Rager has shown his big, hard dick.
That's what I'm talking about.
I've never seen a fake boner in a movie.
You have through the pants I have.
Never bare.
You have Wolf Wall Street.
I don't remember.
Jonah Hill runs out like jacking off
and it's very clearly fake dick, but it's supposed to be his dick.
I think I thought when I saw that he was holding a dildo
and it was like a joke like we're all fucked up.
Right.
So, but outside of that, can you name one?
Because I can't really know.
I mean, there was a fake hard dick on girls,
but in the moment I was like, okay, that's real.
I looked it up.
It wasn't.
Fake hard dick in, so like the blue is the warmest color.
How pretentious is that title?
Yeah, the criteria on movie.
It's like a French erotic.
It's like basically a lesbian pornography film.
Underage lesbian pornography.
And the director has gotten in major trouble in recent years.
But she fucks her boyfriend early on and he's got like this, you know,
11 incher rock hard.
And I was like, Jesus Christ, looked it up.
That was fake.
So I think you have to be able to prove that it's fake if you're going to have it.
And then who was NC 17 even?
That I believe we've discussed it before.
That girl that's seen in girls where you see Adam drivers come.
Oh yeah, Lena Dunham's like neck area.
I was, this is the worst thing I've ever seen on television.
It was the most disturbing thing I've ever seen on television.
And then he's the hero of your precious Star Wars.
Every time you say him, you got to remember that.
The guy hits it out of the park every time he hosts us.
He's such a good actor.
Yeah, he does a good job.
He just morphs into character to character to character every scum like this guy.
He's scaling it.
I'm a fan.
Yeah, I can't deny it.
Yeah, seems like a very strange man.
But I don't mind that.
He's, I think he's a very disciplined, you know,
he's got that military background.
He's a very disciplined.
Yeah, you know, like he gives me like Michael Shannon vibes where I don't know that I'd want to have
a beer with him.
I, I would like to talk to Adam Driver.
I don't think Michael Shannon has a glimmer of hope inside of him.
Like I, like I smile anything.
Well, him talking about the world, he's extremely funny and dark,
but like real like us dark.
Right.
And then he's a big fan of like good, really extreme comedy.
Like, you know, David Wayne and etc.
That kind of shit.
Okay.
He's into indie comedy.
And so we'll talk a little more extreme.
But you know what I mean, left of center.
Yeah.
We'll talk a little deeper about Michael Shannon on the Knives Out episode,
which maybe probably be the one after this, I guess.
Today, by the way, we are talking about the shudder original series Creep Show.
You've long promised we'd do it.
And, you know, it's just the excitement that we had for it,
at least in my case, really peed it off once I saw it.
But we'll get to it.
Second season just announced.
Yeah.
Greenland.
And I shuttered when I heard.
Ladies and gentlemen, hopefully they give him an extra 20 bucks
to shoot it.
Save it for the review.
All right, don't blow it out now.
I got a great news psycho.
Please.
It's just happened last night.
And we might actually talk about this also on my news podcast without a country
that I do with current Fisher.
Yeah, this is the kind of story we often cover.
But this is just too perfect for, we'll see you in hell.
You stepping out on me.
Oh, yeah.
It's an open marriage at this point.
All right.
It's an open, what am I supposed to wait for you to get another CBS sitcom
that I can get a potential part of?
A little, a little wait in a while.
I'm doing my little brony, which is me and a male friend of mine discuss
episode by episode my little pony.
Is brony a real term?
Brony for the guy.
Brony is a term for male, but not just male fans of my little pony.
They go to conventions and dress up.
I watched that documentary years ago.
I heard about it.
Didn't watch it.
I watched it and you're waiting for the other shooter drop.
The other life to drop.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Folks.
You're waiting for the big twist where it's like,
and then they got caught with the pornography.
You know, like something bad out, and then nothing bad happens.
They're just like, no, like we just like, we really like the show.
We think it's a great show.
I know that's right.
All right.
God bless, guys, you know, sure.
This story, well, it was tipped off to me last night on Twitter.
Somebody said, are you going to talk about the South Park controversy this week?
And I said, I don't know another one.
I said, well, I don't know what that is.
And then I looked on Twitter and everybody was tweeting about South Park,
saying like, if you think it's not funny, you're wrong.
You're in if the funniest show ever, you know, and all of a sudden, I was like,
what is what is happening?
What happened with the show since I was 16?
So this is what happened.
It was a response to a tweet from a writer.
She writes for.
I was a little close.
Here's the, I'll just get into it and then we can get into what she does.
I like jazz bells sometimes, by the way.
This writer is blaming South Park for everything that's wrong with the world.
And people aren't happy.
This comes from Indy 100.
Now, let me guess because this argument came out about two years ago.
It might be the same thing.
I'm just going to guess.
Is it that South Park taught a generation how to how that it's better to not care at all
and be nihilistic than it is to care passionately about something?
Not quite that.
I remember that making the rounds.
Writer Dana Schwartz has started a debate online after saying,
it seems impossible to overstate the cultural damage done by South Park.
The journalist and author added,
smugness is not the same as intelligence.
Provocation isn't the same as bravery.
The lesser of two evils aren't the same.
So she's saying like that this show and her supporters
on Twitter were saying things along the lines of,
I agree, this show's only duty where they've made it their duty over the last
next number of years to attack anybody that has an opinion differing from theirs.
And all this bullshit, every, the truth is they make fun of everybody for having an opinion.
If that's your argument, that's what I was guessing.
That's a valid argument.
They make fun of you for caring, but that's their right.
Sure, but it's also how satire works.
Yeah, you take a thing that a lot of people care about and you, and you satirize it.
Like that's how it works.
Would you, and then they'd be, they'd be shitting over a show with nothing to say.
South Park always has something to say.
This is the part that pissed me off and especially after I saw how old Dana is.
To be clear, I don't blame the show itself as much as I do.
The generation of boys who internalized it into their personalities,
which maybe isn't the show's fault.
It's like, you know what, Dana?
Fuck you.
You know, you're coming at this thing like you're the one that's enlightened.
You're the one that's higher up.
You're the one that's progressive.
You're the one that gets it more than the rest of us do.
And then you just take this swinging sexist comment.
Like only men love South Park.
I know shitloads of women that love South Park.
The only people I know who still watch South Park are women.
When it's like two of them, I liked it for it.
Honestly, 10 -year period, but I can't say anything about the show
worked its way into my personality at all.
I know she's not saying every guy did this, but
she's turning it into like a Bernie bros thing.
And it's like, I'm sorry, I haven't seen men in South Park
t -shirts in the streets screaming at people.
Yeah.
People like the show because it's funny.
I don't even hear it.
I don't even watch the goddamn show.
I've seen it plenty, but like it's not like I'm some South Park
diehard, but it's like to just bring it back to gender.
And then I looked up her books.
And of course she's got some book called like
the whitest white man in the whitey white things.
They did your white Dana shut up.
Anyway, this is a very folks attack on one person.
I don't even know who she is.
And I don't endorse these remarks.
No, no, I'm telling you who you don't have to.
Okay.
There's Dana Schwartz.
And I don't like how she backpedaled.
She made this commentary about the show.
And then when she started getting shit and realized,
oh, I might have pissed off two of the most famous TV makers in the business.
Now I'm going to backpedal and say,
no, it's your asshole fans that I don't like.
It's not the show.
No, you're attacking the show.
But what started this?
The show's been on for 25 years.
I think this week they did a thing making fun of the the democratic caucus
and the presidential presidential candidates on the left.
I think that's what it was.
How could they not?
That's they they've always done what's in the news.
And that's what's in the news.
So although what was their take on it?
All these people suck.
I didn't see the episode.
But but what I saw in the, there's the thing.
I couldn't find when some when this guy asked me,
are you going to talk about this?
I was like, I don't know what this is.
I don't know what it is.
I'm looking for it.
Yeah.
And then he sent me this story.
And then she writes, it seems South Park has been trying to reckon with this.
I admit I haven't been watching the show in recent seasons.
But I'm fascinated to see this.
And it was that when they made it up, they they apologized for something they did.
What did they do though?
Well, that's not that wasn't from this week.
She was just saying, oh, look, they're capable of the apology.
I've never seen them.
South Park issues rare apology for man bear pig scurrying of alcohol.
That was 15 years ago, 20 years ago.
Yeah, without she saying like, oh, it warms the cockles of her heart, I guess,
that they're able to apologize because of course these people must be monsters.
It is really, you know, it's just becoming the old thing of video games,
cause people to become violent and so on and so forth.
It's like, can we get over it?
It's the only thing South Park worked its way into my life is that for a long time,
I really like going, this is fun.
And I love doing the voices.
Not Carmen, it hurts my throat.
A guy named Don Hughes responded to her.
The Flintstones played a big role too.
Made a joke out of ecologically sustainable cars and left us unprepared for climate change.
All right, that's pretty good.
I would hope even miss Schwartz liked that one.
Anyway, I mentioned her age.
Yeah, she's 27.
And I'm sorry, but as a 40 -year -old adult,
it bothers me when a 27 -year -old comes out swinging like,
you know, people, let me explain to you the damage you've done.
Stop it. Stop it.
But no, I just, I'm sorry, I just, I think, I think with,
I'm not saying nobody in their 20s kind of a valedict, that's not what I'm saying.
But it bothers me when I hear an aesonine opinion and then I see it's coming from somebody in their 20s.
Because it just reeks of that Gen Z,
late millennial, whatever, you know, bullshit that everybody's always annoyed with.
But you wouldn't argue she has every right to say it.
Of course she has every right to say it.
All right.
Just like I have every right to say, Dana, I don't like you.
Right.
Never met you.
Hope I never do.
Okay.
Well, if I don't know if I do, you know what?
I take it back.
Dana, if I do ever meet you, I hope we can have a nice conversation.
I bet you.
Well, we can exchange ideas.
She was also ranked one of the 100 most influential people in Brooklyn.
I mean, doesn't this make you sick?
Come on.
It's just, it's just ticking every box of what stereotypically is hateful about that generation.
That's all I'm saying.
All right.
You know, I don't know where I'm not speaking ill.
I wonder if I follow her.
Speaking ill, Pat is a rapper now, everybody.
He meant that in the hip hop way.
I don't follow her.
More importantly, she doesn't follow me.
So feel free to speak at will.
I mean, she definitely doesn't follow me.
I don't follow her.
I looked at her thing.
I remember who it was, but I remember seeing people we knew followed her.
So I mean, who knows?
Maybe I crossed paths, whether at a, you know, some sort of cocktail party that,
that, you know, somebody that could just got on to the latest season of powers posting.
You had a lot of cocktail parties, Joe.
The power is called a cocktail party for a reason.
It's 50 cent is jerking off.
All right.
With this cock.
What's the last thing that you used to watch it religiously, South Park?
Did you ever?
No, I do the thing where every season, like, they'll be like, oh, there's like the two episodes
that are as you got to see.
And then I'll watch those and went, I'm not a big cartoon guy.
I'm not a big animation guy.
I mean, I just, it's wildly uneven at this point for sure.
And it always kind of was when it's hilarious.
It's unbeatable.
The greater, I guess the greater point I'm trying to make is because, you know,
instead of just jumping into the fray of, I think you're wrong.
Well, I think you're wrong.
I think that's stupid.
Why I think that's stupid.
You know, that doesn't help.
I guess the greater point I'm getting at is like, you were saying about like when people were
saying video games were causing violence like this concept.
And I just don't understand how much it's coming now from the liberally minded people
that a TV show was, she could have said it about touch by an angel.
And I would have had the same reaction.
It's like, it's, it's a TV show, guys.
Yeah.
If you got to start, you got to start shining the light on the real problem.
If you think people are being influenced by a cartoon in a negative way,
that's what's wrong with people.
Yeah.
That's not the show's fault.
That's not, and she, that she does backpack, I don't say that.
Well, you're certainly not going to like change your whole personality based off of
watching South Park.
Doesn't make any sense.
If you do, it was never going to work out, buddy.
Right.
You know what I mean?
If a, if a, if a, I always say, if a Nazi yoga studio opens in the neighborhood
in a guy walking by and sees it and goes, I never thought about being a Nazi.
But now I think I mentioned that guy was done.
Right.
It's like, you're done.
He was thinking about being a, yeah, it's like if your convictions don't run any deeper
than that, forget it, man, have fun over there.
I'll see you later.
You see a pair of Lulu lemons with a swastika on them bent over.
Yeah, you know, and you can be very persuasive.
Yeah.
And you say that looks good like in a Jack Hayes voice.
I watched a guy this morning at the hotel.
He was, you know, maybe 35 or so.
I'm going to, I bet all of my money that he was a finance guy.
And he's sitting and eating and this baby comes in and
family, adorable family, adorable baby.
They sing happy birthday to the baby like, happy baby.
I'm saying next to them, I could barely hear it.
They sing to them.
The chef at this place brings them out.
Superman pancakes.
It was adorable.
What do you mean by Superman pancakes?
They had put a stamp on it, you know, like a fruit stamp.
I'm Superman.
Hey, feed the ink to a baby.
You know, it was like a blueberry stamp.
Okay, this guy is looking over at them.
Like he's going to kill them.
And he's like, oh, he's rolling his eyes.
Moving his whole head around like his neck doesn't work.
Like you can't believe this is going on.
Then another girl comes and joins the little birthday group.
She, look, she had an amazing butt.
And she's wearing the Lululemon, whatever the other pan.
Oh, but the Schwarzer got it.
Right, exactly.
That's what turned you.
So I basically had this girl's butt
graze against the right side of my face essentially.
I'm sitting there enjoying a pot of coffee.
And she's like, oh, excuse me, I'm sorry.
You know, like some like, Jesus, I look over.
This guy, I see turn,
double take like Eddie Murphy, like in like, you know,
one of his worst mood, like a norbit double take.
Kind of dare you speak.
He's like, no, looks and he's like, oh, like staring at the ass,
leans all the way back so he can see it to where he's going to fall over.
Then I watched all in time as she turns and reveals.
She is probably 14.
Right.
Now, even I feel weird saying that the girl had an impressive butt.
But I watched this guy's face just like,
it almost didn't seem to matter to him, you know,
but he also sort of judged himself for what his reaction was.
Because he kept looking and ladies and gentlemen,
Pat won't say it, I will.
That man was Bernie Sanders.
Look, I had to say it.
He lost my vote today.
That's, I mean, I'm completely dumb with Twitter at this point.
I, you know, I still have the account.
But it's like anyone but Trump.
We all have to vote anyone but Trump.
Nope.
I'm voting Bernie Sanders or I'm not voting at all.
What are you doing?
Why wouldn't you vote for Elizabeth Warren?
Fuck Elizabeth Warren.
Everyone is going in these circles now where it's like,
you're going to do it again, aren't you?
And they are.
Yeah, yeah, they absolutely are.
This thing is, you're going to do it again.
This thing is a side show, dude.
By the way, my prediction of Trump getting the second term,
I'm now extending to, and I'm not getting into the house and wise.
He'll handle that.
I think Trump's going to do three terms.
Pat at this point, I just want to see where it goes.
Yeah.
Going down, but I mean, it's just, he's going to do three terms.
He's going to change the constitution as well.
This is a wild scene, man.
Yeah, we're, we're, I'm, I'm just curious at this point.
Call it morbid curious.
Call it whatever you want.
But I'm, you know, this is, this is, this is once upon a time in America.
I'm two and a half hours in.
I'm not, I'm not bailing out now.
I mean, for him to be like, you,
motherfuckers, I'm going to impeach me.
I'm staying like that.
We're in a place now where it's like what anyone says doesn't matter.
Well, it's, it, listen, it's, uh, and we won't get off on politics here, but, uh,
and by that, I mean, masturbate to them.
Uh, it's just exciting.
Like, I'm not even really scared anymore.
I'm just kind of like, there's something exciting.
I wish I could have thought of a better analogy than once upon a time in America.
But you know what I mean?
Like, it's like, it's like watching that long movie.
That's bad shit, which that movie isn't, which is why I say,
I wish I would have thought of something better.
But it's like watching that long movie that's bad shit.
And for the first hour and a half, you're like, I'm going to fucking leave.
I'm not doing this.
And then you hit the two more better examples.
It's a spirit remake.
Yes, yes, that's perfect.
And you're like, whoa, shit got even crazier.
And I love it.
Yeah.
I feel like this might go full Susperia.
Yeah, I want to see what happened.
A witch shuffling things into her pussy.
Isn't that what happened at the end of Susperia?
Pretty much.
Pat, I still don't understand what happened at the end of Susperia,
but I loved it.
And I was glad I stuck with it.
I kept the blue ray.
By the way, I just did another like DVD purge.
Yeah, because I wanted all my DVDs to fit on that shelf under my TV there.
I wanted things to be a little more succinct in here.
I got rid of
the only Woody Allen, I had every Woody Allen movie.
The only one I kept was hand in her sisters,
because it's my favorite movie of all time.
But I got rid of every Woody Allen movie.
I got ribs and misdemeams.
Yeah.
I love the, I'm not saying I don't like these movies,
but I was like, this wasn't a purge due to like reasons.
It was a purge of like, when are you going to watch this?
You've had crimes and misdemeanors on your shelf for 10 years.
You've put it in one time.
Well, forget that.
And when are you going to watch scoop?
I almost kept scoop over crimes and misdemeanors.
Because scoop makes me laugh.
But I was like, it doesn't matter.
I'm never going to watch it.
I never would.
So I was getting, but I'm getting rid of these.
I got rid of, there were Scorsese pictures in this pot.
I was just tossing, there will be blood.
Just tossing shit that I was like, I'm never going to put this in again.
And if I want to see it that bad, I'll rent the goddamn thing.
I don't need to like it from place to place.
True.
The point I'm getting at, you know what one made the cut
and is still on that shelf.
Norman?
Who's Harry Crump?
Oh, of course.
I was like, you will watch that.
Of course, yeah.
I was like, now this is a movie that will bring me endless joy.
Like, I will put it on.
Yeah.
That's a movie for a Sunday when you're hungover and sad.
You put that in.
You go, I just need to know everything's right in the world.
Who's Harry Crump?
Jeffrey Jones getting work.
Always good to say.
He's not in who's Harry Crump.
He absolutely is.
Well, who's Jeffrey Jones in there?
No, he plays a key role.
No, you're thinking of Tim Tomerson.
No, he's in the footsie scene and everything.
That's Jeff.
Wait a minute.
Jeff Jones is definitely in Harry Crump.
Tim Tomerson is the footsie scene because she's married to the guy from 16 candles.
The dad.
I'm telling you, she's married to the guy from no country for old men that goes
digging into that whole hard,
cliche, that guy when he's young and she's it's Tim.
It's her and Tim Tomerson.
It's not Jeffrey Jones.
Look, can't they both be in it?
Jeffrey Jones is the second name that comes up.
Candy Jones pots.
Oh, that's right.
He plays like the he's the other guy that wants to fuck any pots that she's like Elliott
raisin, kind of playing for a sucker.
Yeah, Jesus, I forgot.
Whenever I think of that movie, I never remember that he's in it.
He's a key part.
I have to remind myself that Dylan, not Dylan McDermott,
who's the guy that plays the petter ass and suburbia?
Suburbia.
Not so happy to, sorry.
Phil Psymore Hoffman?
No, no, no.
Oh, the petter ass, Dylan Baker.
I have to always remind myself that Dylan Baker is not in who's Harry Crump
because this was, he was in Delirious and planned strions.
He's oh, and he pulls up with a truck.
Yeah, get your lazy behind up here and put that truck in the back.
Her first baby come outside ways.
She didn't scream or nothing.
Speaking of Joe, we got to be pretty deep into this.
We're almost 40 minutes.
We should get to the movie court.
Can I please, can I please take you over to Pat's movie court?
See, we caught up.
We did.
Now, will it, I'm going to ask you legitimate.
Will it bother you if I smoke a cigarette in here?
No, not at all, not at all.
All right, so why don't you launch it off?
I'm going to get my smokies happy too.
Babe, Joe, I saw, oh, we're doing that one.
Let me bring this up, hold on.
Okay, I saw a picture called tone death.
It is on the showtime, I believe, the on demand.
And it's from this guy, Richard Bates, Jr.,
who almost goes for like a Costco rally.
Like he's put together a nice little group of very strange
low -budget horror movies.
Okay, trash fire was kind of his recent one with Adrian Grignet
and acquaintance of mine, Angel of Trimber.
It was very well done.
I liked it. He did suburban Gothic with cat dennings.
By the way, that's how you say that, Grignet.
I think it was Grignet.
I thought it was Grignet.
I've been saying it wrong for 20 years.
I might be wrong.
I feel like you're right.
I feel like he'd want it pronounced, Grignet.
I feel like that's like how I always said
silly and murphy.
And then somebody was like, no, it's killing.
I've said silly.
And I was like, well, it's stupid.
It shouldn't be a sea.
Should be so Lloyd from entourage in Vegas alone.
I don't think he's worked since that show
where he spent nine years
having his sexuality and race
screamed at by Jeremy Pithin.
Did you walk up to him and go, doesn't look like much of an entourage anymore?
Well, he was never in the entourage.
Loser.
He seemed like a very nice man.
A little lonely perhaps.
I was just in Vegas.
Fun town.
We were downtown.
Did shows at the plaza, stayed at the plaza.
Yes.
Went to the dive bars down there.
Had a fucking blast.
The Irish bar down there.
Almost there.
Cave.
We went to the Griffin, which
that's the one.
Well, the Griff.
Steve Burn is buddies with the owner.
And the owner took wonderful care of us.
Thank you to the Griffin and the staff and everybody.
We had a fucking blast down there.
Hit that white castle hard.
Hit that Coney Island dog hard.
Did you see the restaurant there where
if you weigh yourself going in and you weigh yourself coming out?
Yeah.
If you've gained 10 pounds or more,
your meals free.
Yeah, it's called hard attack burger.
Shakes made of butter, like butter milkshakes.
I even I have a limit in that restaurant disgusted.
I wouldn't even go in the outside of it makes me sick.
Anyway, Richard Bates, Jr., he makes, you know,
I think he'll make a really great one someday.
This is not it.
Tone Dev stars, the great Robert Patrick
who you never really see get a showcase for himself.
And it fully embraces his,
the fact that he's kind of like old and like the whiskey's gotten the better of him.
I love it.
So it's basically he's a guy who's putting up his house sort of as an Airbnb.
He hates millennials and can't connect with his son.
He does several Ferris Bueller style rants to the camera about hating millennials,
which is always a little tricky and a narrative movie.
And then incomes this girl and she is a millennial.
They kind of do battle.
It is a horror movie, you know,
I can't really recommend it, but it's interesting.
Okay.
You know, and the most interesting thing I learned was I googled Robert Patrick.
See what he'd been up to.
He played an amazing role in sopranos as a compulsive gambler.
And I know he's on one of the CSIs, but the biggest takeaway was that his brother
is Dan Patrick, the lead singer of filter.
Really never knew that I didn't know that.
So like back in the day, he's doing tea to brother is in filter filter.
That family was killing it in the 90s.
I know.
Holy shit.
Was there jealousy between him?
I mean, that's what I want to movie about.
All right.
I watched keeping on the theme of my Richard Patrick is the lead singer of filter.
Sorry.
Keeping on the theme of rants to camera.
Yeah.
I watched the TV adaptation of high fidelity.
I watched the first two episodes.
How was it?
I enjoyed it.
I originally didn't have much interest.
I thought the movie was fine, but I wasn't like a huge, huge fan.
Yeah.
But my buddy Justin Silver, who's a funny comic and one of my closest friends, he
was in episode one.
He played one of her exes and he came from the premiere last night and I said,
how's the show, how to turn.
He goes, it's great, dude.
I'm happy for my friends.
I want to support.
Right.
So I watched it thinking, I don't know if I'll be that into this,
but I just want to watch.
And I thoroughly enjoyed it.
Zoe Kravitz is really wonderful in it.
And she's always bored, man.
I got to say, I find her.
I find that she nails the part of the record store owner.
I think it's Brooklyn.
It seems very Brooklyn.
It captures the New York spirit very well.
It made me happy to be a part of New York.
It captured all that stuff.
It was a nice new take on the source material.
It was funny.
It made me laugh legitimately a few times.
I felt for her, the relationship stuff was endearing and sometimes very sad.
Is the music fan stuff accurate, good, funny, relatable?
They don't beat you too hard over the head with it.
They do a good job of showing how the music bonds her with certain people
and why it's a point of maybe contentions too harsh of a word with other people.
And some of it's funny.
Like Justin's character, she goes, this was a strange pick for me.
His top five were Jay -Z, M &M, Lincoln Park, Dave Matthewsman.
She's like, I didn't really know what to do with this,
but I was like, that's funny.
But they did a great job of adapting.
I think this was in the movie.
Like there's a part where I can't sell you that record.
And I think in the movie and in the book it was just kind of like in good conscious
that record sucks I can't sell to you.
But in this, it was, I just called to say I love you up.
Okay, well in this it was Michael Jackson off the wall.
And it was about one of the women in the show that's playing the role that I think
Jack Black played in the movie.
She was like, I can't sell you that.
Like he's a pedophile.
And then the customer's going allegedly.
And then Zoe Krabitz is like, it's a great record.
Like buy the record.
What we're supposed to take money out of Quincy Jones's pocket now too.
Like they did a good job of attacking that discussion
of like why is it okay or not okay to still listen to this.
I'm going to check her out.
I thought it was good man.
I just thought it was a nice TV show to watch.
It's the best way I could put it.
See, I, you know, everything is getting gender flipped.
We had a lady dirty rotten scoundrels and let, you know, they're doing them all.
And I'm kind of indifferent.
But this one, it feels like that sort of toxic fandom like the,
you know, the person who's so obsessed with music or movies that it
keeps them from having functional relationships.
I think that is such a male trait.
And I don't even feel like I'm being stereotypical because it's definitely a negative thing.
And it's definitely a trait I had for most of my life,
where you just, you're so passionate about music and movies that it
fucks up your relationship.
That's what the book's about.
The John Qsack movies about.
So I'm interested to see how they adapted for a woman.
They changed it for this.
It was in, it was more about how music is a nice way to bond with people.
And there's even a scene where she's on a date and she goes off about, oh, you'll love this.
Their Fleetwood Max song comes on in the bar and the guy goes, I have a question.
Will you judge me if I tell you that I really love this song?
And she's like, no, this is a great song.
And she's like, rumors, great album.
And she goes through like every track.
And then she goes, I got to be honest though, I'm a tusk girl.
Tusk, I know that's controversial, but I think Tusk is the best work.
All right, a lot.
And then she's like, the band though, the drama, the music is the drama.
I mean, it's Lindsey and she's going off about all this.
And then she goes, I'm so sorry, I'm still, this is embarrassing.
Sorry.
So they do it a little bit, like a little more self -aware of like,
you know, I know I'm a little obsessive, but I know it's a little nuts.
Okay.
Joe, I saw bad boys for life.
How was it?
I heard it was fun.
Well, why are you going to call?
They're going to do a fourth one.
Now they got to be pissed, they can't do bad boys for number four life.
But, oh yeah, good call, dude.
Bad boys one is fun.
You know, it's Michael Bay.
He knows how to direct fucking action.
Those two are funny and fun together.
Bad boys two amps it up and I think it's just pretty awesome.
I like the franchise enough and this is just kind of falls into line.
You know, it's like, it would be, and I like Vegas vacation,
but it'd be like the Vegas vacation, you know, it's like, it's fine.
Okay.
It continues the story if there is a story.
You got paneliano, you know, Eaton Tom's like, I told you to,
you got to get off the, you know,
panel 73 years old, still the full.
You know, the role Michael Keaton was making fun of and the other guys,
the old hardened police chief.
But, you know, Smith and Lawrence are funny together.
I like that Lawrence is clearly not as concerned about his body anymore.
That's why you had all those problems.
He wrapped plastic bags around himself when he went for a run and like,
had a heat stroke.
Yeah.
So he's, you know, got kind of big, you know, and they're just cops and,
and the story is very stupid.
You don't have to know anything about the bad boys, but it was kind of fun.
The jokes to me were really lame, but the audience was hooting and hollering.
The trailer jokes were not funny.
No, and that's par for the course.
The audience loved them.
I never even heard the trailer get laughed.
So I was surprised about how much the audience is into it,
but there's something to be said for two likeable guys,
shooting guns and jumping off buildings.
It was, but one interesting moment,
you know, one of Michael Bay's many trademarks is,
you know, the transition between most scenes is like two girls' asses and
bikinis walking down the beach or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
And look, it works.
This movie 14 -year -olds,
this movie, there are a group of girls like in a crosswalk walking across
and they are showing them above the waist, really above the neck,
like you just see like women's heads bobbing by,
and then they cut to like Martin Lawrence and Will Smith,
and they're not even really looking at the women.
So I think that's how far we've gone or come or whatever you want to say,
but like, they're trying to make it feel like bad boys,
but I'm sure somebody was like, you can't just show girls butts,
and you can't show our heroes looking.
Martin Lawrence is married, you know,
and to be honest, I think that's kind of a drag.
I hear you.
But I hear you.
You know, it's an average movie.
I've gone as somebody who liked Will Smith,
yes, to somebody that didn't was not a fan anymore
to now loving Will Smith, like what changed it?
He made 10 bad movies in a row.
It's not the movies.
It's it's when I see him in things,
like like Suicide Squad was not a good movie,
but I really enjoyed him in it.
His charisma is just undeniable.
He's a very capable guy on many fronts.
And then the clip that went viral of him
with Sway and Heather B at Sirius XM when they put on brand new funk from the DJ,
he's the DJ on the rapper record,
and he just started rapping the song.
And like it was it was awesome.
And you're like, oh yeah, I forgot.
Will Smith was like a good rapper.
Like I forgot about that.
I can't go that far with you.
The earlier stuff, that album is a classic.
That one album is a classic.
All right, you know, he lost me with,
you know, welcome to Miami and the men in black and all that stuff.
I mean, all I know is the singles, but like summertime, you know,
that song's fun, but I wouldn't say his rapping is amazing.
On the earlier Jazzy Jeff in Fresh Prince Records, he has songs,
they have real rap songs where he really just
raps and he's good.
He's very good and Jazzy Jeff is an amazing DJ.
But Miami, they played at my personal training the other day.
And I had to go like, I'm sorry, can we switch this?
I've never done it in two years.
I was like, we got to take this off.
I can't lift weights to Miami.
He did a rap recently that he just released
a song line that was just like, you know, it was like
the kind of rap I love, just a guy bragging about how awesome he is.
Right.
And did it include any lines like on the quickest there is.
On the slickest there is.
Did I say on the slickest there is?
No, that's from the song Wild Wild West.
No, no, but he did have a line that really got me.
And this is when I started to be like, I think I love Will Smith again.
He said something about like, you know, if you're trying to,
if you're trying to like, reach my level, you don't have that many summers left in you.
Like, like talking about how many summer blockbusters he said, I'm fucking lined up.
But I was like, that's a great brag.
He's going to make that brag now.
I think it was a pretty good.
In a post -gemini man world.
I guess Aladdin made some money.
I thought they were making Aladdin too.
I know.
So, remember, I don't know, I'm sure they already pulled them,
but they were going to make it about the one white character, the prince.
Did you hear that?
No, they were like, we're spitting him off.
And everybody was like, are you fucking getting me?
I'll do a fast one, Pat.
All right.
I was on an airplane.
I finally saw the film Judy.
I watched Judy.
I was very disappointed.
Bad movie.
I thought it was a biopic about Judy Greer.
You can imagine my disappointment.
No, I enjoyed it.
It was, it was a typical biopic.
I liked it, though.
I thought Renee Zalwigger was excellent in it.
But, you know, like all biopics.
And I'll leave the review with this.
Was it interesting?
Yes.
Did it have some interesting moments?
Did it have some inspiring moments?
But at the end of the day, like every one of these movies, it's like, hey,
you know how you like this person?
Well, now you're not going to like them anymore.
You know, like you're like, she said this horrible life.
She feel bad for her.
But then she acts horrible.
And then you're like, I don't know who I'm.
I don't know who I'm supposed to be rooting for at this point now.
This is just everybody's just being horrible.
Like, I didn't like the movie.
And I was blown away that in 2019,
this is a movie that nominated for Oscars that ends with an audience
slow clapping for Judy.
Oh, hold on a second.
Not slow clapping.
Her choking up on stage.
Yeah.
And then the director of JoJo Rabbit standing up
take away Tite.
Isn't that I think that's not are you sure that's not him?
Yeah, he's an actor.
He's in what we do in the chat.
He's not in Judy.
Doesn't he play the one of the gay men that she'd be friends?
No, that's not him.
All right, well, then it's a guy that was Jeffrey Jones.
No, it was not take away to Tite.
Well, the guy that looks like the guy that directed JoJo Rabbit
stands up and starts singing somewhere over the rainbow.
Yeah.
And then the audience slowly joins in and went and I thought
because that's where the movie ends, when I'm watching and I'm cringing,
I'm going this is one of the worst written humiliating.
And then because the movie ends there,
I'm like, well, wait a minute, maybe that really happened
and they're just saying like, this is clearly our end to the movie.
Yeah.
But but I don't know if it did or not.
I didn't care enough to research it.
My money's on no, but even if it did,
you don't put that in your movie.
You certainly don't end it that way.
Well, she died six months later.
Yeah, but but anyway, I saw when I lived here,
I saw a Broadway play here.
It was Hugh Jackman as the boy from Oz.
I remember that.
And he was one of her gay husbands.
Yes.
Fascinating tale.
I remember that.
Was he like one of the first people to get HIV, too?
I believe so.
Yeah.
Yeah, the third act I might have walked out.
The song's got a little more bleak.
My last one is killer inside the mind of Aaron Hernandez.
I heard this is excellent.
It really is.
I know so little about sports that I thought Aaron Hernandez was the guy
with fake plastic legs who killed his girlfriend.
That was Oscar.
Pistorius.
Pastrovsky.
Stone.
Me?
No, Oscar.
I've shit over.
Fuck.
Forget it.
Sorry.
No, Oscar Pistorius.
He was like an Olympic runner who killed his girlfriend.
I'm talking about a grouch.
Folks.
I was halfway into this thing and I'm like,
okay, this is a football player who killed people.
Yeah, wild fucking story, man.
It's such a wild story.
I almost don't want to spoil it for you.
But you probably know it if you follow sports at all.
Crazy shit.
And then it's one of those documentaries where like huge reveals are
just casually dropped.
So it really keeps you on your toes.
Like they're talking to this guy who was a quarterback with him in high school
or they were quarterback wide receiver, whatever together.
And he's like, yeah, I mean, so that's when we started
having sex.
They pan out in his dad there and he's like,
oh, I didn't know about this at the time.
Then for an hour, this thing's about like Aaron Hernandez's secret gay life
from high school up to the present.
And you're like, what is going on?
It just keeps twisting and twisting and twisting.
Very well done documentary at three parts.
You're not going to regret watching it.
If you like Drew crime, it's top notch.
Okay, so I'm going to call an audible here.
I said I was going to do a Rolling Stones related thing.
I'll save it for the next episode
because it is appropriate, especially since we're pressed for time
that I say JoJo Rabbit as my third entry.
Okay, saw it.
I tried, guys, I tried, I tried, I couldn't do it.
I got about 40 minutes into this thing.
And I was like, I just don't, it's, I like that Taiki.
It's a very, take a white, take a white TT.
I like that guy, I like him on what we do in the shadows.
I like that show.
I like that movie a lot.
But JoJo, it's so.
It's a Thor Ragnaraja, which you know how I feel about Thor Ragnar?
I know how you feel.
Yeah, you know.
JoJo Rabbit is so blatantly derivative of Wes Anderson.
Yep.
And I'm telling you, it made me step back and look at this guy as a director and go,
okay, are you able to do anything aside from carbon copy other directors?
Because I love the movie what we do in the shadows,
but it's Christopher Guest.
Yeah, I like, I hated Thor Ragnaraja, and it was Flash Gordon 1982 or whatever.
This was Wes Anderson.
It was a fucking Wes Anderson movie.
Yes, it really was.
And to see it get more praise heaped upon it, then Anderson.
You know, like we, we never saw 10 and bombs nominated for best picture.
We never saw Rushmore, Bottle Rock at any of these movies.
Right.
It's enough to make you a little angry.
I just couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it.
I was so distracted by that fact or that aspect of it.
I just couldn't, I just couldn't get into it.
And I just felt like it was, I also felt like it was one of these things.
Now look, you listeners all know when people start telling me something's brilliant,
I'm already going in like half aggravated, but this was one of those movies.
Everybody kept saying it's so good, it's so good, it's so good.
And I was like, okay, you know, I want to see it.
And then when I finally sit down to see it,
not only does it wreak of Wes Anderson, and I like Wes Anderson,
but it just felt so fucking quirky.
Like, like we're going to take the one awful guy in history that we can all make fun of.
And we're going to turn it on its ear and just make a silly time out of this Hitler imaginary
friend thing. And like, and I know it gets way here.
I know it has deeper moments and messages.
I get, I get all that.
But it just felt like a very safe thing to do that was presented and received by everybody
as being daring and not safe.
Yeah, I'd assume the movie is rated PG 13.
I don't know for sure, but I don't know.
I mean, yeah, it was not breaking any boundaries.
And there's been other Holocaust comedies.
Like life is beautiful, whatever your thoughts on that.
I liked it a lot in high school.
I doubt I'd like it now.
I always wanted to see the day of the clown cry, the Jerry Lewis vehicle.
It's, yeah, the search continues.
Yeah.
But I liked half of JoJo Rabbit.
Whenever we'd get real cutesy and Tweet and the Hitler shit,
I tuned out when it was focusing on the kid who I liked a lot.
And especially the portly kid with glasses, his friend, I thought was fucking hilarious.
So there was enough for me to get it to like a three out of five stars.
But, uh, you know, the best picture talk I didn't understand.
And I haven't talked to a human being who raved about and thought it was awesome,
but I have seen a lot of people online saying it was amazing.
I could see it being a three out of five.
I just, for me, and it's maybe it's a shortcoming on my part.
I couldn't get past the, the Wes Anderson.
Did you see his new trailer?
I did and, and it's, it's like every Wes Anderson trailer.
I see the trailer and I go, Christ almighty.
This again, oh, the office has pink walls or whatever.
And I don't care.
And then I end up seeing it and I go, that was great.
I know, but has any director ever done something that specific that many times,
that many times back to the well and not said, okay, I got a branch out.
It's pretty incredible.
I mean, it's the same cash.
It's like, oh, Bill Murray's
the editor when we, when he adds somebody, you're like, oh, he's adding
Francis McDorman to the mix.
Then his next six movies she's in.
It just, to me, it gets a little boring,
interpetitive.
I think the first three movies are about perfect.
Balorock at Rushmore, uh,
ten of bombs, beyond that.
I think they're, they're pretty good to great.
You know, I, I like them too, but it's time to try something else.
I absolutely loved Hotel Marmaduke or whatever it's called.
Grand Budapest Hotel, yes.
I thought that that movie, especially to see Ralph finds,
yes, Ray, Ray finds excuse me, be that funny.
I was like, what the fuck, man?
This guy's really funny, man, Jesus.
But I thought he was funny as Voldemort, to be honest.
He's, uh, he's amazing as Voldemort.
He was awesome and Rickman and I just rewatched that whole trilogy.
Our octopla G, whatever it's called.
Um, those movies are awesome.
I love the Harry Potter ones.
Uh, all right.
Let's get to the movie at hand.
What the hell?
I know creep show.
Sorry, not a movie, TV series.
So Joe, as I get a refill,
you talk about your history and love of creep show.
Because for me, I think creep show is a fun movie.
I saw it when I was in my 20s,
so I have a different relationship to it.
And I think creep show too is largely not great.
But I was still very excited about the show.
So creep show, and I've talked about this before,
but I'll say it again, creep show, the original creep show is in my top 10 movies of all time.
In fact, did the tweet challenge or whatever the hell you call it today,
where top 10 movies that define me, creep show was on that list.
As I tweeted it out, uh, didn't get a ton of love back, uh,
from not didn't get hate, but people responded much more strongly to other movies on my list.
But I love the movie creep show.
I love anthology horror.
I'm a huge tells from the crypt fan, both the comics and the TV series.
To me, creep show is as perfect as a horror movie can possibly get.
It's five short stories already.
We're off to a good start.
All of them are fun horror.
You know, it's you're dealing with a man turning into a plant and, uh, you know,
a dead dead that comes back from the grave as a killer zombie.
And an asshole who's obsessed with cleanliness that gets overrun by roaches.
I mean, it's a, these are all very, very fun stories.
And all in the vein of what I think can be anthology horror at its best.
Creep show two, I have a great love for.
I recognize that it is nowhere near as good as the first film,
but I still really enjoy the movie.
And then the unofficial third installment is tells from the dark side of the movie.
Because it's all the same creators as creep show.
Uh, and the reason it's called tells from the dark side of the movie.
And not creep show three is because when they tried to make creep show into a TV series,
they couldn't get the rights.
So Romero and, uh, the crew called it tells from the dark side.
Uh, and then they made the movie adaptation of that based on the success of that show.
Uh, that all said.
Oh, last, last I'll say, I've, I've often said on this, uh, podcast.
It is in my opinion, the one flawless horror franchise.
It is a perfect, a perfect, but a damn near perfect trilogy of horror films.
And we all know horror franchises go way off the fucking rails.
Uh, and this is one that I felt never really did.
It stayed in the vein of what it was.
You know, uh, each one had a wraparound story, uh, that showcased the five stories.
And it was just simple, great fun.
And sometimes very funny horror.
Um, I was incredibly excited when creep show the TV series was announced.
I followed it week to week, month to month, leading up.
In, in the same way I followed, like the Irishman build up or Star Wars, uh, Force Awakens or whatever.
Any, I followed it as much as I follow anything.
The, any huge reboot or relaunch or reunion type of project.
Uh, I was extremely excited.
Um, and then it finally hit shutter.
I liked that they did the weekly release of the episodes that they didn't put it all up at once.
Because that brought me back to being a kid again and waiting desperately for Friday night to come
so I could watch the latest tales from the crypt.
Uh, we're being a kid and waiting desperately every week to see what the new tales and the dark side was going to be.
Um, it really, that approach to me is the way anthology horror should be approached.
Um, and then the show hit shutter.
Yeah. Now, there's a lot to say here.
I feel that I'm going to be a little more positive than Pat will be.
Um, but we can start with the first episode.
And I thought that it was good.
I thought it was a very, very solid first episode out of the gate.
Um, I liked that the first story they adapted was Gray Matter by Stephen King.
I thought that the adaptation was pretty cool.
I love that Adrian Barbot was in it.
She's in Creepshow the movie and she's also a horror icon.
I loved that what's his name that played, uh, jigsaw was in it.
Um, I thought it was cool that they took another horror icon and put him in the role of actually a good guy in the, uh, in the episode.
And Joe Morton, correct, from Terminator?
Yeah, I believe so, right.
Um, and then the second story was how I thought Gray Matter when it started, I was like, oh, okay, they nailed it.
Yeah, it's going to be awesome.
Yeah. And I liked that they're doing the thing with the comic book pages showing the story and the animations of that and whatever.
Yeah, uh, my first initial issue with the show was the way the creep looked.
I didn't understand why they took this approach because the creep, if you're unfamiliar, is basically the creep keeper.
I'm sorry, it was Giancarlo Espazino.
Okay.
From Breaking Bad.
Sorry.
So in the first movie, uh, the creep is portrayed just a, it's a, it's an animatronic doll and it doesn't look amazing,
but it looks good enough.
And the second movie, Tom Savini, is in makeup and plays the creep.
And I think that looks great.
In Chelsea, the dark side of the movie, obviously, the creep isn't in there because it's not creep show officially.
Um, but then in this, they had a creep that didn't talk but laughed a lot.
Uh, and it looked literally to me like a thing you would buy it like Walmart for Halloween.
Like I was just like, I don't understand.
And then half the time would be animated and half the time wouldn't be.
And I was like, just pick one.
Yeah.
Just, just have a consistent thing that you're doing here.
So right there off the bat production -wise, I was starting to get already confused.
Like, what, look at this half cartoon wrap around approach, but half the, the puppet,
like the puppet's not adding anything.
This is a mod.
It doesn't look like the puppet from the original movie.
Like, what's the point of this?
So, um, but that was my initial takeaway.
What was your initial takeaway of that first?
And I liked the second story.
House to the head too.
I thought that was cool.
Uh, uh, haunted dollhouse story is always fun.
Yeah, we can briefly go through each, but so I saw Greg Nicotero was kind of the creator of this.
And he's done the walking dead.
So here I am thinking he's the guy who runs the walking dead.
That certain point I looked it up and I was like, well, that's a pretty carefully plotted show here.
Like these, these, a lot of the stories just didn't hit for me.
And the guy's never written anything.
And he didn't write anything to do with creep show.
He's a makeup guy who shuttered gave the reins of like creating creep show.
I find that always so interesting.
And look, good for Greg, Greg, Greg Nertar is at a long history and horror,
but I do very long and, and, and, and brilliant shit.
I do think it's often strange when they just take a guy that's never been sort of
make a, like I get it when they give a writer a chance to direct eventually.
It's weird to me when they give a, like, like an actor who's not famous a chance to direct,
like a makeup guy, just a chance to, it's a, it's a strange, but Greg, I think it's a showrunner too.
Yes.
That's not me saying he did a bad job.
I just think that's sometimes it's a weird choice.
I don't quite understand, but I agree.
And for the showrunner to like not really write any of the scripts is certainly very strange.
I've never heard of that.
But, um, Gray Matter was very well done.
And the house of the head felt like a, to me, like a UCLA short film kind of thing.
I, you know, here's my overall thoughts.
The elephant in the room here is that this thing is outrageously cheap, outrageously cheap.
For a shutter to like dip its toe into the, we're producing series now waters with a title
as big as creep show, with a fan based as big as creep show.
They needed to quadruple the budget of this thing.
They really did because, you know, the effects and sometimes it's, it's kind of can't be fun,
which I know is part of the creep show appeal, but sometimes like even just like this,
that what it's shot on looks like soft core porn.
It really does.
It's like the USA up all night of horror, you know.
Yeah, and that, that's an aspect of it I didn't get.
My biggest criticism of the show, and look, we don't have to go through every episode.
But here's my biggest criticism of the show.
There was no consistency.
My biggest gripe with modern day horror anthology films is, and you'll, you know,
I'll buy them sometimes just on blind faith, because it looks kind of cool on DVD or something,
you know, something I've never seen, just because I want to give it a shot.
Yeah.
You know, I watched nightmare cinema on shutter recently, and people were saying this was a
solid anthology. I couldn't get through it. I thought it sucked.
Was that done also for a shutter?
I don't, I don't know if that was a shutter, I don't think it was a shutter original.
But a lot of the, a lot of the recent anthologies are shot like solo, but here's,
here, and this is the, this is the issue.
They did this with ABCs of horror. I think that was the one that kind of set the mold for this.
Right.
They take, they have five directors and five writers,
yeah, and five different production teams and staff and whatever.
And everybody goes off and does their own thing.
And then you come bring it together and you kind of add the glue of a wrap around
and then suddenly you're looking at this thing and you're going, this is completely inconsistent.
The tone is off. It doesn't make a lot of sense.
Stylistically, it doesn't mean George Romero directed creep show.
Yeah.
Every story felt that it was through the same lens.
Right.
Even though they were based on stories by different writers and whatever,
it was, it was all, it all felt unified.
And this does not feel unified.
Even in the same episode, like the, the one I just watched today,
because I watched the first three as they aired and then it took me a while to pick it back up,
they do skin crawlers, which is the one with Dana Gould,
and we can get to that though the weight loss one, which is essentially a horror comedy.
And it's okay.
It's fine.
The very next one by the silver water of Lake Champlain,
the worst of the series and it also seemed like the highest production value.
It's, it was written by Joe Hill.
It's based, he didn't write the screen.
I'm sorry, story by Joe Hill.
It was written, it was based on one of his stories.
I was so excited for that because Joe Hill is awesome.
Yeah.
And I'm like, this is, it looked awesome.
And I got so bored immediately by it.
I'm like, well, one can't be a tongue -in -cheek wacky gross out.
And then the other like a somber, you know, dragon story.
Whatever the fuck it was.
I don't have a problem if you want to do a big tonal shift with two different
stories.
I do have a problem with bad writing.
That Champlain adaptation is so poorly written.
These characters are really stuck.
That's step -dad character.
It's like, you better watch out.
Jacob is home.
And then he comes in like, you dumb kids aren't
cleaning clean to that damn house yet.
Give me a beer with my dinner.
It's like, what is this?
This is pathetic.
The kind of shit like my wife is never this person who comes in like,
what the fuck are you watching?
Every time I was watching this, she'd come in and be like,
because I think she thought I was sitting in the living room watching pornography.
Because everything about it, the acting and some of these was atrocious.
I'll get back to it.
It missed the boat.
Gary Ange.
The consistency issue is best pointed out.
And now the second episode seems to have everybody's favorite story.
And I loved it.
But it's bad wolf down.
Yeah.
I'm looking at it so I'm going to help you.
Awesome.
That wolf down was fantastic.
It's awesome.
It's every Rob who did Sarah Silverman program, he did the pilot for Heat Vision and Jack,
which is the Jack Black thing with the car who's voiced by Owen Wilson.
It's like a night writer's booth.
Find it on YouTube.
It's incredible.
Ben Stiller had a hand in it as well.
He's a great guy, a good comedic guy.
And that was an awesome story beautifully done on a low budget,
but you don't feel the low budget.
Well, because they used the techniques and devices of the show to their
advantage, they said we obviously can't afford to show a werewolf transformation on screen.
So here's what we're going to do when they train when these sold it's an episode about soldiers
who encounter a werewolf.
So when they show the werewolf transformations, sorry for the sirens, everybody,
if you can hear them, they go to the comic book pages.
And they show it by pages flipping and drawings of a man transforming into a werewolf.
That episode, they also did, they also brought back devices.
They use the original creep show movie, which is like they'll have a guy yelling and behind him
is like blaring, you know, glaring red lights and stuff.
And like, they'll be like a comic book, yeah, you know, explosion drawn behind him, whatever.
And I was like, this is awesome.
This feels like creep show.
They're nailing it.
And then those types of things almost never happen again through the entire series.
And it's like, guys, Greg showrunner.
Yeah.
It is your job to be like, that has to happen once in every single up.
Now maybe shudder or the execs came and said, no, and fucked it up.
I don't know, but that has to happen in every episode.
That's how you have a consistent series.
You never know what goes on behind the scenes.
I assure you.
I know.
And that's what sucks.
But like, it seemed to me they gave every director a hundred grand, maybe, maybe 50 grand
and said, go make what you want is what it felt like to me.
And that just winds up being a hot mess.
What it really does is help you play who's the best director.
It quickly edges a lot of people out or who's the best writer.
But this really should have been a hey, we've got budgetary concerns.
Let's bring in all the writers, all the directors.
And let's talk about how we're going to do this.
And I completely agree with you.
Like I wouldn't have batted an eye if they cut to like paper dolls to act out something.
Or like shadows on a wall.
Like the Harry Potter movies again have these two hundred million dollar budgets.
But when they're telling you the story of the Deathly Hollows,
they do it through like candles flashing on a, do you remember that part?
Yeah.
It's almost like a kill bill tactic where they switch formats completely.
And you're watching this like beautiful animation.
Like it can be so effective.
And I totally agree.
All of these could have benefited from doing some little handmade thing.
The audience understands you didn't have the money to do it.
The horror audience understands low budget.
And you know what the problems with it are.
But like get creative.
And so many of these things did not get creative at all.
There were also several episodes.
Now by the way, before we go on here.
Yeah.
I felt like if you took four, maybe five of the best stories from this thing.
Yes.
They could have been cobbled together.
And what would have been a very, very satisfying
fourth installment to the franchise.
Right.
I would have walked away and went, okay.
The David Arquette one.
The Werewolf one.
Gray matter.
House of the head.
Like I was like, there were four or five in there.
I was like, if you showed me that as creep show four,
I would have been like, okay, that's great.
I'm not happy.
I'll buy it.
I'll buy a copy of that.
Right.
The bulk of this
did hurt it quite a bit.
And unfortunately,
what happened with a lot of these stories,
particularly the Bruce Davidson one
about the monkey's paw.
A lot of these started so great.
The premises were so great.
And then the next thing you know,
it's like, you're looking at your watch going.
Why did this not end that in that scene?
I know.
They're adding a whole fucking
coded of this thing that it doesn't need.
And it's ruining the goddamn story.
It's not good now because of it.
The show was 45 minutes.
And it should have been two 15 -minute segments or two 12 -minute segments.
Like the movie.
Yes, exactly.
Like the movies.
The um, should we roll down them real quick?
The finger is the next one after bad wolf down.
They, I think they probably intentionally
paired one bad and one good because that seemed to be the
everybody loved the finger.
For me, one bad and one fine.
Everybody loved the finger.
Like that, like when I read like the,
like I think it was on play to disgusting,
a writer did like here,
here they are best to worse.
Finger was like way out from road trip.
Yeah.
He was, look, he was good in it.
And I thought that one was clever and played
with the small budget well.
I'll give you that.
All Hallows Eve.
I really liked all Hallows Eve.
It felt a lot like a story from another one of the
I think it's called Halloween.
Tales of Halloween.
Yeah, it wasn't but tales of Halloween.
I, it, for me, it was a little more,
it was a little higher quality than it.
It was a little more trick or treat to me.
Yeah.
But I liked all Hallows Eve.
I thought that was a fun one.
Man in the suitcase.
Terrible.
Weird.
That's one.
I've seen less it as a favorite.
I thought I was baffled by.
I have to.
I don't even understand.
It was, it was terrible.
And it, by the way, that doesn't feel like creep show.
And neither does keep going.
I'll point it out with the companion was the bully
with the scarecrow.
I love that one.
Oh, man, I didn't like it.
Really?
At the beginning, I'm like, oh, we're doing a little stand -by -me thing.
And then I'm like, he's sick to scarecrow.
Like, when they're telling the long history of the scarecrow,
I was just like, why would you tell the story?
I love, I really love that one.
Okay.
I thought that one was a lot of fun.
Lydia Lane's better have.
Harble was just a disaster.
That's the other one where I was like,
this doesn't even feel like creep show.
This feels like one of, you know, me and Pinkstone always laugh
about like the disappointment you would feel
when you waited all week for the New Tales from the Crypt.
And then the episode would start and you'd hear like,
sultry sex.
It would say based on a shock suspenser.
You're like, yeah.
God damn it.
Here's one about a wife that kills the husband
because he's rich.
And there's going to have a bunch of sex in it.
Like, I was like, I don't want to,
that's not what I'm here for.
I want to see like fucking monsters.
That Lydia Lane, I was like, this is a bad shock
suspense story.
Like, I don't care.
I would have been there for sex.
Especially at that age.
I mean, nobody hated boobs at that age.
But I'm just saying like, that's not what I was watching it for.
That Lydia Lane's was a real mess.
And right off the bat when it's like, okay,
this is the me too episode of creep show,
you get it.
You can almost see in the writer's room day one,
somebody writes on a card.
Me too puts every show does that.
But like, my God,
what a mishandling of it.
Like, just nothing work.
And it was like about how, really,
it was almost anti women in the end.
It was women, you know,
shitting on other women.
She gets her just desserts.
But anyway, night of the paw was.
That's the monkey's paw one.
The monkey's paw one.
Now Bruce Davison was
Emmy worthy in that episode.
Yeah, he's great.
And I probably, I probably, I wouldn't say
as if it wasn't a true complement
but he is a man, you know, recently,
recently he was in all the X -Men movie.
But he's also been an actor.
I just watched Ullzana's raid with Bert Lancaster
and like, he's 19 in it and he's awesome.
Bruce Davison is incredible.
And he would audition for all these parts
on cool kids no matter what came up.
Like, I guess he's just a guy who wants to work.
And he would always be so perfect.
But like, so the zodiac killer one,
he was so good that I was shaken to my core.
I couldn't laugh.
I was like, he's going to murder this one.
And every time I had to say I'm sorry about Bruce,
please tell him he did an amazing audition.
But what an actor.
And for him to sink his teeth into this,
you know, this is beneath him.
Let's be real.
My God, he was good in that part.
He's great.
And that episode starts awesome.
And then it's just by the end of this thing,
you're like, the woman is back in the morgue,
trying to raise her dead husband after so many times
because I was confused in a 20 -minute story
what was going on.
That can't happen.
Didn't make any sense.
It was so chilling when he goes,
when you realize his wish was for his wife to not be dead
and that she's fucking going to crawl out of the grave
because he didn't word it.
I was like, this is awesome.
And then he's like, and then she's like,
why am I here?
And he's like, because my third wish was for somebody murder,
to murder me for the awful sin I've committed.
This is fucking great.
And then all of a sudden, she throws the pawn,
the thing, and then he catches on.
I'm like, what the fuck is going on here?
You know what?
And who knows?
But this came from somebody either at a showrunner
or probably a network level being like,
I just wanted to be crazier at the end.
Or so you know, because they all just kind of take this turn
where you're like, what?
They were at, yeah.
For me, that one was the biggest slip up.
And they let Bruce Davidson down.
I mean, he gave it as all the fact that that was the one
where they're willing to go nudity
like you're looking at corpse bush at one point.
And I love the effects on the corpse.
I love when he like cut her teeth open
so that she could open her mouth.
There was cool stuff in it.
But that to me was the biggest mess.
You know, by the way, that that was the original name of bush.
Was corpse bush.
Yeah, the label said you have to drop corpse.
Trust me, you'll sell more record.
We already got cannibal corpse out on tour.
After that was, and I heard you mentioned it in the good ones.
And that stopped my heart.
But times as tough and musky hall are here.
When those heads are in the ground,
I was sickened at how pathetic that that story got.
That's why I said for maybe five.
That was a maybe five one.
Okay.
But I will tell you what I did like about it.
And at this point in the run,
I was pretty starved for some traditional creep show stuff.
Yeah.
The zombies looked exactly like the zombie father
in the very first creep show story in the original movie.
And I thought, okay,
they're getting back to this tone.
Like this is what I want.
Not an amazing story,
but good enough if it were surrounded by four great ones.
They go, oh, that one was fine.
I don't care.
Again, the guy playing the mayor gave it his all.
I have no idea why David Arquette,
not that he's in demand,
but why he would agree to play like the fourth lead in a creep show segment.
I think that's where he's at.
I think so.
We should have seen that fucking Sherlock Holmes and Burbank.
And it wasn't a comedy, right?
No, it was David Arquette, Sherlock Holmes.
Yeah, I didn't like that one.
And then we discussed six.
But six,
we discussed the the Loch Ness one,
but skin crawlers,
the Dana Gold one.
I have to amend my list now.
So I always had a list of the worst makeup
in the history of film.
So now my list goes third worst of all time,
end of beautiful mind when they age up,
Russell Crowe, Jennifer Connell.
Yeah, humiliating.
Yeah.
Second worst was used to be my number one,
J Edgar.
That's my that's my been my number one for mortifying.
Yeah, honestly, the same makeup used in nothing but trouble was used in J Edgar.
And now my number one is the fat suit
and makeup that they put on the woman
at the beginning of this episode.
Gould looks fine.
They fattened him up fine.
Yeah.
They they decided the only thing we'll do to make this woman obese
is give her a giant bullfrog neck.
And then they just take it away in the next scene
and she's a beautiful woman.
When she's sitting there at that table,
I could not believe that they put it on the air.
I couldn't believe it.
And here's the thing.
It's it's like this this to me just goes back to writing.
Why does it have to be 400 pounds to supermodel overnight?
Why can't it be this is a 250 pound woman
who struggled like Dana Gold's character was?
This is somebody who is not insanely obese.
It's somebody struggling with right weight.
And then when you see her again,
she's 190 pounds.
And maybe she still has a little extra on her.
But it's an impeccable or it's an incredible change that's occurred.
Yeah.
Why can't it just be that?
Because then you could get an attractive woman
who has a little bit of meat on her bones.
Right.
Be for up to what it looks like a believable fat.
And then the story works just so much better.
But they swing it from one side so hard to the other.
And it's like guys you don't have the budget to do this the right way.
And it happened in three days.
They said what you had it even worse.
So that one with the, you know, the goal of it was fun.
I watched it.
I like that one.
The goal was well done.
I watched that one with my mom.
My mom really liked that one.
That's always fun for me when my mom's into it with it with a hard thing.
So I became a monster.
It worked really well too.
You know, like when the the worms all gathered to become a monster
or whatever it is.
They're all puking up.
But like that's that one had a real issue with writing.
Because there is a million things to say about body image, weight loss,
fat diets, whatever.
And it says none of them.
You know, like if you nail the theme,
if you nail the story, people will forgive anything.
People will forgive terrible makeup, whatever.
Okay, they didn't have the money.
But what a cool fucking story.
But yeah, it just sort of ends like literally with Dana Gold looking at the camera
like, yeah, a big grin.
I guess.
Eating a candy bar.
And I guess that was supposed to be the moment where it's like,
just love yourself because the guy that didn't do the thing, yeah, ended up winning.
But I mean, again, from writing standpoint, it's like when he's got when the when the main
got the doctor that created this thing is going to die, yeah,
the whole thing of like when Dana Gold's character is going like, you don't care.
You just want to have the money.
It's like this person wouldn't say that.
It's very obvious this doctor didn't know that this was going to happen.
Right.
You would have some empathy.
So it's just like from a writing standpoint, have a moment where he goes,
okay, we're going to get out and then the guy explodes on your face or whatever.
It's like, that's better.
It's just, you know, so like I just don't get like, they have immediately run over and do the,
you move the headstones, but you didn't move the bottom.
Yeah, yeah, he does the same thing.
I also didn't buy the Dana Gold's character who was
deathly afraid of these worms and these parasites clearly had some sort of, you know,
I don't want to say a German.
It's not a German.
But you know, he had his, he had much harder boundaries than everybody else.
Right.
I don't believe he's going to pull a zag nut off the ground, covered in blood and
plus and take the wrapper off and eat it.
Man, either.
And that's one of those moments where you go, guys, you're going for this button here,
but it's, come on, man.
Like I'm pulling out of his pocket.
Survivor type, the Stephen King short story from Skeleton Crew was announced as being one of the
segments of the pilot episodes.
So it's maybe they shot it and it wasn't good.
I don't know.
Man, that story is awesome.
And we'll get it in season two.
Yeah, hopefully they, as I said, a joke before we started.
Hopefully they double the budget to $40 for season two.
Well, look, Twilight Zone season two is Greenlit and Crepe Show season two is Greenlit.
And I hope that in the second round,
they take a bit of a better swing and, and now the tone of these things a little bit better.
We'll see.
I don't know.
Did you, by any chance, go to Halloween Horror Nights because they did a maze -featuring
Father's Day, the crate, and they're creeping up on you as well as from the new series,
Grey Matter and Bad Wolf Down.
Now, and I'm really upset to hear that right now.
I'm sorry, I told you, but there it is on the Wikipedia.
You love to rub my nose in it.
Folks, that's Crepe Show.
I feel like that was a very long episode of the show.
When the hour 30.
We got to record another one.
So that's it for this week's episode.
Or this one doesn't, what does it even matter?
Patreon, you know what?
What is time?
I'm Joe DeRosa.
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Joe DeRosa comedian on Facebook.
Joe DeRosa info for all tour dates.
And what have you go by the new record?
I go to Atlanta all the time.
Now available for purchase digitally on iTunes and Amazon or wherever you can purchase
digital records.
And the hard copy, double album, double vinyl is either out or about to come out.
Released via my good buddy Vince Avril at capsule records.
Go to the capsule records website to get your copy
colored vinyl.
Very fancy.
And it's not streaming anywhere.
So you got to buy it.
Sorry.
Vince came over to watch the Oscars with me and gave me a test pressing of the vinyl that I have
not listened to yet, but I am excited.
Son of a bitch.
I just got it.
This is how the bootlegs get out into the streets.
I had to watch episodes of creep show.
Anywho, my name is Patrick Walsh.
The Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.