I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell. You thought last episode was us talking about a long,
sad movie? Well, you got nothing. That episode's got nothing on this one. Oppenheimer!
Hello everybody, Oppenheimer. Heard of it? Half of Barbenheimer. We already covered
the other half. Didn't we do Barbie? We did Barbie. Yeah, we did Barbie. We did Barbie.
It's time we finally get to Oppenheimer as it comes exploding onto Blu -ray and DVD.
I'll probably scoop up the 4k. We'll get there, we'll talk about it. It's probably
going to be our best picture winner. I think its main competition is probably the last one we
reviewed. It goes to the Flower Moon. I think those are the two probably front runners at
moment in time. We have a good friend in this film and that we promise will not affect our
review of it. I've hated so many David Krumholz movies. Krumholz was in the film, he's very,
very good in it. He's excellent in it. I hope they push him for the supporting actor award. I
thought he was excellent and fantastic in it. You see your friend one way when you're hanging out,
but then up in that 70mm IMAX pulling out the great character actor's viewer.
Yes. It's pretty cool, very exciting. Congratulations David if you still listen to the
show. Congrats my friend. I texted him while I was watching and I said, you are doing exactly
what you were put on this earth to do. Yes. And I meant that. Several people in the screening I
saw when David appeared on the screen yelled out, that's Rabbi Gill from CBS's Living Biblically.
Right. Followed by our second favorite character to the pilot's Gary.
Yeah, and I was like guys, shut the fuck up. That's a lot of things to say in a movie this
complicated. You stood up, folks this isn't about me tonight, all right. Let's please.
I would also as a little tantalizer for the upcoming season of the Miss Pat show, I got in
a Oppenheimer run between Miss Pat and her sister Denise about whether or not Oppenheimer had hoes.
And it's one of my favorite things I've ever written and I hope it doesn't get cut. And
the show, it won't. He definitely did, I think. He was like a known womanizer.
I mean, you see him bang. I did not expect going in. I was going to see Oppenheimer,
sloppenheimer, you know what I mean? Well, and also too, a big surprise with all,
I mean, it was in the news, so I knew it was coming, but like all of the Florence Poe nudity,
she really laid it all out. There was a lot of articles about like, you know,
the people's reaction to all of the flow pose, you know, full frontal, whatever the hell,
I don't know how they said it. This wasn't like Brian Williams we're talking.
It was no, it was Brian Gumbel. In the middle of a sports thing.
Whoa, whoa, breaking news. Bring it in tight.
Yeah, yeah, breaking news. And then about in my pants, something about that is underwear.
Come on. All right, we'll get to Oppenheimer. In the meantime, I've got a new psycho
that I would like to discuss. I sent this to Pat.
Uh, God, I've lost all track of time. But this was sent to you, I guess, probably just after
Thanksgiving. Well, no, it must have been after we last recorded. So it's probably early December,
or mid December, because I can't remember when we last recorded, but this was a headline I saw on
movieweb .com. Yeah.
And I said to you that this might be the most batshit entertainment headline I've ever read
in my life. Chicken Run 2 addresses the ageist recasting of Julia Salhala, or however you say
Salhala and Mel Gibson. What the fuck is going on?
One of the wildest headlines I've ever seen.
I mean, first of all, they're doing a Chicken Run 2 sequel 23 years later.
But the dear Lord.
Chicken Run sequel controversial due to ageism. I mean, I didn't have that on my 2024 bingo card.
Uh, Dawn of the Nugget. Dawn of the Nugget. Not with a gun to my head, folks.
What would I watch? Chicken Run 2 colon. Dawn of the Nugget. What? But Chicken Run was so great.
I saw it. I don't, I don't agree with you. I've moved on with my life. I don't need more Chicken
Runs. I'm closer to death than birth. I don't have time for the Chicken Run sequel.
They've recast the two leads with Zachary Levi and Tandy Newton.
Tandy Newton in Chicken Run 2.
All right.
I don't understand. It's a, it's claymation. Why don't you just put the other two people in it?
Since the, since -
Who was the other one? Tandy Newton and who?
Zachary Levi.
Zachary Levi. Is this, so this is not a comedy? What are you doing?
And I love this, man. I love this. This is, there's so much going on with this.
So, the original, I guess, uh, one of the main reasons, this is an excerpt from the article,
one of the main reasons that Chicken Run 2 was stuck in limbo for such a long time
is partly because the partnership -
Because the beaks kept hitting the pole.
Yeah. The partnership -
And they tried to go under it in the limbo line.
See, folks?
All right.
The partnership between Aardman Animations and DreamWorks Animation ended in 2006,
per Reuters, after the release of Flushed Away. I love it when it reads like a divorce paper,
you know, like the Flushed Way broke the camel's back.
Right. And what a title to go out on, Flushed Away.
Here's the best part, Pat, and you don't know this part, on the poster,
uh, it says at the top of the poster, this time they're breaking in,
is the first time, I guess, they had to break out of the coop, right?
Uh -huh.
They flew the coop.
Yeah.
Uh, it says this time they're breaking in, and then the main character is featured there,
now voiced by somebody else, and then under it, it says a Netflix film,
and under that, right above the title Chicken Run, Dawn of the Nugget, it says,
Aardman, as if anybody on earth.
It's so confusing, it doesn't say Aardman's Chicken Run, it just says Aardman.
Yeah.
Who the fuck sees that and goes, oh, all right, this is, this is good.
People, there are Aardman nerds, Joe. I haven't met many, but they are out there,
I bet if you listen to this podcast, I bet there are people who are going to comment
about how much they love the work of, what about Wallace and Gromit?
Fuck off.
Oh, that's, Aardman is Wallace and Gromit.
Oh, yeah.
Nobody likes Wallace and Gromit, but people do.
It's like people that like, uh, what's the, the old guy, Lake Winnihaka,
who's that guy? Lake, Lake Manitoba.
The what?
They did, Robert Altman did, Garrison Keeler.
Oh, okay.
You hear that people enjoy listening to that, but you can't imagine that that really happens.
I didn't, well, by the way, the quietest of any of me too,
because just like him as a celebrity to begin with, nobody, who the hell is watching?
Yeah.
Or listening.
I was watching Garrison.
I was watching.
Did you know that originally the ambiguously gay duo, the pitch from, I believe -
Robert Smigel.
I don't remember if Smigel, oh yeah, Smigel created it.
Yeah, you're right, I'm sorry.
Smigel, the pitch to Dana Carvey was, it's Wallace and Gromit except they're fucking each other.
And Dana Carvey was like, that's really funny, but we, it's too much.
We just have to make it two men, like Batman and Robin or something.
Right.
It can't be a dog.
Okay, yeah, that's funny.
I actually, I don't even know if I've ever seen anything Wallace and Gromit,
it's just that kind of animation makes me sad.
Although I do love, like, the California Raisins.
I'm not against all claymash.
No, but Wallace and Gromit is that, it's that shit that only English people think is funny.
It's like, you know -
Blackadder.
Yeah, you can hear the teacups clinking as you're watching it.
You're like, who is this for?
It's so just dry and oh god, it sucks.
It sucks.
Always on PBS.
PBS, like while I was waiting for Siskel and Ebert to come on on Saturday before mass,
sometimes we'd go to 5 p .m. Saturday mass and then go to Old Country Buffet.
And before Siskel and Ebert, I would just watch
shitty British sitcoms on PBS or I'd watch the end of like Red Dwarf or something.
Awful.
Not a laugh in sight.
Rowan Atkinson was in every one of them, Mr. Bean.
Yeah, you know, I'm rooting for -
I've rooted for Rowan for many years.
The guy's never -
His thing about the bit, the standup thing he did about where he welcomes you to hell
or whatever, that was pretty funny.
But like his movies and TV shows, I've never even cracked a smile, man.
He's got a sizable role in Wonka, so you can see him there.
Yeah, I remember I was on Craig Ferguson's radio show and I said,
do you like American sitcoms or English sitcoms better?
And he said, he almost scowled at me.
He was like, for Christ's sake, it's American.
And I was like, well, no, I don't know, man.
I think the English ones might be better.
And I rattled off like Peep Show, The Office, whatever.
And he was like, you've only seen the good one.
Don't you understand?
Like, go over there and watch TV.
And I was like, oh yeah, I guess you're right.
They had so many like friends type ripoffs that like you'd catch a few minutes of them
they would like try to outdo it and and only the vulgarity, but the writing would be horrible.
Like, did I hear you right?
Do you want to shag me, Fanny?
Like just that obnoxious.
That's like your that's your racial character.
So then imagine the character who comes in who's supposed to be
Chandler's girlfriend with the annoying voice.
Oh, God, like everything's just played at that like
10 plus level on British sitcoms usually.
Yes.
Actually, I mean, that's what they were spoofing on extras though.
Are you having a laugh with the wig on?
Like that's that's their sitcoms.
He took to quote to coin a British phrase.
He he or to turn a British phrase.
He he what's it called?
He took the piss.
Yes.
Out of British TV like like that whole thing with that.
And then the thing where he was like, I'm not doing a Doctor Who.
It's beneath me.
And then it cuts to him doing the Doctor Who.
And just the scene they did for Doctor Who.
And then him on the fucking the the like trap.
That show was so funny.
What was that called?
Where they're all trapped together.
The reality show he ends up doing like just the depiction of all of it.
It's very sad too.
Yeah.
I cried like a baby when he gives the like apology soliloquy to the to camera.
He's done so much good.
And then this latest special.
It's nice to be able to laugh about something he's done because this latest special was not it.
Yeah.
It's like guys you're supposed to be above this stuff.
Like him and then you watch the new Chappelle and it's like guys you've devoted hours now.
Hours.
We we look forward to what you have to say.
And it just keeps going back to these same wells almost doing the same jokes.
Yeah Gervais is really and I'm a fan but he's really caught on that like woke.
Like I'm woke now and I'm it's like dude you you you've made fun of this for like
least three hours like like dude go back to like this shit is so funny when he's doing like the like
Hitler read this book and then thought it was about gave him the idea of the holocaust and
he does the act out of Hitler talking to the guy that wrote it and he's like I read between the
lines like it's so creative and it's so funny and it's edgy and it's like just be edgy without
saying I am edgy.
Like you don't have to say you're edgy.
Yeah.
There's like really funny shit in the new Dave special but then it it keeps getting couched in
I'm being edgy and you're like right you don't need to tell us that just just just just like
yeah like just do the thing you know like in a special that like you know I was disappointed
when I saw it was going to be 54 minutes or something then there's three minutes at the top
where we're acting like it's the return of Jesus Christ then they go into the special
and it's like everything is a seven minute story with like a bait and switch punchline at the end
so I I sort of just there are there is funny stuff in it but like you're not even getting
a lot of content you know in terms of like punchlines even it's just like everything is
kind of this I don't know it's like they want to do one a year but you might not have the material
sometimes and just because Netflix is paying you 30 million dollars I felt like the old
I don't want to say the old versus the new Dave whatever but like I don't mean like I'm very
very I've known him for a long time and I can't sit here and go we're friends he's a global
megastar but we're very friendly yeah and well he's you know and a massively funny man yes and
he and he is and I just feel like there's another version of himself that would have done that same
special with the same punchlines where it would have just the setups would have been a little bit
different and there wouldn't have been this constant wink to camera like now I'm gonna make
fun of crippled people right because I'm being a dick like or whatever it's like it's like
you don't have to be that's I don't know I don't know if I'm phrasing it right but
I just felt like you can you can say outrageous stuff if it's genuinely funny you don't have to
it all up though as I'm about to say outrageous stuff see and you're like yeah but who cares like
we know you can do it we know you're allowed to do it yeah like like who are you saying fuck you
too everybody that hates you isn't going to watch this now anyway you know right it's going to be
the number one show this week no matter what you do or say everyone will watch it you have the
public's ear like talk talk about something meaningful Burr's movie was like that where I
like we're doing 90 minutes here on on woke people suck and it's like right yeah okay
like you're you're one of the most prolific funniest comedians that's ever lived like yeah
there's not there's not a little this can't be couched in something a little more masking you
know what I mean like or whatever so it's weird it's a weird time of like very weird on your
from all from all sides by the way you know but of course I know I go I know I go fairly hard at
the at the at the more bleeding hard side of things so so I want to show the our listening
audience that I also criticize the other side too you know but it's weird it's just a weird
time anyway I've got no follow -through with this it's the weirdest time hard for me with comedy
you see the you know it's like I try to be honest on the show but I also get it's like how you get
nervous sometimes I'll bring up a tv show I hate you're like why I know the creator right right
yeah so anyway uh let's hit that corner yeah hit that corner I saw a documentary I'd love to
recommend on HBO Max called last stop Larima colon murder down under very very entertaining
documentary that could have easily been stretched to one of these 10 -hour jobs and then I probably
never would have watched it they wisely keep it a tight two hours they tell the whole story
it's a fascinating story it's a town in the Australian outback it has 11 crazy
neighbors who live in this town like one of the smallest towns on earth
and one of the 11 people that live there gets murdered okay so it's like a real life Agatha
Christie basically and they have extensive interviews with the guy who got murdered they
have extensive interviews with everybody in the town and they have them all theorizing and
you learn that like these 11 people just have grown to hate each other over time they had a
lot of fun drinking at the they drank every day and every night at this local bar for a long time
and everything just over time went sour between them so all kinds of twists and turns they pack
a lot into a two -hour story I've actually have really been enjoying the Duplass brothers as
documentary producers they do a good job with their documentaries I like them
and this one is no exception it's really interesting and it's got some great great
characters obviously real life people but check it out well the reason I knew the
the story of Wallace and Gromit the ambiguously gay duo being Wallace and Gromit is because I
watched too funny to fail speaking of documentaries you've reviewed this I think already but it's the
documentary about the Dana Carvey show yeah I loved it I loved it I thought it was great
uh just a quick recap Robert Smigel and Dana Carvey Dana Carvey was the hottest thing on planet
physically I mean uh he was the hottest thing when he was leaving Saturday Night Live he says at the
top of the thing he goes I had too much heat on me it wasn't good yeah and um he he talks about uh
he he now yeah everybody wants to see what he's going to do next he had been the longest running
player on SNL everybody had eyes on him he chose to do a primetime sketch show that was going to
be very edgy and offbeat and different because he wanted to follow in the footsteps of
speaking of English television Monty Python uh Robert Smigel was his main man
Smigel brought in Louis CK as the head writer they hired uh as their main cast members uh uh
amongst a few others and uh this was it they had they had dynamite albeit unknown forces at the
time but but like unstoppable comedic forces and it didn't work uh it was too edgy it was too weird
people wanted Dana Carvey to do his characters from the show he wasn't doing any of them he
wanted to do something it's the classic I want to do something different right and uh and people
say no um but it's a great documentary it's very funny and speaking of it I mean they had that had
the all -star bench writer staff like just legendary Charlie Kaufman came from there oh yeah Jesus
so uh yeah they're they're all really funny guys it's Colbert and Correll and all of them have
commentary on it too and you know it's interesting because Smigel sees the show as it like pains him
that he just sees it as a failure he also talks about it when he finally what their lead -in was
home improvement he talks about when he finally watched home improvement and saw that it wasn't
like an edgy sitcom that it was like a very family thing he felt horrified at what they were hoisting
their show onto the public like he actually felt bad about it it's a very very interesting um show
and everybody is so funny in it and and it's heart the heartbreaking to me speaking of guys that
have an ability to be funnier than they allow themselves to be Stephen Colbert it's like you
you forget this is one of the funniest fucking guys that's ever lived yeah all he fucking does
is this hackneyed trump shit every fucking night nine after ad nauseam
i know and it's just it's the other side of what we're talking about with the gervais thing it's
like dude come on you're funny like do stuff man so he's a tragedy i knew when he when he took that
gig i was like oh boy i mean although he could he could have kept his edge not like Letterman
didn't have an edge for a long long time not even edge just be funny just like stop my dad's always
sending me clips of his monologue where he's talking about his relationship with god you know
with without jokes i'm like come on a come on dad but b come on colbert he's super catholic
he's like super catholic yeah which is odd that's one of those weird things you find out that about
a celebrity sometime who's very big and you know there are certain people slip to the cracks like
colbert doesn't get chastised for being catholic or christian whatever he is
right despite the church's views on many things that hollywood would have a problem with
walberg skirts by walberg gals kelsey grammer an outspoken republican he just got they think
they the publicist cut him off he just said in an interview that he still supported trump and
immediately the public was like we have to go it's like who cares like that's gonna stop somebody
watching frazier um so anyway um but the documentary is very entertaining it's very funny
and it makes you really above all things uh root not that we're not rooting for dana carvey
but really truly like re understand his talent yeah and just the force that that guy is and
and and hope that he get because i feel like that show prevented him from getting that was it that
was kind of like he did that show that was back when if you had a bomb you had a fucking bomb
it's like the chris elliot thing with cabin right they were like sorry dude you're done
and not that dana carvey was done but he certainly was not dana carvey after that
to the to the extent that he deserved to be and i movie career like i don't know if it was agent
or what the issue was but i mean opportunity knocks is such a bad starring vehicle for him
clean slate terrible starring vehicle for him you got road to wellville which is just a
insane movie and an insane role for him to take trapped in paradise sucked but maybe the best of
those trapped in paradise should have been good and it's just not it's just not um anyway and
of disguise for christ's sake i mean all uh all well wishes too to dana carvey with his son
absolutely that's terrible uh you know i hope i hope to see that guy well he actually talks
quite triumphantly uh at the end of it that he the the show failing led him back to stand up
and he says it's it's where i'm happy i get to create and it's been quite lucrative so i'm sure
career -wise he's fine but yeah that's true but i would love to see that guy on screen a little
bit more again in stuff uh you know but maybe it's his choice not to be i don't know but
anyway wayne's world hit and it's like it what's weird is that you could you even imagine
a movie with the characters and wigs like that being made and released today like
that the fact that we all just took it seriously they keep teasing wayne's world three
and as just as he keeps teasing ralston powers four i would go see both in a heartbeat of course
and uh but you know then it's a bummer because you find out like carvey and meyers
that had a problem and right you know and then they now they're kind of cool and then
i don't know man anyway from everything i gather meyers was largely an asshole
and i think he has been humbled and become better and i think he has acknowledged those
mistakes and blah blah also i heard that in wayne's world too and this was in like an oral
history of wayne's world or something but it was from the sources on the set was that a lot of
what mike meyers had written for dana carvey would be like dana does something funny here
and dana was like well if that if we're just going to keep having me do something funny here
then i'd like writing credit on the movie and like things just started going sideways which i get
yeah i get it all i have i have a lot of friends who act in commercials and they show up and it's
like uh well improv and they improv they don't get the job but their improv winds up in the commercial
like stuff goes on shit i uh i i heard that story quite early on and anytime after that if i went
into a commercial and they auditioned and they said we want you to i said i would go nope yeah
leave and then i would start yeah i'd start telling my commercial agent if they were going
to ask me to improv up it's a pass and that's it like they're they're they're it's gross anyway
for sure watch too funny to fail it's a very entertaining and overall quite funny and uh and
more uplifting than not documentary it's quite beautiful uh uh so it's good stuff
i saw on a plane are you there god it's me margaret
um when i was a boy i read i loved uh ralph s mouse Beverly Cleary you ever read those joe
no when you were a little boy all right i mean to ask me you're much older than two men in their
40s the guy just leans into the camera have you ever read ralph s mouse i i honestly i'm not
familiar with it i don't know what it is all right well it's Beverly Cleary uh and she did
book and they were adapted into like after school specials and they had i think Fred Savage might
have been in one of them or my boy all right um anyway they were great books they led me to older
stuff and then judy bloom judy bloom did super fudge you ever read those my guess is no uh i
think i may or may not have when i was young i don't honestly i don't quite remember but uh i
know super fudge and you know Ramona Ramona the pest i didn't read it but i'm familiar i was a fan
those were Beverly Cleary anyway jude brought a lot of like scary i was into the scary stories
books and and like yeah freaky stuff anyway go ahead judy bloom had this book called forever that
my mom put on the top shelf so i knew it was dirty and i used to take that down and and spank it to
the pages of judy bloom's forever very tame sex scenes in a book that's how bad we had it back
then all right um but i really enjoyed when i was a kid are you there got it to me margaret except
its depiction of a period was always very troubling to me it remains a little troubling
to this day no it doesn't um but you know it was about puberty from a girl's point of view and it
was fascinating to me because i i think when i read it i probably hadn't even gone through puberty
so the movie captures that and it's i don't know i thought it was fantastic james l brooks produced
it um it's rachel mccadams it's kathy bates both of them in particular were great um and
it's the book just like adapted beautifully it's a girl maturing going through puberty her friends
kind of walking her walking through it with her they're all kind of competing to get their periods
that kind of stuff there are very funny moments in it it never feels creepy which i was sort of
concerned about watching it on a plane but i kept hearing how good it was um it was just really
entertaining i think the the the male puberty story has been told on screen a billion times
so it was just very refreshing and cool and i thought that i think either mccadams or bates
might pull off a nomination because they were both very very good in the movie excuse me all right
i said i had two more christmas ones for this episode i do uh the uh
excuse me i watched a movie called oh boy i put this on as a like a almost as a joke
yeah on christmas night and it drew me in uh not in a good way but i watched a movie called
dashing through the snow
a disney original starring who else who else besides ludicrous okay not what i would have
guessed but all right i love how some like i actually love the music of ludicrous and i
think he can be effective as an actor at times but um he and he's a great live performer too but
why does it not matter that ludicrous has released all this music with extremely explicit lyrics
when he's going to be in disney channel movie why does somebody's past matter
hugely in one instance and not at all in another uh well it's he's been explicit but i don't know
that he has been he's talking about pussy splashing like i don't think he said anything
hateful i don't think he's been like i'll beat a woman or something like that you know what i mean
like true but you know who has ice cube who was in a lot of these family movies for a long time
ice cube is is is the is the literally the american dream if you had to be like yeah here's
the american dream like it's ice cube the uh ice cube is is a is a great story uh because yeah he
he he he's got some crazier stuff with nwa when he's younger but it's not as crazy as they got
without him they go like he said about the second nwa album he's like they went to places i wouldn't
have gone to had i been on the album like i was like wow that's that's heavy but um
dr dre is a great example you know like you know but uh but anyway um uh dashing in the snow is a
movie where uh ludicrous plays a uh suicide negotiator chorus christmas film where he talks
men down from ledges who hates christmas uh because when he was a kid a guy he thought
was santa claus came to his house not to drop off gifts but to rob his house so he hates christmas
his daughter loves christmas he and his wife are temporarily separated he's trying to heal the
family uh he has a night to spend with his daughter and on during this night he encounters who the
santa claus played by little rel howary um this movie is god awful little rel by the way an
acquaintance of mine who turned down my film uh yeah i this movie is so fucking bad i mean even
by kids movie standards it's terrible uh and the most of it's it's it's it's it's it's a goose
chase film uh because santa uses an ipad that that's how he has his naughty and nice list
by the way i guess it's christmas eve because he's
because santa's going into houses and dropping off gifts but then the mom of the little girl is
like out shopping for the evening and the dads with the kid it's just so poorly fucking executed
the whole thing doesn't make any sense uh disney plus movie or a disney channel movie i saw it on
disney plus i don't i couldn't tell you though it feels like a disney channel movie but i can't
that these guys would have done a disney channel movie but um they uh anyway um it turns into a
a chase caper because santa claus who uses an ipad for his naughty and nice list gets his ipad
mixed up with the ipad of a corrupt politician uh and the corrupt politician needs to get his ipad
because it will send him to jail it's got files on it or something sure uh when santa claus
is in the house of the this is what i mean with just god damn it guys just write something that
makes sense why does santa claus encounter the corrupt politician to begin with because he's in
his home leaving gifts when he suspects that the corrupt politician might be corrupt when he gets
caught by him in the house santa then beats him and his cohorts up i'm like what the fuck is
going on like santa claus is beating people up he's got a naughty and nice list he doesn't know
that this guy's no good like what the fuck is happening right now i don't know this doesn't
make any sense like right you had some nuts anyway in the mix up of course santa claus takes
that guy's ipad by accident and uh hilarity is supposed to ensue it doesn't uh
we get a cameo from kevin connolly in this you mean e from entourage e pops up uh
wow there's a scene always an electric presence on screen there's a scene in this
there's a scene in this where it is supposed to be snowing yeah and dude when i tell you
they they use like an iphone app effect for snow these people there's there it's a 10 minute
sequence multiple characters are standing out in the snow yeah and not one piece of snow is
sticking to their clothing or anything it is so clearly fake i mean the no by the way is not
that hard or expensive to produce i've done it multiple times it's it's easy the cheapness of
this thing is so crazy yeah uh so i'm like this is insane this movie what fucking rookie wrote
this piece of shit pat yeah it's the guy that wrote things to do in denver when you're dead
high fidelity uh uh steve pink gone in 60 seconds okay uh yeah two of the jumanji sequels
yeah he's writing the dirty dozen remake it's not uh what's his name hold on not that's uh
scott rosenberg scott rosenberg yeah i don't know beautiful girls which is a great movie yes
yeah i don't know what's going on anymore like i'm like is this guy just mailing it in because he
wants to check and he's had enough or is this just been butchered by the by the studio like i i i
it's just there's no way anybody looks at this project and goes i need to be a part of that
that's worth a year and a half of my life money money but but how much everybody in this thing is
it is accomplished and has money like that's what i don't understand it's not like nobody is a
newcomer nobody is look i would leap to be in a movie like this why because it would be a huge
payday for somebody like me because i'm not in a lot of movies and tv shows right but uh you know
tim story directed this uh he just did the blackening he did the he directed the tom and
jerry movie he directed shaft he directed ride along he did ride along too he please don't quote
the tom and jerry movie amongst his accomplishments i'm just saying i'm just saying this guy he directed
both fantastic four movies he directed barbershop i'm just saying this guy has directed major box
hits like he nobody involved in this needs the money nobody unless they've squandered their money
uh i just don't get it man i just don't get it like and it takes me back to this place
is this is this the goal is this the goal to work at any just to not ever have to get a real job
ever again to just keep doing and i've cited it before i'll cite it again
look i've met the guy he seems nice enough i but i have no allegiance to him is this the goal to
become ken jong on the mask singer in a michael jackson glitter coat pumping your fist going you
girl is this the goal at all costs to not just go oh fuck it man i'll go work at staples i just i
i thought the goal was to create things that you believed in at least sort of at least i think
at a certain point it becomes i just want to provide for my family the money is great the
money is crazy the job is easy and a lot of people do it i get it it leads to a much
less stressful life you have to decide what your priorities are i don't know i guess yes
family changes things but i mean again pet these aren't people who aren't working yeah sure ken
jong is in a zillion things true it like you made the joke about keegan earlier it's like
or in the last episode it's like it's not that people aren't working it's like look
camille is a guy i've known for many years i don't mean this as a shot but for christ's
sakes camille doesn't need to do a tide commercial mark walberg doesn't need to do
a fucking at &t commercial it's like i get it get it while the getting's good but my god almighty
like it's like i just i don't understand i just don't understand keegan was in wonka by the way
forgot to mention i always like to give a shout out when keegan's on board in a fat suit by the
way uh i got that's okay again i guess after the whale yes so wasn't when i tried to pitch a movie
a few years ago anyway dashing through the snow yeah i think i'll miss that one um and then what
did i see joe i i've seen most of the big oscar movies i saw i'll go through the rest of them on
the movie corner but i did ferrari michael man's ferrari uh which i saw in the theater christmas
day like christmas morning had nothing going on why would i uh the movie is very dull michael man
for a while was the best last the mohegan's heat that whole run i love collateral um man hunter
you know i could go on the insider for christ's sake i fucking love the insider beyond that it's
been kind of miss and miss you know not a lot of great stuff i hate to say it i would be excited
about a heat too but seeing adam driver gangster squad oh what was that no public enemies public
enemies i did not like public enemies it sucked man it fucking sucked it did and to be real michael
man is a guy who people will never get off his dick like to a lot of people he'll never make a bad
movie he can't the i like miami vice i think it got a bad rep but the people who who passionately
go to bat for it now it's like guys calm down a little bit all right like you know he shot that
thing on like a lake click camera from walgreens it shows um you know collateral i think he got
better at that sort of format but this movie the story just doesn't work i don't like adam driver
as an italian he's been defending all week that he's played two italians in a row it is a little
weird um i don't care about the ferrari guy i loved ford versus ferrari because they found
an interesting story in there this story is essentially a standard biopic here's here's
the description um a biopic of enzo ferrari whose family redefined the idea of the high -powered
italian sports car and practically spawned the concept of formula one racing
okay should have known that's just not anything i give a shit about um and it's kind of like that
tucker the man in his dream thing like a guy building a car and perfecting a car is of no
interest to me personally adam driver i thought stunk frankly i thought he was better in house
of gucci uh panellope cruz fine i thought she was better if she was in house of gucci
oh yeah oh yeah well this is why i scoff at that not because she can't pass as italian
she cannot cut through that spanish accent with a gun to her head she doesn't even try to joe she
doesn't even try to um i can't say salma hayek is like a texan or something i know i know yeah
all right then you got shaleen woodley in the mix doing some third weird accent out of nowhere
as really bugs me me too joe and i've heard here's just some bad hollywood gossip that
that everyone seems to know apparently she refuses deodorant as does patinson
they're just two people walking around stinking i would say having love scenes and everything
i was going to say this about shaleen woodley i wasn't going to say it but now i will say
she's got a look where i'm like she looks like her breath is sour to me she's she's got a look
where i'm like she just looks and look i bet she doesn't brush her teeth now it's potentially
confirmed all right yeah uh yeah she looks miserable to me she just doesn't seem like to
be an enjoyable person but that's i'm being judgmental of whatever i realize i'm sorry
it's all good the uh the heart of the movie really is this love triangle between adam
driver as ferrari panel de cruz as his wife and shaleen woodley as his mistress it's not
interesting at all you don't really like or care about any of these people or at least i didn't
and as i said the story of the car is just not that great so you're like okay what do we got we
one or two of the racing scenes yes are awesome is that worth it to you i don't know check it out
if you want i didn't even see black hat did you see that one joe no god i didn't i couldn't
yeah i mean to me he's fallen off then he did the tokyo vice show with ansel elgort and i'm just
kind of i'm willing to say all right the guy's past his prime you know but the people who still
like everything he comes out with his heat are insane i think it's just not a very good movie
uh my final is uh i reached the end of the first season of frazier and the finale
was a christmas episode the christmas episodes of the original frazier were some of the best
episodes and in my opinion they did christmas episodes better than any sitcom has ever done
they're up there with the you know people love the rosanne halloween episodes to me the the
frazier christmas episodes are are you know top tier um and the episode was actually pretty good
it was it was it was a very disappointing season uh you know for reasons i've already stated but
this one captured the farcical nature of frazier it was a plot they did on friends already so i was
a little disappointed that it was a rehash of a thing i've seen already but the plot was he throws
a last -minute christmas he doesn't want to throw a christmas party because he's depressed about
his dad being gone and it doesn't seem right they bring back some of the decorations that the dad
had so there's a little bit of john uh uh for god's sakes mahoney in there um
and then the plot is is that frazier then at the last minute decides to throw a party he promises
to keep it small and of course he goes way over the top and it's a disaster uh meanwhile a smaller
party starts to gather across the hall from him and people sneak out of his party to go to the
farcical had some truly funny moments had some truly great frazier moments uh and then
raz shows up and that was great it was awesome seeing raz um and it was it was it was very very
endearing she shows up as his gift when he's very depressed made me cry uh i really really enjoyed
it and it gave me hope that see it sounds he said recently publicly i think we have a home
here for many many years so i guess they're already saying you're you're going to get another
season but it gave me hope that the next run might be a little more in vain with what we want
we'll see we'll see i'm a sucker to you know i hang in there with this shit so
right we'll see all right worth my time as of now i didn't plan on watching it
i think it's good enough that if you put it on you'd be like that's a
that's a very passable sitcom episode and it's not anything you know you're not going to be mad at
it you know uh and i think you might laugh here or there um it certainly captures what they're
trying to do for what we're trying to do for the season um but uh but anyway yeah uh i enjoyed it
um is that it is that the whole we got that's it let's talk about bobby
oppenheimer uh portrayed by killian murphy is that correct yes idiotic pronunciation i know
and i sort of wondered how he had stumbled into like being the star of a movie of this magnitude
and then i forgot i always forget about peaky blinders which everyone i know is obsessed with
i've never seen an episode so i don't i don't get it i've always kind of liked the guy he's also uh
he's also nolan camp dude he's he's one of the nolan guys and he's the scarecrow right right
nolan's at a level now where he can be like he's he's like tarantino he's like i'm this is my guy
he's starring in it and that's right yeah that's true that's true uh i'll say right out of the gate
i loved oppenheimer uh i thought i wasn't going to be that into it uh because of the length
i did think it could be a little shorter i didn't think it needed to be three plus hours
but uh the length of it i found intimidating and the subject matter i thought was not going to
pull me in uh and i also knew it was going to be a very talky film but lo and behold
it pulled me in in the way a lot of those movies you mentioned from michael man
particularly the insider did yeah uh in the way that a lot of the david mammet movies have
pulled me in uh you know like like there's something about a movie where if you do it right
with like these sort of square -jawed men uh of a different era talking shop and taking crazy
chances and some of them doing terrible things um it it i find it riveting uh and i thought that
this was a riveting film uh in that sense but also just the the horror of it and and the way
and the way that the horror was depicted and the way it was no one really can direct his
ass off man he's you know there's always that that that turn of phrase of of uh
so and so is the next spielberg nolan is the next spielberg i think like the guy can shoot the shit
out of a movie i mean it's wild like yeah he's he's great you know he's extremely talented i saw
openheimer for the first time on standard imax and then i saw it 70 millimeter imax a second
time and i'm very glad i saw it a second time the first i was kind of checked out uh when it
started in college i was getting like boring beautiful mind biopic vibes and i just never
kind of sometimes i'm just in a funk with with a movie to be honest with you um seeing it again
a you really and there's i think there's still time because it's still playing in los angeles
that was a theater movie for sure like i get why it was so important to him that everybody
see that one in the theater sound was incredible you know like rad even in the theater without the
ass rattling seats the seats were a rattling um and i think because it was nolan i was expecting
some sort of action fest the first time i saw it then i realized oh this is a movie like a jfk
like uh the insider or something where it's just kind of like you said joe guys in suits
wearing suspenders black ties horn rim glasses um discussing things yeah and drinking in every
scene right yeah smoking in every scene yeah it's madman shit yeah but everybody was really great
in it that way i think we've made fun of jason clark on here before but he's kind of the head
interrogator in this one and he was also in that cane mutiny court marshal and i'm starting to
love him as a as the character actor he was always meant to be they tried to elevate him to
movie star for a while and he's not that charismatic but he's really good in a supportive role
he's great in this the guy at the end of the table the lead from walking dead uh in the
interrogation i think that's the guy that's the original guy from walking dead isn't it uh whom
uh hold on i know we got macon blair in there who i like from several indy films and green room of
course uh walking isn't andrew lincoln the guy sitting at the end of the table yeah i thought
oh well i know he's in walking dead i don't know if andrew lincoln is the guy at the end of the
table because i never watched the walking down well let me see here uh andrew lincoln most
importantly we got a david krumholz nope that's not him who the hell is sitting at the end of
the damn table uh uh yeah let's it's a massive cast it's it's tons of great character actors
um and as i was complaining about our lack of great character actors on recent episodes in favor
of pretty boys uh here nolan is finding a lot of great character actors and reminding me
and hollywood itself that they are out there and um bringing up some up -and -comers jack quaid
i don't i haven't seen the boys so he's kind of new to me i liked him i hung out with jack quaid
in new york he was very cool and we had a lot of fun and it was fun seeing him in this
yeah josh peck i mean how cool is it that kid was like a nickelodeon kid yeah he's a good actor
we got emily blunt we got great we got puke great by the way uh d speaking of actors that
downey jr it's always been great character actors that they tried to elevate and now
putting them in character roles dane dehaan or whatever he's fucking great alden erenreich
he's fucking great matthew moe dean yeah he's fucking great tony goldwyn was who i was thinking
of tony goldwyn yes from ghost back um he's the guy at the end of the table in the interrogation
i believe so um and then of course our boy davey davey crumbs uh you know everybody i mean it's
such a strong cast i loved we didn't even mention matt damon matt damon by the way josh hartnett
hartnett coming out of the shadows yeah i'm watching it and i'm going
i know this guy from somewhere who is this guy and i'm like jesus christ it's josh hartnett
kc afleck coming back out of the shadows i love i love too that he played a lot of these
uh supporting roles against type i love that he's got damon playing a hard boiled brick
i love that he's got josh hartnett playing a brainiac i love that he's got afleck uh playing
like a straight you know what i mean like by the numbers cold military man like yeah he really
played these guys against what you expected a lot of them to be rami malek swinging in for like
one scene yeah you know uh yeah that's i think that's what kind of gave me that that oliver
stone early 90s prime feel like a nixon jfk kind of feel because it was covering a it's a three
hour movie covering a huge incident in american history and then the fact that you have just all
these incredible actors right down to the smallest part because no one can kind of get whoever he
wants um and that's kind of the fun of it to me i you know the second time when i realized that
like its action was going to be very restrained and it's not going to be fun action i got way
more into the story um i don't know why i don't know what i was anticipating i think just because
the way it was marketed they needed to make a certain amount of money on it obviously they
made a billion dollars on it so it worked but i just wasn't expecting kind of a quote standard
biopic but it's also just an excellent excellent biopic it's it's very beautifully crafted and
well done um and you get a real sense of the character through his relationships with women
and through his relationship with the scientists and friends and and you see how guilt -ridden he
is about what he's done and what he's creating and so you know it's a very kind of sad but epic
story and it's great do i think it's nolan's masterpiece no i don't but i do think it's a
great movie uh i liked uh i liked now now this movie posed what i was complaining that that um
killers of flower moon didn't pose for me this posed challenging questions where you know
is it more important that he did his duty for his country and uh versus what ethically was right
did he have any right to have remorse which is the great scene with jason clark where jason
clark screaming at him and saying you you had no second guessing when you built this thing and
whatever right uh uh is science a you an ultimately useful tool when it barrels because it's now
out of control and allowed man to to play god literally and create an extinction level event
um the there were just so many challenging moments in this and then also the fact that
you've got oppenheimer next to david's character isaac uh where it's like
you you have no question throughout the movie that that krumholtz is playing a very just man
right and the fact that he's standing next to oppenheimer who at times is is a prick at times
is arrogant at times is very selfish and then also is leading the charge of creating this bomb
you know has a lot of questionable qualities at questionable to say the least qualities yet here
his best friend is who stands by him through everything and is clearly a decent person it
was a very very interesting interesting take uh and my favorite scenes were and i'm not just saying
this because i know david my favorite scenes were the scenes with the two of them matched by the
scenes between alden and and i loved i thought robert downey jr in this was fucking awesome
and i loved seeing him not playing a smart ass and the scene was playing a superhero which it's
been a really long time the scenes with him and alden erenreich the sparring of that and then
the way that takes the turn and this is what i was saying again about killers of all the moon
the way that takes a turn where alden erenreich is like is like at his mercy at the beginning
and he's kowtowing to this guy and whatever and then at the end when he flips it on him
and is like fuck you i played you you thought you played me i fucking played you you're like
that you know that's there you go that's a story great yeah you know um yeah it's it's what a lot
of biopics forget to do it's finding the story in your event not just retelling it um and this
nolan nolan is great at that it's also you know we mentioned all these people obviously but it's a
great ensemble in that and it's again a testament to his directing but nobody varies from the tone
there's nobody coming in like doc brown like we gotta get the atomic bomb you know there's nobody
like gunning for the oscar everybody is excellent in it but also everybody is playing a very
controlled part of an ensemble and the movie is just put together beautifully you know like
he's a really great filmmaker probably yes i would say our new spielberg i didn't realize benny safty
was playing the uh the russian guy or whatever he also plays the dad and are you there god it's me
margaret i didn't even realize that was him god god's a great actor man jesus yeah yeah yeah he
is you always see good time you ever see good time no i've only the only thing i've seen by
them is uncut gems oh watch good time tonight put it on your list i don't know about tonight but
and by the way the most stunning turn of acting in the entire thing and when i realized it was
him my jaw was on the ground gary oldman as truman i'm watching this thing and i'm like who the
is playing president truman this guy is great and then i look at him like jesus christ like
why old oldman's always ready to slap on a wig and some prosthetics he'll he'll be down there
in five minutes if you need him and like can change his voice in ways like where i'm like
at a daniel day lewis level of like i can i can do any voice you need me to do right
he should have played the wife in ferrari
when's goldman gonna play in italian would have been a lot more interesting that's for sure
folks we thank you for your time i am on instagram for the time being at the patrick walsh check out
the miss pat show which will return at some point in this year uh that's what i got joseph please
get your tickets for my shows at the grand mercy theater on january 13th the comedy mothership
january 19th and 20th and then uh onward to nashville la san diego a bunch of other places
in february and forward uh jodarosa .com come through and if you're in new york check out
joey roses joey roses .com we're open seven days a week serving sandwiches and drinks
we'll see you next time folks and we'll see you in hell