I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with Poker Icon Phil Helmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a Slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon.
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Welcome to we'll see you in hell.
The podcast you resort to when you need to figure out what's going on in that big bad
cinematic universe. Hollywood, indie films, television, YouTube, made for YouTube, all of it.
We cover all of it. There's already a lot of not even true things being said for things to have
just started on the show. I figured if somebody's listening for the first time, maybe we reel them in,
It's a bait and switch bait and switch all right. What is a bait? I mean
bait and switches you bait them with something and then switch it with something bad
Yeah, but it doesn't come from the fishing world unless it's a hook
Well, I think it's based on that meaning like the bait them with the delicious hotdog piece and then they get the hook
Yeah, all right fair enough mess with the bowl you get the horns
But now you said you resort to us, which already is slapping us in the face before we even
get started.
I thought it was a funny way to put it.
And then this cinematic universe, people are going to think it's some sort of marvel thing.
You also included YouTube videos as part of that cinematic universe.
YouTube does, we've reviewed stuff on YouTube, we reviewed Cobra Kai, that was on YouTube.
We talked about that in the movie corner, I don't think we'd, we 100 % talked about, we didn't do
an episode on it, but my friends, Duke Oberkai, yeah, we talked about it, we're gonna, you know,
we've definitely talked about made for streaming product, you know, but I mean, I got to be honest,
I wasn't expecting the questions afterwards, I just was kind of talking, I mean, I think I've
to let too much stuff slide on this podcast from you, frankly.
You're sick today?
You sound sick.
I don't feel well.
I felt kind of, since I wrapped on the job,
I had to do a little editing today,
and I'm officially done today.
But I was just holding onto a great deal of tension
and anger for too long.
And now it is over and I just feel
a lot of residual anger and tension
and I feel sick, and I feel very bored also.
And just sort of amazed at how boring life is,
when two weeks ago I would have given anything
to just not have to go into this job.
And then you're out, and I'm not happy there.
And I'm wondering if perhaps I'm cursed
to always be on that?
Is this a good start to the podcast?
I think that's the...
But I like how you thought YouTube might set the wrong tone for listeners.
I think this sets a very accurate tone, but I'm talking about it.
Yeah, it sounds like you're, I don't think you're destined to be unhappy, but it sounds
like you're unhappy.
And it sounds like you need to figure out why you're unhappy.
Yeah, but it doesn't ever really work for people.
They just lie and bear it.
you know, I went in to get a cold shake from this place or cold buster product. And there's a guy
there 55 or something sitting balls nearly out of his shorts scrolling through for two other
people there at this place. His dog's Instagram feed and the dog's there. They're not engaging with
the dog. He's just showing the pictures of the dog. And I couldn't tell these people were
going along for the ride if they were actually into it, but both are disgusting options.
And that's the problem with L .A. You can't tell. You'll never know. And I'll never know
if they really wanted to look at it and they were that vapid or if they were just faking
wanting to look at it because they're that phony. It's, it, I think it's always 50, 50.
and both options suck because you can never get a genuine moment out of anyone.
Especially when you're working in the entertainment business, when people are like,
hey, it'd be good to go to lunch to see you and you're like, great man, I haven't seen
you any year.
I'd love to sit down and then like, you're left but cheek hits the chair and they're like,
so I've just finished my new spec, yeah, yeah.
You know, but the conversations I was hearing up here,
like if you were watching LA story
or like a 90s satire of Hollywood,
a dated satire, this would have still seen more extreme.
You know, I just said, what do you have
that's like a cold buster and she goes,
well, cold buster sounds like you want a job of juice
and we don't serve anything with all that process sugar here.
I'm like, all right, that was really annoying,
but you work here and I get that you're trying
to sell me on a product.
I accept it, but then old dog Instagram starts chipping in and he's like us
You need to set him up with a lash curler shot lash curlers the way to go unless you want to spring for the golden silver
Then goes back to his dog. What is a lash curler? Well, I took a lash curler. She goes this is on the house
I go okay. Oh thanks. Thanks. You mean I could have some of the extract from the tree root for free. Oh my god
Thank you so much. So she goes, well, this is like the Kayan and the lemon and whatever and I go, oh, yeah
I just I just picked up this cleanse thing for you. I've done this before
It's like this is a little more intense. There's a reason they call it a lash curler. I'm like all right
I do this shot and then I became very panicked because I had 15 minutes till Joe got home from his
appointment and I was concerned I was gonna ship myself right there in the floor of
Of this health food store just from the one shot the second it went down
I was like that's coming out it's coming out and I can't control it
Well, I'm glad you waited till you got here to take care of it
I haven't even taken a sip of this thing. I you can see it. What's collecting on the bottom looks very
I mean you walked in here. I'm not trying to pull up your spot
But you walked in here you strike like our bungee style straight to the fucking look group
That's what happened. I still haven't touched this juice for fear of what's inside
But that thing looks nasty, dude. They look at all that sediment on the bottom, man. I see it. Yeah, that's fucked. I just felt like it was all
Lame and then she's asking me if I want CBD in it. Oh, good. And I'm like, you know what it's hard to get me off weed, but
Don't don't offer me a CBD at the juice place, you know
Make it feel like you have to answer one question correctly to get marijuana.
You know, just don't throw it in a juice.
I really can't. That's a new thing here and maybe it's everywhere.
Unfortunately, I'm only able to live in one solitary hell at a time.
So, I've only noticed it in Los Angeles, but that's like a thing here now, where like,
I went to get breakfast with Crystal, our friend Crystal the other day yesterday, and
we go to this place and I go, do you have, can I get a bagel?
First of all, it's one of these places you got to walk up order yourself, walk back to your
table with a fucking number on a metal thing.
Sure.
That's most restaurants here.
Yeah.
And then they bring it to you.
And they I still the audacity on the little screen when you're paying to put 25 % as
an option.
The first option.
And it's we're really on a wavelength because I did a lengthy rant about this yesterday.
But you're not talking about this.
They didn't offer you CBD at this breakfast place.
No, no, no, no CBD OJ or something because they do it at bars now.
they do it in like lattes and this but this was a bar I get to you're there to
get altered in some way this was a little weird but I got a breakfast yesterday
with our friend Matt Inga -Bratson the star and co -creator of corporate I think
more of the credit to Jake I don't think Matt did much the corporate just
Just wrapped a season two, I love those guys.
Good man.
Congrats.
And it's a really, really good, strong, well -made funny show on Comedy Central.
But, you know, I'm kind of a big timer.
I spring for the lunch and the guy flips the counter or the charge thing around and I went
on this with Matt for like seven minutes.
I was like, they do nothing for you.
They're gonna have the bus boy bring out the meal. He doesn't even leave his post. He barely said it good morning to us when we approached
Flips it over. It's like your options there. You want tip 50 percent?
45 % or 42 % or do you want to make this really embarrassing and hit other?
So you have to bring up a new thing and then say oh, I'm a cheap asshole. Yeah, and it's like
It's crazy. It's crazy. Yeah, I always just hit it. I'm like yeah, take your 20 %
I tip 20 % regardless, but at some of these places, they're pushing you and I'm not trying to be, you know, Mr. Pink here
But there's a real difference between you like coordinating my dining experience and
tapping off my water eight times and et cetera and you
Snapping at someone who doesn't speak English to bring me my meal and then hopefully
Sharing that tip with them, but probably not yeah, no, I know I
It's gross. I don't I don't care for it. It's it's this this meet me halfway bullshit
Did the lady at this place yesterday I
Go so can I have a toasted bag old she goes yep, and I go she goes what kind would you like? Can I go?
You got blueberry no
Okay, send him in raisin no this is literally how she's answering me. I
I'd enjoy our goji barriers.
Yeah, and I go, okay, I guess I'll have a plane.
And she goes, okay, and I got cream cheese.
I go, yes, please, I go, do you have jelly?
She goes, yep, and I go, do you have grape?
Nope, and she's smiling.
Like, tough shit, you're not in Kansas anymore, Dorothy.
This is an L .A. shit hole you're in.
I would have walked out.
Why does she not have to, at some point, say, we do have this.
Yes. She goes, she goes, well then she goes, she goes, we have raspberry and I go, do
me a favor. Take it real easy with that raspberry jelly. She goes, it's on the side. Fucking
bagel comes out. Thing is closed sandwich style. Guy for, no jelly. Again, some other guy
from another place. I don't even think he worked there when he brought the food out. It was
just some man that carried it to my table. Yeah. I had to ask for the jelly. Not once did
Nobody gave us water, nobody offered it.
Yep.
It was fucking disgusting.
I mean, it's just like, and then we tipped 20%.
Of course you did.
At the counter standing there.
I'm fucking believable, man.
Well, it really makes the whole tipping system moot.
I mean, I've never gone to a restaurant
tipped less than 20%.
No.
But, you know, I don't find that if somebody is truly amazing,
I'm going to 40, you know, I might say I'm gonna tip extra. I just find that it's not fair to the people who suck. It's like when you go to Vegas, like, if you have a card dealer, blackjack dealer, who's like, hilarious and riffing with you and, hey, honey, I think he needs a drink over here and blah, blah, blah, helps you out, you know, I don't know, you sure you want to do that. The book says this, blah, blah.
Sometimes you want them to shut the fuck up, but if they're really helpful and funny and telling you about their life, asking about their life, whatever, you keep the tips rolling, especially if you're if you're winning, then come to find out they all split the tips.
So the asshole who I'm like, would you hit or stay on this is like, I don't know, man, do what you want to fucking do. That guy's getting the exact same cut as the lady who's, you know, going out of her way to bring a little joy to your life because you're on vacation.
Yeah, it's this it's the sick it's sick. It's a sick culture. We live in everybody's got to pick up the you know
We're gonna start getting into it's gonna it's gonna it's gonna start sounding sociopolitical in a minute
But I don't mean for it to but I'm just kind of tired of this
Everybody gets the even take kind of thing and it's like
You know, it's like even when a waiter or waitress is shitty in a full service restaurant
I tip 20 % because I know how hard that job is,
and I know also maybe she's just having a bad day
or maybe he's sick or whatever the fuck it is,
I still tip 20 % because I have a heart and sympathy
and some empathy having done the job before,
but this shit now where people saw
that that was the standard for any weight staff
and then applied it to a counter person.
Yeah.
Well, what's the difference?
you tip them. Why can't you tip me? It's you're not fucking doing anything.
Yeah, your job is no different than the guy at the gap or the guy at Wetzel's pretzels or whatever
else you're doing, which is fine, but those people don't get tips either. It's fucking crazy.
It really does bring us back, I guess, to the very prophetic reservoir dogs, Steve Buschemi. But
everybody is just, it's just the amount of coddling in this culture anymore. My buddy was tell me last
That's nice.
I forget what coach it is, and I'm not a sports guy at all, but this coach is going
to let his team.
This is an NFL team.
NFL, the amount of money on the line is staggering, the amount of money these players make.
This guy's going to let his NFL players take phone breaks every 20 minutes because they
need to go to check their phones every 20 minutes.
They can't focus for long.
These are adult men, grown adult men that need to be granted phone breaks from their code.
He announced this at what an NFL press conference.
It was a news story, a sports story.
And the guy goes, that's what I do with my college team.
And it's like, more shame on you for doing it with the college team.
Well then, I guarantee these people are all getting pussy shots.
It's, you know, there are NFL athletes, the, the, it's all, I mean, people are sending
them pictures of, yeah, pics of their pussy and so forth, Instagram DMs and all that.
God bless.
I hope so.
So, like, you're out there, you're like, like, let's say I, I know it's not a great comparison,
but let's say I'm doing the, the tape night of a show, Friday night, the audience is there,
actors, the director everybody's running around. I'm in charge. I'm running the show.
Then I take a quick phone break and I see that four beautiful women have sent me pictures
of their pussy. I'm not going to be back on my A game when I return. And either are these
guys, they're like, boy, I wish I wasn't here in the hot sun. I wish I was enjoying that
pussy.
It's that. It's, it's texting with your boyfriend or your girlfriend. Okay. It's texting
with your kids, it's texting with your family, it's checking Amazon, it's going on eBay,
it's reading something on Twitter that a fan wrote that's going to piss you off.
It's just not staying focused.
You can't do that.
Dude, we're literally at a point where it's like, like a used at least be like athletes,
you could kind of clump into that sort of like military mindset of like, hey man, like
like focus, drive, sweat, bleed, do it.
Now even athletes are falling out of that.
Are we literally gonna be at a point in this society
where the only people that understand discipline
or people in the military, like that's it?
That's the only people left getting trained
with any sort of discipline for anything?
It's fucking crazy.
I think we're already there.
I mean, I thought the trade off to the $8 million payday
for your fucking running around with a football meant that you had to do some of this discipline.
Apparently, it's not the case. What you should be doing is googling how your concussions
gonna take place and then step off the field and perhaps run a nice mortgage loan company.
Yeah. How are you gonna do that fancy touchdown dance with a concussion? Or better yet,
Check out the documentary realism of a little film starring Will Smith called concussion
Where he said the immortal line
I'm the doctor now. What did he say? That's from Captain Philps
He said no, I'm the captain now is Captain Philips but Will Smith goes
God damn it. What's the line? He has the worst accident? I don't know the line, but this movie is where will he goes tell the truth
He's in a core room and we'll Smith with this accent that you know he thought was just killing it
He goes
Tell it to truth almost like Darby O 'Gill and the fucking little people Irish accent
Concussion if you haven't seen it is a movie about a vampire that goes into sports medicine
Nothing I was funny. I'm sorry. I was
As I am all day thrown by something that infuriated me sent to my text
Which is a sure sign that we should not allow these phone breaks. What did you say, John?
I said it for those of you haven't seen the movie concussions a movie about a vampire that goes into sports medicine. Yes, making for the truth
It sounds like I fucking like Eugene levy character. No, it's rough that movie
That's the one to where he was like I'm not going to the Oscars anymore. You didn't nominate me
Yeah, and his wife was all upset like you had a real legend here, and you blew it
that's like, you're his wife, Jada.
I guarantee my wife thinks I'm overlooked at the Emmys.
I, the rest of Hollywood does not.
You gotta shut your damn mouth.
Anyway, I love the Smiths.
I love their sham marriage, allegedly.
I think they seem like lovely, multi -multi -multi -millionaires.
And their kids seem like real treats.
Well, here's, here's the one dress is like Gandalf
and, uh, you know, the other one, I like that with my hair
sun. That was pretty catch. Uh, well, here's good news for me.
Will Smith's doing stand -up comedy now because there aren't
enough fucking people just jumping into this thing because
they think anybody can do it. It's not bad enough. I got to
compete with fucking stormy Daniels and every guy that was
ever in a sketch group that had three episodes on television.
But now Will Smith's doing it too. Well, look, if you had a
sketch group with three episodes on television, I would say
you have as much reason to get him to stand up as anyone. But how many times are you about
to go up and grab the mic? And they're like, oh, sorry, Joe, you're getting bumped by
stormy Daniels. Is she really messing you up? It's never. Obviously, even though you're
off Twitter, we know too much. Everyone today was upset about bagels. They said, I had the bagels
cut like we used to do it back in St. Louis. And the bagels were all cut like bread, like each
Bagel had like 14 slices in it and actually it's good for L .A. where everybody eats like a corner of a donut and moves on
It seemed kind of smart. I saw and it's still going on now in the 10 minutes. I looked at Twitter
50 ,000 tweets about this and they're all the same joke or some variation on this person should be in jail
I'm calling the police huge accounts. I'm calling the police this person should be in jail same joke every time and it's like guys
you'd never know that one guy sliced bagels long ways if you weren't obsessed with
this godless time suck of a website by the way I lived in St. Louis for 22 years
no one has ever cut a bagel in that manner it's just some guy who happened to
do it in his family and you don't need to know about it you don't need to comment
on it I agree with that move on with your life I agree with that and the only reason
in the Stormy Daniels thing, it's close to home for me is because I have seen first hand
John Merrick coming to New York clubs and bump comedians, so he can do time.
I've seen first hand him steal one of my tweets for beta.
Well, there you go.
Then freely admit to it via at DM.
Yeah.
Then leave it up.
I'm just, you know what?
Look, obviously I'm not worried that I've got a knock heads with Will Smith out on the circuit.
It just annoys me that people think it's this easy.
Like if you always did comedy and it was a thing you did and you did other stuff like a Scott Thompson from kids in the hall
Yeah, who's a hilarious stand -up and also a great sketch and sitcom actor. Yeah, that's different
That's not what I mean or you know, you were a comic that that that always or musician that always did comedy too
Whatever even like a Nick Cannon fine, but like these fucking people that are just like
like, yeah, I want to try it, man, I'm funny.
And it's like, you're not funny.
I have never seen Will Smith say a funny thing ever,
except once in a while on Fresh Prince of Bel Air.
But didn't, I don't even know the story.
But didn't Will Smith just say, you know,
it's always been a dream of mine to try stand up
and they let him do it.
Like Dave Chappelle coached him on it for a TV show
and he did it once and that was it.
Oh, was that it?
I mean, are you thinking it's gonna be 10 years down the line?
Who knows anywhere?
They're bumping you off a marquee.
Is it that crazy?
There was a time we could have sat on this couch and said,
yeah, what do you think he's gonna be president?
Yeah.
It happened.
Will Smith?
It's not in Trump, I mean.
It's not that crazy right now to think that 10 years for now.
In a country where that, where we've seen it all happen,
that Will Smith could be like something like the biggest
comic in the world.
It's not crazy at all.
I mean, that's why I get surprised anyone's even upset
about anything.
And I think that this constant like cattle prod shocking
of people like did you hear this, did you hear this,
did you hear this?
It's what makes this now time I have off
that should be a time of rejoicement.
It makes it feel empty and boring
because I'm like, what am I doing?
What am I doing?
I am heartbroken that you're sick
Because I'm going to Vegas. Well, this just comes out after I was already in Vegas, but I was hoping you were gonna make the trip
It doesn't sound like it. It's I mean it's still conceivable. It's gonna have some real dirty fun, you know
Just got loose. I mean, yeah, I'd have to wake up tomorrow feeling a lot better and not on the downward slide
But I'd be down to go is this Wednesday or Thursday
Today is Wednesday. Yeah, I can maybe get it together by Friday. Oh, I'm not ruling it out this air is on Monday though
So who knows, it doesn't matter at all.
I know.
You're in my plans for going for that.
I don't want to confuse new listeners.
You say these guys don't even know what tape is.
I'm not going to be like getting in the car to go with you
to Vegas and go shit.
We told the listeners I wasn't going.
No, no, no, that's not what I was saying.
All right, let's get on with the show
and at the same time, on with the,
oh, Joe, that was a sick one.
But I didn't actually call from the mic.
Take us down to the corner, would you?
Oh, I got my driver's license today.
Hey!
I went, I just finally went.
25 years behind.
I retook the test, finally, passed it.
That was a nerve -wracking test, man.
Jesus Christ.
Dude, I'll tell you what, if I didn't study up,
I would have failed it.
I remember taking the driving part.
And the driver instructor was just like 65,
like Walter Mathau type guy.
And he goes, and he goes, and he goes, and he goes, and he goes,
what?
So what because I don't know what you're saying it led to us pulling over and I said sir
Can you point or something because it's not clear to me what you're saying. So he starts going like this
Like that. I'm well you can't see what I'm doing
But like these real half -assed up in the air non -committal points and then I
Just assumed it was some sort of prank or something. I said did I do something wrong and he's like roll size and it's like make a right, sir
Okay, made a right, 16 years old.
Yeah.
I don't know how to talk.
I did mine.
I was the guy screamed at me the entire time and then we pulled him to the lot and he
goes, Joe, you passed by the skin of your teeth.
Nice.
I was like, that's a weird way to put it to somebody you're about to send out into traffic
but it is.
Anyway, I got the license back.
I got my car registered and it hits the streets tonight.
Beautiful very excited. How many weeks do you think it runs? I bet you I get a few years out of this thing
I really do it's a really nice shape. I'm telling you and it cooks baby it cooks
I'm tempted to take a Devegas, but I don't think that's a good first trip
Dying the desert
Joe mentioned Scott Thompson. I did go see Scott Thompson a little theater by my house
He was fantastic. He's great. Did some of his old buddy coal monologues from kids in the hall very funny
Very outrageous shit. He was like I'm not updating anything whatever I said in 95. I'm saying it tonight. I knew it good
It showed it was very fun. Good
So look let me take you down if I may
to Pat's movie corner. I watched a picture called, you know what I'd like to start with,
is a picture that's on Shutter, and I watched it the night before the man died, which was really
kind of creepy, but King Cohen, and King Cohen is the story of Larry Cohen, the famed low -budget
at filmmaker who passed away last week.
Documentary is called King Cohen,
the wild world of filmmaker Larry Cohen.
He made a bunch of low -budget Roger Korman type shit.
Some of you may have seen Queue the Wing Serpent.
I like that one.
It's alive.
Yep, the stuff.
I have not seen all these, but a lot of them are on shutter.
The guy just clearly made films that he was excited about
and loved. Everyone has great things to say about them. There's a lot of great tales if you like
stories of low -budget filmmaking. It's a lot of fun. And then later in life, kind of like, you know,
generally you hear like age 50. You're pretty much out of the business. You know, maybe you can take it
a little longer, but like writing everyone thinks it's a young man's game. 2002, the man's like 65 years old,
he wrote phone booth, which is a pretty cool movie with Colin Farrell. All right, I know he wrote that.
But then he did the story for Cellular, so he probably was like, yeah, I got a pitch.
You want this?
Well, that was based on Stephen King, wasn't it?
No, set cell.
Oh, okay.
Cellular was like a paparazzi type movie.
I think Kim Basin, but not paparazzi, which came out that same year.
And then he did the screenplay for captivity, which is a movie I basically shed on last week
with Alicia Coothpert locked in a basement.
Okay.
But the guy worked right up to the end.
And I found his story very inspiring.
It just makes you realize that, you know, you don't have to be concerned about whatever
one thinks of every little thing you do.
This guy's got a richer career than most.
He's proud of it.
He's happy with it.
People have a lot of great memories about his stuff.
And it's a very well -done documentary.
Check it out.
I watched, I never watched it completely.
I thought I had, but I had and I finally watched the film Canadian Bacon in its entirety.
Not great. No, and here's the thing. It's not a bad movie. It's just you just don't care.
There's nothing like alarmingly bad in it. You just don't care. And it's John Candy and Rip Torn and
Kevin Pollock and you know, there are a lot, I'd re -approve and there are a lot of funny people in it
that you want it to be funnier than it is and it's just not.
But Candy, you can't keep a good man down.
He's still got a few laughs out of me in the movie.
There's a part where he's interrogating a 90 -year -old woman
because he thinks she's like a Canadian spy.
She's baked cookies.
So as he's interrogating her, of course,
she's got to keep eating the cookies.
And he's got like a mouthful of cookies.
And she's like, and she's like, of course,
like I don't know anything and he goes look sister we can either do this my way which is very nice
right now cookies like falling out of his mouth or we can do it the hard way he's got a few funny
parts okay uh all the as the president very likable but not not a great movie what is it the kidnap
the president or we go to war with Canada okay but the joke is is that like even as we're
Basically, waging war on Canada when the Americans are in Canada,
Canada is still being like really nice about everything.
Okay.
It's an interesting idea.
It's not, it's, you know, it's, it's like a lot of Michael Moore shit.
I go, that's a good idea.
And then you get annoyed halfway through.
Yeah.
I mean, I hate to shit on John Candy after we did our tribute to him, but I rewatch deliverance
on, I'm sorry, delirious.
off of Joe's constant recommendations and talk on the pod.
And this movie is very bad.
And just as I remembered when I was 13
and the target audience for it, it's really bad.
What do you, I don't get what you,
like you didn't get, I just don't get how you didn't get
any enjoyment out of it.
I could show you the, the periscope of me watching it,
motionless.
Uh, but I just thought it was poorly made. Uh, there was nary a laugh to be had and I was looking.
All right. Candy's always likable. He was in that phase where I would argue
he crossed over into too fat to be super funny. He looks kind of like there's an extra body hanging
off of him. You didn't think it was funny when uh, the gag with Dylan, which is face getting sicker
in sicker, excuse me, Dylan Baker.
No, Dylan Baker, you think it was funny when Canny goes,
no showing off tomorrow night, I'm only going to do what's necessary
and it cuts him doing the piano concerto.
I mean, it had like Harry Crumb moments in it that made me laugh.
I think you need to keep Harry Crumb's good name out of your mouth while you're talking about Delirious.
Um, I watched Free Solo, which is now streaming on Hulu, and it just goes to show, I think
I watch movies for different reasons than most and vice versa, not that I'm all that
fucking special.
But like what almost no one is discussing about the movie is to me 1000 % what the movie
was about and why it touched me and why I liked it.
Free Solo everyone's like you're not going to believe the climbing footage.
Oh, you can climb and friends, critics.
Where do you see him climb?
And that's true.
It is a man who wants to climb mountains.
He does these things in like three hours.
He'll scale an entire mountain.
Seemingly impossible.
He uses no ropes.
And I find that cool to watch that once,
but it doesn't hold my interest.
I'm like, I know the guys alive.
Got you know, he made it out of the documentary.
So while there is some cool climbing footage, everyone's like it's all worth it for that final 10 minutes when he's climbing
Okay, he you know spoiler alert. The man lives. It's very clear. Okay building up to that
Is this guy who had
Aloof parents emotionally closed off parents who currently lives in a van
Who does nothing except plan to climb mountains and climb mountains?
He doesn't buy clothes, he barely takes care of himself.
And, but he's, you know, a good -looking fit dude.
He's a mountain climber, so women come into it out of his life.
But he tells all of them, my number one interest is climbing.
I have no interest in being with you, but look up, let's do it.
He does this about as long as he can until someone finally gets to him, beautiful young woman.
And he opens himself up to her a little bit.
But day three of them trying to climb together, usually climbs completely alone.
She misses the rope that she's supposed to be holding.
He falls and seriously injures himself.
So as I've been climbing alone for 20 years, I bring a woman into the mix and I immediately
fall and hurt myself.
Basically, it becomes a long allegory for the creative process and it's tackling the same
shit that Phantom Thread tackled.
It's just more about physical than about art or emotional, but it's the same struggles
I saw Neil Brennan talking about how much he loved and related to this movie and I was like really dude
You're a comedian and I watched it. It's the exact same thing that all comedians and performers unless they're well -adjusted in which case
You're in the wrong business
But it's what you deal with I related to so much of it of like
Never wanted to commit to people throughout most of my life because I knew I was on a track. I wanted to do
television. I want to be a writer then
You wind up hurting a lot of people doing that.
You can't help it.
Then you finally decide I'm going to settle down
and immediately you're like,
now I'm really falling for this person,
fuck, am I going to forget about
what I'm trying to do my whole life?
Then in the end, they give you a little bit of hope
because he does this.
He makes this great accomplishment,
but the first thing he fucking does
is call his girlfriend and she's telling him how proud
she is of him and he starts crying
and she starts crying.
And then it's like, okay, in the end,
without ever commenting that that's what the movie is about and apparently what most people did
not take from this movie somehow is that it's a great allegory for that for yeah, it can be
difficult to balance anything that requires this much of your life, the entertainment industry,
athletics, whatever it may be with a relationship but in the end it's worth it and your successes are
only taking you so far if you can't share them with somebody. I thought it was a lovely movie,
the climbing footage is cool.
I'd check it out.
All right.
My last thing for the movie corner is
we almost did the episode on this people,
but we didn't.
Critters, a new binge.
People, I'm gonna do something I've never done
on this podcast before.
Critters a new binge just to catch you up
in case you don't know what it is.
It is the fifth installment to the critters franchise.
Critters has been a dead franchise for about 20 or 30 years.
I think the last sequel came out in like, you know, the early 90s or something.
Never seen any of the critters picture.
The first two are very, very enjoyable.
The third one is passable in the fourth one sucks or it might, that might be the other way
around.
The third one might suck in the fourth one would be passable.
but anyway, you can get the four pack of critters on Amazon for like $5 .99. It's in one of those,
you know, where they cut the dollar critter. Yeah, where they put like the four panels on the front
cover and it says like four critters on the spine. Anyway, so there was talk that they were going to
reignite critters. I first heard about it when I ran into a friend of mine who is basically the
owner of a Bominable Productions, his name is John, and John does a lot of cool work,
and he, in fact, produced my comedy special, his company. But I ran into him over Comedy Central
in the lobby, and I said, what's new? And he said, well, do you know Jordan Ruben? I said, yeah,
Jordan and I used to do comedy together in New York, and we're buddies, and whatever. I haven't seen
him in a while. What's going on? He said, well, he's directing a new Critters movie. Do you know
that franchise critters. I go, John, I have a horror podcast. I know critters. That's really fun.
And I even asked him, do you do the critters ball? And he was like, I love that you just asked me
that. We had to figure out how to do it because of the budget constructions and we figured out
a way. And oh my god, that's, I got to tell Jordan you said that. I'm like, yeah, that's,
that you got to do the critters ball. Anyway, I was like, I'm excited to see this. Can't wait.
Then, words started circulating that there was going to be another critters thing.
I think it's still happening on sci -fi.
I think they're doing a critters film.
So they're doing a sci -fi, I think, is doing a film, Shutter is doing a series or did did
a series.
It's out.
You can see it now.
I was more excited for the series because of my friend's involvement.
I thought, well, here's a chance to maybe see this going in a different direction than the
the first four movies went with instead of just another film,
Allah, what sci -fi is doing with tremors,
shutter, the much much much to my opinion,
superior company.
Look who's talking some props for tremors.
No, no, no, shutter, I said.
Instead of what I'm saying, shutter is the superior to sci -fi.
It's fair.
production. Production company. Sci -Fi keeps making the tremors sequels. Yes. I thought,
and all my friends are not all my friends, but some of my friends are involved. This is great.
I'm super excited. I texted Pat the other day. I said, hey man, that new critters is out. It looks
like the episodes are really short. It's about 10 -10 minute episodes, so I guess it's about an hour.
Uh, that's weird to do that short, but this is an easy watch and it's a big event in horror and we should review it and he said great, and we both watched it and people.
As I said at the top of the spiel, I watched three of the nine minute episodes.
As I said at the top of the spiel, I'm going to do something I've never done on this show.
I've got too many friends involved in this thing.
I'm just going to play the fifth.
But wow, much like the movie we're reviewing today, the predator, I don't know how a group
of people managed to make the worst installment of the critters franchise by far.
I had nothing to base it on.
It is a lot of the critters talking to each other with subtitles.
I don't think the critters were without personality and charm. I just wasn't caught up in the
project. It didn't didn't move me. That's a very diplomatic way to put it. I appreciate
the hard work. I appreciate what they were trying to do. I appreciate the tone they were
going for, you know, it just didn't work for me at all. They really, really leaned heavily
into, look how low budget this is. Yeah. And they were, you know, the characters are making jokes
about it. And, you know, that kind of, that kind of wink to the camera will only take you so far.
It doesn't make up for the fact that you're not watching a quality product. But even if that's being
said, even if the gag is, this is sort of like a B movie, kind of experience, fine, which
the critters films are. I mean, these, these originals aren't, you know, you're not watching
fucking Warren peace for God's sakes, right? You know, but my point is, even if you're
going for that B movie vibe, I've still got to believe in what I'm watching. I've got
to, I've got to be willing to go on this journey. And I just not once ever was pulled
did enough to do that. I saw a missed opportunity for not expensive these days. You can shoot stuff
that looks cool. I'm sitting here going, this could have been a stranger things. I'm not saying
so rip off stranger things because they're the holy grail or something. I was like, this could have
had mood to it. Like it could have had some depth to it and still been funny and whatever.
And it just, I mean, right off the bat, the effects, everything. It looked like it was
made for sci -fi and the sci -fi channel like 94. You know, like, yeah, I mean, the critters
are looking up porn and they look up shaved, bush porn and the ones like, I'd like to eat
that. And you're just like, what is going the well, then one of them,
one of them, was that the critters style leaving back in the day? I don't remember that being.
I don't remember. I remember the tone being far more gremlins. Yeah, you know,
like a gremlins or a ghoulies kind of thing because all those movies were
derivative of gremlins. Yes. Um, but no, it was not in what he, the line is.
and I remember this line because that joke really stood out to me because I didn't like it.
He looks at the porn, he goes on a porn site and it says, all shaved and he goes, man,
things have changed a lot since the 80s on earth.
That's the joke, which is contradicted two scenes later when the mother starts saying, ready
for this reveal?
I fucked one of these things in the 90s.
That's the plot twist.
Yeah, the mom and the third episode starts going the critters are back. They're back
They're back so then that's confusing because you're sitting there going
I don't remember this lady in any of the movies. Am I missing something? Wait a minute
Is she a character from one of the other movies?
Wait a minute they were just saying the last time I hear it was the 80s. She wait what the fuck is going on
Then you realize no, it's just written that way where so they can set up this reveal
She's not a character from a former movie. She she just starts saying
they're back, so you go, what does she mean by that?
And that's just a set up for her to leave a reveal
that she fucked one at a Y2K festival.
She fucked a critter.
Yeah, she goes, we all thought we were gonna die.
By the way, at a Y2K festival, she fucked a critter
who is the president of the critters
who looks like Donald Trump.
Hardy, hard, hard.
Look a little wig.
He's in the first episode.
But he's full size?
no no it's he's a little disgusting because I guess I guess that helps it's
soft in a little bit when the the lead kid is screaming at into his mom's face
in episode three everyone at school thinks you're a whore and I agree with them
you're a whore mom because she has a boyfriend over I was like is this okay a
A single woman has a boyfriend over and her son's screaming that she's a whore.
That part was originally written for Joe Pesci.
Well, that I want to watch.
Joe Pesci doing the critter's new batch.
New binge.
Um, I'm sorry, guys.
I love you all over, debominable, and I love you, Jordan, but I, man, wow.
my last picture is the dirt the Motley crew bio pick on Netflix I hear this is a
lot of fun this thing I mean I've seen a lot of people like better than
Bohemian Rhapsody because that movie became the big punching bag it's just as
much of a fucking lie about the band that it's about as Bohemian Rhapsody is I
I read The Dirt.
I really enjoyed the fuck out of the book The Dirt.
And I don't like Motley Crew.
I like Kickstart My Heart.
I think every other song of theirs sucks.
Every other song.
I hate everything they stand for.
I don't think, hold on.
I hate the personalities in the band.
I think you could put together a pretty killer
Motley Crew greatest hits.
They're not for me.
Kickstart My Heart is by Jam.
Kickstart My Heart is incredible.
to hear outside of a strip club, and I don't even need to hear them inside a strip club.
But this movie is a lie too, you know, they said, we're not going to clean this up just
because it's the me too generation, but you did.
And that's fine, but let's not, I mean, there is a scene of, you know, Tommy Lee hitting
a girlfriend of his, but they make her call him the worst names in the book and salt his
mom over and over. It goes on for so long, you're about ready to hit this woman because
they have to really make sure they cover their bases. It just didn't, and I was excited
when two minutes into this thing, Tommy Lee's going down on a woman and she ejaculates
across the room. I was like, I remember that from the book. This movie's going to be a
wild ride. I've missed this kind of disgusting sleazy energy from movies. And then that's
It peaks in the first two minutes. There's not a lot of nudity and any of that stuff that you're coming to or not
Enough for my taste for a motley crew movie and the rest of it falls into these really boring
Rock biopic
Moves about a band you don't care about to begin with then the more small see parts of the book like people's health scares and things like that
Are handled so melodramatically. They're embarrassing and they don't link up with the rest of the tone
Might be because the man directing it is Jeff Tremaine from the jackhouse family
Jackass is production company jackhouse who I've met the nice guy and I love his fucking comedies
He's made some of the best comedies there is yeah, but he makes comedies where guys jump off a roof on to a thing that hits them
They're balls like he doesn't you know, but you know, I'll say this for a guy who to my knowledge. This is like his first
You know narrative full narrative film. It looks good
It's just really lacking, I guess, star power, I gotta say, and you know, Bohemian
Rhapsody.
You mean, machine gun Kelly didn't bring it?
That is my biggest issue.
I feel like I am just watching idly by and I am chained to my couch and cannot stop machine
gun Kelly from becoming a star, and it's becoming a real nightmare for me.
Somebody has to get in there and stop this kid from becoming a star.
He's he's a mediocre talent at best
Clearly he has some Netflix holding deal and you know, yeah guarantee Netflix does holding deals with people
I think they got the girl from patty cakes. Oh, dude. It's and I know they got machine gun Kelly. They're in bird box
They're gonna start showing up in every movie. It's insane. This guy sucks and they honestly would have done just as well
Having Tommy Lee play the part. He's a better actor and he's more charismatic
I'll say this about
Netflix, before we move on to our review, ooh, we've been talking for a while already.
We're steaming today.
I'm just saying this, I'm not saying I'll never use the service ever again.
I'm just saying this is something to think about.
That looks disgusting.
You just sip that drink worse than you could ever imagine.
I'm just saying this is something to think about, and I'm not saying so you got to walk
away for life or whatever, but I mean, all these, again, all of you complaining, not all
of you. I don't want them to like you fans. I don't mean like that. Just mean like for
everybody out there complaining about what's happening in the White House and what bankers
are doing in this country. And this is not the other thing. Guys, I was in a fucking block.
In one city block on the sunset strip last night, one block, there were four billboards in
a row, four Netflix billboards in a row telling you what to watch all featuring major, major,
major Hollywood talent. And I'm just sitting there looking up at this and I'm going in this
country. If that was four billboards for Trump or four billboards in a row for any sort
of political stance or mindset or opinion, you would be like, this is insane. We don't
live in an extreme communist country. Why am I seeing that? It's a fucking monopoly. It's
fucking crazy when you dry and I know that this is the land of entertainment, but that's the point.
It's supposed to be evenly spread and you drive down the sunset strip and it is billboard after
billboard after billboard of Netflix. That's it. I mean, I've said it before. I don't know what
fucking Saudi prints is funding this goddamn thing, dude, but it's like it's very obvious to me that
that they are in a course to try to stomp out
every other form of entertainment
so they can be the only thing.
And look, Disney's question.
Did you see the body on it?
Disney's trying to do it too.
And so is AT &T.
I mean, they're not alone in this game.
Did you see Netflix pretending that they do it
for the person in a small town
who can't make it to the art house?
Yeah, that was my favorite.
That was my favorite.
You might have even sent that to me, bud.
We, yeah, that was my favorite.
Yeah, as they put out another season of like,
like, you know, fucking a master of none, you know, or like,
or like some dumb like fucking, you know,
I don't even know what they put out anywhere.
I'm, that would have been a great bit
if I could have thought of a good example,
but I couldn't think of one.
I couldn't think of a dumb enough show to make fun of.
Apple TV is the next of these.
I don't think it's gonna hold a candle
because nothing's got into early.
But what Netflix did in a very short amount of time is got and how would I know the numbers because they quite illegally don't release them, but
They got a fourth of the country at least to say I'm done with paying a hundred dollars a month for cable
I'm going to get this ten dollar a month
Streaming service and I'll just watch whatever Netflix tells me to watch for the rest of my life and people are okay with that and people who aren't
passionate about entertainment. I think it is a smart choice. You're saving 90 bucks a month.
But what it is doing to the culture at large and will continue to do, and it's already done
in such a short amount of time, is deeply disturbing, I think. And they're smart. It's a business
like anything else. They are making a ton of money, but doesn't mean I love it or I agree with it.
They are absorbing all talent, and they are going to make it that if you don't work for them,
you don't work for anybody. Right. But then like, and Disney's doing the same goddamn thing.
That Ben Affleck movie came out. I don't know anybody in the world who's seen that movie.
Nope. Every Ben Affleck movie that came out for 20 years, you at the very least knew what it was.
Yep.
You know, so something weird is a foot, but I don't think they care if anybody watches them
because they can just say everybody watched it.
And then they cancel shows that supposedly do well.
Right, I only watched the pilot of one day at a time and it felt to me sort of like a filmed
drama, perhaps it gets funnier, but it was certainly viable. It was certainly about an
interesting subject and it was serving the, I mean, forget underserved, basically not
served Latino market. I was a family sitcom about a Latino family and critically acclaimed
and they're just like, sorry, I wish we could keep telling stories like this. We just don't
have the money and everybody's like, what are you talking about? You don't have the money.
your Netflix. If you're going to be this artist helping place, do it. Don't tell us,
sorry guys, if you'd only watched more, we could. People were watching. You chose not to.
Nobody's watching anything they're doing. That nothing they do is getting enough eyes on it
to justify the money they're spending on it. So with that logic, no show should ever be canceled.
right. But I will say that it's not a very critically acclaimed show when most of their shows are critically
panned outside from their small hits which they play out over and over and over. I'll say this
then I'll shut up. If you don't think that there's some weird conflict of interest going on here,
just always remember this. This is a company that started as the company that said we are going to
cook you up with every movie.
We are gonna help you see every movie that you wanna see.
And they went from being that
to being the company now saying,
we make every movie.
You have to come to us.
Right.
That's a little fucking weird to me, man.
That's a little fucking weird to me.
I agree.
So that's that I am still open to generals,
general meetings over at Netflix HQ.
Yeah, hopefully my friends that work there never hear this.
Anyway, let's get to the review, man. I did want to say, though, this Apple TV. Oh, yes.
Two weeks ago, Spielberg's like Netflix is the end of movies. Fuck them. And it was blown
out of proportion, but he was basically like, you know, voicing some concerns, which somebody
at his level should very much be doing.
And everyone was like, you're out of touch, fuck you.
Two weeks later, he's a keynote speaker
at the Apple TV announced.
Yeah, it's.
And I guess in his mind, it's like, well, that's TV.
That doesn't affect the film business.
You think Apple's gonna sit and cross their hands
and move aside?
He said what he said about Netflix
because he's in bed with Apple.
Clear.
Disgusting.
People would disgust me.
All of them clearly.
God damn it.
And it's like, okay, Steven.
and so you need four hundred and fifty billion because the the four twenty five billion wasn't
enough. Oh, yeah. This is how you want to go out. Steven, just make one last Indiana Jones
police and just leave. Meanwhile, I have friends with big Apple shows tons of money being spent
and they're just like, this isn't what we wanted. Sorry, we were hoping it'd be more family -friendly.
I don't know if we can air this. Like they have a real crisis going on that they've kind
kind of kept, you know, contained.
But we'll see.
Well, Apple or another group of,
I don't get me started on that.
It's all disgusting.
Every, everything's pig.
All right, let's talk about something truly great.
The predator.
The predator remake.
2018.
Ritt, I could, I mean, look,
I find the predator to be a secondary franchise
at best, I know I disagree with Joe. We don't have to get into it. Can't hold a candle to aliens.
All right. Well, don't say you're, don't knock my thing down. Can't hold a candle to Terminator.
And you know Joe thinks the opposite of both of those. Yeah, better than both.
I think Predator starts with a good action movie. Follows it with some absolutely terrible action
movies, including, of course, the dreadful alien versus predator.
And I thought there's certainly potential.
The predators are really cool monster.
And who better than the great Shane Black who wrote some of the most fun 90s actioners,
the very underrated long -kissed good night.
Leith the weapon.
Last boy scout.
He was recently a nice guy.
He was in Predator and then he had a, you know, later career
Resurgence with kiss kiss bang bang directed. I'm directed iron man three. He knows what he's doing with the shit and
the great
The nice guys which I just rewatched and fucking loved all over again, and I think Gosling is a mother in that movie
It's a master masterful
Performance by both Gosling and and Crow, but Gosling really is like wow
Gosling's physical comedy on the toilet when he's trying to pull the gun on Russell Crowe is like Steve Martin
78. Yeah, and no one gave her shit. No that no one cared the Abbott and Costello like I just found a dead body thing
Yeah, like you can't get the words out. Yeah, I mean it's he's he's magical in that movie. He's really funny
Anyway big shame black fan over here and he started and I believe contributed some dialogue punch up to the original
predator. She's a joke man in the original. I don't remember. There he was got a big pussy.
Yes. Big pussy. Why'd you say it twice? I didn't. That joke. Yeah.
This movie really got away from somebody. Let me say this. Just right off the
bets. You know exactly where I stand on this film. Much like the critters commentary.
I don't know how you manage Shane to make the worst predator movie. I mean, we were all
a little upset when it went from Schwarzenegger to Danny Glover in the second one. That was
a little bit of an action here. Very bucy action hero drop off for us. All right. We were
all a little upset. But predator to at least capture some of the tone of predator one. I was
little upset when you went from Danny Glover to Adrian Grenier and the third one. Brody, right?
Or Adrian Brody, sorry. I was well been Grenier. It didn't matter. But again, it has its moments.
It's not a bad movie. It's passable compared to the original, not great, but passable. Alien versus
predator comes out. Now we've got a predator that teams up with a human being at the end of the movie
to fight the aliens.
Some people thought this was sacrilege.
Some other people also thought the fact
that it was only PG -13 was sacrilege.
These were all points.
I think they were both R.
Second one was R. Covenant was R.
The first one was, or not Covenant, Rekweeham.
First one was PG -13.
You can look it up, but let me finish.
I'm gonna go to Tara here.
And those points were well heard at the time.
Then Alien versus Predator Rekweeham comes out.
And you say, my God, who wants to see an alien predator movie that takes place mostly
in the suburbs and features kids and has pointless gore with no storyline?
Wait, alien versus predator Requiem takes place in the suburbs?
Yes.
Then I didn't see that one.
That's the second one.
So Shane Black, you heard everything I just said.
And you come out with this fucking movie, holy shit, not only is it not Danny Glover,
not only is it not Adrian Brody, it's fucking like Keegan Michael Key and a gaggle of
other people that I don't find intimidating tough Olivia Munn, believably bad as not, it's
not Gary Bucy, it's Jake Bucy, you return the setting to the suburbs. You bring in an
even younger child. At the end of the movie, the predator helps, not only helps the human,
but his half human himself. What the fuck, this thing is a mess. This thing was one of the
The biggest piece of shit I've ever seen in my life can't believe a bad fucking movie was.
I was blown away in myself.
A lot of it is that I read a lot of positive reviews, and a lot of Twitter reactions like
it's the predator you've been wanting guys, blah, blah, blah.
I mean, it didn't really make sense beat to beat.
There was like, and I have very few like strong memories of it, and I watched it a couple
months ago, but like they're all in an SUV early on the whole team and you're like how
they all get in this SUV like it keeps making these jumps I feel like a lot of it was cut
out it keeps making jumps that don't make sense and in addition when I looked it up there
were tremendous amounts of reshoots yes so I think really what they were left with was probably
three hours of footage, a half hour of it good, and then just trying their best to make
something stick and hang together as a movie.
And then as the movie's being released, they find out it's a little fun prank, Shane
Black cast his friend, a convicted child molester, in a key role, Olivia Mungo's, hey, I would
have appreciated being aware that I was in a scene with a convicted child molester, I'd
like the scene removed, all the fans, fuck her, want to lose, you know, really a great
moment for, for internet trolls everywhere. And they took his scene out, I'm sure it
didn't matter, but like these characters get shitty introductions. You know, there's no
one to root for. And okay, if you don't have Arnold, you have to do the work to make me
know who the character is. I even give a shit about. If you're going to do an homage to
these movies, you know Arnold never movie was out chopping a block of wood shirtless and
the camera pans up his body and then a beautiful woman is watching from inside like I love
that man and the kid runs out and hugs him and then you're like, oh, this is a good guy,
a family guy.
You know, as we do, they don't give you those hero moments anymore, they just throw you
into a bunch of chaotic action, poorly shot action, I might say.
It was hard to follow what was going on moment to moment.
Oh, it was this movie made so many mistakes.
Now, let's start with the comedy number one.
This thing is there were 10 scenes
that were like outtakes from Destiny Turns On The Radio.
Like people written in a kitchen,
but like I say that I intentionally did not
say a Tarantino movie.
I picked one of the many ripoffs that came in its wake,
but just like shitty dialogue.
How can Shane Black write shitty dialogue?
The, this was, this was, this was, the jokes were terrible.
They took precedent over logic, over character development, over depth.
The action sequences were boring and poorly shot.
The writing was an abomination.
I mean, this scene, that scene where you're first on the, like, the prison, the army prison
bus where you're going to meet the rag tag bunch, it's one of the worst things I've ever
See, it's literally the main guy who I can't even remember who plays the main guy because every character is so fucking forgettable
He goes around the entire bus like
That guy there's named Joker. He used to be into killing now. He just likes telling jokes
That guy over there is called mama's boy
Yeah, we call him that because he carries a picture of his mama around his neck over here's juggler
You can take a guess of what he does. It is fucking
terrible. It is terrible. It's like literally, that scene is literally like what they would
do on it's always sunny if the guy of the characters on it's always sunny made their
own predator movie. Yeah. And then you that would be the scene they would show and then
you would laugh at how stupid Dennis and Mack were. Like it's it's it's it's so fucking
bad. And then talk and then above all above all above all when were these fucking people
learn when will these fucking executives and these studios and these movie makers fucking
learn, stop over complicating it, stop it.
We don't need a half human predator.
We don't need to know why the predators come hunt.
We don't need to know that one of them doesn't agree with the other ones and now they're going
to turn against each other.
We don't need to know any of that.
This movie would have been perfect if you put an infantry guys in a rack, you know what
or overseas, somewhere overseas in the Middle East,
they're over there doing fucking second golf war shit.
This fucking thing lands.
They don't know what the fuck is going on.
They think the enemy has some kind of crazy new technology.
That's the movie. That's the whole fucking movie.
I will say I probably would not have seen that movie.
I don't like to see movies about Iraq.
I find them all the same and very boring.
I'm just saying it would have been better than this.
Well, you said it would be perfect.
It would have been looked it would have been exactly what the movie should have been which was this movie was supposed to be a throwback to the original
It was supposed to write the wrongs of all the sequels and it was supposed to get things back on course
So how do you get it back in course make it about a fucking military mission?
I gotta say I even heard though that it was gonna be a funny
Fun crazier version and got excited about that version. I think basically what we're just saying is we were lied to
No matter what you're right or listen to, it's not this movie.
This movie is a complete mess.
And if a guy like Shane Black brings this movie in and they're like, this is a mess
you've got to reshoot a bunch of shit, you wonder what's going on.
Because Shane Black does not make these sorts of errors in his screenwriting.
All you never know what the process is, but the man's got quite a track record and they've
been going to him for literally three decades.
Here's my theory.
I think this is what happened. I think the studio started stepping in too much, the movie
started falling apart. There were problems on set that we didn't hear about. One of the
problems that we did hear about was the casting of this guy. Olivia Munn probably started
saying, way, way, way before she went public, that she was going to go public. Shane Black probably
got fed up through his hands up in the air and said, I'm fucking done. Some studio interns
came in, cut the fucking thing together, and then put it out and it sucked.
That's what I think.
And then Schwarzenegger II turned down the coming back as Dutch at the end, which would
have set up a major sequel for him to be Dutch again in the next one.
He turned it down and he goes the part was too small.
That's not why he turned that down, dude.
He turned it down because this thing was a piece of shit and he knew fucking problems were
going on.
So he didn't get involved.
He did a goddamn two -setting scene in the inexpendables world.
That's true.
He's got no problem with showing up for a cameo, you know, and it's with his job now.
It's like the perfect thing for him to do, you know, the governor that was a diplomatic
way of saying this thing is a fucking mess, and I want nothing to do with it because he
was attached for way was he was visiting set and shit.
Yeah, he clearly just saw it and was like, and he's probably sure he's friendly at least
with Shane Black.
They made the movie together, but it does definitely, you know, Shane Black.
In fact, these movies are all, I would say emphasize character over plot, which is not
to say they are bad plots, you know, but like, kiss, kiss bang bang and the nice guys are
from that Cohen brother's school of plotting where it's like, just keep a bunch of balls
in the air and maybe they'll all land perfectly and maybe they won't, but you're going to have
a blast while you're getting from A to B.
I just don't feel like he would have released a movie this sloppy and it definitely wreaks
of like, but wait, I thought you were going to do the alien and where he's or the predator's
half human thing.
Yeah, no, it didn't work.
So we cut it.
We went this different direction.
No, just find a way to shove that back in there.
It seems like that kind of thing.
That's some, you know, all these studios do a lot of like, what happened to that thing we
liked?
We talked about it for days.
It didn't work.
So we cut it.
Yeah, but shove it back in, anyone.
Literally every predator movie,
and the only one I can include in this is Requiem,
because I don't remember it well enough
with who the characters were.
Frankly, I didn't know it came out.
But literally every other alien or predator movie,
including alien versus predator one,
had better character structure,
had better defined characters,
had better character development,
even like even in predators.
Toe for Grace playing that slimy fucking doctor
who eventually betrays everybody.
Yeah, that's a good character. That's a good character. Even though I don't buy Adrian Brody as this military badass
It was still a well written character. I got it. I believed it. I believed who he was
I believed that that Lawrence Fishburn was this crazy guy that was stuck on that planet for fucking 20 years or whatever it was
I believed it. I believed that Danny Glover was a grizzled LA cop who was who who who had seen a lot of shit
I believed it. I didn't believe one fucking character in this thing, and the best, the best
inside I heard on the movie was the reason the original work so well, or one of the reasons,
is they set up a group of the most badass dudes of all time who are almost comically badass.
Like Jesse Ventura, I ain't got time to believe. You know what I mean? They're almost comically
fucking hard asses right and then when the shit starts going down you see these guys become
afraid and you're like oh my god this is fucking this is serious they're in trouble and this
head none of that none of it they all seem very cocky and just kind of kept up that attitude
throughout and we're joking throughout that's our show folks the predator terrible I think that's
the official last nail in that coffin. I don't think we're going to see any more predator
stuff from now on. I mean, yeah, right down to its title, you know, it's just not trying
to do anything really, and it succeeds at doing nothing. We'll be back. I don't think Pat
Cemetery will, Pat Cemetery will be the next episode probably. I think, right? I think
that's because it'll comes out that it should be, right? Yeah, we'll see it next weekend
them do it. All right, Joe, there was a comedy on Instagram. If you're in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, I
will be, uh, God damn it. Why can't I remember that? I'm doing a casino in Milwaukee, Wisconsin,
Saturday, April 13th. Uh, that's this Saturday. No, it's not, it's not this Saturday. It's
a couple, you know, it's April 13th. Uh, bonkers presents. Just Google that in my name. You'll find it.
Uh, that's it.
I am at the Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram, although I use them both sparingly these days.
Keep checking out the Facebook page.
We'll see you in hell.
Keep checking out the Etsy page for any merch opportunities.
That's the Hog House on Etsy.
Run by Emily Florence.
Thank you, Emily.
Check out see you in hell pod.
Also run by Emily Florence on Instagram.
And, uh, that's all we got.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you now.