I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
So it's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear some discussion, some commentate,
some review of those films you like so much.
I'm Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick Walsh with a gaspie opening breath to start the podcast
today.
Mm hmm.
I always do it when I do the solo corner.
I always remind myself to take the big breath before I hit record.
Otherwise, you're like, hello, everybody.
It's not the most professional kickoff.
That's all right.
It's all right.
You know, they come, they don't come here for for gloss.
They come here, you know, for some down to earth, lugs that they can relate to.
That's true.
A little rough around the elbows.
Yes.
If you will.
Well, today's episode is the Oscars 2021, yeah, in review, looking back at one of the
greatest years in film history with a ceremony that lives up to that, that magic.
We're going to get right down to it as we usually do with these theme episodes.
But first, if I may, if I may, and I think that this is related, this is not a segment.
We usually don't do segments on these theme ones.
This is not a segment I'm about to launch into.
See, I wasn't considering this a theme one.
I thought we'd do the segments and enjoy ourselves and have a nice leisurely record.
I'd enjoy it without the segments, to be honest.
I got a lot to say about these damn Oscars.
Wow.
All right.
But I want to, I just want to discuss something with you that's my opinion in it around about
way is Oscar related.
Okay.
We both went to this big grind house video sale online when they were having it.
Yeah.
Who would you say that was about a month ago?
This point.
Yeah.
I'm realizing I haven't received my selections.
How do you mention it?
I was realizing the same thing, Pat.
And I kept checking up on it over the last, let's say, two weeks.
And every time I went on, I was seeing when I would do my order update, it would say we
will notify you when it ships.
Right.
I'm sitting here going, when it ships, it's been like a month, man.
Like what is happening?
Right?
Yeah.
So finally today, or yesterday, I placed a very polite email, I put the order number in
the subject line, say, hello, I'll place this order a few weeks back, any update on when
it might ship.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Kind enough.
Right?
Yeah.
I wake up this morning to this.
We are working as fast as we can to get orders out from the Easter carnage sale.
Please be patient while we get through those orders.
That's it.
Well, that's just a form letter.
I write, I write, but hold on, let me tell you, I wrote back, I'm being patient, I just asked
if there was an update on when it might ship.
Yeah.
I then followed that with a message that says, also, I didn't tell you to be patient when
I gave you my money, I handed it right over there, maybe show this, maybe show some courtesy
when one of the super fans keeping your niche website alive asks a simple, polite question.
Honestly, a beautiful response.
They had it coming to me.
You're right.
And they haven't responded.
Now, I texted with Matt McCarthy about this because Matt McCarthy put in, I would say
a quite large order.
So did I.
With that, with that sale.
So did you.
Matt informed me today that not only has his order also not shipped.
But the website now is saying the store is temporarily closed.
Oh boy, this is going to be some sort of we work type deal.
They're going to clean us out.
This is fire festival all over again.
I mean, I spent a lot on that sale and it hasn't shipped.
When they say something hasn't shipped, it's like, look, here's the only explanation.
You have one person working in the warehouse who's trapped under a crane or something.
Otherwise, you're picking up items that are in stacks in a warehouse and you're putting them
in a cardboard box and sending them.
That's all it is.
Right.
So what I'm thinking is they don't have the stock, but they don't want to lose the money.
So they're trying to get the stock is probably what's happening.
That frightens me because when you're going to a website where the key purchase
is the special edition, blue ray of microwave massacre.
This is not a stampede of customers coming in.
This is these are orders that are pretty easy to fulfill.
I smell a rat.
Yeah.
But you know what?
I'm going to say it publicly and by that, I mean to a select small group of Patreon members.
Fuck you, grindhouse video.
This kind of shit is why people shop on Amazon and you're doing a great disservice to the
independent movie distribution industry.
You know, people want to service the mom and pops.
They want to keep them alive and when you act like it's our privilege to shop with you,
this is what makes people go fuck you.
I'm going to just go to a big box store because at least I know I'll get what I ordered
and if I don't, they'll just give me my money back.
It's true.
I hate to agree with everything you're saying, but I absolutely do.
I made a bunch of orders from these type of specialty sites in the recent months.
I guess they all were probably struggling and did some big sales.
They all got it to me and if they didn't, there was an email explaining why and when exactly
it would show up.
Right.
So I got to say fuck you, grindhouse as well.
I mean, Warner archive is going under Warner brothers just said we're not doing any
more physical media.
We're done with it.
These places are falling apart and I understand that you might not be able to hire an Amazon
level staff, but again, you're throwing things in a box.
We paid for the shipping.
So that's not it.
Also too.
If you're that behind, how about you say our apologies?
Yeah.
We're swamped with the influx of sales.
We promise you we are working.
There's a way to say it, but I'm buying grindhouse movies from a grindhouse website and you're
going to turn around and talk to me the way I would expect, you know, sun coast video
or blockbuster or whatever, one of these other shitbag chains from the 90s was, it's like
give me a fucking break, man.
And while I'm on the negative of saying it's, it really bums me out when a, when a so -called
indie grassroots operation X so Hollywood, I'll go to two positives.
If you're in the Connecticut Bridgeport area, you got to get yourself over to the archive.
I talked about that last time on the show.
They're the real deal.
They are tremendous people and go to the vinegar syndrome website if you want to just buy
directly via mail order.
That's not a plug.
That's nothing.
I'm just telling you where to get good stuff from good people.
And props, major props to Hamilton bucks.
I order almost weekly off of there now.
I get the things in three days, four days, it's cheap, it's affordable, it's friendly.
Yeah, shipping's like four bucks for your order.
Yeah.
So anyway, no, that sucks.
And I'll tell you this too.
I mean, I don't know where they're at, but like, I was a temp in New York for years.
I was a temp in LA for years.
There are temp agencies where you just call up and say, hey, we're backed up at the warehouse.
Can somebody come in for eight hours today and put blu -rays in a cardboard box?
And a temp will be thrilled to have the $10 an hour.
And you'll get your stuff out faster.
If it's a staffing issue, just like, you can always get stuff done.
How the, that's why I think it's got to be a stock issue.
They're trying to like track down stock on all these out of print things and they're
getting fucked because they're going to have to say, we don't have this.
Deep discount did this to me as well.
Deep discount had amazing deals.
You and Matt got it.
And they told me, yeah, we were not sending it to you.
We're not honoring that price, but here's the thing.
At least deep discount said immediately, sorry, we don't have anymore.
And that's it.
Yeah, here's your money back.
That's true.
It's like, you know, if that's the case with with grind house, whoa, boy, I just kicked
my mic stand.
If that's the case with grind house video, then say it.
And I don't even know if it's the case because there's no transparency.
And I think it's a really, you got was was a form letter.
That was just something that you got sent automatically.
I bet.
I don't think so because it came back a day later and there's misspellings in it.
There's typos in it.
Okay.
I'll go it's some guy being an asshole right or gal.
I don't know, but you know, it's somebody being an asshole.
And it's like, it's like, I went into a record store in New York a couple of
weeks ago.
I can't remember the name of it.
I wish I could, but, you know, I'm just kind of walking around on a Sunday,
lazy Sunday.
I look up some record stores on the G Google maps and I find what I've never
been to and I go, all right, I'm going to take a stroll over see what's up.
I walk all the way over to this place.
I go inside.
It's, you know, it's one of these spots that's like 10 feet by 10 feet.
There's a guy behind the counter, just a fucking, I'm sorry.
I'm just going to say this.
If I walk into your indie record store and avant -garde jazz is playing,
you're an asshole.
Yeah.
You're just an asshole.
It's you're trying way too hard.
Did it sound like the homeland theme like that?
Like the Spike Lee scores from like Mo better blues.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, that's blanchored.
Yeah, you walk it.
I love this.
You walk in the store.
It's like wall -to -wall, everything they sell, it's like wall -to -wall, DMX, Metallica, Black
Sabbath.
You know what I mean?
And then the guy behind the counter is listening to like, you know, like he's so, my
cat's looking over like, do I have a new friend in the house?
What's going on?
What does it say?
Three stooges short, but I walk in and I'm literally the only person in the store, literally.
And it's very obvious from the energy of the store.
I mean, the only person that's been in the store for an hour's.
And a guy doesn't even look up, doesn't even say how you doing.
Now, it's like, you know what, pal?
Fuck you.
I will never come back to your store again.
I'm one of the ten people keeping this thing that your parents funded, or at least trying
to keep this thing that your parents funded for you open, and you can't be bothered to
greet your customer.
You can't be bothered.
Meanwhile, you know, I go into like a fucking subway or a blimpies and people are like, how
you do it?
You know, I go into Lulu Lemon today to look at socks and 30 people are like, how are you
sir?
What can we get you today?
You know, I'm like, well, it's just because they're trained to.
And like the whole attitude at a record store is like, just be cool, be chill.
You know, it's my friend worked at Abercrombie when we were in high school.
My friend's a good -looking dude.
And they told the people working there, don't approach anyone.
Let them ask you twice for help, twice for help.
We're the elitist, the six -pack ab store, make them ask you twice for help.
So I think that the record store, I'm not saying they train people to be assholes, but they
definitely want to be like, they're the guy who has too good a taste in music that he wants
to brag about all the time, personified, as a store, you know, like, they don't want
to help anybody, they don't, they don't want to help, it's like, it's high fidelity.
They think they're cooler than you so they won't help.
I went into a bookstore this week.
I had a stack of like five books and I knew they had a great movie TV book section.
So I went in and I go, hey, I'm, I'm wanting to maybe make some purchases, but I'm also
looking to sell books.
Do you guys buy books?
The guy does not look up from reading.
He also did not say hello, doesn't look up from reading.
And he goes Tuesdays, goes back to turning pages.
I said, I'm sorry, Tuesdays, what?
He goes Tuesdays, we buy books and I said, isn't it Tuesday?
He goes, it's Wednesday.
I said, okay, well, I'm here with the books.
Can you take a look at them?
And then he looks up from the book, real annoyed, and he goes, look, man, we only do it on
Tuesdays.
Oh my God, I hope you're busy, I'll never be back here again.
Yeah.
And honestly, I'll probably sell them on Amazon.
I didn't want to, but here we are.
Yeah, it's like the, it's like the casino scene, they turn you into peshy, like I got your
head in a vice, please don't make me do this.
Yeah, please.
I'm trying to be a good guy here.
I went into the new Amoeba also, Joe, break it down for me, babe.
Folks, I mean, I know a lot of you don't live in a lay, I'll keep it brief, but you know,
you know this was a special place, a church, if you will, for Joe and I.
I spent at least two Sundays a month walking its hallowed holes.
Yeah, so I caught you kneeling and praying a couple of times in a corner, employees would
come over and say, sir, please get up.
That was a glory hole.
But I, they moved it around, let's pitch that to weird now, you know what?
You wouldn't have to change the cover of the born of the USA, I'll have it be called glory
holes.
It looks, he's wearing the Kirchiff in his pocket, like they cruising when they're like,
if you're looking for a blow job, put the Kircheef in your back pocket.
So here was my Amoeba plan.
I asked Vince, you know, because I know he wanted to get over there.
And Vince, I think is a little skittish about returning to society.
A lot of people are, I'm vaccinated.
I say I'm going to Amoeba, I take a lot of edibles.
I go over there, don't glaze over the details.
What's a lot for you these days?
Well, because I was driving, it was a lot, I took, I took 50 milligrams, 50, which is not
even a lot, but it would put me out for two days straight.
I'm not saying, I'm not just sizing, I'm just saying that would cripple me for days,
literally.
No, over the pandemic, my, I'm way up there in my tolerance.
And I need to, I need to kill it because I used to be a 10, 20 man, but my plan is to
spend four hours walking the halls of Amoeba and I'm not bringing up anything to sell.
I'm like, don't go in and get in a bad mood right away and try to sell to these pricks.
You know, they haven't bought anything in a year.
They're not going to be, you know, feeling generous.
I walk up, as I told Joe, 400 pound man and suspenders with a wheelbarrow of DVDs.
A wheelbarrow and boxes packed high on the wheelbarrow.
And I was like, he's out sweating in the sun because they had a line outside, huge pit stains.
And I'm like, they're going to give this guy six bucks.
Last time I brought in DVDs, the guy was like, we don't take him anymore.
Yeah.
I weighed in the line, the lines, you know, it's only 15 minutes.
It's not bad.
I get inside.
They're monitoring how many people can be in the store, obviously.
I'm bumping into people every time I turn around.
It's half the size of the previous Amoeba.
The previous Amoeba had a second floor that you walked up stairs to a beautiful,
blue ray DVD paradise that has gone and replaced with the back wall has some blue rays on it.
Is there now, when you say half the size, okay.
So obviously we're alleviating the second floor, as you said, yeah, if, if you're going just on the floor
size of the original, how, what are we talking here with the new one in comparison?
It, even without that second floor thing, I think you're still talking about their main floor is,
is about half the size of the previous place.
That was a warehouse and this is like a target and it feels very, very different.
Okay, I won't say it feels super corporate.
I mean, they did a good job of bringing over the posters and everything.
But like, man, just seeing like five cash years in like a neat little area as opposed
to the old free for all where they had 25 cash years.
Yeah.
You know, just everything feels different and worse and it, it feels like it's not going
to be a go to visit for me anymore.
I just don't have the interest.
Now in comparison, I know what you're saying.
It's like what happened with the Alamo draft house by the time it opened in L .A.,
you were like, this isn't the Alamo draft house.
This is just a movie theater that has food in it.
Exactly.
So what, but still that said, in comparison to a regular run of the mill movie theater in L .A.,
the Alamo was still kind of cool.
So in comparison to your run of the mill record store, would you still say this will be a place
to go to when you want to buy something at least?
Or is it not even that good?
I mean, you know, I'd say now it feels like you're holding the wall strip mall L .A.
record store, but with way too many people in it.
So it's, it's kind of like, I mean, thinking about this place not being monitored.
I don't know how people are going to walk around in there because the same amount of
people want to shop and they have so little space.
So it's a bummer.
I made a few purchases.
They also make you buy to validate, which is fine.
They do have a parking garage, which is good.
But just on the whole, it's on Hollywood Boulevard.
The whole feel is different.
I just wasn't a fan.
How far is it from the old one right around the corner?
It's, it's basically right up fine and make a right.
Jeez.
That's a shame.
Let me down.
I mean, they're closing the arc light movie theater, the best, most beloved theater here.
They're closing a lot of joints.
I think, you know, Tarantino will prop up the new Beverly for sure.
Netflix is propping up the Egyptian.
I mean, the fucking boo hoeing online from L .A.
entertainment folk about the arc light closing.
I think it was on the same day as one of the
you know, police recent police killings.
Yeah.
And I only say it that broadly because I've lost track at this point, you know,
because there's so many.
But it was like on the same day as that and people were like, I'm just going to miss
spending.
I mean, just when I would go in there and spend $36 for a ticket to see teenage
mutant interturtles out of their shells.
Yeah.
And by a $16 Jim beam on the rocks, it was just my time at the arc light and it shut
the fuck up.
It was a theater that even when I lived down the street, I went, but I was not a
frequent member because of that.
It got up to $18 a ticket, which is like the highest in the country.
And the dome is cool.
Don't get me wrong.
But like, you're exactly right on the drinks.
Outrageously priced even for a movie theater.
And one of those bars, too, where you're getting the guy pouring it into the
thimble to measure it first.
Oh, yeah, you're not getting just a, you're not getting a bartender, poor.
I mean, you know, his thumbs in the thimble.
So it's splashing the juices underneath his thumbnail are going into your drink.
But then the big issue with it is, now when I moved out here, yeah, it was a big deal.
People were, people love the arc light because you could pick your seat.
And that's what something my aunt used to say to me when I was a little kid.
You go on to the movie theater and I'd go, why?
Because you're picking your seat.
Oh, yeah, my dad just said to me too.
Yeah, but you know, by now, every theater in Los Angeles, you can pick your seat.
The AMCs, the groves, the arc light is nothing special.
Every movie theater in the country, dude.
Yeah, every movie in the country now has individual reclining arm chairs.
Right, you know, like it's, and they never remodeled the arc light.
It's like, it's as good a quality as your standard mall based AMC.
And people treat it like it's this elite experience.
And man, it was a, it was a schlep.
I always got annoyed going there.
You park you to walk so far from when you parked to get to the theater itself.
And then once you got inside, they'd be like, you're up in 17, 17, 17.
Yeah, you're like, what?
Like you walk up those stairs that are like entering the palace of Oz.
You know, the stairs just keep going and going and going and going.
People taking these halfway up the stairs to breast.
Do you ever go when this this happened to me a couple times?
You'd, you'd be like.
Your theater'd be at like the back of the second floor, which is like a mile away from where you buy your ticket.
And you get up there and the snack things upstairs were closed.
Yeah, I've been there.
I've been around call all the way back down.
Yeah, they had good caramel corn.
Yeah, you know, you'd eat it and feel deeply ill, but it was very tasty.
Look, I had a bunch of good times at the arc light. Don't get me wrong.
But and it's probably not done.
You know, they're somebody you'll buy it. I'll be a hero.
It's God, the Twitter, Joe, the Twitter.
I can't anymore, man.
I can't believe and it was me just a year ago, but I can't believe people are still on there like making their little quips.
You know, the world's done, guys.
Enough. It's enough.
I got to be honest, I was surprised too.
I was on there today and I saw a couple random musings, humorous musings from friends quite frankly.
And I just was like, what what even motivates you to do this anymore?
What even drives you to take a walk?
Yeah.
Go talk to your local barista or something.
Just go, go connect to somebody who gives his shit about this.
It's like, okay, there'll be another shooting of an innocent unarmed black person, terrible tragic.
And the officer's name is like officer martyr.
And then you'll watch, you'll watch 1500 people, people who you know are funny at their core.
Right?
More like officer murder.
Yeah.
And get 500 likes.
And I'm just like, what are you people doing sucking each other's dicks?
These aren't funny.
Why do you need to make a man's death into a quip?
Yeah, or why do you, and this is something I've been really, and I want to, I want to write a,
I want to write something about this.
Maybe a stand up joke or something, but why do you have to turn any death into being about yourself?
Like, I mean, it is sickness.
The amount of selfies people post when somebody from any tier of the show business world dies.
It's sick.
It's, it's, they make it about them.
Twitter is to a point where people when they wish happy birthday to somebody are posting selfies.
Yeah.
With the person, sometimes without the person, this is, I've seen that.
This is me at your, remember your 37th.
This is me there.
So shit face.
It's sick, man.
It's sick.
And they're not saying happy birthday to their actual friends who care about them.
It's like, I'm going to give a shout out to Ray Romano because I met him in 1998.
I saw somebody wish a happy birthday to Barbara Streisand the other day.
Yeah.
It was one of the most insane things I've ever seen.
And again, a friend.
Yeah.
It's always like happy birthday, Luciano Pavarotti.
Here's a shot I got of you at the baggage claim at the Bobo airport.
And it's like those.
Who is this for?
Who are we impressed?
I love those.
And I love the ones that are like remembering Vivian Vance on what would have been her 97th birthday.
You're like, who keeps a shit?
Yeah.
It's so crazy.
By the way, here's how sick I am.
Sometimes I'll see like three Vivian Vance posts and be like, am I supposed to be shouting out Viv?
I like Vivian.
You know, it's like it also makes you feel like you're not doing something right because you're not doing it.
It's insane.
That's one of my favorite Jimmy Glick things ever with the Julie Lee.
Yeah.
Who are your influence?
Viv Vance.
She died, Jimmy.
And he starts crying.
I wonder if Marty's short.
He's got to just be a hilarious old man.
He's very funny.
Every interview I've ever.
What's interesting is is when I go back 20 years from now.
I mean, I know he's still funny.
Yeah, yeah.
But I mean, when it's funny, man, when you go back and rewatch, like Martin Short interviews through the years.
Yes.
It's all Jimmy Glick stuff.
It just not in the character.
Like he makes all those same references, the weird celebrities that he references, like chasins, the restaurant, all that stuff.
That's like his repertoire.
And he figured out finally how to put it all into one character where it made total cohesive sense.
But yeah, I thought that was interesting.
I never really.
I watched a clip of him.
Holy shit, man.
It was me and Jay Okerson were hanging out the other day.
We were watching like SNL and SCTV clips on YouTube.
And he had never seen Martin Scorsese's Jerry Lewis live at the Apazzeel, whatever it was.
It was an SCTV sketch.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was supposed to be like the band movie that.
Yeah, right.
It was Jerry Lewis.
Yeah, Jerry Lewis.
Yeah.
And it's, you know, it starts, it's just highlights of the show.
And it starts with Martin Short doing him and just like, like Xanely conducting the orchestra and dancing around.
I remember it well.
Yeah.
He tries to let his cigarette, the flame is that high.
And then it just, as it goes, it devolves into him lecturing the audience about what a genius he is.
And the best part we were laughing so hard is when he's, he's smoking a cigarette and he's ranting at the audience.
And he goes, because these people are afraid of a perfectionist.
And then it cuts out to a wide shot and he's in a baby sailor suit.
Uh -huh.
He goes, whatever 12 year old is running the studio this week.
Yeah.
I love the man.
Funny stuff, man.
He's, um, he is the best.
And the fact, I don't even know if your average Joe finds that super inside Hollywood stuff funny with, with Jim.
And he's satirizing such a specific old time thing that many people are not even aware of.
I don't think they do.
I think that's why it didn't catch on.
I think there's like a big enough demographic that it lasted as long as it did.
Yeah.
And I think that's why the movie was so low budget because it was like, man, you're playing to like a million people at best.
Right.
In this country, you know, yeah.
But I mean, I think too, that's, well, I guess this thing was always going to be to interview celebrities, but.
I think comedy central thought that would potentially carry the show that that would be enough.
Yeah.
I mean, I will say I don't remember anything about this show other than that.
And I watched every episode.
I mean, I remember Michael McKean as the band leader, but I don't really remember much of the sketches in the man on the street.
It's all those interviews.
I regret so much, man, when I know when I met Martin short, all I said to him was I'm a comedian.
I love what your work, Jimmy Glick is the funniest thing I've ever seen.
Yeah.
And he was, and he said, thank you very much in the Jimmy Glick voice to me, which was really cool.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
And he was with Paul Schaefer, which was surreal.
But I regret greatly one time on Better Call Saul.
I met Michael McKean, and I just completely forgot that he was on Jimmy Glick.
I just, it's just, and I regret to this day that I didn't, because he's, he's not on the show anymore.
It's characterized.
And I regret this day that I didn't get to say to him, hey, dude, like Jimmy Glick, holy shit, man.
What was that like?
We talked about video, and he was, I know I could have because I, he was like, what are you doing in your trailer?
And I was like, I just been playing video games, man, waiting for my card to come.
And he's like, do you ever play any name, some game?
And they go, no, and he goes, that's the one I was in.
And I was like, okay.
And I'll, I'll check it out.
But he would have talked, I know he would have talked me about it.
We were just at the, like, the buffet, getting like spaghetti.
For sure.
Yeah.
Damn it.
Are you on the new season of the BCS?
I don't know.
And if I did know, I wouldn't be allowed to say.
All right.
That's how they roll over there.
Real heavy.
Yeah.
You know, it's a big program.
You get the emails for the offers.
And it's, it's like, it says it's going to self -destruct at the end of it.
Like, you know, you're, it's real top secret shit.
Inspector Gadget stole the show runner over there, right?
Yeah.
He's great.
Let's do.
That was a self -destruct joke.
Joe.
I left.
Okay.
I thought you didn't see me left.
I didn't because I'm bringing up the Academy Awards 2021.
Oh, yeah.
No, I left.
I did a quiet.
I was laughing now.
Now, here's what we're talking, folks.
This.
This Academy Awards.
It aired on Sunday.
It was, it was somewhere between the event as we know it and zoom.
The movies this year.
There are.
Look, this was not a great year for film.
Very often I would look at the nominees and go, I don't care.
I don't really, I didn't love any of these.
There were a few good films this year.
There were, there were several good films.
I just don't think we had anything that we talk about as a masterpiece.
Anything we're going to be remembering decades from now.
I really don't.
I don't think there's one movie.
But, um.
Now, Joe, you did, you watched the Oscars highlights.
You've not seen any of the nominated films, correct?
I saw one night in Miami.
Okay, right.
I saw, hold on.
I'm actually pulling up.
I probably should have done this before, but I didn't think I need.
I don't know why I didn't think I would need to Oscar 2021 winners.
Actually, you know, I'm going to go nominations.
So I can see everything.
Excuse me.
I mean, look, we don't, we don't need to talk makeup, hair styling, that kind of stuff.
There's no hilarious choice like J. Edgar.
I saw half of Mank.
It was unwatchable.
Mank, Mank is almost unwatchable.
Yes.
I saw promising young woman as, you know, we did it on the show.
Good.
I saw the trailer for Trial of Chicago seven.
And the trailer, I think I fell asleep 25 seconds into that.
It's a bad film.
The father I have on my shelf.
I do intend to watch it.
Judas in the black Messiah.
I have on my shelf.
I do intend to watch it.
Minari.
I've never heard of.
Sound of metal.
I'm shocked that it's.
I didn't see it, but I did not think it was this like.
Yeah, critical.
A claim.
Whatever.
I thought it was just kind of this little Amazon prime movie, but I guess I was wrong.
I can't believe.
Hillbilly.
Elegy is nominated.
Yeah.
I've seen every, every movie up.
The only one I did not see was wolf walkers, which was an animated apple film that I,
I might watch, but I didn't see it.
I can't believe Borat is nominated.
Borat.
It's insane.
And then they, they read off the 12 writers nominated for best screenplay.
I'm like, guys, that's not a screenplay.
It was improvised.
And if there's 12 writers, what are you doing?
Yeah.
It's just, it's just come on.
And I mean, also, too.
It, the girl Maria.
Back Alova is nominated for best supporting actor.
And it's like.
It's not the same thing, man.
I don't know.
It's just not.
She's great.
And it's crazy.
And it's ballsy.
And it's nuts.
And I think she's got a bright future.
But.
I don't know.
I just don't think that that kind of movie counts in the same.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
A comedic performance does and should count.
I, but I think that they should do what the Golden Globes do.
And do a comedy category and a drama category.
But because comedy never gets nominated, horror never gets nominated.
Really, it's just drama.
Um, I just, I don't even think though it's not because it's comedic.
I think like it's just a different format.
It's like, it's like improvising is different than you're improvising.
You're improvising.
You're dealing with real people.
It's just a different dynamic.
It's a different type of product.
So make a category for that.
If you want.
Right.
Well, it's what they always say.
The only true test would be five actresses performing the same scene.
Or are playing the same character.
Um,
Look, obviously this year, whether or not somebody passed away,
became a huge part of the discussion with Chadwick Boseman.
Um, they give awards for all kinds of reasons.
Many times it's just because they feel it's time.
Al Pacino won, you know, 25 years into his career.
For sent of a woman, which I don't think anybody would say is his best.
Scorsese didn't win best director till the departed,
which is a great film.
But I don't think anybody would say it's Scorsese is best.
Um,
So the Oscars, while being more legit than the Golden Globes,
which they basically decide by letting an eagle fly up into the sun
and then coming back with the winners.
That's about as much thought as they put into it.
Right.
The Oscars are still kind of bullshit.
Let's be real.
Uh,
This year, the fact that people really upset because Chadwick Boseman didn't win.
It's like.
He was a very young man who passed away tragically.
And his career was still pretty new.
You know, that was a supporting role that he played in in Ma Rainy's black bottom.
Anthony Hopkins is one of the best actors of all time.
And his work and the father is one of his best performances.
I mean, to beat the man up because he won.
He's 83.
He's doesn't want to travel.
He said, by the way, now that I'm 83, I can tell you, I'm autistic.
I don't like being around people, especially not in crowds when there's COVID going on.
I'm 83 years old.
And I still saw tweets that are like fuck Anthony Hopkins.
Yeah, I think the, uh, the curvy critic, I think her name is actually had a good take on this.
I watched her on entertainment.
Tonight's review highlights of the Oscars.
Wait, isn't wasn't she in living Biblically?
Is that the curvy critic?
I mean, I think she goes the same lady.
Wait a minute.
Is that living Biblically?
I'm pretty Carla Ranata.
Yeah, she goes by the curvy critic.
Oh, I didn't even recognize her.
That's great.
She, uh, yeah, excuse me.
I was just about to, uh, a very, uh, a small role in the pilot of Biblically.
And we liked her so much.
We brought her back.
Whereas I had a large role in the pilot of Biblically and was immediately removed from the program.
Yeah, but that's neither here nor there.
Uh, Carla's great.
She's very nice.
I didn't even recognize her.
Um, that's, that's awesome that that's her.
Well, I was going to say a nice thing about her commentary.
She was like, because the, the co -host on E was like, or the entertainment tonight was like,
I mean, I just thought Anthony should have been there.
And Carla was like, he's 83.
Yeah.
If he, he's earned the, he's earned the spot to, to say, like, I'm not coming, you know.
And it's like, yeah, especially during a pandemic.
And she was like, look, I'm disappointed in a jet, Chadwick Boseman didn't win.
But no, no, shade it, uh, uh, uh, Anthony Hopkins or anything like that.
And I, you know, he's great and blah, blah, blah, blah.
Which I think it's a fair response.
It's the people being like, fuck him.
Like you just said where I'm like, yeah, would you come on, man?
Like, what, what, what is this thing suddenly where it's like, just because I want this,
if I don't get it, the only reaction is spiteful, seething anger.
Right.
Like there is no more just like, well, I'm disappointed.
I'm just, okay, I know it's, it's like, fuck you.
It's, it's really gross, man.
So when you see somebody like Carla on entertainment tonight have like this, this, this balance take on it
and a rational take, which is I wanted Boseman to win.
He didn't win.
I'm disappointed in that.
But hey, Anthony Hopkins did a good job.
And yeah, he's 83.
Sad home.
What are you going to do?
Yeah.
I mean, if your grandpa was 83 and was going to fly from England to America to go sit in a train station
and potentially accept an award, I would hope you'd go grandpa.
You need to stay home.
That's what his whole family was doing.
This is the people think he's famous.
He doesn't have a grand kid or a son or a daughter going, you're not going, dad.
Right.
You're not flying to the stupid fucking Oscars.
You know.
And by the way, when they probably thought he was going to lose anyway, they were like, oh, shit, you won.
Sorry about that.
Well, that's what made it such a glaring issue is that Alec are, I'm sorry.
Anthony Hopkins was very, very much like I never expected to win.
I guarantee it.
I promise you.
I did not think I was going to win because everyone thought it was his.
Chadwick Boseman's to win.
The Oscar producers were so sure of it that for the first time in my life, they put actor and actress after best picture.
So they clearly were going to like, let's end on a tribute to Chadwick Boseman.
And that's a huge error on their part.
I look bad, but that's their fault.
I agree with that.
I did agree with the tweets I saw that said, Chadwick Boseman deserved to not be used as bait like this.
I hundred percent agree with that.
That's exactly what they did.
And I'll say what I always say about Hollywood.
It doesn't matter if you're white, black, Hispanic, Asian, stop looking to them to do the right thing.
They will never, and it's got nothing to do with the fact that Anthony Hopkins won and Chadwick doesn't.
It's got everything to do with the fact of how they position that award.
And played on your emotions and expectations about Chadwick Boseman and then knew exactly what they were doing.
They knew how to retain viewers to the end of an extremely painfully boring fucking ceremony.
That's painfully boring when there are no health restrictions.
Okay.
This, this pair down version of it was not going to be an excitement fest.
God bless Arnold Schwarzenegger coming out and just shitting all over it.
Oh, I miss that.
He just came out and he was like, it's so boring.
It's so boring.
I was like, God bless this guy.
How great is it?
But I'm.
And for Soderberg to be the guy.
When they brought Soderberg in as producer, it's usually some, you know, I've interviewed the guy before the guy who does the Oscars and the guy who does the Grammys.
They're old dinosaurs and the Oscars and the ward shows reflect that.
Soderberg is a very cool guy who knows everything about film production, who knows everything about how to make things fun and exciting and interesting.
And he didn't do a good job.
It was a bad show.
A very bad show.
It was a terrible show.
I have a lot to say because I'd have watched the highlights.
Yeah.
I did watch the highlights, which is all you really need because they kind of they kind of filter out all the stuff.
Let's start with.
Now a lot of people are upset that Chadwick Boseman didn't win.
I would like to say I'm thrilled.
Not that Chadwick, I'm thrilled about somebody else winning that actually did win.
I am thrilled that you thank God once again.
The world's most miserable woman.
And Francis McDormand got to win another award.
I mean, what an unsufferable human being.
That speech.
I wanted to fucking puke.
I feel so bad for whichever Cohen is married to her.
Whatever living hell that is.
That comes clearly is coming across in every Cohen brothers movie now that ends with like utter disaster and pain.
Just fucking miserable, man.
Now the common brothers are the best.
The greatest.
Love him.
Francis McDormand.
A very good actress.
She's already won twice, deservedly so in Fargo.
And she was good in three billboards.
A third Oscar for her seems a bit much.
And I will agree with you.
I have always loved her as the person.
I have only heard the nicest of things about her, but those speeches and the whole like.
Get the camera off of me while I'm going up to accept the Academy Award.
What was that?
I didn't see that.
She's going like, and like stop.
Get the camera off.
I mean, it's just then don't go to the ceremony, Francis.
Don't sit there.
Sit home.
Boycott.
I'm so tired of this shit.
We're going to come in and and and fucking act halfway.
Like we get this, but we're like, it's just ridiculous.
It's stupid.
It's like if you think that something is unethical, then don't be a part of it.
That's it.
It's that fucking simple, man.
It's that simple.
I'm sorry.
Like they are positioning her to be to be the next.
You know, they're kind of, I feel like what they're doing with Frances McDormand.
And this is not me saying Merrill Streep is done.
I think Merrill Streep's got a lot of juice in the tank still.
But Frances McDormand is younger than Merrill Streep.
And I think they're trying to position Frances McDormand to be the person
that kind of steps into that role now is the sort of the mother of Hollywood.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
The matriarch of Hollywood.
And I think that's what they're doing.
And the fact that she gets up and goes, I have no words.
My words are my sword.
And my sword is my work.
Yeah.
And you won't know how much I love my sword or something.
I love to work.
And she goes, yeah.
That's it.
Walks off.
Doesn't thank anybody involved with the movie.
Including the ancient woman that directed her work.
That made history.
The ancient woman that made history.
She doesn't mention her name.
She did, she did do a wolf howl, which I guess was a shout out to some crew member
who died with the last name of wolf.
Okay.
Yeah.
She was up there twice and she came off pretty annoying.
And they cut to Joel and he looked a little annoyed.
Although when I've seen him in the past and he gets emotional,
I think they have a lot of love and respect for each other.
But her displays up there on stage are the kind of things that the coen brothers
love.
And it must be difficult for him.
It must be.
I mean, look, after I read the Sam Raimi thing,
but when he talked about dark man and.
Yeah.
And he was like, well, I thought Francis.
I thought I understood her, but I don't know that I did.
Yeah.
And then her quotes are like, that's the only bimbo I've ever played.
And it's right.
I'm just like Jesus Christ.
You know, and it's like, you know, Francis,
you do have words because two years ago,
when you won, you lectured everybody.
So don't act like now all of a sudden, you're, you know,
you're the quiet church mouse that just wants to quietly,
you know, be, you know, I'm so humble in it.
Oh, bullshit.
Get out of my face.
I can't stand her.
I think.
I think there are people more deserving of hate than a Fran McDormand.
But I will say she's a she's become a bit annoying.
It's too much for me anymore with.
Yeah.
Um, was.
No, no, no, no, had land a good movie.
Well, let's start with, with actress since we just did.
Uh, the nominees were Viola Davis from my rainy.
She was good.
I mean, Viola Davis gives three Oscar worthy performances a year.
You know, yes.
I agree.
Francis McDormand, uh, has now won best actress more times than Marl Street.
Marl Street has, has some supporting sprinkled in.
So she's actually like the number one at this point.
Um,
Andrew Day for the United States versus Billy holiday.
I watched this.
It was done by Lee Daniels who did, uh, precious.
So you're in for a wild ride.
There's lots of fucking in the film.
It opens with Leslie Jordan wearing a three foot tall,
Liberace wig going.
Now tell me.
Why do people hate Billy holiday?
And it is.
Who's he playing?
Some like radio DJ.
You know, but it's.
The movie is wild.
I found it pretty entertaining.
Andrew Day does a good job of, of being Billy holiday, you know.
Uh, that's the only thing that movie would be nominated for was her performance.
But that's a Kirby and pieces of a woman.
Uh, it's just one of those pain and suffering movies where a woman's like losing a child
and you watch her cry a lot.
It's got shy love buff.
I barely remember watching the film.
And then Carrie Mulligan promising a young woman who was really good in a challenging role in a really good movie.
Those were the actress nominees.
No madland.
Me and my wife didn't care for it.
It's one of those where I'm like, should I watch it again?
But I'm probably not going to.
Oh, everybody's like giving her accolades because she actually lived in the van.
Right during the movie.
And it's like, yeah, that's not acting.
Yeah, put me in a van and pull me out and yell action.
I'll be convincing as a guy that lives in a van.
Joe between us.
You're convincing as a guy who lives in a van right now.
Uh, she shits in a bucket.
She has violent diarrhea in a bucket at one point, you know.
Um, who has no madland.
I've heard that the IMAX experience makes it great.
You know, it's a lot of being shot outside, you know, great landscapes and stuff.
But at the end of the day, the movie, it's politics are a little weird.
They're using actual people who do live off the land as extras.
And you probably, and, you know, also actors in the film.
I don't think they were paid very well.
I, you don't see them at the Oscars, you know, or maybe you did.
I don't know.
Maybe they were in the audience.
It's just the kind of thing Hollywood loves to do where it's like,
let's, let's shine a light on this.
These overlooked people.
And let's live like them for three months.
And pretend that we are as, as, as, yeah.
You know, this is all deserving of praise as they are.
This is all, this is all trenchacing.
No bandland one, because a lot of people in Hollywood that work in the entertainment business during
COVID went out and bought super sized A plus plus plus top of the line RVs.
And went and lived on the road to have an existential journey as, as they kept their,
their million dollar homes under close watch with their, with their dog sitters and their,
and their house cleaners and, and whatever the fuck else.
Yeah.
It's bullshit.
They know it's a trend in Hollywood right now.
So they gave it an award.
That's what it is.
They want to pat themselves on the back.
They want to make the people that are making the wheel stirred feel good.
So they gave it an award.
They gave Anthony Hopkins an award and not Chadwick bows in the award.
Why?
Because Hollywood has been criticized heavily over the last year for its neglecting of old people.
As was many other institutions in this country.
Right.
Our government in particular because of the neglecting of, so what are we to?
Oh, we've got an 83 year old guy.
He'll be the oldest person in history to win an Oscar if we give this to him.
So they give it to him.
They're, they're, they're passive aggressive and far as I'm concerned.
And you may say that this is too, not you or whoever may say this is too venomous.
But I don't think it is.
They are saying Chadwick Boseman, your time has passed.
We paid tribute to black people last year.
This year, we are going to give an award to an old man because that is what has come
under fire as treatment of old people this year.
We are going to give it, we are going to give an award to, way too many awards to a movie
that shines a light on the poor and desolate that roam the fucking barren wasteland of this country,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
Because that makes us feel good.
And what a coincidence.
What a coincidence.
Just as Asian hate crimes are coming into the forefront of the media and this terrible,
terrible thing is happening to Asian people.
What seems to be much more prevalent than ever, ever before.
All of a sudden they break all the records.
And they set just in time, Oscars.
You give awards to Asian people for the, I mean, if this is so disgustingly transparent to me,
not because these people aren't overlooked, not because these people don't deserve awards.
Obviously, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying this is pandering in its worst form.
It is insulting.
It is rich, white giving things to people and telling them with a pad on the head,
I hope you're happy now.
And I think it's really, really fucking gross.
I really do.
I'm offended by it.
I agree for the most part.
All of these people left union station and drove right past get row.
And how many of these Academy award nominees and winners do you think lock their doors?
And how many of them do you think walked out and gave them $500 to support the,
they'll go see the move, not even go see it, they'll watch the screen or the movie, they'll vote.
But they were in the epicenter of homelessness where our city is turning to homelessness
because people can't afford rent.
They're not helping any of these people.
I assure you.
And by the way, Pat, union station, the very place where they told people who were going
to get COVID tests, regular working people, sorry, you can't come.
We're shooting the she's all that remake today.
Yeah.
Remember that?
No, that was that union.
I remember it.
And everyone downtown on Sunday was told basically you have to stay in your homes.
That's, that's what LA thinks of the movie industry and what they think of you.
Like you're not leaving your home on Sunday because we've got the Oscars.
Like they posted signs up and expect people to go, OK, OK, sure.
Instead of before it's this country's number one export is entertainment.
And if you think that this is any more dignified or reputable or ethical than the
wheel industry or wall street banking, you're out of your fucking mind.
This is a multi billion dollar international worldwide export period.
That's, it's as simple as it gets, which makes it gross that they also want to pretend
that they're the beacons of charity as well.
Don't, don't do that, you know, just admit what you are.
Right.
It's all where you can.
Don't also say we're great while we do all this terrible shit.
Right.
No, it's when you, it's when it's like when you get the, you get the box in the mail from Amazon.
And it has like black tape on it.
And it's like it's supportive BLM Amazon is taking a stand.
Yeah.
OK, guys.
All right.
In the midst of all this, Amazon was sending out individual packages for bad shows in a lot
of cases.
I know Amazon has some good shows.
But Amazon sends, they'll send you like a music box that you twist in the ceramic ballerina
spins around.
And it's like, this cost $60.
And no one votes for it.
And the show, you know, doesn't get, they're just throwing money away in the middle of all
this.
And it's like, give it to homeless.
I got it.
I got to miss Maisel one that was like a full purse with like lipstick in it.
Yes.
What the hell are you going to do with that?
But I give it to my wife and she's like, what the hell am I going to do with this?
It's for nobody.
It's for it is for you to go get this fucking thing out of my way for like a month in the house.
So that maybe it sticks in your mind as opposed to like watching it and having it stick in
your mind.
I can't tell you how it goes from my door to the garbage faster than a quarter pounder wrapper.
I don't even, I throw it away immediately.
Sure.
Yes.
It's just such a waste of money, man.
Oh my God.
And then he can't give him away because they tell you it's illegal.
I was watching the father of the other day and they made me swear that I'd cut it in half
at the end of it.
I'm like, fuck you.
Sent this to me.
It's mine now.
All right.
I'm going to go through just the major categories.
So director was Chloe Zhao for nomad land.
She's doing the next marvels.
The eternals with, you know, Camille can herrington a bunch of actors.
She's, you look, visually she's got a strong sense about her.
I'm not familiar with Chloe Zhao.
She emerged on the scene as like, you know, the biggest director in town.
You know, these things can either flame out or she'll be around forever.
Good for her for winning.
Nice.
Emerald Fennel was nominated for promising young woman.
Good for her except as I told you, she unfollowed me on Twitter when I followed her.
Not mentioned at the ceremony for some reason.
Lee I think deserve that win.
By the way, from what I've seen of this stuff.
Or I love viola.
As viola Davis won yet.
Any.
An Oscar.
She did.
She won.
And she won for doubt or fences.
For fences.
I think that's right.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Isaac Chung for Minari.
I thought Minari was pretty good.
You know, it's.
It's the the immigrant experience kind of told without really any story.
It's shut.
Kind of cool, but it ultimately didn't move me or, or.
You know it's a pretty well done version of the immigrant story.
David Fincher who is a great director.
Mank is his worst movie and to nominate him for best director is absurd, Thomas.
I would say it was cool.
It was coley directed.
That's the only redeeming quality.
and I thought Holman's performance was fine. I don't think it was a best actor nominated
for nomination worthy performance. But I will say out of everything, the visual aspect
of that film was what made it cool. Maybe give it best cinematography nomination. It won.
It did win for best cinematography. Okay. All right. Well, then that I, you know, I could
at least see. Yeah. And then the last nominee was Thomas Vinterberg for another round with
Matt Meckleson. Now that's a movie I think I told you about Joe where four guys and they're
four. It's kind of like husbands, you know, four guys decide. Let's all be a little drunk
at all times as an experiment. The capitalist already remaking it, you know, it's a, it's
a good movie. It's entertaining. Not a great movie, but it's a good movie. And the director
when he got up there for screenplay or our foreign language film that won best foreign language
film, he talked about how his daughter was killed in a car accident, like a weekend
to filming. So then the movie became a celebration of her life. And I was thinking your daughter
dies in a car accident on a Friday and then Monday, you're back at the shoot. Look, that's
not my business. But like, come on, man. I don't know. He seemed like a cool guy. I liked
another round. I'd like to see it, but it's subtitles. It is. Yeah. And it subtitles
turn me on. No, it's not. No, it's not. It's, it's Dutch. It's English. But it won best foreign
language film. I don't know what the hell is going on anymore with this. Another, because
it's from Denmark. Yeah, but doesn't it have to be not in English to win best foreign? Look
at this. They changed it to international feature film. I didn't even notice that. Okay.
All right. So yeah, for average or actor, we've already kind of covered, but it was Anthony
Hopkins. Look, the movie, the father, I'll never watch it again. It gives you an idea of
what it's like to have Alzheimer's. It really puts you in those shoes. If that's an experience
you want, have at it. But Anthony Hopkins was undeniably incredible in it. Nobody saw the
movie. So everyone just gets angry at him. It's one of his best performances. It's easily
one of his best performances. And I think you deserve to win. The only reason I wouldn't,
you know, Chadwick Boseman, I think it was a it was a honorary Oscar, if he would have
gotten it. And I think he should have been put up in supporting category. But you know,
what these things go on, like the two actors, Lequith, Stanfield and Daniel Colluea from the
Black Messiah. Basically, those two guys had to be put up against each other as best supporting
because they put Chadwick up for actor. It's like they try to balance out the black performances
and yeah, it's it's not. It's just not a good way of doing things. I also saw that movie
by the way. She was great in it. I would have been happy with her winning, but she's she's
been great in a lot of things. She's kind of had her day. But yeah, it's it's a really good
movie, the father. I liked it a lot. Riz Ahmed would have been my second choice for Sound
of Metal. It's a great performance in a really good movie. I like that movie a lot. Stephen
Yoon from Inari. I don't understand why he's up Gary Oldman from Mac. I don't understand
why he's up for the award. Yeah. Did you know that Gary Oldman dated Uma Thurman and then
they got married when she was like 19? I think I knew that and I forgot. I mean, he was younger
too. I think it was 30 and 19 or something, but what an odd couple. And then on to Ethan
Hawk. I don't know. Oh, man. Oldman and Thurman make sense to me. They seem like two
like sort of fair enough. In that period, like two kind of brooding actors, you know, on
the indie scene. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, I want to talk about Welsh. Let me just interject
with one of the other things I saw take place at this place. When Rail came out and did
the game. No, we got to talk about that. Now, first of all, two actors, Glenn Close, and
the first woman he went to whose name I don't know. I didn't know. I didn't recognize her.
That was the lady from the Billy Holiday movie. Oh, that was the actor from who played
Billy Holiday. Both of them did this thing where it's like, hey, did purple rain? Well, hers
was purple rain. Was it dominant? And she's like, well, it's a good song. So probably
not in this fucking bullshit or whatever she said. They believe it out. And you're like, again,
I say to you what I said to McDorman, then don't go to the thing. I'm not saying go to the
thing. I'm not saying you're lucky to be at the thing. I'm not saying you should appreciate
the thing. I'm saying none of those things. I'm saying the thing sucks. Yeah. We cut the
thing. Why are you there? If you think they're assholes, they are assholes. Don't go to the
thing. Right. And also you're nominated. Yeah. It's hard to be angry that the system is
racist when you're nominated. You know, it is. Don't get me wrong. But it's an odd stance
to take when you're sitting there nominated for best actress to be like, well, you know,
they didn't nominate Prince. It's like, when, when, when can we all be okay? You know,
when does every award have to not be a political statement where it's like the Asian woman
got it. That's good. That checks off. It used to be only women. They used to only care
about women getting more awards. Then immediately it turned into, okay, guys, it's embarrassing
that no black people have won. And I agree. It's all embarrassing. Okay. So let's do that.
Then this year Asian Asian is the focus. And look, it's all in theory, great. But when
each year will, okay, we'll award this group of people because they had the roughest time
this year. And then next year we'll say, fuck them and bring in exactly what they're
going to do. What are we going to do? They did it to women already. They did it to it.
They did every woman, everybody wore black to support the women and this and that. And
that was enough of that. And last year they did it with black actors. And that was enough
of that. Now they're on the Asian people. I wonder if they think we fixed the problem
with women. And now we're on to black people. And we fixed the problem with. They don't look
at it as they don't look at it as they don't look at it as a real problem. And they don't
look at it as a real solution. They look at it as a fed. This is trending right now. So
we need to be a part of it. Doesn't matter what it is. If it was Polish jokes are now offensive
and the most racist things on planet earth. And we've been telling them for too many years,
that would be the the crux and the focus of the show. That's it. Period. But my thing is
too. I didn't even when she said that I didn't even take it as a racial thing. I took
it as a quality thing where she was basically saying like anything good doesn't get nominated.
And it's like and then two seconds later either you're nominated. Yeah, you're nominated.
So it's it's a weird thing to say when you're nominated because you're making a commentary
on the judgment of the people that are saying you're great. Right. But then on top of it,
two seconds later, the next question was about Donna Summer and it was about how she won.
Yeah. So the thing this woman just said that all these fucking white people in the audience that
are rich and whatever and you know, cheer about and everything and who gets immediately
contradicted and and invalidated when they say Donna Summer won. So now if you were just
cheering for what she said, you're kind of cheering to say anything that's been nominated or has
ever won is bad. But the next thing they had brought up was a black female artist that got nominated
in one. It's so fucking nuts, man. It's so nuts and it's so much posturing and it's so much whatever
down to the fact that when they finally get to Glenn close. Jesus Christ, dude, Glenn close says the
same thing. The first lady says about the butt. I'm a huge rap fan, huge. I've been listening to it
my whole life, my collection adorns my walls. I'm not exaggerating. I have been listening to hip hop
all my life. I like go -go music. I'm a fan. I love the culture. The butt is not a fucking Oscar winner.
I'm sorry. Purple Rain is. Yeah. I think yourself is. The butt is not. I think they knew that. I
think that was the joke with Glenn close. The bit was very baffling and a lot of people thought Glenn
close actually knew about the butt, which is kind of crazy. I agree with you. How did she
rat all that? They just gave her that info, I guess? It's a scripted bit. The only thing that wasn't
scripted was she stood up and shook her ass, which I thought was kind of funny. She had to kind of do
something because she knew she didn't deserve to be up there for hillbilly allergy. That little bit
with Rale to me was the only place where the awards showed any kind of life. I agree with you that
its message was baffling, but it was at least some sort of spontaneity. It was some sort of spontaneity,
but it was like, what are we doing here? We're at the end of the show, too. You've got grown,
I think Rale's either 32 or 56. I've never known, but my point is, this is a grown man they have
coming out going, we're going to play a game everybody. What do we at a senior home right now?
What the hell is this? What is going on? I don't know. I don't know, but it was really one of the few
attempts at comedy. All the presenters didn't even have jokes. It felt like going
to your grandpa's retirement ceremony at a hotel. It just felt boring. One thing I do want to stress
is that, Joe and I, I think we're both being very clear with this. We love inclusion. We're all
about inclusion. The way that Hollywood and the Oscars goes about awarding diversity is gross.
It's needed. They do their doing a job. I don't know if it's a good or a bad job, but the way
they go about it is often very gross. I don't know how else to say it because it's not real inclusion.
It's pandering. I can tell you from one of the few things I have actual first -hand experience in,
I can tell you as one of a small handful of white comedians that started in an all black comedy club,
I know what pandering is, and there was nothing more embarrassing than when some white guy that had
never set foot in the city would go up on stage in front of an inner city audience. The entire audience,
and I'm saying that because that's where they were from. They were from the inner city of Philadelphia.
They'd go up in front of that audience and go like, what's up, yo? I'm here with my peeps, dog. A guy
would pull out, there was a guy named Mike Rage, Jesus fucking Christ on his cross. He would pull out a
thing of peeps, marshmallow peeps, and he'd go, I'm just chilling with my peeps,
and it would get laughs because it was like, look at me, I suck, I'm white, I'm doing the thing
that the black guys do, and it was pandering, and black comics, two -ray Gordon mentored me,
pulled me aside, and was early on, and was like, dude, you're doing the right thing, you're being
yourself. That's what you got to do. It's going to be a harder road, but you got to be yourself.
And I did, and then the next thing, you know, you're up in front of that audience,
and you're the minority guy in the room, and you're having a great fucking show because everybody's
just being honest with everybody, and it's awesome. That's what, that to me is what inclusion is.
Hey, man, I'm going to be honest with you, you'll be honest with me, and we're just going to talk and
accept one another. This shit that the Oscars does, and Holly, what award shows in general do,
it's pandering, and pandering is condescension. That's, it's nothing greater than that.
You're talking down to somebody and saying, I've got you figured out, I know what you're all about.
I'm going to come down to your level for a minute. So you, it's gross, man, it's fucking gross and
insulting. And that said, if they nominate you, I mean, I take the award because it's going to
help you get some footing, I guess, right? I mean, I don't know. I mean, I always bitch about
these things. And if anybody gave me an award, of course, I'd be there. But I mean, I don't know.
So maybe the lady is right to sit there and go, yeah, I'm nominated, but this fucking is bullshit.
I don't know. I don't know what the answer is. It's confusing. I don't either.
We know where we're coming from. Everybody knows who we're coming from. Yes. And if you don't,
you should. That's our supporting actor. Oh, shit. Oh, we still got, how many more do we have?
I'm just going to run through the main categories. Sasha Baron Conn for trial, the Chicago 7 was one
of the worst performances of the year. And it was embarrassing. Dana Kluya was awesome.
And Judas in the black Messiah, a deserving winner. I watched. He walked over to address the press
after winning. And a woman said, what was it like working with Regina King as your director,
because she thought he was Leslie Adam Jr. Oh, boy. And if you want to watch it, he handles it. He
handles it with grace. He really does. But you can tell he wants to scream at this audience's face.
And it's worth watching the clip. And by the way, that's another thing I want to stress.
Joe and I do not think that racism is not a problem. We do not think that that things need major change.
I mean, he walked off winning the Oscar. And they just took him for another black actor. It's insane.
Yeah, it is insane. It's absolutely insane. You're absolutely right. I'm just saying going to the
Oscars to fix racism is like going to the bank to fix poverty. It's exactly right. You know,
Leslie Adam Jr. was good in one night in Miami. That movie was not my thing. Joe liked it more
than me. Paul Racy is that is deaf. And he also plays in a black Sabbath cover band here in
Los Angeles. He's a non actor who was incredible in sound of metal. And actually deaf. Yeah.
How does he play in the band? Are you know, hearing impaired? Okay. Okay.
Leakeeth Sandfeld for Judas and Black Messiah was also great. Yeah. Colleague deserving winner.
Bakalova, Horat, Glenn Close, Hillbilly Elegy, Coleman the father, Amanda C. Fried for
Mank. So basically we're talking about one good performance there. Olivia Coleman. And
the end Bakalova, you know, she's got a big career ahead of her. She's in Appetale's next movie,
et cetera. The winner was you Jung Yone for Menari, who was good. I like that woman a lot. Her
speech was funny. She called out Brad Pitt for never coming to set. He's one of the producers.
Do you see that moment? No, I didn't see that. She was like, it's so good to meet you, Brad. She's
like, I wonder why you never came to set in Atlanta when we were shooting. It was very funny. It was
rough because you know, that's what these people do. They're like, yes, obviously I produce Menari
because I care about it, but he was never on set. It's, it's a tale as old as time.
So for best picture, the nominees were no madland, the father, Judas and the black Messiah,
Mank, Menari, promising young woman, sound of metal and the trial of the Chicago Seven. I think the
worst of those movies is trial of the Chicago Seven or Mank. The best is probably promising young
woman, sound of metal, the father, but none of these movies rank above a B plus for me. And
and that's just kind of the year that we got. It was a shit year. The fact that we had an Oscars
at all is a hilarious that Hollywood still felt we needed this in a year where we had the pandemic.
Yeah, no, yeah. It's all like, you know, we kept the tradition up whatever fun. We need this. Everybody
goes spend $20 ,000 on address as people lose their complete lives and end up in, yeah, this is
this is the time. And it was the lowest rated Oscars in the history of the ceremony. That makes me
happy. I hope they keep dropping. I really do. Yeah. That is it. I won't go through, you know, your
screenplays and all that. I will say documentary was a pretty strong category. The worst of the nominees,
my octopus teacher one, but I would highly recommend collective in particular as a great doc.
The other docs are fun too. And the ceremony was a mess. Congrats to soul for winning best animated.
That's congrats to soul. Yeah. Trent Rezner winning for scoring a Pixar movie. Always interesting.
Trent Rezner scored soul. Yep. He did. Yeah, him and that guy Atticus, they did social network and do
that. That I knew. I didn't think he scored soul. That's interesting. All right, folks,
well, that's our show. See, that's our assets almost an hour 20 there. That's why we don't do segments
on these specialty apps. Anyway, we're back next time right after this with a strong review.
Not mean I'm not going to say if we like to or not, I'm just going to say it's going to be a strong
review of the mortal combat 2021 adaptation. Something I waited quite some time for.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter. And if you want to hear more of me, you can check out
Taste Buds, the other podcast I do where I also plug this show. What I'm on it.
New episodes 4K YouTube, 11 a .m. every Monday, audio wherever you get your audio every week.
You need 4K to look at you in San Volcano talking about whether nerds are better than sprees.
Listen, you want to you want to break my balls? You want to break my balls?
The Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram. I'm on my buddy Jimmy Smagula's podcast, Baby Mouth.
I am also, what else am I doing, Joe? Anything? Do I have anything going on?
I got nothing. I go over to my friend's house and argue about cheesecake.
I got nothing going on here. I don't got much either. All right. Well, if you want to listen to
the special Mike Nichols edition of Pat Sola movie corner, I went through all 21 of his films,
which I watched or rewatched, and you can check that out on Patreon. Thank you all for joining us on Patreon.
Thank you, Emily, as always, for all your help. Also, Emily told me that she is now showcasing
shitty horror movies on Instagram, as particularly Instagram stories. So she's back, she's posting,
check it out. She started Emily's horror -able stories corner. It's going to be clips of terrible,
wonderful horror movies. So check it out. We will see you guys next time and we'll see you in hell.