I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
We're here today to talk movies.
As always, I'm Joe DeRosa, and I'm Patrick Walsh, and today we'll be discussing
M Night Shyamalan's old film about the beach that makes you old.
Yes, yes, that really is the plot of the film.
I saw, usually it's not jokes that break me, although lately on Twitter I just see no
matter what the topic is, I see a hundred people in a row, people I respect make the same
exact joke, and you're like, you all follow each other, do you not see this?
That's what Twitter has really become, it's sad, it's pathetic, there's no original jokes
coming out of the thing, but there were so many jokes about old and the beach that makes
you old that I again, nearly deleted my account, it's time to delete my account, it just
makes me furious, they're not, they're weren't funny, it's just like, the whole of Twitter
now is like little memes, little expressions that just get slightly altered, you know, like
everyone changes one word of the professional comedians coming through with, I saw a lot of
people changing song lyrics to be about the beach from old, I'm just like, what are
you doing?
I know we're all bored, but yeah, my God, it's the worst time for comedy, the worst time.
It's not a good time, it's not a good time, I'd imagine a lot of dumb like, you know, going
to the beach was embarrassing enough, yeah, now this, it makes me, yeah, or the beach that
ages you, or as I call it, the beach, I saw that 5 million times, that doesn't make
sense.
Is that a joke?
I guess because sun ages you, it's like, is this some sort of hard hitting take that you
have here?
Jesus.
All right, well, hey, what can you do, what can you do?
I, I think it's this compulsion, people, and I had it a little bit too, you know, like
just at the beginning of the pandemic where you're like, I guess I should just keep making
jokes, but then it hits a point where you're just making jokes to like do something and
we have to read this shit.
It's pretty wild.
Yeah, it's a bad time for entertainment in general, as we always talk about on here, did
you hear about this?
I guess this would be a new cycle, did you hear about, yeah, Scarlett Johansson is suing
Disney.
I almost brought it up in the last one, but I thought there might be a little more juice
to it.
So yeah, it's Scar Jo suing Disney because of Black Widow, I saw Black Widow, I fell asleep
at the 45 minute mark, I despised it, but I can't really rate it fairly because I only
watched 45 minutes and was awoken by people pushing past me.
That's how deeply I fell asleep.
Sober is a judge daytime show, by the way, after a full night of sleep.
But yeah, she's suing because she's like, and look, you're never going to get fucking
sympathy when you're suing because you're supposed to get 40 million and you only got
20 million, but those aren't the actual numbers either.
She's saying, when you, you promised me that you were going to give this a theatrical release
in my contract, and that I would get my salary, the bulk of my salary from getting, you know,
they get a percentage of the back end in some of these big projects when they did a dual
release on Disney plus and theatrically, she's claiming she lost out on a ton of revenue.
And look, if you're willing to look past it being 100 millionaire bitching about wanting
to be richer, I agree with her.
It's like, you can't just suddenly dump something on Disney plus so you get incredibly rich
off it and the actors who are supposed to profit from it get nothing.
It's not fair per se.
Now Emma Stone is apparently putting together a lawsuit for Cruella, same exact issue.
And Disney comes through and tries to act like their sympathetic throughout all this and says,
apparently Scarlett Johansson doesn't realize that we're in a global pandemic.
She doesn't care about all this whatever.
And then her agent comes out and says, how dare you criticize Miss Johansson's good name?
And meanwhile, the world is falling into shit.
You know, there are bigger issues, but I do think that this is going to be a huge topic going
forward. And if Scarlett Johansson were to win, odds are they'll set a lot of court because they
don't want this to set a precedent. But they got a leg to stand on all these movies that got dumped
on HBO Max and etc. Those actors are going to have some valid complaints.
And if the studios have to start paying up, I mean, that's going to get crazy.
We're talking about hundreds of millions of dollars in payouts.
And everybody's pretending they got no money.
You know, I'm setting up a pitch now and you hear places say like, we don't have any money.
And then they release Kong versus Frankenstein or whatever.
It's nuts.
You know, I can't say I'm rooting for Scarlett Johansson or Emma Stone to win this or anything.
And there's no real winner here. But I do think if you're promised a portion of the gross
and half the people watch it on streaming, that's fucked up.
Well, let this be let this be known.
This is a moment and everybody should be paying attention to it.
That this is what this is what entertainment has finally fully become.
This is Wall Street now.
You're watching a multi multi multi millionaire who could
who got a laugh on the joke when she hosted us an L about Colin and you know,
what do we need the money Colin, you know, about his job and you know,
get a huge laugh for a reason.
But you're watching a millionaire, however many times over,
sue a conglomerate, evil rotten corporation,
sucking up everything it can in sight.
We are now down to, so is there a winner?
Well, I guess I'm rooting more for Scarlett Johansson than I am for Disney, obviously.
Because Disney does sound to be in breach of contract and Disney's pretty awful.
But at the same time, it's a hard situation to feel sympathy for
because we're talking about millions of dollars versus millions of dollars.
But, you know, I was talking with a friend about this last night.
It is officially big banking in Wall Street.
You've got four entertainment companies now.
There's Warner Brothers, there's Paramount,
there's Disney, and there's Fox.
And that's it.
Those are your four choices.
Well, Disney bought Fox.
Oh, Disney bought Fox.
Yeah.
So Universal, I guess.
Please.
Universal's got fast and the furious.
I mean, that's keeping them afloat.
Yeah. I know.
But Universal isn't, it hasn't been, at least as far as I know,
isn't buying up all these other properties.
I mean, if you go on to Paramount Plus and you look at the amount of properties
that belong to Paramount Plus,
if you go and you see what Disney now owns,
and if you look at what Warner Brothers now owns,
you know, and they're, they're league with HBO and all that stuff.
I mean, this is these are big, these are big bank mergers.
That's what this is.
And we have now narrowed mainstream entertainment down to three or four of these entities.
And the only people playing on the field with these entities are major players.
You're not getting in.
It's not happening.
Yeah, and it's, you know, as a guy about to take out a pitch that I feel like it's foolproof,
you know, when I hear about the things that are getting passed on,
when I hear about multi, multi, multi billion dollar corporations
claiming their broke, you know, like it is to be a creative at this time.
When I say everyone I talk to in the television and film business is talking about getting out,
some more seriously than others, but definitely it's always on people's lips out here in L .A.
Like I got to find something else to do.
It's because no one cares anymore about the qualt.
They have, they're basically trying to see how shitty they can make their product
and have you still shell out the money and you're still shelling out the money.
I said, I said to, uh, I was talking to Mike Vekion who's very funny,
comic and a dear friend of mine.
We were at the club last night talking about this and he said,
could Holly would be any, could they could, could they not get it anymore?
Like are they, could they be any dumber?
Yeah, and I said, no, I agree with you.
I go, but you're looking at it through the wrong lens dude.
I go, everybody creating is a chef and Holly Wood is McDonald's and they're going, we don't give a
fuck how much time you spend on that, how you learned how to do that, how delicious it is,
that the tact and skill it takes to put it together.
People will buy these cheeseburgers.
Yeah, that's it.
That's why they set the release date and if the movie ain't ready,
it's coming out anyway.
You know, like the script's not done.
Oh, well, start shooting the, the, the edit's not done.
Oh, well, release it.
You, I mean, you saw a Wonder Woman too.
It doesn't make sense seen to scene and the executives and the people who are, are,
you know, I've experienced it on the TV side.
You're hearing five opinion, five different opinions, completely different opinions.
You're expected to address all of them and it leads to this like
just just this product that, you know, if you roll over and take it and many people do,
the products just suck, you know, and you're wind up pleasing nobody and everyone who told you
to do the shit doesn't have your back.
Certainly, they're not going to step forward and lose their job.
So it's just, it's, it's a nightmare right now.
It really is and there's nothing good on all these HBO Max movies have been
average or way worse than average.
Nothing's been great.
Nothing.
No, no, you know, your best bet these days and, and this is, and this is something
anybody's stupid agent would, this is something anybody's stupid agent would say,
you know, you'd say, why don't we go pitch to Shutter?
Which is no small potatoes.
You know, Shutter is a, is part of AMC like it's, it's not a small thing.
And, and the reps in this business were literally, literally say things like,
they don't have any money over there.
It's like, no, no, no, they have money.
They don't have all of the money.
Yeah.
Like, what the fuck are we trying to do here?
Are we trying to get something made reasonably?
Are we trying to only get it made at a place that will
A, ruin it and B, even if they don't, if they don't ruin it, we, we, we've got it.
We've got all our chips on one number that will make a gazillion dollars or whatever.
Yeah. Well, little by little, you learn that your agents aren't even
considering or making you aware of these smaller places.
Because like, I had a bit of a breakdown the other day.
I'm like, there are a billion channels.
And I, like, can't find a job.
Like, what's going on?
And if they don't want you at any of these smaller channels,
they want you at the big glomerates because they're the ones who will pay.
And they take 10 % of your income.
So that's all they care about.
And they think all their clients are like them
who have no interest in making something good and just want money.
And it's, the, the greed that has ruined this country
is certainly ruining the entertainment industry as well.
It has ruined it.
You can't really find a personal film.
You can't find films about just normal people anymore hardly there.
They barely exist.
And it's a goddamn shame.
It's just a goddamn shame.
Yeah, it's, it's, you know, it's unfortunate, you know,
because when you look at all those, like, you know, and maybe, you know,
Dune, at least, look, I'm not a Dune fan.
But you can tell that I love Villanue.
And you can tell that he's going for something artistic and something special.
And will it work for me?
Probably not, because I don't give a fuck about Dune.
But all those film acts movies.
It looks so fucking stupid and boring.
And I agree with you.
It's colorless.
It's fucking colorless.
And you watch that Jordowski documentary about his vision for it.
And you're just like, what a loss that this is not the Dune that got made.
It's this fucking, like, black leather tech.
Ugh, it looks, and then the fucking, what a boring cast to, of, you know,
Dave Batista for the 80 millionth time this year is in Sunday.
Josh Brolin, and for the 80 millionth time this year is in Sunday.
It's like, I think Timothy Chamolay, who's just,
the new powdery face for 2021 is, and by the way,
Batista now is the spokesperson for Disney.
He's the streamer, the character they created called the streamer.
He voices it?
No, he is it.
He's the, he's the physical.
He plays the character in the commercial.
What does he look like just himself?
He's like dressed up like a fisherman and it's called like the streamer.
He's a wrestler, right?
Was.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, I don't know nothing about him now.
I've seen a couple of Batista movies.
This man seems to be, you know, desperately trying
to get the charisma of John Cena.
He's, he's got nothing, brings nothing to the fucking table.
I mean, but, and it's just a thing.
Can you fucking please, how much of a fucking company man
and a shield do you have to be?
Why is this being praised now?
Why are people in the artistic community praising people
like Dave Batista when it's like he's a fucking company man?
He's being, he's now reduced himself to being a corporate
shell for one of the most evil conglomerates on planet earth
from day fucking one, not nothing new.
Disney has spent the last year
doing nothing but apologizing and cleaning up their own bullshit
because of stuff they perpetuated throughout the decades, okay?
Why are we praising this?
Why are we praising Ryan Reynolds when he's selling
fucking cheap sell?
It's like, how much fucking money do you people need?
When is it an intmoble?
He gets Moranis out of retirement to do an ad
for like cricket wireless.
I'm like, he's own and fucking soccer teams now
with with McElhenny.
It's like they, they want to be Elon Musk.
And yet if you ask them, what do you think of Elon Musk?
I bet they'd say I hate him, but you are him.
Yeah, it's all such bullshit, man.
This free guy movie, I texted Joe the other day,
what the fuck is this movie?
I have seen posters and previews of free guy
going on two and a half years now.
I don't know what it's about.
I was told that he's a non -playing character in a video game.
Okay.
The clip I saw, Ryan Reynolds is stuttering and having trouble talking
to a woman like he's Michael fucking Sarah.
He's got a 16 pack.
He's one of the best looking men in the history of time.
And he's charming and funny.
So you also get to play a nerd now?
What the fuck are you doing?
Yeah.
I'm I'm disgusted with everything.
They just released Jared Lito
and all his makeup for this house of Gucci movie.
He looks like Jeffrey Tambor.
Yeah, so it's yeah.
It's like where are character actors?
Where are the character actors?
They're like, they're not working.
Alex Black posted that.
Alex is a writer and a TV guy.
He posted Jared Lito
starring as Jeffrey Tambor and as Hank Kingsley.
Well, I'm good friends with Alex.
I might have been stealing that from him to be honest.
But I mean, it was so Jeff Tambor.
Yeah, yeah.
But I mean, that's and that's and that's a classic Hollywood move.
You know, take a beautiful person and just slob him up.
We're about,
we're a few days away from actual real life slabs
forming some sort of committee and being like,
wow, give me the slob part.
Yeah, I just I just saw a picture of
Joaquin Phoenix in the new Aureostra movie.
I love Aureostra.
Joe has his issues, of course.
But it's called Disappointment Boulevard.
And they're like, holy shit.
Look at this transformation of Joaquin Phoenix.
And he he has a better body than me in this photo.
It's like, can you believe how disgusting he looks?
And it's like, yeah, I do believe it.
Because that's what everybody looks like.
I need you to back up for a second.
Disappointment Boulevard.
You know how balls you have to be to call your movie Disappointment Boulevard?
That's a terrible name.
After your last two movies have been critically acclaimed.
To name this one.
Disappointment Boulevard.
Oh, oh, well, now I get you.
Sorry, I get you with the yeah, with the critics.
But I mean, my god almighty, that's it.
There's no ring to it.
It's that's a terrible title.
A very bad title.
And you're coming off hereditary and midsummer
to catchy, punchy titles that kind of tell you what it is.
Well, also too.
I mean, you want to talk about depressing
as we was we rail against Hollywood, right?
Yeah, the the the you know, the sort of the golden children
that we're kind of out there doing the right thing.
A 24 leading that pack, you know, now a 24's, you know,
they're selling for with it.
What was they asking for $4 billion or something like that?
I mean, it's it's nothing is sacred.
Nothing remain.
Floyd, Lloyd Kaufman is the only last like remaining real human being
making anything, I think that's it.
Just I loved him in that blockbuster documentary when they were like,
yeah, what you say something nice about blockbuster is like,
fuck you, fuck you, you know, yeah, like the hope is really, you know,
I read this great book called I want to say pictures,
pictures of a revolution, I want to say by Mark Harris about
kind of a last gasp of this big bloated Hollywood system.
And it was like, I believe the year they're focusing on as 1965,
I should look this up, but I'm not.
It's a great book.
And they're talking about basically how Hollywood was at this bloat.
They did the doctor do a little movie that cost like an absurd amount of money.
And then then easy writer came out.
And then all the sudden things started changing.
And maybe that's coming, but I somehow don't think so.
But we're definitely in need of some sort of rebel,
renegade force to shake things up.
And what that means is make a lot of money.
What that means is some great edgy and dependent movie making a ton of money.
Unfortunately, that's the only way we're going to change things.
It's a shame, you know, I still have my script up in the air.
And, you know, we're hoping we get it made.
But I got to tell you, dude, after that,
my effort is, I'm not putting effort into this at all anymore.
I'm podcasting.
I will do stand up in the way I want to do stand up.
I will write things I want to write.
And I will run a sandwich shop.
And that's it.
Like, I'm done.
I'm never stepping back into that arena again.
I'm, I don't, I'm fucking auditioning any of this bullshit.
It's like, for what?
For what?
Like, there's a great deal more, more honor in that, you know, like I,
I don't know.
I think people talking about getting out,
some are more serious than others.
But I also think I had a buddy the other day who said something that shook me to my core.
He, you know, he's a bit older than me, but he was like,
I'm at a point where I feel like I'm retired and nobody has told me.
And I was like, oh, yikes.
You know, but, but I, I felt that, you know, like you could be retired and not know.
That is the entertainment career.
You just kind of one day, you're like, well, I haven't worked in six years.
I guess that's it, you know?
If it's not on my own terms at this point, I'm not doing it.
I don't give a shit.
I don't give a shit, you know, I don't give a shit.
There are so few things that could motivate me to care.
If you, like, you know, if you said, hey, it's an audition for Scorsese,
that I'd be like, okay, that's really cool.
That's a lifelong dream, whatever.
But I turned these things, I got an audition two weeks ago for twice now
in this for a very popular TV show.
And I, both times, I said, I'm not doing it.
I don't care.
Majorly, you should do this.
Good show.
I go, I'm not doing a fucking zoom audition.
I'm not doing this.
Well, that's what everybody's doing now.
I don't care.
Everybody was also doing comedy shows on zoom.
And I said, fuck off.
I'm not doing it when these people want to do their jobs properly.
Again, I will think about it until then I have better shit to do with my fucking time.
Period.
Fair enough.
I mean, you tell them shit like that, by the way.
That's not going to, I was about to say that's that's the kind of talk that gets the agent thin
in the ranks a little bit.
But um, no, totally.
Just because I'm a city, I need to finish my little thing about Dune.
I was sorry.
No, no, no, we that was a well, well -needed tangent.
But, uh, Dune, I learned that they did not learn the like Lord of the Rings, okay?
It's not my, it's not my bag.
I find them entertaining, but I don't love it as much as most.
That was New Line Cinema, who had built up some capital through decades of great
low budget in many cases movies that turned a huge profit because they cared and they made great
fucking movies.
Boogie Nights, Friday, Nightmare and Elm Street.
The list goes on and on and on and on.
Then they achieved this tremendous amount of capital and were able to partner with another studio,
put aside their differences, shake hands, and produce the Lord of the Rings trilogy,
which was really the capping jewel in the crown of New Line.
Like it, it brought in all their money.
It made their entire life's work worth it.
And it's kind of a beautiful story in a way, even though at the end of the day,
you are making a big action -packed movie.
It was made with soul.
It was made by people who cared.
It was cast the well.
It was directed well, written well, et cetera.
Now, Dune, just, what is it, 15 years later, 20 years later,
they don't even have the faith in it to shoot the movies back to back to back.
What they said is, go ahead, make Dune for $200 million.
Shoot it in the middle of the desert with some of the biggest actors currently working.
So their salaries are all outrageous.
Make these lavish sets and worms or whatever the fuck is in Dune, giant worms.
And then if it makes money, we'll rebuild the fucking stats.
We'll go back to the desert, we'll pay all these actors even more money and go out.
But we don't have the faith in it to just shoot these Dune movies back to back to back,
and make it into something special.
And just say, we believe in this.
We have faith in it.
They're doing one.
And then if it's a hit, they're bent over a barrel and fucked because
they didn't have the faith in their product.
You know, Lord of the Rings is a huge gamble,
but if you're not willing to make that gamble,
it means you don't think you've got something worthwhile.
And that's what they're saying with Dune.
They're like, hey, good luck to you.
Meanwhile, then this guy makes this $200 million art movie.
And they're going to dump that on HBO Max.
And he goes, which I respect the hell out of him for,
no, you're not going to put my fucking movie on HBO Max.
I designed this to be an IMAX and he won.
They're releasing it theatrically.
I hate to even be standing up for Dune because I can pretty much guarantee I won't like it.
But it's like, I think he probably looked at that list of movies on HBO Max.
There was that period where they had a movie every Friday.
Somebody at Warner Brothers should be, forget fired, should never work again.
Look at that slate of movies that Warner's dumped on HBO Max.
That means you get 15 swings in a year and all 15 are bad.
Where's the quality control?
Who's running the studio?
Yeah. My favorite thing is all this uproar that the new space jam wasn't good.
I want to say what kind of a fucking numb nuts are you that you thought
this was going to be a good, what part of your brain made you think this would be good
after you have an original space jam that was awful.
What is wrong with everybody?
And by the way, you know, who makes an appearance in space jam for fucking, you know,
precious fucking HBO and Warner Brothers doing the right thing and what's politically great.
You know, is it in space jam?
Pennywise, the clown is in fucking space jam is in the new one.
The nuns from Ken Russell's The Devils, a movie that Warner Brothers won't release
because it's so controversial, even though when it was on fucking criterion channel,
I was like, okay, not really for me.
You know, there's nuns in it who fucks.
There's nuns.
The nuns from The Devils are in that array space.
Are you serious?
I'm dead serious.
Yeah, they're in like the back.
They use all this WBIP.
It's like, this isn't a claimed, many people consider it a masterpiece and you won't put it out on
Blu -ray because you're worried about the fucking Catholic church.
And you're putting them in space jam, too.
Pennywise, Pennywise is in space jam, too.
But Peppie LePue was too much.
But we'll put Pennywise into the movie.
The kids, the rabbit that had boobs was too much.
Yeah, my buddy John, I won't say his last name because he is currently working for Warner Brothers,
but he wrote me and I was laughing so hard.
I will not watch this movie.
But he says, space jam, too, has the worst opening few scenes I've ever seen.
The studio should be burned to the ground for releasing this.
Don Sheetle gives a five minute scene, delivering pipe to a cartoon bot question mark
about how he is a Warner Brothers algorithm.
And LeBron is a social media king.
He's perfect.
I have to get him for the launch of the new Warner Brothers technology I made.
There's a five minute discussion about Warner Brothers.
We've got to get, they're basically trying to be self -aware.
But they're just saying we're a gross conglomerate making shitty product.
And everybody's supposed to laugh.
And everybody goes, oh, that's so cool that they just, they just call it what it is.
Look, here's the entire mentality of everything right now.
Sorry, I'm a bitch.
That's the mentality.
Hey, at least I admit it.
Fuck off.
You admit it.
You're a bad fucking person.
Fuck you.
Drop dead.
Anyway, our movie corner this week, speaking of fuck you, drop dead.
Hey, wait a minute, speaking of fuck you, drop dead?
Were you saying that to me?
I don't know.
No, no, no, that's the thing I want to, oh, first, we'll go for it.
A lot of back and forth on the internet about this.
I'm going to jump in.
I might get shit.
I don't know.
This master's of the universe.
OK.
You know how excited I was.
I'm a huge fan of the original cartoon series.
I grew up on it.
I couldn't wait.
Kevin Smith said left and right that this was going to be a direct sequel
to that original series.
This was for the fans.
Spoilers.
I was a work off for Halloween.
Yeah, I was, I was a work off for Halloween.
Here's a couple spoilers for you.
He man dies in episode one.
I cannot believe this.
Focus then shifts to teela.
Fine, I don't care.
This is the point I want to make.
I don't care that it's transparent, gender swapping stuff.
And they're trying to course correct what was criticized at one point
as being too masculine or toxically masculine a cartoon,
which by the way was run by many women at the time in the 80s
or written by or something.
But there were a lot of women involved with the project in the 80s.
Well, you don't think Hannah Barbera is a woman's name, do you Joe?
Yes, that's right.
I don't even know if I think it was Mattel.
It wasn't Hannah Barbera, but OK, yeah.
But let's put all that aside.
I don't give a fuck if they focus the show on a female character,
on a male character, on a goddamn green fucking half man, half fish character.
I don't care.
What I care about is fucking he man isn't here.
That's all I care about.
So to add insult to that injury, to add insult to that injury,
they not only kill off he man,
they put teela and put teela as the centerpiece of the story.
They make man and arms retire and shame.
He gets banished or go dies.
Really, or go is like depressed because the magic is leaving his body and he dies.
Sacrificing himself.
Mermaid is articulate, which really pissed me off.
Really pissed me off.
Mark Hamill's in here doing Skeletor and everybody goes, oh my god,
Mark Hamill just with his voice work.
He does the same fucking voice and everything he does.
It's all a version of the Joker and it's a great voice.
But it's just one voice.
He's got that voice in the Luke Skywalker voice.
Those are two voices.
But to add insult to injury, they're then adding characters that never existed.
So it's like guys, what the fuck are we doing here?
What is it?
No, look, is it my comedic?
Did Kevin Smith write it all?
He wrote the first episode.
There's there's a tiny tiny.
Oh, oh, cringes are not scared anymore.
Cringer now is like found confident.
It's like it's like a bad like here.
Do you ever wonder what happened to the lion after the wizard gave him Kurt?
Not really.
Didn't give a shit.
But anyway, it's um,
watch Toto slowly die of like advanced dog aids or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, uh, so then it's just a completely convoluted,
nonsensical storyline that is as we often complain about on this show.
It is way too fucking complicated for no reason.
The magic is leaving attorney and then skeleton and he man die in the first episode.
And then Tila hates the king because he kept the secret from her that Adam was also he man.
So then she hates everybody and she's off on her own.
And man and arms is over here.
And it's this thing that they do in a lot of these reboots and sequels and things.
They scatter everybody across the fucking universe.
And then it's then it's like, will they all come back together?
Or not I don't give a fuck man.
You told me you're making a sequel to the original series.
Give me the fucking original series.
I want to see the people I love doing shit together.
Okay, that's it.
It's that fucking simple.
And a lot of the time when they try to do this approach,
it doesn't fucking work.
We saw it not work with Star Wars.
Okay, the big promise was that Han and Luke and everybody's going to come back together
finally in this sequel trilogy.
And guess what happened?
They fucking kill Luke in the second movie.
Carrie Fisher dies before the release of the second movie.
And it never fucking happens.
So maybe you could have just kind of just done the right thing from the jump.
And whatever.
So my point is is it's a convoluted plot.
They bring Adam back to life at the end of the first season.
And then he dies again.
He gets killed immediately.
They bring him back and he kills him in.
So Kevin Smith.
I just I want to like him so badly.
I want to like Kevin Smith.
I just don't understand man.
Like I just don't get it.
Like he like I watch the like talking about he man after show.
Yeah.
And he's like, you know, and they say at the top, they're like, okay,
so go, you know, don't.
Oh, that's the other thing.
Evil Lynn is like good in this.
And she's like helping the good guys.
And then it just it just sucks.
Now look, maybe it's all set up for season two,
which will be he man's back and all that.
Who knows?
But this was a bad season one.
Okay, and I'm willing to give them the benefit of the doubt.
But anyway, I'm watching the after show thing.
And Kevin Smith goes,
you know, if you haven't seen this yet,
this is going to be all spoilers.
So just stop watching this now and then go watch.
And they take a beat.
And then he goes, all right, enough of this shit.
Fucking spoilers, man.
You know, for some reason he always like talks like a cartoon
character now all the time.
And and he goes, I hate, I hate looking at the man.
I hate, I hate space.
And he goes, we killed Adam twice twice, man.
And it's like, why are you excited about that?
This sucks, dude.
This sucks.
And then he saw an Instagram of Kevin Smith
and he had the whole clerks team reunited.
And he was like, I know everybody on the internet
has pissed at me right now because of he man.
But onwards and upwards, I'm over here working on clerks three.
We just heard the table read or whatever.
And look, clerks two is really his last decent movie.
I know you like his horror stuff.
But I mean, if we're supposed to be going off that last
Jay and Silent Bob, I mean, I'm, I don't mind not see clerks three.
I feel like the man has given up.
The movie has looked like they're shot in his yard, you know.
Pod has ruined him.
Yeah.
And for a guy that like talks so beautifully
about like, like if you watch his clip from Rogan,
where he talks about getting over his fear of death
with his heart attack and what that experience wasn't right.
It's a beautiful conversation.
And it's like it's, and he speaks so beautifully
about what, what the release of, of all that was
and how it changed his life and how, you know, he got this second chance.
And he's not, he doesn't fear death,
but he's not going to tempt it.
He's, he's trying to appreciate all this.
And it's like, dude, then why are you walking through it
stoned out of your fucking gourd?
Why?
Why is that okay?
If you were drinking like this,
there would be an intervention happening.
But because it's pod everybody actually gets fucking fine.
So anyway, here's what I'm really pissed about.
The show sucks fine, it sucks, whatever.
And that's the consensus of male and female fans alike.
Again, I don't give a fuck that it focuses on a female character.
I give a fuck that it doesn't focus
on the main character of fucking He -Man.
Anyway, and what I'm really pissed about is,
is he and Netflix both said repeatedly,
this was a direct sequel to the original show.
And he said repeatedly, this is not a tealous story.
It's a He -Man story.
He -Man is front and center.
On both counts, he lied, which is just a fucking weird,
shitty thing to do.
It's like why would you do that?
Why can't you just say,
yeah, dude, I'm rebooting Masters of the Universe,
but it's like going to be more tealous centric.
And I would have been like, okay, I don't care.
Like that's just another show.
There's been plenty of reboots of this series
that some of my likes, some of my didn't.
It's just another cog in the fucking wheel, I don't care.
Why is Netflix and them going out of their way to doop fans
into what this thing is not?
And then, because they knew what a backlash they'd get,
I don't like, I used to watch He -Man clearly.
There's a picture of me in an oracle costume,
but I don't know any of these characters
you're referring to outside of He -Man and Skeletor,
no recollection of Tila.
So I'm sure people were just like,
you know, they probably said, keep it under your hat
or nobody's going to watch the fucking show.
They did Netflix.
Netflix has a new Shira show that's been on for years
and it's very popular.
And they redid it to make it look like Powerpuff girls.
It doesn't look like the original.
And people love it.
And you know what?
I like the Shira cartoon when I was a kid too.
And I'm just like, no, this isn't for me.
It's a little too like Kitty.
It's, I don't know, I'm just trying to do it.
They could have done that with this.
So we're going to do a Tila lead master's.
You know, and there would have been the assholes like,
oh, come on.
Let them talk, but at least you didn't lie to them.
Right.
You lied to people.
And Netflix is just doing this now.
They just lie.
They just lie about stuff.
And then when they get called on it, they're not accountable.
They did it with the, with the Fear Street part two.
They said they were claiming publicly that it was shot at the same
campground as Jason Lives.
And a guy that had just done a documentary about Friday the 13th
came out immediately and was like, no, you didn't.
Jason Lives was shot at this campground.
You guys shot at this one.
It's not, I was just there.
Right.
And they just don't even respond to that.
They don't correct it.
Nothing.
And so it's weird to lie.
And it's weird that Kevin Smith kept saying,
this is a direct sequel.
And then in the 11th hour before this thing drops, he goes,
well, technically, we're not allowed to make a sequel to the
Mattel one.
So in essence, it's a sequel, but not it's like, you've
said I was a huge, he said at one point, I was a huge master's
of the universe fan, whatever.
And then there's an interview before that where he was like,
I was never into masters of the universe until I got onto this project.
It's like, why are you lying?
Yeah, I mean, it might be with the, with the weed.
It doesn't even know what he's saying at the time.
I mean, I don't know why, what the benefit would be of lying.
And last, and Netflix is like, don't say that.
We want people to think you're a fan.
I mean, who knows what goes on?
I have no clue.
Yeah, anyway, I do, I shouldn't say, I do have some insider
information that when they went to Kevin Smith's house
to hear the presentation of what this, what the he -man's
season would be, he had nothing prepared.
And they were like, no, we expected this to be you telling us
what the season would be.
And he was like, oh, I just thought we were kind of like shooting the shit.
I mean, he just, it's just so fucking disappointing.
And it goes with everything we were saying earlier.
It's like, Smith, you're supposed to be one of the good guys, yeah.
You were the guy that was always like, look man,
I know I'm no fucking genius and I know I'm not the best director
and I'm not the best writer, but I care, man.
And I make what I care about and I make stuff I can relate to.
It's like, I've got, at this point, several, I'm nervous talking about this.
I've got several close friends at this point that are close friends with him,
you know, mutual friends.
It's like, I don't want to bash the guy.
I just don't understand what this is.
It's like, why are you doing this, dude?
Like, why are you shilling out for fucking Netflix?
Come on, man.
Come on.
Money.
Yeah, well, that's all it's all mine.
I'd like to take us back to the year I graduated high school.
Woodstock 99, peace, love, and rage.
The new documentary on HBO Max.
I'll talk about this.
Yeah, it's, it's, you know, one of those things that everybody's got to watch
and have an opinion on.
I watched it the day it came out because I was just like, man,
I remember hearing about this.
I have good friends who went to it, said it was, you know,
as insane as you've heard.
They burned the place down essentially.
Documentary is, it's disturbing for a variety of reasons.
At first, I was amazed at how sort of,
how I felt in my bones, how I felt when I was 18 years old
and watching pop, like now popular music is just sort of
uninteresting to me.
It's generic, whatever.
The popular music at that time was the worst music in the history of an
American music without question.
They're doing corn, biscuit, dursed is up there, like,
yeah, motherfuckers, yeah.
And then just eight million shirtless guys going like,
unbelievable.
I mean, he literally walks out on stage holding his dick and he's like,
and you sons of bitches.
What's up?
You fucking assholes.
Nobody's like,
I, it was so traumatic to me because I remember sitting with my buddies
like in a basement watching MTV constantly around this time period
and just feeling like I don't understand what's happening with the world
with my generation.
I'm not interested in the music was so bad.
Our local alternative station in St. Louis, 105, 7, the point,
overnight went from like Nirvana, STP,
Soundgarden into the worst frat jock rock shit I've ever heard in my life.
And they touch on that.
They talk about how, you know,
Cobain in addition to sort of changing the music landscape,
he was up there performing in a dress,
you know, way before that was that was a common place occurrence.
He was saying he wishes in his bones that he was gay because he, you know,
he would be able to change people's minds and stuff like that.
And then to have Durs come out like that, they had,
I was, it was intriguing.
Who came off kind of good in it and who came off kind of bad?
Like the offspring comes out.
And the offspring to me, I'm like, okay, you're nowhere near the depths of a limp biscuit,
but you're also, you know, you're not even a green day.
The offspring kind of sucks, in my opinion.
But they're up there on stage.
And the lead singer, by the way, you want to talk about people aging,
they interview the offspring today and it got an audible scream from my wife
when they showed that they look at that.
They look strange is all else that they look like exotic birds or something.
So they've dyed their hair like in like those blonde and black streaks, but they're 55 years old.
It's wild.
But they cut, they cut to Durs,
basically going like, let's burn your mother, look at down.
You know, and then they burn the mother, fuck her down.
Then they cut to the offspring.
And they're up there going, guys, I'm seeing girls out there getting molested,
fucking stop it, like stop it.
And it was impressive to me to see because that was not the time where that kind of thing went on.
So they come off as kind of good guys in it.
But there is a 45 -minute segment of this documentary about the sexual assaults at Woodstock 99.
And there's all these, there's a guy who's like an ex -New York City cop who works security
and he's like, I tell people, they ask me, what's the worst thing you ever seen
in your career as a cop? And I tell him it was unquestionably Woodstock 99.
Jesus Christ.
There's foot, now here's where things get weird.
There's 8 million shots of girls with their tits out and girls walking around
fully frontally naked. So that, that was insane to me.
There's the promoters of the things saying, look,
in my opinion, at an event where everybody's drinking, you want to walk around full frontally naked,
you know, if something happens, it's, okay, that's a super fucked up thing to say.
The promoters are basically blaming anyone but themselves for what happened.
There's all these talking heads. Some of them are good. Dave Holmes from the MTV days,
who I know a bit is always a very intelligent commentator on that on MTV and what was going on
in the 90s. But then there's also commentators in this thing who are idiots and who use words incorrectly.
And who are, you know, it's the kind of thing where when you're looking back, they're like,
you could feel the rage from the death of Kurt Cobain coursing through the, and it's like,
no, they were animals who were fucked up and being cheered on by Fred Durst, you know,
like, so there's a lot of, it's a badly done documentary and yet it's a fascinating
time capsule of what was going on at that time. It's, they have footage of guys approaching
kind of scantily clad women with their hard dicks out and their faces are in the documentary.
I was imagining, like, what, what if some guys sitting at home with his wife and she sees him
rubbing his hard dick on a woman, you know, it's, it looked like just a goddamn nightmare.
And things, I'd say things are bad now in a very different way, but my God, looking at 99 and what
what was popular, they, they go into like the blender, maximum FHM culture where, you know,
they take the greatest actresses of the day and have them like bent over with a bowling pin in their
ass or something. You know, it's, I mean, it was a gross, gross period of time. I do think we've
over corrected, of course, to a shocking degree lately, but I'm real glad we're not living in those
days anymore. I felt like I was not even a part of society at that time. I felt like I was
just not happy with the world and where pop culture was going. I was in college. That was right in
the heart of my college days. And you're seeing that shit become so popular. And so dumb. I saw
limpskin get boot off stage. They were opening for faith no more. And they got boot off stage.
And Fred Durst literally said on stage, and look guys, I'm quoting here. All right. I'm just going
to tell you what he said, because we're all adults. And I'm going to tell you what he said. He was on
stage. Roddy bought him in faith. The more is gay. There was a table for gay rights in the back.
Limpskin immediately started getting boot. They were unknown at the time. They immediately started
getting boot by the second song, maybe, you know, the crowd wasn't into it. And after the third song,
Fred Durst said, I see the gay rights table in the back. Why are you here? I didn't invite you
dick -sucking -faggets to my show. That's what Fred Durst said on stage. Then they got fully
boot off the stage. They were surprised, but I'm glad. I'm surprised they did get boot. You're surprised
they got boot at that time? Yes. No, no, no. Nobody knew who they were yet. So everybody's there for faith
no more. And they're like, okay. Who are these fucking knobs that are like doing this shitty rage against
the machine thing? Yeah. Because that was the thing. Like back then, rage was really cool. When rage
against the machine came out, that was really cool. And that was a huge moment for me because I
loved rap music. And I was starting to get into rock music. So like the judgment night soundtrack,
when that happened and they blended rock and rap, they weren't the first ever, you know,
Rundee, I'm seeing Arismith really lit that fuse. But like when that album came out, that was
incredible to me. And then when rage came out and did it so well as a group, it was awesome. And
so then when limp isca came out, I was like, that's how we all looked at it. This is shitty rage
against the machine. Right. And I remember rage was that Woodstock 992. Yeah. You can make the,
you can tell it very much like what one one group is extremely passionate about what they believe in
and trying to connect with an audience and the other guy is up there going, you know, what with
this song break stuff? Let's get it. It's real. I've got a chain saw. I mean, what a deal though.
But anyway, I mean, you know, it was crazy. It was fucking crazy. I saw I did a podcast with
Billy Gold from Faith No More, which was exciting for me. My friend Dan Dunn's, what are we drinking
podcast? It was a lot of fun. I was excited because they're one of my favorite bands ever. But I told him
I was like, do you remember that show in Philly? I was there when limp isca got boot off stage. And he
was like, Oh, yeah, that was pretty crazy. Like, yeah. You know, and like, it was just like,
fucking, it was not, but I remember saying these guys are not going anywhere. This is a flop. And then
not two weeks later, they were on the MTV beach house performing. And I was like, come on,
are you kidding me? And people loved it. And I was just like, here's the moment where I no longer
understand my generation. I remember girls talking about him being hot. Do you remember their behind
blue eyes cover? No one knows what it's like. I mean, their faith cover, you sort of got why that
connected with people. It's hard to fuck up faith. But God, God, they fucking sucked. What a terrible
thing. And, you know, anybody who went who's gone to rock shows has had that moment in a pit where
you're like, Oh, okay, now everybody's just pushing each other. And there's there's no fun to
this at all. And I need to get out of this situation. Yeah. So when you see a hundred thousand or
however many, I'm sure way more than that people all doing that, pushing each other in this giant
mass. It's like, God, no, I mean, no wonder people just felt like they could freely assault anyone,
you know, because there was no consequences. And, you know, the commentators are up there like,
it was it was people rebelling against capitalism. You know, like a four dollar bottle of water
who wouldn't throw down? No, that's not what he's talking about. They're mad because they're
fucking idiots. They're there. Anyone there cheering on Fred Durst is a fucking idiot. And that's why
they're fighting because that's what idiots do. They're not mad about the water. Yeah,
and by the way, all the guys that they're with that are majoring in business are mad at capitalists.
Oh, sure. They all went on to be Wall Street guys. Absolutely.
Fuck off. All right. I saw, you know what, here's a positive one.
Wall Street, I'm going to close, I'm only going to do two today because we're we're deep in at this
point. And I've put a lot of venom into this show to so far. And I need to save some for our movie.
Yes, sure. I'll say a positive. I watched the hustler.
Hmm. Great movie. I mean, my God. What a beautiful looking movie. Beautiful,
superbly executed on all fronts. Everything about the film is perfect. Every single actor.
It's just oh, my God. What an amazing, amazing film. It's amazingly directed. It's amazingly written.
And it's just a superb piece of work and a reminder of the dog shit that we have to look at.
I mean, you're watching the hustler and then you back out of it on like, I think it was HBO Max
and you're seeing the space jam too. You know, you're just like Jesus Christ. But
if you've never seen a treat yourself, the highlight of the film for me is Gleason. I'm a huge
second dramatic role. I mean, to watch that guy just kill it. Yeah, just to kill it.
I mean, George C Scott. It's like Paul Newman. What's your name from Twin Peaks?
You know, I'm talking about Peggy Lepton. No, no, no, the why she's the mom on the
the, the, the, she's like the ruthless lady in Twin Peaks. The ruthless girl. I'll tell you
in a second. All right. Patricia Neal. Is she Emma? Not Patricia Neal. No, hold on.
She was in HUD. You've never seen HUD from the same period. That's an amazing Paul Newman movie as well.
Hyperlory. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I'm sorry, Papal. From Carrie. Yeah. Yes. From Carrie as well.
She's a fucking, she's amazing in it. The whole, I mean, God, damn it. It's a good movie.
Jesus Christ. Vincent Gardini is in it. You know, it's just a great flick.
And when color of money came out, everybody was like, Oh, you know, movies have gotten bad.
It's, it's, this is nowhere near as good as the original, whatever. And you look at color of money now.
It seems like a fucking classic. You know, they're money is just great. Slip it and slip it and slip it.
Slip it. Color of money is great. I was really disappointed to read after I saw this because I was
like, you know, I've seen color of money. And I don't remember them really ever mentioning Minnesota
effects. Yeah. In the book in the sequel book of the hustler, it's about Newman and Minnesota
fats reconnect to go take down like this pool tournament. So they did a very different story for
the movie. But I did read online that Gleason was tapped to do, to come back and do a scene
and that he and Newman both agreed like, this is just like fan service. This is stupid. I mean,
there was a time if you could believe it, people, where actors actually made decisions like that.
Yeah. This doesn't service the plot or the story. Let's not just do it to have you in it. That's stupid.
Yeah. So, but watch this film if you haven't ever seen it. Newman just, I mean, you want to,
Newman's one of those guys where you understand why they say acting is all in the eyes. Like he's one
of those guys. Like the looks he's given people in this thing. Like the like Glee that he
translates in his eyes when like it's he's going to get the game going. And like, yeah, it's a
challenge. And you know, but he's that good. And you know, it's just, it's just awesome. It's just an
awesome, awesome movie. Well, Newman's whole thing, he was a man, a man's man. Women were obsessed
with him. Men loved him. But he also exuded like goodness, class, you know, married for whatever
50 years immediately started putting his money into charity. They can still find the fucking salad
dressing just a legend, just a legend. And we don't have those anymore. You know, like you talked about
jungle crews last time. Like the rock is is who people would probably say is our new Paul Newman.
Or so I mean, the rock looks like no one else that Paul Newman, although he was always in great
shape and a beautiful looking man, you, you felt like you could get a beer with the guy, you know,
like we just don't think as close as you're going to get is, is Clooney, that's as close as you're
getting. Clooney, Affleck, Damon. There's a couple guys out there where you're like, all right,
it seems like if I ran into you in a bar, we'd chop it up. And you know, but I hear you it's, it's
a different thing. And then also too, how often are you going to see a gleece in type out there
anymore? This is a man that just, he's constantly sweaty. Yeah. But the talent pushes through all of it.
It's such a shame. I get very sad when I think about it because I feel like Chris Farley really could
have been another gleece in type. I feel like he had a dramatic thing that he could have done and he
just never got a chance to do it sadly. It's very, very sad to me. But he was, he was the prime candidate
in my opinion. But yeah. And then like, you know, a guy like gleece and it's like he just just
chain smoke every interview, talking about like booze. Like, you know what I mean? Like I love,
I would say these fucking guys are awesome. Yeah. I mean, it's awesome. You check in with an old
Carson or anything. You know, I watched Mikey and Nikki the other night and then it led to me going
into watching Fox and Casavetes on these talk shows would drunk out of their mind and speaking
their mind and and getting booed and being like, I shut up and then getting cheered five minutes later
and and now it's, it's literally, you know, Andy Sandberg on Zoom, cutting out, talking to Jimmy
Fallon and then like, well, now we're going to play a game over Zoom. You know, it's, it's it's not
it's not a country for men anymore. It's no country for old man. Yeah, no.
Yeah. Before we get to Glenn Gary over here, yeah. What, what do you got? I'll combine my last two
because I went, I made my triumphant return to the New Beverly this week. Tarantino's now owned
theater here in LA. It was great. It was a little unnerving to be, I mean, you had a mask up here
again, but it was a nerving to be in like a sold out house. I've only been going to movies during the day
lately. Here's my question really quick. Yeah. Are you, if you're eating, are you allowed to take the
mask now? You are, which seems absurd to me because people just buy a popcorn and you're eating popcorn
for 90 minutes. Yeah. That's the point of pop. It's so dumb. Yeah. All right. Sorry. And honestly,
I think these places are getting a lot more money in concessions because people buy the big
tub of popcorn so they can leave the mask on. Yeah. I couldn't care less about popcorn, but I'll be
getting it if that mask mandate comes back in New York. It's back here in a big way. But I saw a double
feature done by Lynn Ramsey, who was a great director who has only made four movies. They are Rat
Catcher, her first movie, which I watched the other night, Morvern Collar, which is a really great
little indie that many consider one of the best films of the two thousands. I'm not sure I'd go
that far, but I like it a lot. We need to talk about Kevin, which was the other half of the double
feature, and you were never really here, which came out a few years ago with Joaquin Phoenix,
which is a very intense movie where he basically just goes around killing sex offenders with a hammer.
It's kind of like taxi driver, but an art film or even more of an art film, I should say.
Then she got fired off in Natalie Portman, Western, and somebody else stepped in and directed it.
She's made four really special interesting movies, and then when she tries to do something else,
we don't get it, you're fired. It sucks. I read a lot about her career because I think she makes
really special movies. Rat Catcher is her most sort of personal. It's in Scotland. It's in this
little like the town is so dirty that if you get in the water, you get sick. There's rats everywhere,
and it's very much a kid's eye view of growing up in extreme poverty with an alcoholic abuse of
that and being bullied and so on and so forth. The kid's 10, I would say. He has a very strange
relationship with this 17 -year -old girl who is kind of the town fuck. All these guys look like
they're 14. They go one after the other and fuck this girl like in a shed, and she's not even getting
paid. She's just like a girl who does this, and the kid forms a bond with her, but then they
they're like bathing together and they're naked and they're kids, and this in a theater setting was
very, very wild to me. I will say it felt a little uncomfortable, but the movie was great. I had never
seen it. It's depressing for sure, but you know, as far as these coming of age movies go, it's really,
really an interesting good movie, but be prepared to see some stuff with kids that might certainly
kind of threw the theater for a loop. Speaking of, I got to say, Tarantino kicks these things off now
with Looney Tunes cartoon, and it was a speedy Gonzalez, and they're in Mexico and it was them out
smarting Sylvester. The opening joke, big laugh from the theater, Looney Tunes are still very funny.
I agree. It gets a big laugh, and then outcome speedy Gonzalez, and a man in the back stands up
and yells, racist. Then he goes out into the lobby and we hear him out there voice getting louder and
louder and louder yelling at these people who are trying to like put together. He makes a stink about
it, made a stink, and we sat there. Look, I thought it was an odd choice to show a speedy Gonzalez
in this day and age, but the theater sat there then and you watched 150 people bite their lips
and just pray that it would end so that nobody accidentally laughed. It was that kind of vibe.
It was so tense. Anyway, we said a lot of negative about him, but let's give Warner Brothers
let's give them, as the kids say, some flowers. Elmer Fudds got his gun back in the new shorts,
baby. They took his gun. They took his gun away. He had a sky,
what's that got a sky? It's like a grim reaper thing. Yeah, because guns are offensive,
but he's got his gun back. Thank God. I mean, for Christ's sakes. Anyway, our movie today is
well, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, sorry, sorry, because I didn't get to the jewel of the crown.
We need to talk about Kevin. Great flick. Holy shit. I saw it when it came out. I remember
being disturbed by it and liking it a lot. I'm going to say it's this Lynn Ramsey's masterpiece
and it is one of, I think it's one of the best movies I've seen. I mean, I was so riveted by this
fucking thing, the guy Ezra Miller who's now the flash or whatever gives an insanely great performance
till to Swinton gives an insanely great performance. You're so sympathizing with her for 90 minutes
and then she's got this scene out of nowhere where she's there's some fat people eating.
She looks back at them. This is the the woman you've been cheering for this whole movie. Like,
God, this kid is so mean to her. She plays basically, if you don't know, at the mom of a kid who goes
on to kill a lot of kids at school, you know, it's like a Columbine type story. And it's how much of
the parents responsible should it's almost asking the question, should you kill your kid if you sense
that your kid is evil? I mean, an amazing, amazing movie. But the scene that jumped out of me is
90 minutes in. She goes, she points at these fat people and she's like, you know,
these people are they claim that it's just metabolism and everything else, but it's because they eat too
much and they eat the wrong stuff. That's the problem with fat people. She's talking to her son.
I mean, it was it was shocking and it's just that's the beauty of Lynn Ramsey is that at any moment,
this character that you're loving and supporting can do or say something horrible. And that's what life
is. That is what life is. She does not shy away from real life. The movie's an a a plus material.
John C. Riley plays her husband. That's an odd couple till the Swinton and John C, but they're amazing
together. They're all they're all great. And he play he's he's great. He plays a real unlikable guy.
Yeah, he won't he just won't support his wife because every it's like every time he comes around
the corner, she's telling her son she hates him in so many words, you know, but the kid they got to
play as remiller as a boy is amazing. The evil coming off of this kid and he looks exactly like
as remiller. There's a scene where she keeps rolling a ball to him and he won't he just won't engage.
They quickly do the work of telling you he's not autistic. There's just something off about him.
He goes they're like, no, he's not autistic. She's rolling a ball to this kid. It rolls over to
to hit him in the crotch again and again. He doesn't do it. Finally, she rolls it over to him and he catches
it and pushes it back to her and her face is just extreme joy that her care son is like engaging with
her for once. And she's so happy. She rolls it to him again. And he lets it hit him in the crotch.
And all he wanted to do this little fucked up kid is be like, no, I know what you're trying to get
me to do, but I'm not going to do it. It's the evil kid thing in a way I've never seen. It feels so
real. There's a scene where she's she changes his diaper and he's way too old to be shitting in his
pants. But she's like, oh, she's disgusted and he's sitting there smiling at her and staring her
in the eye while she changes his diaper. Then after she gets them all done, he stands up, walks across
the room, smiles and shits some more in his newly cleaned diaper. Yeah. Like the theater went nuts. I
mean, the movie, it's an art movie. It's told out of order. It's I don't know. If you've never seen
it, make an effort. I was sent the blue ray by our friend at a silascope who we who we discussed.
Yes. Michelle gave me the blue ray too when I am so happy to own this thing because now it's a movie.
I'm going to be revisiting a lot. I think it's it's an amazing movie. All right. We're done.
All right. Well, speaking of amazing movies, today is Emnight Shyamalan's latest.
Emnight Shyamalan's latest. This idea would have been cool as a 22 -minute Twilight Zone episode.
Instead, it's a two -hour movie. Old about a resort that people go to and then they are told
about a secret beach that they only tell certain, you know, customers about certain visitors about
and they go to that beach and you find out that they are growing old on the beach rapidly,
particularly the children. Yeah. It basically over the course of a day, you go through pretty much
your entire life. So there's an old woman with them who's dead very quickly. There's children who
grow to be adults. There are everyone gets diseases, tumors, etc. You know, because they're
accelerating the aging process very quickly. And they all have conditions. They all have pre -existing
conditions. So one lady has a tumor. One guy has a mental, you know, like an early onset Alzheimer's
kind of thing. One guy has a blood disorder. They all have different disorders, right? So these
disorders start to manifest very quickly and rapidly in advanced stages on the island, which is kind
of a cool detail. The kids getting older is strange and off -putting and interesting. Unfortunately,
they don't do it correctly because, I mean, just right off the bat,
the two, they show, when the kids start to age, they show them talking to two of the adults,
but they're shooting the kids from behind so you can't see that they've aged. But you can hear
their voices of change drastically and that they're older. But and they're talking to these two adults
and the adults say, how old are you two? And they go, I'm six and she's 11. And they're going,
there's no way you're, that's a joke. There's no way you're six years old because the kids don't
realize they've aged, yet the kids are looking at one another.
He's looking at his, he can hear his own voice. I mean, and this is something in the last episode,
we talked about freaky immediately. The second, the second she wakes up in Vince Vaughn's body,
she goes, why does my voice sound like that? Literally the first thing she, they, they tackle this
immediately and freaky in the right way. In this movie, you're like, these kids are hanging out and
notice that they, the other ones are significantly older. So right off the bat, you got some,
you got some logic problems here with the film. You've got a stunningly beautiful like Victoria,
I think she is actually a Victoria's secret model on the island in a, you know, a very revealing
skimpy bikini. And yet they don't necessarily go into anything like, you know, I'm like, okay,
there'll be some commentary on, on Instagram models. And, you know, no, not really, you know,
and like these, these false standards of beauty or whatever. There's kind of dead because she's got
the calcium deficiency and she becomes hunched and twisted because of it, which is, which is an
interesting juxtaposition or fate or an erotic fate for that person to have. But it just wasn't
done in that like they, they kind of mimic the, my favorite scene in the Lord of the Flies remake
when the kids go into the cave and the guy, like the, the half dead pilot is in there.
Right. He like crawls and like, it's like very monstrous. And they kind of do that with the,
a scene in a cave with this lady. But like, she just doesn't look scary. Like, there's just nothing,
she just looks like a, she looks like an old lady with blood. That's exactly. Nothing,
nothing, nothing connects, nothing satisfies, nothing, there's no like good setup payoff to it.
There, I was, Shyamalan clearly needs someone. He needs someone he trusts. And I read a book about
the making of Lady in the Water. It's one of my favorite film making books of all time. You can find,
I don't remember the name off hand, but I know I've discussed it on the show before.
He's a guy who all throughout that book, people are telling him,
night, this movie does not work. This movie, you know, like, he had made so much money off
six cents and unbreakable and stuff. And the studio that he made those movies with was like,
we won't make this. And he was hurt and offended. And, but at some point, you do have to listen
to people. And this movie, he's got a rapper who's supposed to be a successful rapper that he has
named Midsize Sedan. It's so bad. And it's like, so you why not ask one person or a Google
rap, Google, Google hip hop. What is that a parody? I could see if he made the rapper, his name was
75 cent. You'd get that he's doing a little riff on 50 cent. What is Midsize Sedan a riff on?
It's terrible. It's literally in there. It's like the hackiest, oldest rap joke.
Like, I don't get these crazy rap names. That's a 20 year old Bill Marjoke at best.
You know, like from, but from like 97, you know what I mean? Yeah. And then it's in there just so
the dad can go is, you know, is Sedan has made some dumb fucking joke that he makes. Yeah. You know,
um, he keeps casting his goddamn self, which is just beyond distracting. It's not hitchcock
walking by in a crowd of 40 people. It's a speaking role. Like he's, he's got a fairly large role.
He's, he's in there. Um, I thought it was an interesting. I actually thought the casting of
himself in that particular role was interesting because he is the people, he is the person that takes
them to this beach. He's clearly behind whatever scheme is going on here. His character.
So I did think it was interesting. It was, it was sort of self referential. Like I'm the one
fucking with your head right now because that's what I do. Yeah. Um, he also did a pretty good job
in the setup of the film with pulling your focus to certain things to make you wonder. Is that a
red herring or is that something that's going to be significant later or whatever? All of the things
ended up being significant. So maybe he didn't do a good job because it would have been
cool if he had a few more red herrings or a few head red herrings. Um, but my biggest gripe with
this movie is eventually everybody is dead, except for the two kids from the main family.
Um, and they are now by the end of the film, 50 years old, I think, right? Yeah. And, uh,
they try to escape from the island. They figure out through a secret message that somebody had given
them, uh, earlier in the film that there is a way to escape this island. And it's by swimming through
the coral reef because that takes you up into a different area. By the way, the explanation is
there's something about the plates under the earth. I don't fucking know. It's like, it's like
deep nerd shit. I was like, I guess that makes sense. Like that's, but they're growing old because
there's like, because of the way like the rock and whatever and magnetic plates are situated
underneath the ground of that beach, it, it celebrates your age for some reason.
Um, and it accelerates your age much more quickly with your young, like because your cells are
dying more quickly when you're young. Um, so like, you know, at one point, the,
the one, you know, when she gets to the beach, she's like seven. Yeah. The other kids like six. And then
they, they turned into like, when they're like 20, they fuck and have a baby. And then the baby
dies immediately because like it can't survive. You know, so, so there's some interesting details like
that. I didn't understand how these two fucked. I'm like, do you know how to fuck at six?
No, it like, I don't think you learn that by six. And then they were like, there's so many holes in
the thing, you know, it's just, yeah, it's, it's the kind of move where if you think about it for
five seconds, everybody's going to have a different problem with it. And they'll all be correct,
because there's a lot of stuff that just doesn't add up. And yeah, so, so, so anyway, the kids, the,
the kids try to escape at the end, they get stuck swimming through the coral reef. They don't get out
or so you think. And then it cuts to what's going on, which is you learn that this resort is really
a secret government science or medical health facility where they're doing medical health research.
And they put people, they invite people for a free vacation to this place under the guise of you
won this or that. But the, the way they found these people is through their preexisting conditions.
And they send them to this beach so they can test out these medicines that they're secretly giving
them before they go to the beach to see how they can work in curing and stopping these diseases.
And the guy comes out and says, we need a moment of sounds for everybody that died. He goes, but
today we figured out a cure for epilepsy. We saved hundreds of thousands, if not millions of lives
today. Sadly, the only way we were able to through the sacrifice this,
movie should have just ended there. Yeah. I was like, that's kind of an interesting little twilight
zoning thing. That is how medicine works. There are sacrificial lambs that kind of speaks to this
pandemic discussion everybody's having. Are they experimenting on us? Are they not? Medicine can be cruel
in order to save and be virtuous. Eventually, casualties of war, all that stuff. There was such a sharp
commentary on a lot of stuff happening in the culture today. And chillingly, justifiable, almost
chillingly, justifiable, where you're like, man, that's fucking harsh. But that is, I guess you got to
do what you got to do. And then you find out the kids survived. And they did get through the coral
reef. And they bring down the facility and get everybody arrested. And then the last scene is them
flying in a helicopter to go home. And they said, what does your, how did your uncle react to the
news? And he goes, you know, the only way that uncle could when he when his six -year -old nephew calls
him as a 50 -year -old man or whatever. And you're like, so wait, I'm sorry, you explain this over the
phone to your uncle. And he was like, oh, okay. Yeah, it's just, it should have just fucking ended,
man. Like it should, and look, maybe that was a dumb ass studio note of like, no, that's too somber
in ending. You got to, but I feel like old Shyamalan, that would have been the goddamn ending.
Like Samuel L. Jackson wins at the end of Unbreakable. Yeah. Bruce Willis is dead at the end of
six cents, dark. It's also, it's also taking a stance, which Twilight Zone did pretty much 100 %
of the time. It's taking a stance of saying, yeah, sometimes you got to, you know, crack an egg
to make an omelette. Like if they cured epilepsy, and at the end, they're being
corded off to jail. It's like, no, Evan, I at least have the conviction to stand by what you're,
what you seem to be saying here, which is, yeah, occasionally people die in the pursuit of science,
in the pursuit of curing diseases. And he just didn't even have the commitment to do that.
Well, and leave me with, leave me to have that ethical debate in my own head. That's right.
Good and if you'll do that. But again, who knows if it was his decision or if it was a dumb ass
studio saying, you have to put a happy ending on this, you know, you read, I just was when you were
talking about the Kevin movie director, I went and looked quickly at why she got fired from the man.
Now, well, it says she parted ways with the Natalie Portman project. Creative diff, creative
differences. But it said mainly over the producers insisting the movie needed to have a happy ending.
Right. So maybe that's what it was with M Night 2, you know, but it was never the tradition with him.
I've never seen a horror movie insist upon a happy ending. I think the reason there's no stars in
this or in his last several movies, no huge stars. Aside from that Willis cameo, is that he's making his
movies that are at a really low budget. He had some massive failures. I never even saw after Earth and
the happening was awful, you know, and they stopped giving him the big budget. So he makes these
little budget movies with actors you might know and like, but not big stars. And when you, that should
give him the creative freedom to do whatever he wants. I mean, it's based on a graphic novel. I don't
know how that ended. But yeah, clearly, horror is a genre that thrives on the unhappy end, you know, it's
yeah, I think I think he could have done whatever he wanted, really. Yeah. Yeah, the movie village
beautiful. It ends on a somber note. The, you know, that these people have been tricked and lied to
their whole lives. And, you know, the, the, yeah, it's, yeah, it's, it sucked. It wasn't good. I mean,
I didn't actively hate it when I was watching it. I just was like, I just don't give a shit,
man. Like, I don't care. I'm not like offended by this. Like, it's not one of the ones that makes me
angry. Because it's so bad. I just didn't give a shit. I just wanted it to be over. And then
the one payoff was that cool science revealed the end. And then he fucking ruined that too. So then
it was like, yeah, this sucks. I don't think I will see it again to be fair. I mean, I got on
letterbox when I was done. I was like, this is one of the worst movies I've ever seen. But the theater
was laughing up worrisely throughout, you know, like that can really affect how seriously you take a
movie. But it was, it's, it's not good. It looks cool. The beach is shot beautifully,
much like the film, the beach with the caprio like they, they, they, they shot it in a cool way.
But M night is one of, he is one of the most inconsistent filmmakers in the history of the medium.
Because you've got excellent films, six cents, unbreakable. You've got really good B pictures,
split, you know, and the, and the, the, the visit, you know, like kind of good fun little horror
movies. And then you've got these swings, like old lady in the water, the happening after earth that
are some of the dumbest movies you could ever imagine. And it's so weird that they all come from the
same guy because usually directors are not that uneven. But when his highs are high, they're great. I
just, man, he's, he needs some notes. And I also wish that he would direct other people scripts
because he's got the chops. He just, his writing is sometimes not on point.
Yeah, I would, I would agree with all of that. Two hogs down hog, I'm an old hog down for,
which are old. My favorite Ridley Scott movie actually is old hog down.
The, the war movie. I like wild old hogs.
We don't know, we don't know what we're doing next. But, you know, especially now that theaters are
back and so forth, we're going to at least try to cover one of the new big ones each week.
We might, yeah. Sorry. What, what do you got? What's coming? I might do pig. We might do. I've seen
pig. I'm holding off on that. Yeah. I'm going to try to see that. We might do suicide squad. Maybe
sure. I'll check that out with day butt taste. Right? No, no, he's not in it. No. Oh,
John Cena isn't it. Right. I just, I just read that he, he was offered suicide squad and he said he
wanted to take a more meaty acting role. And that's why he went with army of the dead. Oh, God,
sequels. By the way, there's a, there's a, there's a preview for the sequel to fucking army of the dead.
This movie came out a week. No, no, no, no, no, the previews for the TV show.
Oh, oh, the TV show too. Jesus Christ. Yeah. Who liked the movie? Ask people if they liked the movie
before you do a spin -off TV show and a sequel because nobody likes it. No, it sucks. All right,
folks, we'll be back with some good stuff. That's a bunch of new stuff on Shudder. What, what,
you know, we do what we do. Take care of yourselves. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.