Happy New Year, everybody.
A belated, happy New Year.
From us, your friends that will see you in hell.
The podcast that is now part of the Fengoria podcast network
and has been since the beginning.
For more information about this network,
including other programs, how to follow,
our show, other shows,
we'll find episodes of any of these shows,
including we'll see you in hell.
Of course, please visit vangoria .com.
And here we are, Patty, 2016, January,
about to watch the movie Nurse.
I was whistling the old Langzai.
I could tell and thank you for bringing a little flavor.
You're welcome.
To the podcast.
What's new with us?
We're on different sides of the couch.
I can tell you that.
It feels wrong, but it also feels so right.
It's where I moved.
We're in my new apartment.
I had a birthday.
I'm 35 years old.
You're only 35?
Yeah.
You bastard.
When my father was 35, I would have been 12.
Right.
God, that's disturbing.
You're only 35.
If I had a 12 -year -old, it would be dead.
Long dead.
Why do you say that?
I wouldn't think about it very much.
I wouldn't think about the child's death very much.
It would have died so long ago.
Why do you say that, though?
I mean, maybe it would have whipped some responsibility
into me, but I just, I'm in no place.
I'm starting to maybe kind of think
about possibly getting in the place,
but I'm not in the place.
At this point in my life, I don't know if this will
stay the constant forever, but I'd rather kill myself
than have a child.
Well, wrap it up, Joseph.
I just, I have no desire to have a child.
This dog, old Connie boy right here, that's all I need.
Yeah.
He's right next to me.
Seems to me to be pretty much the same responsibility level.
Not at all.
You gotta run home, barking.
You feed him a couple of times a day,
you walk him a couple of times a day.
You know, he goes and sleeps in a crate at night time.
He lays around the house, there's no crying,
there's no teach me about things.
There's nothing.
He'll never develop.
It's great.
You don't have to teach your kid about things.
But the problem with a child is it develops.
That's always been my issue with it.
It's like it's not, it starts sassing you back.
Yeah.
Who wants any of that?
Maybe you get an awesome kid.
There are awesome kids.
Maybe I was an awesome kid.
But if you don't, a parent said I never cried.
I just sat and judged people.
I'd like the baby years.
I think that'd be fun.
And you have cute time with the baby.
And then after that, that's what a dog is like.
It's like a baby.
It's got some Instagram likes.
Yeah.
You know, that's all we're out there looking for.
You're, your energy's down tonight.
I will, I will say.
Does it sound like you're ready to conquer the new year?
I am.
I feel like I've already been conquering it.
And I'm weary from that.
Really?
Because everyone kind of looks at me walking on the street
and they're like, this guy's been conquering 2016.
And I come here and I, you know,
I've already spent my A and B game.
You're getting my C, frankly.
You're getting my C.
I'm not going to lie to you right now.
I already did.
I did Jimmy Parto's podcast today.
Never not funny?
Yes, and it was, I love Jimmy Parto.
I love Jimmy Parto too.
And I love doing that podcast, but it is a solid two hours.
Yeah.
We're more of talking and, and, and with no real theme,
unless it's changed since that last one.
Yeah, you just kind of futs it around.
So, so the idea of talking to you now for two hours
is not exciting.
And it is.
But I did meet a kid.
I did meet a very nice lady on the road
who told me that she's a huge fan of the podcast.
Oh, right.
And she said, I love listening to you guys talk
because I feel like I'm watching a movie with my friends.
And they're just talking the whole time.
And I said, I said, God bless you.
I'm glad you feel that way.
Because about the 60 -minute mark,
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
I'd say I always have a nice time.
I have a nice time too.
We visit, we talk, shoot the breeze.
We're going to watch some nudity.
You pour some sort of a soda cocktail every time.
Something with soda.
Actually, not every time because you never have soda,
but this is a jack with a splash of DC, Diet Coke.
Diet Coke, you brought your own Diet Coke.
It was in the fridge.
Oh, okay.
I just bought some nice natural cane sugar soda
at the new coffee shop that opened near my apartment.
Is it the new green Coke?
No, which I haven't even seen advertised.
At work, we have green Coke.
Green Coke is like, it's like another version of diet
and it's gross, but it's also 90 calories,
which is like, it's like not diet.
They keep, because they keep trying to make this hybrid,
like it's not totally aspartane, it's like some of that,
and then some sugar.
And it always just tastes like Diet Coke.
Is it worldwide or are we in a test market for it?
I don't know, but I got it, I was very excited to try it
because I thought maybe finally it's like a compromise
and it just tastes like Diet Coke.
You can't aspartane, it's like garlic.
Yeah.
Once it's in there, there's no way you're not tasting it.
You know, at least once a year, I'll go up to a bartender
and I'll go, know what I'm gonna have a little ditty
about Jack and Diet, and no one has ever laughed on it.
I would, to this day, no one's ever laughed on it.
Were you to tell me a bartender did laugh at it?
I would go and demand he be fired.
I think it's pretty strong.
If I was a bartender and all of us until now,
I was like, hey bro, you got a couple more shots
to the yeager?
And somebody comes up to me like a classy,
distinguished gentleman like myself.
I go, hey man, I got a little ditty about Jack and Diet.
I'd laugh and I go, hey you're all right,
but it's on the house.
I wouldn't even know what the fuck you were talking about.
John Cougar, Mel and Kim.
No, I know, I get the reference.
I'm saying like, John Cougar.
Were we not talking about Jack and Diet Coke right now?
I'd be like, what the hell is Diet?
I wouldn't even know what you were saying.
Diet Coke.
They get it.
That's what's infuriating is that
they usually do get it.
They just don't laugh out there.
Well, fuck.
Maybe I, maybe I'm just meant to be a bartender
because I'm not finding the humor in it either.
All right, well then go bartender.
I'll finish up this podcast.
I want to have a drink tonight,
but I had so many last night
and I'm just not gonna drink tonight.
It helps me speak freely.
It helps, it helps all of us speak freely.
My problem is as I get one in me
and then I just, you know, I want to keep going.
I'm gonna finish this and then want to go paint the town
and it'll only be midnight.
Let's think about it.
You don't have to work tomorrow?
Worked 11.
So you'll stay up till 2 a .m. tonight.
I always do.
I'm not against it.
It's Wednesday.
You ain't got shit to do tomorrow.
There's a bar over there called L something.
I can't remember the name.
I want to check it out.
Apparently it's a real beer swell and like tough guy room.
Hey, I can be tough when I need to be.
I'd go over there for a beer.
I can't be tough folks, that was a lot.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
we're watching the movie Nurse Today.
Why? Because Pat's seen it and I haven't.
Another new twist for the new year.
We've never done one where I didn't see it and Pat did.
Right, I watched it pretty recently
and it's reasonably entertaining
and it's chock full of nudity.
It's got Paz de la Huerta, who seems criminally insane.
I don't know who that is.
She was on boardwalk empire where she was naked.
Every episode, long periods of time.
I like that.
And that's what this is.
It's kind of like she's a sexy nurse and she kills people.
Okay, very good.
We're back on the Netflix because the new setup involves
my new Mac mini computer.
Thank you again to Keith Robinson
for betting me that Star Wars would not make more money
than the Avengers.
And pretty staying me $500 when he lost that plan.
I can't believe he paid that, but that's the amount
that you can be like, you know, man, sorry.
He's a betting man.
He likes to gamble.
So I took that money to the store.
I bought me a Mac mini and our new setup
is watching these on the Mac mini instead of the Apple TV.
So if you want to pause now and go to your Netflix
and look up Nurse and watch along with us, please do so.
If not, you don't have to.
And here comes the count off, Patty.
Why don't you do the honors?
Okay.
I'm gonna go one, two, three, play.
Here we go.
One, two, three, play.
Now when Nurse, there we are.
Nurse was actually released theatrically 3D.
It was released in 3D.
Yeah, it's coming in a little loud for me.
It's a little loud for me too.
Do you want to talk for a minute while I adjust it?
Yeah, I'll talk for a minute.
You got to cover this.
Okay.
So yeah, Nurse was released 3D and it was one of,
there's been a few of these horror movies
that are released like almost under the radar.
Like my, what's the one?
My bloody Valentine.
My bloody Valentine 3D.
It's still very loud, Jim.
That's better, yes, okay.
They opened with a title screen about how
the medical profession is full of malpractice
and people killing each other and things like that.
We're opening on a butt shot.
I like how they felt like they needed to justify
the purpose of this movie.
Yeah, well, it's probably to pat it out.
It's a minute, it's an hour 23.
It is an hour 23 and folks, we're not going to lie to you.
That's part of why we chose this too.
It's about 10 .30 on a school night for us.
Yeah, we're like, let's do the shining
and then realize it's two and a half hours long.
We'll do something better next time.
I mean, we're not saying this is bad, I've never seen it.
But now, why is she in this horror outfit already?
She's on the hunt.
I think, so what she does is she targets
like cheaters, married guys, assholes.
That's Owen Benjamin.
And then she kills them.
It's sort of like a dexter almost.
Which is probably how it is.
That's my buddy Owen.
I say he's too attractive to be a comedian.
He's a very good looking man.
And he's the tallest man I've ever met in my life.
Oh, wow, I'm going to get to see my buddy Owen get killed.
Yeah.
This is exciting.
Now, have you ever seen one of your friends killed
in a movie or television?
Only in real life.
Speaking of dexter, oddly enough,
I dated this girl for a while when I first moved to LA
and her friend was an aspiring actress.
And then she started getting roles.
She played Don Draper's mom in a flashback in Mad Men.
But her big break, she was like,
I'm going to be on the season premiere of Dexter.
I'm in a scene with John Liffgaugh,
which is probably the best season of Dexter.
Season four.
Okay.
And I'm like, oh, that's so great.
I watched that show.
Also, I'll be watching anyway.
It's so cool that I get to see it.
And she's like, I actually don't think
that's my friend Owen, by the way.
I think I made a mistake.
I'm sorry to cut your story off.
It doesn't look like him now that I see it either.
It just popped into my head.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Also, her ass is out in the club.
That's what I'm saying.
And that's pretty ballsy.
She's got a terrifying look to her.
Yeah.
Already.
She looks like a lunatic.
Who's who?
She honestly looks like a girl I would have dated
at some point in my life.
Now, finish your story, I'm sorry.
Okay.
So anyway, I tune into the season for me
of Dexter.
I've spent like hours with this girl.
She's my girlfriend's best friend.
And I turn on Dexter.
In the opening scene, she gets
full -frontally naked.
Bush included.
I'm like, holy shit.
Then John Lithgaugh murders her.
Spoiler alert.
Brings her into a bathtub.
And like, tenderly caresses her completely nude body.
As she bleeds out into the bathtub.
And I'm like, wouldn't you tell somebody, hey,
not only am I going to be on Dexter,
I'm going to be full -frontally nude and murdered.
She probably decided in NDA.
Maybe.
I thought she was going to be like a barista
who sells Dexter a cup of coffee.
Well, I mean, I'll tell you what's weird is.
Discuss about it.
Give us a dick bit off of it.
You know, how many times did she think
that was going to happen when she was watching Harry
and the Henderson's?
Yeah.
Probably never.
You know, that's a weird situation to be in
with John Lithgaugh.
Yeah, exactly.
You know, she just cut his dick with a scalpel.
And can I tell you, he did not react big enough.
Now, is this, is this girl a good actor?
Or is this, she's, she's convincingly crazy,
kind of like a Sharon Stone.
You completely buy that she's insane.
But she's not a strong actress now.
I don't know if I'm buying this character
she's putting out there already.
The nurse.
It's, I don't know.
It's, it's real monotone, the delivery.
I don't know.
She wasn't great on board again.
I only saw the first season of that show
and I'd like to finish it at some point.
Who did she play on that show?
She played Bishemi's like Mal.
Like, you know, she was kind of like on call to bang him.
And she was always naked.
Well, there's the reason the movie was in 3D.
Oh, God, terrible CGI.
So she shoved him off a roof and one of those,
one of those fence metal iron,
cast iron fence posts went through him.
Yeah.
Oh, the Omen, I believe, is the movie that happens in.
And it was an unnecessarily weird shot.
That clearly was made just for 3D.
Yeah, this is kind of weird.
It does like a, you can tell they're going for a camp thing
but it's never really funny or scary.
Which is the danger of the horror comedy.
I know.
I always want more Nisi Nash in my horror movies.
I love Nisi Nash.
And she's in this.
Yeah, she is.
I don't know if I have a favorite reference to say
I like her, do not like her.
I just don't think horror when I think Nisi Nash
or should do, but she's effective.
She's great on getting homage as an HBO drama comedy.
I do like her on that show.
And I thought she was funny on a Reno 9 -1.
Yes.
I, I missed, I'm a massive comedy buff
and have been since I was five years old,
but I completely missed Mad TV.
I had never seen an episode of it.
Let me tell you something.
You didn't miss shit.
Really?
Yeah, it wasn't that funny.
Now the other night they did their reunion show
and it was done really on the cheap,
but I was like, I wonder if I might have enjoyed this.
I did find there to be a shockingly racist Asian character
that I guess was one of the biggest characters on the show,
done by the woman from getting on, Alex Borstein,
who voices the mom on family guy.
Yes.
And a lot of this, Bobby Lee and a lot of this,
I was like, this is, would probably not fly today.
It wasn't, and it was only 10 years ago.
It wasn't that funny of a show.
I love Bobby.
I have friends that were on, I mean, Bobby Lee's hilarious.
Key and peel were on.
Key and peel are not friends with them,
but they were both on the show.
But yeah, there, there have been some great people on the show,
but I never found the show to be that great overall.
Okay.
Look, I can best describe it like this.
Mad Magazine is funnier than Mad TV.
Oh, I forgot that it was, they were one on the same.
Yeah, so, you know, and I'm not hating on Mad Magazine,
but you're not reading it and, you know, doubled over.
No.
Oh, no, no.
Unless maybe you're like Homer Simpson or something, you know?
Right.
The, uh, look at Judd Nelson making an appearance.
Judd Nelson, you sort of figure he retired from acting,
but the truth is he's probably just not getting work,
which is a little sad.
But, I mean, that's pretty cool that he was in a movie
that was in theaters again, because I think he was kind of...
Yeah.
Is that Kathleen Turner?
You know, I watched, you know, Dumb and Dumber 2,
and I saw some California Cation,
which is a show that got pretty bad by the end.
But Kathleen Turner, her entire role in both of those projects,
and in most of the things she does now,
is everyone tells her how fucking ugly she is
and how much she looks like a man.
Really?
And there's 800 jokes in Dumb and Dumber 2 about how ugly she is.
And look, she was unbelievably sexy in her prime.
But people age.
Yeah.
You know, Jesus Christ.
Like, she's a decent looking woman for her age.
It really bothers me.
And, you know, Dumb and Dumber was kind of a nasty movie in some ways,
but it was also very sweet.
Dumb and Dumber 2, like on the 20th minute of Kathleen Turner
looks like a bulldog jokes.
I'm like, I want to write this woman a letter
and say that I find her to be attractive.
Well, why don't you?
I mean, I should have.
Who's stopping you?
Okay.
Then again, she, like, she gets sent the script.
Her Asian has to send her a script where it's like,
you're playing really disgusting looking woman.
It breaks my heart.
It hurts me.
That hurts me to hear that.
I don't like to hear that.
And that was woman who people wanted to fuck for 30 years.
That scene in War the Roses, where she like seduces Danny DeVito.
Oh, yeah.
Is.
Whew.
Yeah.
That's the part where she like walks on her hands and everything.
Like, yeah.
Yeah, she was something else, man.
War of the Roses is spectacular.
I love it.
I still remember my priest doing a homily or a monologue or whatever
about War of the Roses and how evil it was.
Because it was about divorce?
Yeah.
I was like nine years old and they're like,
isn't it funny?
A couple divorcing.
Just shameful.
I don't know.
Right.
You know, I respect the guy for sticking to it hardcore.
The priest?
Yeah.
I don't know.
And if you're going to do it, do it right, right?
Yeah.
You know, you're good for him for not being a half ass.
I don't agree with him, but I just admire how fucking nasty
that movie was and it was a huge hit.
I loved it.
And they both died at the end.
They do.
It's incredible.
I remember the first time I saw it.
I couldn't believe that they both died at the end.
Yeah.
I could not believe it.
I was waiting.
Are you a death to smoochy fan?
Love death to smoochy.
Yeah.
I mean, DeVito is just one of the sickest fucks in the world.
He's, you know, even as kids movie Matilda is fucked up.
Is it?
It's really dark.
This is Katrina Bowden of 30 Rock fan.
This is the girl from 30 Rock?
Yeah.
Who'd she play on there?
I didn't watch TV.
We're seeing this guy.
This guy's butt and you see no nudity of Bowden.
Well, that's stupid.
I think the kid is from high school musical.
That's upsetting.
Yeah.
You know, he's got a Donald Glover vibe.
This kid.
Yeah.
Just watched Donald Glover play the smartest man in the world in the Martian.
That's literally who he plays.
Yeah.
He plays like this lazy stoner guy who strolls in.
And it's like, oh, I think I can solve your problems, NASA.
Is that movie good?
It's pretty solid.
It's not a comedy.
It's just one best comedy.
I don't understand.
Yeah.
What is that?
It's a, I mean, the Golden Globes is the most worthless television program on Earth.
They just buy the awards.
The best comedy television went to Mozart in the jungle, which no one has seen.
And I think it's a drama as well.
But basically it's like everyone behind the Martian is like, all right, we know we have a good movie here that people really enjoyed.
But it's not going to win best picture drama.
So let's just enter it as a comedy.
And the Golden Globes people are like, yeah, that's fine.
It was Obama's favorite movie of the year.
You know, it celebrates science and it celebrates intelligence.
And I like that about it a lot.
It's very nerdy.
Like the last line of the movie is like, well, science sure is special.
Isn't it?
It's like that nerdy.
Like some of you should watch the school.
Spoiler alert.
If you haven't seen it.
I, I, that tells you nothing.
I'm never going to see that.
I'm asking science is a wonderful thing.
I'm asking you to tell me the end of the movie.
Oh, no, I don't want to do that for the podcast list.
I just said spoiler alert.
Well, now do you think Matt Damon dies alone on Mars?
Do you think he comes home?
I think he comes home.
All right, well, you're right.
I'm right.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like a big triumph.
But it's a good movie.
I liked it.
Look, it's a good team of people.
It's just not the kind of movie I care about it.
It looks like Castaway with a lot of gardening in it.
Well, I fucking love Castaway.
And Martian's nowhere near as good as that.
But I did like it.
I enjoyed Castaway.
I've heard the Revenant compared to Castaway.
I don't see any comparison.
Castaway really kind of broke me up as if I can get a little pretentious
as like a metaphor for loneliness.
I thought it was pretty fantastic.
I didn't.
I haven't seen Castaway in many years.
Yeah.
But I do love the part where after he gets rescued they have that party form.
And then he's alone in the room and he just picks up that king crab leg.
Yeah.
And like just throws it.
Like he got to be kidding me.
Yeah.
Like in bridesmaids I love that Kristen Wiggit when she's sobbing watching a movie it's Castaway
and she's not watching like when Harry met Sally or something.
You know, like Castaway is to me a perfect metaphor for like just being completely alone.
And then how hard it is to readjust to people when you're not alone anymore.
Can I just take us back to the movie for a second?
Yeah.
Did you see that?
Look at this.
She's showering in her underwear because she clearly has some no nudity clause.
But then why cast her folks?
This is an all hard r horror movie.
That's not anyone who's going to put out the shot of the shower head with the water coming out of it
just so you can have the 3D water.
Yeah.
So stupid.
This movie's making me angry.
I am finding the main character sexier and sexier as we go alone.
That's what she does.
That's kind of her thing.
But she's got like, you know, I write for a show that does a lot of current event jokes
and I look at a couple of different websites each day to see what the new like celeb gossip is
so I can be up on it.
And there was a period of like three years where she was always like
tit falling out of her dress, blackout drunk, fainting at a bar, like leg spread, like every night,
like a Wednesday night there she is.
All right.
You know, look at that.
Look at that ass.
We said like a couple of pigs right now.
We're just disgusting.
Yeah, I know.
But she is, she is, I'm seeing the appeal.
Yeah, I get it too.
Now do you see her boobs in this?
Oh yeah, there you go.
Constantly.
I just came from seeing Daddy's home.
I thought you were going to say I just came.
I came a little bit.
All right.
You saw Daddy's home.
God only knows why.
I am a huge fan of both Farrell and Wahlberg.
Well then there's your answer, you know.
But the movie looks terrible.
And like there's so many comedies that are just completely panned.
A great example would be the remake of The Cation, which is not a classic by any means,
but I laugh throughout and that's all I need.
And critics made it seem like it was a fucking disaster and it wasn't.
So now sometimes they're right.
You and I saw get hard.
Get hard wasn't good, but I'm like Kevin Hart.
Well, Farrell, why would I not see this?
I didn't see get hard.
You saw that with that.
Not with me.
We saw get hard together.
We did.
I've never seen that movie.
Well, Farrell and Kevin Hart pretty movie.
Yeah, I know what it is.
I've never seen it.
We didn't?
No, I didn't see that either because it was like this movie looks terrible.
I think we talked about it on this podcast.
We might have talked about it.
They're in jail.
You saw it at the Glendale Galleria.
Pat, I didn't see it with you.
I've never seen the film.
All right.
I don't know who I fucking saw with.
That's disturbing.
I didn't think it looked funny.
And I am a fan of both of those guys.
Well, now Dad is home.
I didn't see it.
Dad is home did not look funny either.
Right.
You know, on the last podcast we talked about get hard,
and you said, yeah, that fucking sucked.
We saw it.
Pat, I didn't see it with you.
I might have said it sucked because I thought it looked like it sucked,
but I never saw the movie.
It looked like a terrible movie, so I didn't see it.
I'm baffled by this.
What do you think I'm playing a prank on you?
No, I guess not, but I just.
The lamest prank ever.
I can remember who I saw like every movie of my life with.
And I couldn't.
I barely can't.
Apparently, I can't.
Your brain's going to shit.
I don't think my brain's going to shit.
What's that from?
Because your brain's going to shit.
What is that from?
What movie's that from?
I don't know.
That's going to kill me.
Good thoughts?
No.
Because your brain's going to shit.
I can't remember.
Anyway, go ahead.
How was daddy's home?
So.
I don't give a shit about Wahlberg, really, but I love Farrell.
I like Wahlberg in a comedy.
And I figure Farrell is going to make me laugh ten times minimum,
whether the movie's good or bad.
And I was wrong, folks.
It's really bad.
And a woman I work with who I think is very bad.
Very funny, said it was good, but then I remembered she's got kids,
and she never leaves the house.
And sometimes you go to see a movie once a year, that movie's going to seem pretty good.
It's really aggressively bad.
All of the music is from 2001.
What's the music?
Like the year 2001?
No, I know.
Give me like a...
The hives.
Like, hey, to say I told you so.
And what is the significance?
Dirt off your shoulder.
Jay Z, it's literally all the music is from 2001.
Tell me how many times do white guys walk in slow motion to the Jay Z songs?
Well, that's the scene.
But white guys walk in slow motion ten times in the movie.
They walk in slow motion to dirt off your shoulder once.
How many fucking movies are there?
It's in every trailer.
How many?
The guys walk into a place in slow motion to hip -hop music.
It's every fucking movie.
It's honestly, even though I know it's not, I'm going to just say it's racist because I'm so sick of it.
Alright, I'll back you on that.
Like, stop it.
What the entire joke is that a white guy is walking to rap music?
Stop it.
This girl's got an unbelievable body.
I'm talking like Howard Stern right now, but it really is...
She really is a tremendous...
She's just naked the entire time.
It's all natural.
Yeah, that's...
I'm confused.
I don't really feel comfortable watching this movie with you anymore.
I chose it so we could perhaps take our friendship to the next level.
She's got this amazingly boss pimped out apartment and then she's got a carry coffee machine.
Carricks, you know, they're not cheap.
Guess they are.
They're pretty cheap.
I used to live in an apartment building that had a...
Carrick in the lobby.
And I go down there and have eight, ten cups a day.
And then one day I was like, you know what, if you're heating a small plastic thing
that can't be good for your cancer was and I stopped.
That's why I switched coffee pots.
I used to have the Carrick big time.
I switched because of that.
But then my parents are still in the Carrick and they found...
They found cake cups that are the safe plastic or whatever.
Okay.
There's like a safe plastic you can use.
So I guess that's what you do.
They make some that aren't.
They make a majority of them aren't.
I would assume.
That's pretty disturbing.
I would assume they're not.
So they recognize the cancer risk because they make an alternative.
There's nothing...
There's been...
Look, I switched just to be safe.
There's been really no proof yet about the hot Jesus.
She's going full frontal folks.
That's full vagina shot.
Yeah.
Not no bush.
That was like full...
You just saw her vagina.
Yeah.
It's also like this Bowden who's going to be doing this the entire time,
like wearing a bra and underwear.
You're in a scene with a woman with her vagina out.
Did anyone like say to her like...
Also, why do they keep showing...
Here's the thing.
I respect if Bowden doesn't get naked in a movie.
Why do they keep showing her in her bra?
Stop showing it.
I don't need to see her putting her shirt on.
They're trying to wind you up a little bit, I guess.
Do they just show this girl's clam?
The hell am I going to get out of her Victoria secret horse shit?
I did enjoy it.
Maybe they're going for the guy who likes something a little more classy like myself.
That guy would walk out of this movie by now.
That would have been offended.
So, I mean, Daddy's home.
The premise, everything about it's like...
You're like, okay, this is a no -brainer.
This is going to be a pretty solid comedy.
And they just miss again and again and again.
And none of the jokes hit.
Nothing about it is funny.
They do this bit where Will Ferrell talks about how the Ford Fiesta or something is like...
A great car.
It's got some fun bells and whistles for him, but also it's safe for the kids.
And you're like, okay, I get that this is a joke, but you know they got a lot of money from the Ford people?
Right.
Then they do it again at the end for longer.
So for like two minutes, they talk about the legitimate features
of the Ford whatever car it is.
You're kidding me.
And it's a new Ford model.
And it's the first and last scene of the film essentially talk at length about how great this actual car is.
You're kidding me.
And they give its full name.
I was kind of appalled by the whole thing.
And it's not done satirically either.
It's not like a Wayne's World where they're doing the albatino sponsor or whatever.
Which is fucking genius still.
Because that was, unless I'm wrong, that was like the first time I had ever seen anyone call that shut out.
No, it was...
I was blown away by that when I was a kid.
Yeah, that killed me.
The new print part.
Yeah.
Where it goes black and white.
Little yellow.
And it's the choice of a new generation.
Yeah.
That killed me.
My favorite sequence and the whole thing though is when Garth is sitting back with his feet up in his hands,
when I said, in full, Nike air, gear, gear.
And he's like, it just makes me sick, man.
You know, these people, it's like they're corporate slaves.
Yeah.
Yeah, like real like above it.
And this daddy's home.
It did everything that just bothers me about a movie where there's like scenes where like,
it's Thomas Hayden Church playing a scumbag, which should be funny.
He did it great inside with.
And it's him and Farrell and they're sitting in this office.
And for like a six minute scene, neither of them says anything funny.
And I'm like, why not just show me a recording of Will Farrell talking to Thomas Hayden Church for six minutes?
Because it'll be funnier than this.
Where the hell was Thomas Hayden Church been?
You know when I bet happened as he got nominated for an Oscar for Sideways and he got all that acclaim.
And then everybody was, didn't really know what to do with him.
But he also wasn't going to take some shitty project.
I actually also heard that he's like not like, he's just kind of like,
I'll work if I feel like working like he's not like that.
Okay.
He's got wings money.
They kind of had to talk him into Sideways.
Well, that role was written for Clooney who wound up not being able to do it.
Yeah.
And Alexander Payne apparently called him and said, I want you to be in my movie.
And he was like, nah.
I did not know that.
And he said, you get to have sex with my wife in it because he was married to that girl.
Sandra, yeah.
Yeah.
He is great in that movie.
I would have loved to see what Clooney did with it as well.
But it would have been the same.
No.
Clooney's too likable.
I don't know if I've ever seen him play like a dark.
Not that dark, not.
It's really.
It's just like such a small kind of special movie and Clooney would have upset that balance, I think.
Yeah.
And it also would have taken away from GMOD and that was kind of his breakout.
Right.
I felt like, you know.
Yeah.
This daddy's home.
Now they have Paul Sheer come out as this announcer at a big basketball game.
Paul Sheer is on screen for five minutes.
And I'm not saying that nothing he said was funny.
I'm saying they didn't write him even anything in the proximity of a joke.
They just didn't like you.
You couldn't.
I'm sure Paul Sheer is on set and it's like, guys, you don't want to give me one joke.
I'm funny.
I'm a funny actor.
You don't want to give me something funny to say.
It's an infuriating movie.
I find it's always a bit problematic when Farrell is without Adam.
What's his face?
Yeah.
Okay.
And then I saw McCay produce it and I was like, well, that's kind of a shock or two.
You know, like I liked, I liked the basketball one, semi -pro, but it would have been 20 times better
if McCay did it.
I agree.
I'll take Blades of Glory over semi -pro even.
I like Blades of Glory.
But like Andy Daly and semi -pro is a great example of like a bit part where they gave them
some funny shit to do.
Like Andy Daly is really funny in that movie.
And it's very funny in it.
But by the way, how happy are you that that trope has finally ended?
The zany announcers?
Oh, yeah.
That are saying like...
Well, you're never going to do it better than Yooker in Major League.
I would say the crown.
A Yooker in Major League is really great, but just a bit outside.
I would give the crown to Fred Willard in Best and Show.
Okay.
Well, sure.
Can you really call that a sports movie?
I don't know.
But it's the character.
It's the announcer saying like inappropriate stuff though.
Yeah.
Now on our last podcast, we talked about John Michael Higgins and how he steals Best and Show.
Give it a pepperoni.
I'll hold it over.
Yeah.
He was on the show right for two more girls this week.
Just fucking killing it.
And it's crazy.
We had this part.
The role is basically this guy is going to break up with Kat Dennings using his therapist to do it.
He brings his therapist to dinner to break up with her.
Okay.
And it's a pretty funny scene.
But you know, again, the therapist didn't really have any funny lines.
And we heard it was him.
And I just like sprang to life and wrote like 20 jokes for this guy.
And then you see him in the thing and it's like, yeah, we're going to need to bring him back
at the end of the episode.
Like he just elevates everything.
It was him and Coolidge.
And then we also had the woman who played the descendant of Blaine Fabin and waiting for
government.
The really intense, weird black hair woman.
Yes.
These three, like I'm hoping they do some improv even though our show doesn't really allow it.
But just reading what we wrote, they were fucking incredible.
Yeah.
They're just fucking pros.
They make everything funny.
He worked with Coolidge on the guest movie.
So it was like a little reunion thing for them.
It was a reunion.
And you know, you didn't get the feeling they didn't like each other.
But like they came in and didn't seem to know each other.
And then you remember that those casts are so huge.
Coolidge and him probably never met.
That's weird.
Like they're in no scene together in those movies.
He hits honor in, oh yeah, that's true.
In for your consideration.
That is true.
I forgot about that.
Which is the only character I've ever seen him do that could conceivably take the trophy
from the best in show character.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, it's, it's, it's tremendous.
All right.
So here she is in a brawn panties again.
Why?
I don't know.
I mean, she's, she's not a name so you can get anybody in there.
I never understand in a hard art movie like this where the nudity is a lot of the appeal.
Why you're casting somebody with a no nudity clause.
It makes no sense.
I, uh, and again, I know I sound like a scumbag.
I don't really care, folks.
I've paid zero attention to the story.
There's not much story.
I mean, she's, she's kind of a, it's a single white female type deal with her and Bowden.
And then on the side she, you know, says a bunch of dudes and kills them.
She's obsessed with Bowden and she wants to be with Bowden.
Yeah.
And she also, you know, she tries to kind of blackmail her by saying that, you know, she got her own
ecstasy and got pictures of her with dudes out at a bar.
She just likes to fuck with people's lives.
She's a villain.
It's all there is to.
What, what does she try to blackmail her for?
Sex?
Uh, I don't even remember.
I don't even remember.
Okay.
Now, now, if you had to marry one of these two characters, which one would you marry?
It's a fascinating question.
It's like that same question works from Mahal and Drive, you know.
But you didn't know that the dark -haired one was crazy.
You can't, that can't come into account.
I think I could sense that she was crazy.
That's what I feel like, too.
It took me 10 years, but my crazy radar is so strong right now because I've dated a lot of really nuts girls.
Actually, that's not true.
I've dated a couple.
I always say, if a guy says every girl is ever dated is crazy, the guy is crazy.
Right.
But if a guy says one girl he dated is really crazy, that girl's crazy.
Well, give him a few.
A few should get more than one.
I've had a couple.
You know, I'm sure girls have thousands of guys that they think are crazy and I'm sure they are as well.
Uh, now, how many times did you, I'm not done with Daddy's home yet.
How many times did you laugh out loud in the theater?
I usually, a movie like that at the beginning, you'll laugh because you're still kind of like,
this could maybe get funny or whatever.
I didn't even have that.
I didn't laugh out loud one time.
Nothing.
Uh, at the end of the movie, I liked the ending of the movie and it's a dance scene and they go up against your dear friend Bill Burr.
Bill, Bill's in that movie.
He's randomly in the final scene of this movie and he has a dance off with Mark Wahlberg and Wolf Feral.
That's kind of funny.
Bill dances in the movie.
He dances.
He's like an asshole who wants to fight the dads.
Really?
Yeah.
All right.
It's a nice little part.
In fact, I think he told me when he was doing, I don't remember.
It's the kind of movie where you just feel like I bet everyone had a way better time on set than I did watching this movie.
Okay.
And they didn't show any outtakes, so maybe they didn't have fun because these are the movies that always have outtakes.
The outtakes from, uh, there's a, there's a clip online, a YouTube clip of Will Farrell, the best of Will Farrell like bloopers.
Yeah.
And it's just one after the other from all these different things.
And as an acting exercise, I've watched it and tried not to laugh.
Yeah.
Because I was like, what if you're in this situation? You'd have to get through it.
And it is impossible.
The funniest outtakes in the history of film and television are Will Farrell and Eastbound and down.
That's the, that's, it starts with that.
That is the funniest thing I've ever seen.
And he has Danny McBride like it's in the scene as air.
Danny McBride's head is violently trembling.
It's brutal.
It's so funny.
The thing when he saw how I was kidned down to my plum.
The kid walks in and he says, let the boy watch.
When I was having sex with his wife, I said, let the boy watch.
They are, those outtakes are the funniest things ever.
If you get a chance, Will Farrell Eastbound and down bloopers outtakes.
Let the boy watch.
Yeah.
He talks about how his ball, he keeps doing the thing about his nuts.
Plums.
And he goes, take him to Phalmas mock.
Yeah.
Oh, get ready for the market.
Put one in my sack lunch.
From my dessert.
I feel the juice dripping down my chin.
Yeah.
It's funnier than anything he did on Eastbound and down.
Like the outtakes are incredible.
I had two moments like that on the shooting things.
And I'll tell you the stories, Pat.
The first was on when I did Louis.
This line didn't make the episode, but he said, Joe, I want to end the scene with you holding up a parking ticket.
And saying, do you guys pay for parking because the fat content at the front desk says you don't validate.
I couldn't get through the fucking line.
I was laughing so hard.
I got through it once by like the skin of my fucking teeth.
And he had the camera right on me.
It was so low close up like it was brutal.
And the second one was the one of the times I was doing Amy Schumer.
I was in a sketch with Kurt Metzger and Zach Braff.
Uh -huh.
I remember that sketch.
Yeah.
And the end of the sketch is Amy saying like she wants to Zach.
Her husband in the sketch is played by Zach.
She wants him to come upstairs and shit on her.
Uh -huh.
And he would end the sketch.
He would grab this chicken wing and he'd go, I better eat up.
I got shit in the do.
And he would start chopping the chicken wing.
And dude, I was fucking, we couldn't fucking get through it.
It was so fucking funny.
It was so funny.
Like there's something about when a guy does something that's so real.
Right.
He was doing it exactly the way like a excited 15 year old kid would do it.
Yeah.
And it was so real.
I couldn't stop laughing.
It was one of the great moments of my life.
He said I can't even, I can't look at you.
And I was like, oh, that's pretty cool.
The guy from Scrubs.
Yeah.
Can't get through it.
I can pretty much always stop laughing.
Oh, it's a rare gift.
I can't even get it like funerals and stuff.
I'm bad, man.
Yeah.
I got it all.
I used to laugh at church with my sister all the time.
Really pissed my dad off.
So now I'm really good at clipping it when I need to.
You what?
Did you stop?
I'm talking.
Clipping my laughs when I need to.
Oh, it's something like you're going to keep talking and you cut it off.
That's all I had to say on that.
Now, she just killed this guy with a needle in his neck.
She said it made her come.
Yeah, that's fine.
But then she pushes the car down an alleyway with the dead guy in it.
And it just so happens, a truck t -bones it and then it makes it look like it was a car accident.
Right.
What?
How did she know that that was going to happen?
I don't know.
Oh.
And what was she going to do if the truck didn't hit it?
She didn't know.
She couldn't see that there was a truck coming.
I can't believe this movie was in theaters.
Three days.
Did you see my bloody Valentine?
No, but it's the second time you brought it up.
No, I might be even getting the title wrong.
But it was a 3D kind of low budget thing like this.
Yeah, I remember.
I remember.
Are you going to tell a story about it?
No, I eventually saw it.
I mean, I have a 3D TV and player and all that.
And I love like I got Mad Max and watched on 3D.
And it was fucking incredible.
I love watching a 3D movie at home.
Yeah.
I love going to the theater and seeing him.
But these low rent ones just scream like like what's like you're saying?
They'll show a shower and 3D and then 10 minutes later.
There's a pencil that gets thrown at the screen.
There hasn't been one 3D type shot.
No.
She's that shower.
No, it's just like a they try to jump on the bandwagon.
There's no need for you to be in 3D.
No, they and they don't make the money.
They think they'll make either.
They think that just any idiot will go see a 3D movie.
But they won't.
No.
The second time I saw Star Wars, the new one it was in 3D.
How was that difference?
It was an incredible experience.
Okay.
Better in 3D?
I wouldn't say better necessarily.
It was just slightly different.
My favorite viewing, I've seen it three times now.
My favorite of the three was the 35 millimeter screening at the Vista.
Okay.
Vintage cinemas.
That was really cool because it was the grainiest of all of them.
Yeah.
And it just, I felt like I was back like a kid again like watching Star Wars in the theater.
Now, we haven't discussed the new one.
I know you loved it.
I liked it very much.
Are you going to see this seven times in the theater as well?
I think I'm going to see it one more time.
I think four is going to do it for me.
Okay.
And then I'll still be excited for it to come out on Blu -ray.
I can't wait for the next one.
John Boyega said that the next movie is very dark.
And the next one is like a clone side shot.
What?
It's like a side movie.
No, no, no, no.
He's saying episode eight, the sequel, the four awakens.
But aren't they making some sort of...
They're making one off.
They're not clone movies.
The first one off is Rogue One.
And it's about the rebel assault to steal the plans of the Death Star.
Okay.
So it's a prequel of the Star Wars, the original.
With any of the same characters?
There's rumors going around that young Han Solo might make an appearance in it to kind of set up his solo movie.
Okay.
But I'm going to show how many of these things are in the theater I think is in it.
Do we have like 30 Star Wars movies coming?
They're going to do one a year, they said.
It's going to be like Marvel.
They're going to do one a year.
Where do you slip in Force Awakens now to your ranking?
Top three or two.
You're saying possibly Empire followed by Force Awakens?
Empire's number one.
I'd go Empire Force Awakens.
Wow.
Star Wars.
Revenge of the Sith.
Return of the Jedi.
Okay.
Attack of the Clone's Phantom Menace.
That's my order.
All right.
Put your order.
Well, I've rewatched all of them now except I need to rewatch Sith.
But I'm going to go...
I think I'm going to go Empire...
Shhh.
Jedi Star Wars.
Out of your mind.
Force Awakens.
You know, I got to see these all again.
It's hard to compare something you saw once on a Saturday afternoon to something you've seen 18 times since you were a little kid.
I mean, Jedi...
I think it's unreasonable to compare those two things.
It's Jedi.
It's just...
I love the opening.
The whole opening.
And I love all the stuff with Luke versus Vader.
But I mean, just the Ewoks.
I love the Ewoks.
The Ewoks...
Like making keystone cops out of the Empire.
Yeah.
And also too.
It's like...
Guys, in the last movie, you kicked the shit out of the rebels when you needed to.
Mm -hmm.
Why don't you have the walkers down on Endor taking care of business?
You got one thing down...
You know what I mean?
Like, where's your...
Where's your artillery here?
Sure.
Doesn't make any sense to me.
I wasn't completely enamored with the two new heroes in Force Awakens.
I thought the...
I mean, forgive me here.
The black guy, I don't remember his...
Finn.
Was just needlessly screaming the entire movie.
Like, scared of everything.
To a point where I was like, shut up, man.
And I thought that the girl...
I loved her.
Was...
Yeah.
Very likable, but also...
I don't know.
They didn't have the same thing where I was like...
I'm excited.
These are my guys here.
Like, I did with the other ones.
I...
I felt like that.
I'm excited to see her...
Like, and Chewbacca kicks a mass in the next one.
Become more powerful.
Yeah.
I did love Kylo Ren.
I love Kylo Ren.
And I love that he was like, weird and like...
Potentially homosexual and everything that he was bringing to the table.
I was like...
I like this.
This is different and weird.
I like Poe Dameron a lot too.
Yeah.
Everything felt a little too familiar to me except Kylo Ren.
That was...
I was like, this is a weird like...
Psychosexual kind of vibe that I'm into.
And I like that he had like a woman's haircut.
And I like this voice.
I was into it.
Now, did you only see it once?
I only saw it once.
I think on second and third views you would appreciate the new characters a lot more.
I think so too.
I definitely think so too.
You know, it's a lot to take in on that first screening.
Sure.
I liked it a lot.
I had a great time.
Yeah, it was quite fun.
What was your favorite part?
You know what?
If I could...
If I may be so bold,
if I had to pick a reason why I wouldn't say it was like one of my favorites of the series
is because I didn't have a scene when I was like, fuck yes.
I didn't.
I don't even understand.
I thought it all kind of was like kept it at an even B plus keel.
And it never really...
It never went anywhere near like the fucking Phantom Menace where you're like,
what am I watching?
What is this trash I'm watching?
But it also never went into the like a zone where I'm like, holy shit this is amazing
to me.
I never had a scene where I was like, this is new and exciting and crazy.
I think you're nuts.
I did like when she was able to use the powers of the Force.
That was very cool.
You didn't light up when she goes garb the garbage will do and they run towards the ship
and it's the Millennium Falcon.
And that whole sequence of her like learning how to fly it.
I think people clapping is what made me realize it was the Millennium Falcon.
Yeah.
That scene literally tears to my eyes.
It got me so excited.
Han and Chewy when the Rhylarks, whatever the fuck they were called, get loose.
Yeah.
I'm not the die hard star wars guy.
Evidently.
You said you didn't know it was the Millennium Falcon.
When everybody clapped I was like, okay, this must be the Millennium Falcon.
This must be the...
All right, let's start.
We don't need to talk about this anymore.
It is what it is.
To a child evidently.
DC Nash, I'm just picking up now, is the comic relief in this film.
Yeah.
We've been talking through the whole film but through all of her scenes as well.
Right.
And I just realized she's...
This is supposed to be some comedic thing.
They've got a character running around the hospital putting smiley face stickers on everybody.
Yep.
Not quite sure why...
It's ironic.
You know, I'm sure there's a reason.
But who is this girl playing the smiley face girl?
I don't know.
She is.
We're having a Judd Nelson.
Is he dead?
No, he's around.
He does die.
Spoiler alert.
I watched the Danish girl.
Eddie Redman dressing up like a woman.
Yeah, how was it?
Didn't care for it.
It's not getting great reviews.
No.
I thought that guy was going to grab a nasker two years in a row.
But the reviews have been kind of mild about it.
I mean, he even shows his dick.
He tucks it back.
Buffalo Bill style.
Does he dance in the mirror like Buffalo Bill?
No, he makes...
Straight up, he makes way too many faces.
Like, he's already like in a full dress and like Sunday ladies hat.
But then he's like really overdoing the faces and acting.
And I thought at times, and I could not be more accepting and tolerant of the whole movement.
Well, here comes the statement.
That was a hell of a disclaimer you're putting in.
I really could, but I was just like this guy is...
He's not trying to treat this with any kind of respect.
He's desperately begging to get an Oscar.
Because he got a taste of it right out of the gate.
And now he's like he's...
You're already playing a woman.
You're already dressed as a woman.
You don't need to insanely gesture and move your face around.
All right.
Well, I don't think you needed that disclaimer.
That's not intolerant what you just said.
I just didn't think he was good at the acting.
Joe, you know the times in which we live.
I do.
I just didn't care for it.
And I'm sitting there.
I turn to my girlfriend and be like, this is ridiculous.
And she's got tears streaming down her face.
So it works on some obviously.
I went to see Creed with my dad.
Love Creed.
It was sold out.
You didn't see it yet?
I haven't seen it.
Joe, that's fucking nuts.
It was sold out because I...
That's fucking nuts, Joe.
The Philadelphia area that movie is even more popular than everywhere else.
Creed is really great.
Well, it was sold out.
So my dad and I ended up seeing hateful eight instead.
Which I couldn't believe wasn't sold out.
Right.
And we loved every minute of it.
It was a little awkward sitting next to my dad during the scene where
there's a forced male on male blowjob.
But let me ask you this.
And I think it's fair now.
It's been out a while.
And that is only the act one break.
Do you think that actually happened or that he was trying to force Brewster in his hand?
I think that's one of the...
All right, we're going to go real heavy spoiler right now.
Because I've been waiting to talk to you about why.
But now wait.
Are we only spoiling up to that hour and a half, Mark?
No, I'm going to tell you our most freely about this movie.
All right.
Well, folks, I don't know what you want to do here.
It's movies and theaters.
I don't necessarily love that we're about to spoil the movie.
We're not spoiling because we're giving the warning so you can tune out if you don't want to hear it anymore.
Okay.
So my...
I...
Then they don't know when to come back.
All right.
Do you want to talk about this any longer?
When you click back into the...
When you click back into the show, just make sure we're not still talking about it.
I'm trying to get through this goddamn nurse movie.
If you're a film fan, you should have seen the new content to the movie by now, frankly.
One of the things I loved so much about the movie was the brilliant setup of Samuel Jackson's character
with that letter from Lincoln, where you didn't know if what he was saying was true or not.
I thought that was brilliant.
Another place where they exploited that was he talks about how the lady that owned the Habadashary hated Mexicans.
Yes.
And when you see the scene in the flashback where she meets the Mexican guy, she's a joy to him.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
So they just...
There were little nuances in his stories and whatever like that where you were like, is he lying?
Is he telling the truth?
Is he not?
I love that.
I thought it was awesome.
Another Easter egg thing that I thought was so cool was when Tim Roth, when they show the flashback
and you see that he is speaking with a put on accent through the first act of the movie.
Right.
The accent he goes into in the second act, which is his real accent.
Yeah.
Is the same accent he uses in reservoir dogs.
Yeah, that's true.
As the undercover cop.
That's true.
I was like, that's so fucking cool, man.
I really...
There were little moments like that that I really, really liked.
Hate the late, there are multiple little moments that I was like, that was great.
And yet, on the whole, it's my least favorite Tarantina movie.
Although I give it a B+.
Gladly.
I had a good time.
I just thought, you know, I would have loved to see any of his other movies extended to a three hour length
and shot in 70 millimeter.
And this seemed to not be the one to do the either of those things in, to me.
I loved it.
It was one of his most impressive movies to me.
As far as the shots they were pulling off.
Yeah.
I mean, the outdoor stuff was fucking incredible.
Yeah, there were shots.
I was like, this is one of some of those beautiful things I've ever seen.
Well, there's a scene where there's a naked man going through three feet of snow and it's really happening.
Yeah.
And you're like, how are they doing this right now?
Well, if I'm going to be in a Tarantina movie, I'll walk naked through the snow.
So there was, it was an amazing.
I got nothing to hide.
There was an amazing feat that they shot in that kind of weather and whatever.
It was to me.
I liked it better than his last three movies.
Oh, okay.
Here's one.
All right.
I liked it better than Django and Glorious Bastards.
Kill Bill or Deathproof.
So it was less four.
Wow.
The only one I could understand would be Deathproof.
Here's why.
I'll tell you why.
It's the, those are all great movies.
Yeah.
Not knocking those movies.
This movie to me was the most Tarantino thing he had done since Jackie Brown.
It was pride and true Tarantino.
More Leonard thing.
It was dialogue driven.
It was these are your characters.
It wasn't jumping like into all these different storylines and sequences
that were happening in all these different places.
I know Pulp Fiction kind of does that.
Yeah.
But I just mean like, you know, Django Unchained,
Glorious Bastards, Kill Bill.
These are like epic movies.
Right.
Epic sprawling movies that tackle very specific genre.
Pieces and cinema.
You know, Kill Bill is the samurai movie.
Right.
You got the World War Two movie.
You've got the Western.
And this, of course, was a Western too.
But it was reservoir dogs to me.
It was like, it was like, here eight guys.
They're strapped in this room.
And we're going to figure out who we can trust and who we can't.
Yeah.
And it was, it just, I loved it, man.
I fucking loved it.
I, again, that's one I would very, I will definitely see,
again, before it leaves theaters.
But, to me, I couldn't help but feel a little let down by the whole thing.
And I hated everyone in it.
It's called the hateful eight pit.
I know.
I thought Samuel Jackson was awesome.
But at the end of the day, I was like, I liked the reservoir dogs.
I don't like these people.
Oh, I know.
See, I felt very similar about the reservoir dogs to these guys.
I felt like they were, there were guys you kind of started to like.
And then they would say something horrific or do something horrific.
Yeah.
And you'd be like, I don't like this guy anymore.
And by the end of it, there was kind of like one or two guys that you liked.
Sure.
And it was, it was Roth and Kytel and that.
And in this one, it was the sheriff that redeems himself.
Sure.
And Sam Jackson.
And, and the whole, the whole revelation at the end of it like,
it's kind of becomes this movie about racial progress.
And I don't know.
I just thought it was great.
We should go see it at the arc light because the arc light is showing the two hour and change
cut.
I'd be curious to see what the tighter version is like.
Yeah, I only saw that road show version as well.
That's all I saw.
Yeah.
I did dig it very much.
Tarantino has done so much greatness that it's really not fair to compare a movie of his to his other movies
because there's some of my favorite movies.
But to me, it's his least successful movie.
Maybe a repeat of you and we'll change that.
Well, here's the thing too that I also appreciated because there were certain people were complaining
about the road show aspect of it and the length and all this stuff.
Oh, I love to have an intermission.
I like that he tried to create an experience.
Yeah.
For my dad.
My dad was like blown back by that too because it took him back to being a kid again.
Yeah.
He, we got home.
He said to my mom.
He's like, when's the last time he saw a movie with an intermission?
Yeah.
Like, my dad was tied into that movie, man.
My dad really falls asleep a lot during movies.
Yeah.
So the fact that he was in there and stuck with it probably helped me.
That my enjoyment, my own enjoyment of it.
Well, I think I said the last time on this podcast, the last, the only movie I ever saw with an intermission was Dance of the Wolves, which was 1990.
I don't think they've done it since.
I've never seen Dance of the Wolves.
I thought that was pretty cool.
Dance of Wolves, at least when I was a kid, I loved.
I'm sure it still holds up.
Shocked that there's a kid you'd have an interest in that movie.
My dad brought me.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It was ten.
It's a western.
It's fun.
Did you, uh, but you didn't answer my question.
We talked for ten minutes and still didn't answer my question.
Do you think Samuel Jackson forced that guy to suck his dick?
Or not?
Well, no, that's, I thought I did.
What I was saying was the beauty of it was, you don't know.
Right.
That was...
But what do you think?
I think probably not.
I think not, yeah.
I think he probably just killed the guy's son.
I did laugh really hard at them.
Because it was just so shocking.
It was intense.
It was up there with...
Well, again, classic Tarantino was like the gimp scene in Pulp Fiction.
Yeah, yeah.
It was like, whoa.
He totally just showed it.
The music is exceptional.
The Ennio Maricone's...
The Ennio Maricone scores is great.
The Ennio Maricone is exceptional.
It just won the Golden Globe.
And then Tarantino got in trouble for saying ghetto.
What did he say?
He said, any Ennio Maricone is my favorite composer of all time.
And he's like, I'm not just limiting it to film composers, that ghetto.
I'm talking about Beethoven.
And then Jamie Foxx gets up after...
Jamie Foxx, who did Django One Change, arguably Jamie Foxx's best movie with Tarantino.
He gets up to the mic after him and he goes, ghetto.
Like disgusted with him.
That's a term that means neighborhood.
And now, no, I'm well aware.
I just thought that people really want to mark Tarantino as a racist.
And I just do not buy it because he's given some of the most interesting parts
for African Americans of the past 20 years.
For sure.
You look at Jackie Brown, somebody who creates that movie around that character.
Simply cannot be a racist.
And granted his usage of the N word is a little insane at times.
I thought there was until the end, until where I realized where hatefully it was going.
I was like, okay, this seems excessive and weird.
Yeah.
And at the end, the way it all came together, I was like, okay, I get it.
I see what he was doing.
To me, what he was trying to do, at least, was he was showing how much of a jump it was
for that sheriff to side with Samuel Jackson.
For sure.
And he was also showing how awesome Samuel Jackson's character was and how mistreated he was.
Yeah.
And the justice being finally served in the end.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, Bruce Dern was another thing I loved in the setup was when they showed the flashback,
Channing Tatum says to Bruce Dern, you say hello.
You tell him your name and you don't say shit else.
Right.
And Bruce Dern can't fucking help it.
He's so racist.
Yeah.
You can't fucking help it.
And he sets off the chain of dominoes that gets everybody killed.
Yeah.
Even just this conversation, I want to see it again.
So that part was great.
Clearly it was not a failure.
Yeah, it was great.
I also love to the, what's it called?
What was I going to say?
I can't remember.
It's funny.
My dad had no, my dad, like I knew Tarantino's name, but doesn't know who he is.
Right.
And he called me and he was like, hey, I just want to let you know that any Omar Akone guy won the Golden Globe for best soundtrack to a movie.
I was like, oh, that's cool.
Yeah.
I go, I didn't see the show and he goes, well, that Tarantino fella accepted for him.
He's a, he's a strange guy.
I was like, yeah, he's kind of weird, right?
He looks like Frankenstein at this point.
He's got like weird fake hair and everything looks like he has bolts coming out of his neck.
His forehead seems to be growing.
Yeah, exactly.
It's very odd.
But I love him.
I'm glad he's making movies.
I'll tell you that much.
Yeah.
There was one other thing I was going to mention.
I can't remember.
Oh, what did you think of the, that's what it was about the Golden Globes.
What did you think of the Jervace Mel Gibson exchange?
It actually made me feel bad for Mel Gibson.
I was like, you know what, man?
Like the guy is going to show his face now after like 10 years.
And you're just going to bring up the same fucking thing.
Yeah, I agree.
I agree.
And here's the thing.
What it what it reminds me of.
And so my favorite songwriter of all time is Elvis Costello.
I love Elvis Costello and I understand he's a divisive person.
I don't really care.
But well documented is in a bar with like Crosby Stills and Nash who he despised in the 70s.
Right.
Costello used to be like a two bottle of vodka day alcoholic.
And he's so drunk he can't stand in this bar.
And he's trying to get a rise out of Steven Stills of Crosby Stills and Nash.
We consider it as like a hippie loser.
And they start screaming at each other.
And he's like, tell me somebody you like or whatever.
And he tells him that he likes Ray Charles.
And Elvis Costello refers to Ray Charles as an end work.
Right.
To get a rise out of Steven Stills and try to give him to punch him in the face.
Now Elvis Costello is based pretty much his entire life on a celebration of African American music
and working with African American artists.
Right.
But this is out there.
And it's been out there and he addresses it in both of his biographies and discusses it like
gives an entire chapter to it.
Right.
When you know he'd rather let it go.
But he feels clearly a lot of guilt and bad about it.
And someone asked Ray Charles about it because they shared a bill together.
Elvis Costello and Ray Charles.
And Ray Charles, they said, now you know Elvis Costello said this about you in 1979 or whatever.
And Ray Charles goes, oh, drunk talk is drunk talking.
It should be left at that.
All right.
Now look, there's a lot to say about this.
It's kind of insane.
But like I, I at my absolute drunkest have not said the end word.
I don't get that.
I don't understand.
Right.
But like when I look at Mel Gibson, I'm like, look, I heard those tapes.
Him screaming at that woman.
You got to blow me in the jacuzzi.
Me and Pete Holmes used to work at outsource.
And all day we would listen to these smellgibs and tapes.
Right.
And how hilariously insane they were.
Like, I'm proud to say it.
My darkest, drunkest moment.
You're not going to find me saying anything that would get me exxile from the entertainment industry.
Right.
Which happened with Mel Gibson.
Sure.
But like, I mean, God damn it.
Like, we're just never going to let this guy back in.
Well, no.
We're going to keep bringing up this the most painful.
But this is why I brought it up.
Yeah.
Well, number one, I've always been in the belief.
Obviously, I don't agree with anything the guy said.
Of course.
I've always been of the belief.
Like, when I've heard those tapes of him, I was like, this sounds beyond drunk to me.
This sounds like a guy that's off his medication and is having some sort of a breakdown.
Thousand percent.
So, obviously you try to give a guy a little more leeway because there are things interfering.
I don't think Mel Gibson is a racist.
Having seen him be like best pals with Danny Glover all those years.
You know, right.
And I mean, I guess his remarks were focused on the Jews.
Correct.
Well, that's the second incident.
I'm referring to his end bomb and the original voicemails or whatever.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
My point is, is like, I think the guy had a problem.
Now, wait, did he say I hope you get raped by a pack of, was that him?
Yes.
Oh, boy.
Mel.
And then we're focused on sugar tits.
That's weird, too.
Well, I mean, I think there's even some things that people don't feel comfortable joking about.
Sure, sure.
But here's my point.
Here's my point.
I think the guy was in a bad fucking place.
Clearly.
And fucked up.
And I think he's sorry for it.
And I think that he's trying to redeem himself.
And he's apologized.
And I think that that appearance was a huge step in the right direction for him.
Because two things.
The first thing is he got that colonoscopy line in on your face.
It got a huge fucking laugh.
Yeah.
It got a huge laugh.
Regeries comes back out, which was kind of a baby move.
I agree.
He got you.
You needed the last word.
Yeah.
Regeries gets the last word.
Walks off.
And then Mel Gibson says in response to the sugar tits question, you'll have to ask the guy that said it because it wasn't me.
Hmm.
So he's just like, dude, he said that on stage.
Yeah, he goes, you ought to ask the guy that said it wasn't me.
And it's like, dude, I was fucked up, man.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I think, I think he got a lot of ground for himself in that appearance.
I really do.
And look, he, he agreed to do it.
He clearly knew like I'm going to be brought out by this guy.
He's going to make jokes.
Yeah.
And he was like ready to handle himself.
And he did.
I just think like Jody Foster who was like an out and proud lesbian and all these people coming forward and being like.
Guys, this isn't Mel Gibson or whatever else.
You know, it's enough for me to like at least be like, all right, I don't need to throw a tin can at this guy when he walks on stage.
No, it's not ideal.
But like, you know, the shittiest things people have said and done.
He's one of the few people that has had his publicly dissected now for a fucking decade.
Yeah, I think he had a bad, he had a bad run.
And he was in a bad place and some unfortunate things were said.
And hopefully horrific things.
He comes back, you know.
But that appearance, I was rooting for him.
I was like, I want to see the guy.
You know what else I think helped seeing an awesome Mad Max movie.
And everybody kind of being like, oh yeah, we love Mel Gibson.
Yeah.
Like, you know, I think, you know, my mother, the only and looking back on it now, it's a little strange.
The only time I ever knew my mom to be like, to watch a movie more than once even was lethal weapon.
And she would watch it like 20 times, all those lethal weapon movies and she loved them.
And later on it occurred to me, she had the hots for Mel Gibson.
Yeah.
He had a lot of butt scenes in the 80s.
And she'd watch all his movies again and again and no one else's.
I remember my mom and her friend talking about how much they loved the bear -ass scene that Mel Gibson did in lethal weapons.
He was kind of a huge deal in his day.
And I think Braveheart and Apocalypse are fantastically directed movies as well.
So like I -
I feel the crisis is a fantastically directed film.
Yeah.
I thought his smart move would be to stay behind the camera and direct.
But then again, anyone who wants to act with him now has to fess up to like people saying, well, now you're aligning yourself with an anti -Semite.
I think -
And I've always been of the belief too that -
This is always my -
This is my Woody Allen defense.
I think when somebody has these types of -
When somebody is this person truly in their heart,
Yeah.
Or at their core, I think they're -
It's never one or two weird slip -up things.
It's like there are several incidences or incidents usually.
That's my opinion.
I don't know if I'm right or not, but -
And I think if he -
If I think if Mel Gibson wasn't a guy that had a bad run -in with drugs or alcohol or whatever and made some mistakes,
And truly was that guy, there would have been a hell of a lot more accounts of it.
Yeah, I mean -
It's one of the first -
I think there is also -
As much as I hear that and respect that opinion.
There's also a part of me that thinks that might be what we want to believe,
Because we like these people.
Whereas if Jamie Kennedy was caught doing it, he'd be like, fuck that guy.
Well -
We don't know, no one knows.
All I can do is say I like Mel Gibson's movies, I like him as an actor and director.
I like Woody Allen's movies, obviously.
And just hope that they're not the monsters that we've come to believe they might be.
I hope not.
It's a scary thought.
But I think there's a lot of people who are way worse, who are never exposed.
I guess my point is -
Oh, Jesus Christ.
It's an endless stream of people saying, yeah, no, he does do that.
Yeah.
I mean, when Travolta got accused of grabbing that masseuse's dick or whatever -
A lot of masseuses came from him.
It was like shit loads.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
It was like, so I don't know.
We'll see.
How much longer does this goddamn movie have, by the way?
It's about over.
I mean, I thought it was about over about four times now.
We're way off.
I don't even remember what -
Well, it's not even midnight and we started at about 10 .30, so.
We only started at 10 .30.
Maybe a little prior.
I'm going to do a little jiggle.
Yeah, we got about 20 minutes.
Oh, 15 minutes.
I think it's a fascinating topic, and it's a topic that in a bar with a big group of people, I wouldn't necessarily discuss.
That's what I wouldn't -
You know, that's why it's kind of fascinating that we're talking about it now, but like -
I feel comfortable talking to you about this.
I wouldn't talk about this.
Yeah, except we're talking to a lot of people about it.
Yeah, but I mean, we're also safely just having this conversation.
You know, the two of us, there can be no confrontation right now.
Sure.
We're just talking.
But yeah, in a bar -
I mean, look, but here's the thing.
I wouldn't have the conversation in a bar, not because I'm afraid to voice my opinion.
It's because it's not worth the person that's going to start yelling at you.
Sure.
I'm just like, I don't -
We're out here to have fun.
I don't feel like hearing this right now.
Yeah.
Here's what I will say in the defense.
Like Justin Bieber, you know, by all accounts, it's kind of a scumbag.
If I heard Justin Bieber raped a woman, I would be like, oh god, fuck him, like immediately.
If I heard that John Candy raped a woman, I would want to do anything in my power to not believe that.
Sure.
And I think that's wrong.
And yet, it's also just kind of a true thing.
Like I look at Mel Gibson and I'm like, he can't be this.
I look at Woody Allen.
I'm like, I hope he's not this because I like their work.
But ultimately, that's not fair to potential victims of -
Of course not.
You're -
You got to say there's a difference.
No matter what terrible things Mel Gibson said, we're not getting 800 women who come forward and say, yeah, he raped me.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
I would agree with that.
Cosby Face and Jill Time.
Facin' Jill Time except he just got Let off in California, apparently.
Yeah, but he's being tried, that big trial that he's going on, that's happening in my hometown.
Oh, is that right that it's happening at the courthouse in my home town
You see him with that sweater hobbling up like he's all old and decrepit or whatever that is a guy who like
You almost want to see people at the court steps like throwing rocks at him
It's just fucking disgusting. It's devastating when when all the stuff came out about Led Zeppelin stealing their songs
Yeah, it was heartbreaking and the example I would always use is I would say my god
I can't even wrap my head around it
It would be like if I heard like that Richard prior stole all his material right and this is essentially now the way way
Way worse version of that right like it's it's it's so devastating to me that a guy
I looked up to that much is this guy like I can't sure believe it and was just held as an example
By my parents and like we have to watch the show every week and like brutal and the fact that he's devoted so much of his life
telling black men
To get their shit together and pull their pants up and stop listening to hip -hop. Yeah, it's you just it makes it it makes you just want to
Just beat the shit out of this guy. Yeah, I know because frankly
If a hundred people say something
It is it is truth and you see this shit
Like I really respect
Obviously outcast one of my favorite musical acts of all time and big boy
I follow him on all the social media. I love what he says all the time and then he randomly posted something like hey
Let's not jump to conclusions on Bill Cosby and it posted some crack pot websites, you know, disproving some woman's
Testimonial or whatever and I was like fuck you big boy
A hundred women aren't lying and it it shouldn't need a hundred women to make something
True and it doesn't I believe the recent
Kel Hartman shit a thousand percent and that's now only two women I
Would believe one woman if they told me I'm just saying a hundred there can't still be people who say that's not true
That can't happen. Yeah, no, I agree. I agree
But I I think it speaks to just how
You what you said earlier how we want to believe certain people it can't be true
It speaks to how devastating it is. Yeah, and I'm not saying so you should be defending him in any way
No, I know that Bill got in my heart. I know Bill Cosby is guilty. Yeah, I don't know for a fact
But I know on my heart
I believe in my heart, I should say but you know, I
It's devastating. This is how devastating it is if you wrote a screenplay
About this not about Bill Cosby. Just a screenplay where this was the story. Yeah
And the big twist at the end was he's been raping all these women. You'd be like this is poorly written
This isn't believable. Yeah, it's it's the most insane reveal I've ever experienced
Ever in my life
Like I can't I there will never be I know I'll never see anything like this ever again
I would think I mean my god. You never you'd just never know with people the coolest thing to me is like thinking back on all those
Tina Fey on SNL and on 30 rock multiple times called him out for being a rapist before anything came out
Never it was like I'll just pretend that didn't happen or like it wouldn't get a laugh
I guess I didn't hear that but it's been kind of legend for a while. I had heard rumblings about it for a while
Well, there was stuff on his you know, there was stuff on his I remember hearing stuff and there was stuff on the Wikipedia page
But then both things said like
They were these accusations and they were settled out of court and whatever
So it was it was just enough that it made you feel okay saying like okay. Maybe he didn't do it then yeah, you know
And then some guy just got sped by the way just to stick with the movie in some capacity scissors through the neck
Again needless 3d shot and it was CGI scissors scissors. I don't necessarily think could go through a neck
I don't know that for sure. That was absurd and this woman would have to have the strength
Mm -hmm of a of bigfoot. Yeah, you know harder would be to shove scissors through the back of somebody's neck and make them pop out the front
I don't but I could guess it would take a lot
And then she just stabbed him to a guy's eye
This is one of those horror movies too because it's in 3d where they're doing like all the Gore effects or CGI
And it's just terrible. Yeah, you know fucking daddy's home had a lot of
comedy
Terrible CGI effects which to me is
Like what more infuriating than horror like wolf arrow gets on
Marky marks motorcycle and then he winds up crashing into the house
It's in the trailer he crashes into the house and the motorcycle flies out the window and it's the worst special effects
I've seen maybe in my entire life and in a comedy. It's like
What is CGI though to me special effects and comedy do not mix unless you're doing like a ghost busters
What is CGI like will Farrow himself or just the motorcycle like when it
The motorcycle crashes he's in a wall and then you see the motorcycle come crashing back out the upper floor window and it looks
like
Basically like they had a sticker of a motorcycle that they moved over the lens
It looks so fake this movie's just really ripping stuff off from a lot of different movies
They ripped off that that omen thing at the beginning. They just did a Freddy versus Jason thing where she cut the nozzle off
One of those like oxygen tanks. Yeah, and it shot
Yeah, this is a pretty shameless film. It's a pretty shameless film
I'm sure there's also a bit of killer nurse and something else too
probably yes
She hasn't orgasm every time she hurts somebody yeah turns around I believe because she saw her dad
murdered in front of her right
Which this also takes a great deal from Dexter
Because she's punishing people Dexter also saw his dad murdered her mom murdered or whatever the hell it was
movie really is just a
Not a good film who directed this thing that I don't know I'm gonna look it up
What if that was the twist that I directed it and I was waiting to hear you give me an honest critique
Did I ever tell you about the time I was talking to a guy about cabin fever?
No, I like cabin food. I said
We were talking about cabins we were working on a acting gig together and we said he brought up cabin fever and I said
Are you gonna be out in LA and he said well probably come out because they're doing it like a cabin fever remake
And I said he said so I want to come out for the premiere of that and I said oh, that's cool and I go
Yeah, I'm not a big cabin fever fan. I started going off on why did it like the movie and what I like about it
And I go you must really love it. I mean you're coming out to see this remake premiere and he goes yeah
Well, I wrote it. Oh
You lie. We're off didn't write cabin fever. This guy wrote it with Eli Roth. Oh, okay
And then I went and bought cabin fever and said I'll give it a second chance. All right, very funny though. I enjoyed Kim
I like when she shaved her skin off. Yeah, I like that part. Was it Shannon Elizabeth in that?
I don't remember
I really don't remember all right hold on here. I'm looking up nurse
The phone's at 20 % I hate when it gets down to 20 %
Is that the killer nurse?
Oh, she's playing fake like she needs help
Believe so and now she's gonna sucker these guys
Now does she make it through this hold on a second. No, they definitely from when I recall leave it open for a sequel
That they may be making for all in
Any movie with violence and gratuitous really good nudity is gonna have a shelf life
It's got a 4 .6 on I had to be it's got a 55 % of rot in tomato is much higher than I would have given it. Yeah
And we're trying to figure out who directed this thing. Oh wait the nurse is a 1997 movie as well
Traumatized nurse plots revenge against a katonic businessman who she blames for the death of her family and this movie is just lift and shit
Jesus God
That's not that different nurse 3d. That's what this one. Yeah
You're paying is her pleasure, right? That's a line almost verbatim out of hell razor. Yeah
What is this part now? She's getting arrested now
She thought she made it out
Another cut Doug Aaronoski that he said a Doug Aaron the
Not a related to Darren Aaronos. No, no, no, it's Doug
Arnie Ocaski. That's how you say that. Okay. He directed this criminal minds and sleepy hollow and arrow. He's done TV all TV
You will yeah Tim Burton sleepy Hall of Fame. Yes, very much so a lot of fucking love that movie
He got to start on the horror feature doctor Mordred
First a D worked on from Dustal dawn
Okay, the faculty
Spy kids
As first a D
First direct to tutorial effort was Highlander end game
Which I believe is the fourth Highlander I own Highlander. I've never seen any of the Highlanders never saw one of them
Never saw one of them. No, never had much of an interest in it for some reason
I don't know why it seems like something to be right my alley. I mean Connery. I'm on board
Conneries in the first two, right? Yeah. Oh, yeah, because I remember the sequel the the commercials for the sequel him going greetings Highlander
Hello Highlander
Who did Connery play like the master or something? I assume he was the Highlander. I don't know
No Lambert's the Highlander
Isn't he like an older Highlander who trains him to be a Highlander? There can only be one
Okay, there can only be one Highlander. So she got the she got the kid the nerdy neighbor kid to help her
Dispose of this body at the end and now it's gonna be like he's her minion because he wants to bang her. I believe so
Something along those lines
Getting back to Jervais
I saw the office very early. I
Had heard a recommend I think Christopher Guest talked about it and something I saw when I was like in high school
And I was like this man is a genius. This is the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life
I watched it constantly
I showed it to everyone I knew right and I was like this this guy is like the coolest
Then at some point I guess it's talking about the atheism and talking about like oh, I don't want to be the bad boy or whatever
He became someone that everyone cool and comedy shits on and hates right
Which I get I don't like somebody who I like like Russell brand who's like I'm a bad boy and has to say it a
Thousand times because then you're not really a bad
However when he's hosting the Golden Globe, which is for a mass audience. Who is that for at this point?
Like middle America middle America doesn't know or care about Rikki Jervais though
He's never been in anything they've seen except like night at the museum. He's apparently that famous I guess
Why don't yeah, I don't really like the the self -aware. I'm a bad boy crap. I think that's stupid
But I don't either and I haven't seen Derek. I like Derek a lot. I'm a fan of his work, you know
If you make the office you get a pass folks and extras is great, too. I prefer to the office
But I see so much hate towards him and I'm like well, who do you guys like them?
Yeah, I mean, I didn't love him at the Golden Globes either and I don't like his whole stick
But like the Golden Globes are not a show meant for entertainers and artists to watch
No, for middle America and that's in middle America. We'll get a kick out of that stuff. And that's it, you know
I don't know am I wrong? No, he just needs to make something else great again
I don't understand that everyone with their arms folded like oh, this piece of shit again the guy was awesome
He was your hero not long ago, right and then if he dies, you'll all suck as dick like you did with Robin Williams when you turned on him
You know
Well all suck is dick
Is this how you saying you want to suck is dick? I
There's no dick. I'd rather suck less than record juvis I'm just saying the guy did the office in extras
Do y 'all have to spit so much bile at this man? I don't I think all you're seeing is some Twitter bio. Yeah, Twitter
That's what the fuck does anybody in Twitter know?
I don't know Joe. I don't know anymore. We're grown men for Christ sakes. It's you know, come on
You ready to close this out patty. Let's close it up. They're recommending that we watch nymphomaniac. That's they say hey you guys are disgusting
perverts
I actually loved both nymphomaniac
I do not feel comfortable watching that with you. No, we're not gonna watch you want to watch a three -hour movie right now
Midnight on a Wednesday you've been listening to we'll see you in hell a presentation of the fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail
An executive produced by Ken Hanley of fangoria entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiries and
Information about we'll see you in hell contact Ken you can email him can at fangoria dot com
We are on Twitter at the Patrick Walsh and Joderosa comedy. We love hearing your guys feedback
Tweet us. There's been a lot of it over the holidays, which was much appreciated and very cool to hear
Yes, and go still doing our best and let's should we announce what the next one will be should we just do the shining?
That's a tall order of that shining man. That's that's two two and a half hours man. We promised people we'd tell them what the next one would be
All right, and we have a month. We're gonna give you guys a real treat. No, don't have a month. We got to do another one
We have two weeks folks. We don't have two weeks
Here's what our next one's gonna be and I guarantee you can watch this because you've already seen it our next one will be the shining a
Two -hour and
22 -minute version of we'll see you in hell
Imagine the things that we'll say and regret on that one because I'm already thinking what did I say about Bill Cosby?
They could be misconstrued but please folks know that we are on the side of good
That is a massive tall order
We're gonna do it next up is the shining if you've never seen it watch the shining the shining next on we'll see you in hell
In the meantime follow us on Twitter and leave some good reviews are the please do yes I tone tunes page to
To fucking combat the
troll cunts that leave one star reviews that take care everybody good night folks