Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help
you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Welcome to we'll see you and how this is your number two episode for this
Monday. This is your bonus app. Let's not even a bonus app. We just didn't do one
last week's we're giving you two today. It's not the best that we've got. It's the opposite
of that. The best that we got would have been an episode on time last Monday. I'm saying
we're doing the best we can with our busy social schedules. Yeah. In the words of Miss Anita
a baker? Uh, I don't know. You know what song I've had in my head, though?
What?
Speaking of R &B. Now I lay me down to sleep. I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid. You don't remember that song? Uh -uh. It was an
R &B song from the early 90s, late 80s. I mean, that was by genre in the late 80s
for sure was R &B and to the rose around that like Joe to see
earlier. Yeah. Yeah. I don't I don't know who sings now I lay me down to sleep.
No, the song's called Don't Be Afraid. I don't know who sings it though. I know
Unbreak my heart. Say you love me again. That was more like grown up R &B though.
Adult content. Talking more like in the club stuff. Sure. You know what I mean? You
spent a lot of time in the late 80s in the club. Oh yeah, I still do. Yeah. I've never left.
Big club kid myself. Yeah. Bumpin and grindin. Yeah. Yeah. Grindin and bumpin. Yeah.
Humpin and dumpin. Okay. That's when you have sex and then take a shit right after.
You know what I mean? It's disgusting. Well, that's how we do it here in the hoghouse.
think you should do it before, ideally. You know, I don't know what is it about good
sex that makes me have to crap. Kingpin, baby. There you go. There's a reason she says it that way
in that order. Yeah. A line probably written by Golden Girls writers, Morton Atheon and Barry
Fanara. Yes. I've been watching a lot of Golden Girls lately. It's a phenomenal show. It is.
to be watched.
I just passed the bird Reynolds episode in season two.
I'm about nine into season two.
Season two is a tour to force.
Yeah, it's great.
Unstoppable.
The great jokes.
I just watched the one where there's the mean old lady
who dies, and that lady kicks her coffin.
They had an amazing joke where she's talking about all the people
who are going to end the bird Reynolds episode, where she's like,
everybody's going to be there.
Dom Deloise.
and then B. Arthur and Rose go oh my god Lonnie Anderson they go oh my god they
go Charles Nelson Riley B. Arthur and B. I. just stare at her stuck Conti Joe you
know it is it's a real hard shot at Charles Nelson Riley who I'm a fan of I
felt bad I always felt bad that he got low he was like the joke guy in that
career he's very funny yeah very funny uh he had a thing that I chose to say the
I see word for the first time in 10 years on the podcast.
Interesting move.
I said it on radio the other day
to a political talk show host.
Okay.
Who was talking down to me so much
and I started getting angry
and he goes, why do you get so bad?
And I go, because you're a fucking cunt.
And he goes, what?
I go, you heard me, you're a cunt.
And he goes, what's that mean?
I go, you know what the fuck it means.
I walked off the show.
What was the show called?
on. Uh stand up with Pete Dominick on serious XM. I wish I
wish I could hear this. You can. Sounds like good radio was
replayed on other radio shows at serious XM almost
immediately. All right. Uh, you can easily look this up. I'll
check it out. Yeah. You were just called on to talk about the
news of the day. He's a guy I know that he used to do comedy
and we we were, uh, you know, we've just known him forever. And
He's got this political show now.
And the last time I went on, he did this to me,
completely like talk down to me
and like try to kind of throw me under the bus
in front of his audience.
And then he did it again this time.
Yeah.
I hadn't gone on three years.
I gave him another shot and he did it again.
And I lost my fucking shit.
But I mean, lost my shit after 32 minutes
of him telling me every single thing I said
was incorrect or wrong or that I was a sad human being
which he said at one point.
I mean, oh, you know, it's just sad to think the way you do.
I don't like to think that it was all very passive -aggressive
and yeah.
And finally, I just got fucking, you know, 32 minutes
and he's like, why do you get so mad?
I was just like, you know what, dude, go fuck yourself.
I'm not playing this game.
I don't fucking care what you think about me,
or if I ever do this show again, you're a fucking asshole
And I'm telling you in front of your fucking audience right now, but boy, the sparks fly when the
Holy cow. Yeah, when you should have heard what was being said off air about you
About both to each to each other
Oh
You guys taught you didn't you left, but you didn't leave the building. He went no
He went to break and I was like fuck you. I'm out of here
And I went to leave and he was we were screaming at each other. It was crazy
It was pretty awesome. It was invigorating. Yeah. I had a good time. All right. I enjoyed
it. I'm sure they love it when that stuff happens. That's radio, baby. Yeah. The old days,
like Stern used to do it. Yeah. I like to pay older days. When you pay them off to play
a song. I don't think those days ever left. No, I don't think they did either. Folks are
show today by popular demand is a commentary of a Halloween episode of
something. We of course chose perfect strangers because there is another
Halloween episode that we did not do yet called aliens and we'll be doing a
commentary on that shortly. If you want to go to your your Hulu page or whatever
what have you it's episode called alien season four episode three. Yes. Perfect
The perfect strangers is streaming on Hulu.
I believe that's the only place it's streaming for free.
This is sort of a mashup week between,
we'll see you in hell in our side podcast, PS, I love you.
Yes, a minute by minute dissection of perfect strangers.
now do you have any movie corner I could probably dust something off I did
watch major league which I had not seen since I was a boy and I cried I thought
it was fucking fantastic. That cast, I was like, this movie ain't gonna hold up. It was just fantastic.
Yeah, it's a great flick. Moving in a weird way, story of friendship,
yuker, still hilarious. Still very hilarious. It's a great movie.
Who plays the voodoo guy again? Dennis Hayesberg. It was now the voice of insurance.
Yeah, it is Dennis. That's what I thought. I couldn't remember.
It's a great movie and the kind of ingeniously plotted really it's by the guy who did the sting and all the twists and turns kind of brought it from the producers where they got to finish last they got to lose the season and they wind up triumphant but great movie.
I saw a fun little horror movie called Southbound. I believe I watched it on Amazon Prime.
fun, little anthology film. Dana Gould is in one of the stories, funny comedian.
Okay. Love Dana Gould. Yeah, it was fun seeing him in there. One of the executive producers
or producers on the movie was Brad Misca, who's the founder of Bloody Disgusting .com, which
is a great site to find all your horror news and stuff. And it was fun. It was five sort
of interweaving tales that were all sort of dark and interesting, well they were all dark
and interesting, but they didn't really spell out everything for you. It had a sort
of mysterious quality to it and it was an enjoyable flick. I recommend it. I think you
should go see it or stream it. And where does it air?
Well, I saw it on Amazon Prime, as I said, just a second ago.
I already said it.
Well, you know, you could listen for once.
What?
I saw...
What did I watch?
Anything?
I can carry us through this if you want, because I got a few.
Yeah, go ahead, but I know I watched something.
chap aquatic. How was chap aquatic? It's exactly how you think it was. It was amazing performances
by the actors and in the most boring movie you've ever seen. That looks very boring.
Christ it was boring and I got to tell you people the level, the level of conspiracy in the
Uh, uh, an accidental death that was his fault.
Right.
I can't believe anybody has faith in anything government related.
No.
It's insane.
Well, they don't anymore.
I don't think.
It's so insane.
Like, it's like, so that part of it, I guess, was interesting.
But, uh, you know, it's Ted Kennedy.
And he's a fucking, they really toned down the drunk part of him.
Like who plays Ted Kennedy your boy
From
From what's it called?
Horror house. What was that fucking with Winchester? Oh
Okay, I forget his neck guy. Yeah, I also saw another movie he was in called all I see is you
Which was him and
What's her name? Wow, this is this is getting dark over there
It's like when you realize grandpa's starting to slip a little bit.
No, what's her face?
It's married to Ryan Reynolds.
There was in the shark movie.
Jessica Biel.
No, no, no, no, no.
She's married to Jason.
Oh, sorry.
Blake Lively.
And that's a movie where she played a blind woman who is married to Jason Clark.
Yeah.
Jason Clark.
Boom.
Yeah.
and she suddenly is gifted sight by a doctor
and it's about how that sort of,
her suddenly not, her suddenly having independence
from him is what destroys their marriage.
I gotta tell you folks, I was about 40 minutes
into this thing, I was jealous of the blind character.
Not a bad movie, again, great performances
by both of them, but it's just a, it's just a who gives a shit. Isn't Bo Bridges in there
probably with a glass of brandy or something? No. Okay. I thought I remember seeing him in the trailer.
And this thing is listed on the, it was listed on the airplane under thrillers. And it's not. It's
just a drama about a woman who can't see and then she gets sight and it, that creates problems in
the marriage, you moved off
chap aquatic. Yeah. No,
this is not. This is called
all I see is you was bow
bridges in chap and
chap aquatic. If he was,
I missed it. I don't know.
Okay. You know who's actually
very good at chap aquatic is
Ed Helms, who plays a very
dramatic role and he's
fucking great at it.
And I'm like, wow, it gave
me. I like Ed Helms, but
it gave me a new respect
for him. All right. I
He's like one of the handlers, he's not one of the Kennedy's, he's great in it and in a very, I've seen Jim do dramatic stuff before, but this was certainly the one of the heavier things I've seen him do.
You saw him do sort of a Shakespeare in the park production version of hot pockets.
Yeah. Well, you're getting mixed up. I would give him hot pockets to come to my apartment and do Shakespeare for me.
Okay, guys, those are two allegedly I saw
30 minutes or less which I had seen in the theaters and remembered really enjoying
Thing with Kristen Stewart no that's
No, well there's adventure land which came out on the same time with Eisenberg and Stewart
Yeah, this is the one where Eisenberg's like the convenience store guy, right?
This is the one where he's like a podhead. It's got a Zanzari Nick Swarsden and Danny McBride
Oh no, it's from the Ruben Fliesher who's in a quaint some mind of directed zombie land. Now at what point does
Aziz
Cesar his fingers into Danny McBride's mouth in the film. I didn't do it. Okay. He didn't know
Why did you tell Aziz ends our identity?
By the way, I
It was I said for that. I said I told him to have scissors sex. I didn't tell him to Cesar a woman's mouth. It was interesting
how
How much comedy has changed even in that five years since this movie came out, like there
are jokes, racist jokes, homophobic jokes, and it's not that long ago that just would
not fly today.
That said, I remember finding it really funny when I first saw it in theaters this time.
It's a pleasant enough diversion, it's an entertaining comedy.
But what's interesting about it is that it was the basis for that Netflix documentary,
the 4 -part one where that woman, you know, the guy blows himself up delivering pizza.
Did you watch this one? Is it another one of these dew -plast ventures?
Yeah, it is actually. Yeah, no. It's a really good 4 -part documentary. I loved it.
I'm giving you the name now, but it's similar to like a making a murder or two.
They've got their names on so much stuff. I don't, I can't write, I can't,
what's what anymore? It's evil genius. It did look good. I just didn't watch it.
Evil genius. That's that'll close my movie corner. I loved evil genius at super entertaining
But it's about these like psycho pass. The woman is a complete sociobipolar and all the interviews with her are fascinating
She's like sweet and then she'll start screaming at the camera
But they basically use this pizza guy as a pawn
He's got a bomb strap to him and that news story became the basis for this like ridiculous stoner comedy
But the true story is actually very dark and serious
Yeah, that's like that guy that was kidnapped the pain and gain or whatever that movie was right. The guy that was actually kidnapped. He's like, this isn't funny. Yeah, yeah, it's a little fun.
I was tortured pain again. I like that movie. That's a good movie. I like the two. I'm just saying the guy was upset
Anyway, let's get to our commentary
Because we got 24 hard minutes of perfect strangers here to get through great
This is season four so they should still be keeping things pretty tight
All right, we saw where they were flying was in like episode 10. Yeah
We're gonna do a one two three play one two three play
Hey, so you should have the opening credits.
Nothing's gonna stop me now.
Now.
Now, Pat and I put the subtitles on to help, so we don't miss a needle dialogue.
I've never seen that before, at the opening, it said, David Perans performing, nothing
is going to stop me now.
I don't remember that saying that on the last one.
No, it didn't.
I don't know who the fuck David Perans is.
I'll stand in my way, this flame in my heart like a long -lost friend
gives every night straight a light at the end.
Standing tall on the wings of my dreams,
her eyes and fall on the wings of my dreams.
The rain and thunder, the wind and haze,
I'm bound for better days, it's my life, my dream, and nothing's gonna stop me now.
Chicago, baby.
I'm going to see the odd couple, and they are, in a way, an odd couple, too.
I'll tell you that, especially that balky.
He's off the wall.
They talk about odd.
So the plot of this one, if I remember correctly, because I have seen it, and we've actually discussed this episode briefly, but this episode is the one where Larry is all excited for Halloween.
And he makes bulky and the girls watch a horror movie marathon, and none of them want to watch it because they're too scared.
Right, and he kind of caused them all chickens and then he ends up watching all of it by himself and then
Get the horror things start happening in his life. Okay. I think aliens abduct Balky or Balky is an alien or
It kind of
It kind of goes from there. I was found this woman very likable. I like her too. What happened to one of your mom's friends or something?
I assume she passed I mean she passed 30 years old. Oh, all right 30 looks different in those days. Yeah, that's an old lady hair cut
She's not 30 here. The boss lady went on to become the wife on family matters. Am I right?
Correct. But did you know that it was a spin -off? That that elevator operator character became Harriet Winslow. They thought she needed her own show
Which I don't understand like the boss of this paper, isn't she?
That's is that her isn't that her? Yeah, she's not the elevator operator. Okay. She just came off the elevator
But it is a spinoff where she's like works this
Paper and then it's also the mom and family matters correct. Is it a true spinoff?
Pat, you're the one that told me it was a spinoff. I don't fucking idea this mask is way too disturbing for us
I mean, that's a terrifying. Oh, it's Balkey.
For those of you not watching along the office, the old paper that they work at.
I can't remember what the paper's called, but it's all chronicle Chicago Chronicle.
It's all decked out in Halloween scramers and stuff because you know how you know how
your office decorates go, you know, like it is during Halloween.
Sure. But anyway, they're all decked out for Halloween in the office there.
Well, well, well. Before Family Matters, Harriet Winslow was originally the elevator operator at the Chicago Chronicle newspaper office in the third and fourth seasons of perfect stranger.
She's the elevator operator.
In the second episode of Family Matters, Harriet was fired as elevator operator. Yes.
Why is she coming in with papers all the time and shit then?
I don't know if that was her, Joe. That's what I'm trying to say. I think you might be mixing them up.
the two women? No, that's her. That's the family matters later. Then why is the elevator
operator wearing a dress? And I remember her being in like a uniform on the show. Hold
on a second. I'm gonna look this up. I just read it to you right off of Wikipedia. Where
was your name? Harriet Winslow? Harriet Winslow. What is Balky a bird? That's a good comedy
costume on Belky. Good choice. Yeah, perfect strangers. Here she is. Mom from family
matters. And no one's disputing that, Joe. This isn't the issue we're contending about.
I'm lost. I don't know. Anyway, what I can't find any pictures from family matters for
some reason. Have you seen the key and peel sketch where he plays Carl Winslow? No. We need
to watch it after this. It's the funniest sketch they ever did. What is the plot of it? I don't
even want to spoil it for you, but basically he goes in and he's pissed because he's like, this was
supposed to be a family sitcom with me as the dad. No, Steve Irkish. I have seen that when and then
the evil earnings comes in. Yes. Yeah, that's her. That's Harriet Winslow. All right. But what the hell
That's one hell of an elevator operator coming in with documents shit. She did appear to be kind of running the show. Yeah, I up until you said she was I thought she was the boss of the paper this whole time right.
Anyway, Balky is now dressed up like a red chicken.
I mean, you know, I don't know why, but he is, I missed it because of our argument about
the elevator.
Now, have we ever discussed, they're fucking these women or they're not?
Of course they're fucking them, they marry them, all right, eventually.
But I mean, do they fuck pre -marriage?
I believe Balky does.
That's kind of like a running gag on the show is like Balky's girlfriend is always like,
like a little balky and like she gets super turned on by him and like takes out in front
of Larry. And then Larry's always like, you know, he can never get a moment alone with
Jennifer. That's the gag. Right. And in fact, after he proposes to her, there's the episode
where he loot the ring is she takes the fake ring by accident. And he's got to swap it for
the real ring. And he sneaks into her bedroom to do it while she's asleep. And he says
is I've always dreamed of being in Jennifer's bedroom,
but this wasn't exactly what I pictured.
So I mean, that's a pretty sad state.
This guy's, this guy's putting a ring on it.
They haven't even buffed yet.
Yeah.
I would guess, unless they're weirdos
and they fucking the street, like buffed.
By buffed, of course, you mean farted, right?
Yes.
Right.
That was, that was part of the cabinet here.
Boothed. They go, what do you mean by boofed? He was flatulence. I was 14.
And an answer for everything. What is this world coming to? What is happening?
Now, were you a TGIF washer? I definitely went a whole decade with all the permeations of
our permutations of DGIF.
Yeah, there was a time in my life where somehow
four sitcoms on a Friday night was enough to satisfy
whatever I wanted out of this world.
But I used to have the best time watching TGIF.
Like I didn't want anything else in the world.
I would have my one soda.
I was allowed per week, a bowl of popcorn
and watch four of the stupidest shows ever made.
I was not, I liked TGIF
But I wasn't as into TGIF as I was into the my big ones were the Thursday must see TV NBC of course, you know friends and Seinfeld
I go no, I'm talking older than that. I'm talking when it was like cheers. Oh, yeah Cosby nightcourt sure and
Seinfeld was a dear John. Yeah, dear John
Yeah, yeah, and I was also a big fan of the Saturday night run because that's when the golden girls were on
old girls empty nest nurses and some other show that would
be all in the same universe. Right. Right.
Like I was like marvel before marvel. Yeah. Back then.
Yeah, they were pitching us on the show on a on a crossover
with lost man last man standing. I was like, well, no, but
also their show takes place in Colorado were in Tucson. And
the characters don't know each other. I was like, this isn't
the eighties anymore. People are a little savvy to be like,
like, hey, I'm just coming to take a tour of your old folks.
Sure, sure.
It's me, Tim Allen.
I have to say, I thought the opening scene
of last man standing was really funny.
Oh, I didn't say it.
It was, you know, they did what you probably expect
that they would do.
It opens on the kid with the mom.
He's like, and he's flipping through the channels.
He's like, what the hell, my favorite TV show is it on?
And she's like, well, maybe it's on another channel.
And he's like, mom, you don't take a successful TV show and just put it on another channel.
Why would they do that?
And then Tim Allen walks in and he goes, because maybe they're idiots.
And I was like, that's, that's pretty funny.
Always good to start a sitcom on the premise that the sitcom does not exist in the real world.
The, I liked when they did it with Futurama where it was like, never saw that show, never
once.
they did the before they brought the show back they did they did like the movies on Comedy Central
or whatever a future out and the first one back was there were a lot of jokes about how it got
canceled for no reason right and uh you know network executives all you know all that shit
yeah sure it's always funny when the network suits get made fun of I think I agree now do you think
there were a lot of battles on perfect strangers you know do you think they had stories like oh
and we fought for that story line because that was about the characters. I always got the feeling
that these T .J .F. shows worked almost like Tyler Perry's thing where they do like, they write
100 in a week. Right. You know, especially by the end, I feel like there were just guys who went
from show to show and Balke enters, I don't know, hey cousin, all right good, that's good enough.
You know, they just kind of they all ease into sort of a very predictable laziness by the end and they had a I bet you they had terms for everything.
Oh sure.
What's our bulky bang in this episode?
Yeah.
Gotta have that bulky bang.
I know there was a lot of cocaine flowing through the 80s sitcoms and also into the 90s sitcoms.
I've worked with some riders who talk about a big pile of blow in the middle of the will and grace table.
yeah I mean this goddamn business let it happen I agree let let let put the
blow on the table you're making everybody stay till fucking 8 a .m. I agree from
the from the day before it's like let everybody get fucked up and write the show
I think some shows will have drinks and stuff I you know I always worry about the
productivity slipping but have I had a drink to get through a tough day at work
you bet your ass. Good for you. Now look at how decked out Larry's apartment was for Halloween.
Did you see that? That's a little way. I did. That he had decorated that place. I mean,
it's a sitcom. You got to make people feel at home. Yeah, I know. I'm just saying, you know, if
if you had a friend that decorated like that for Halloween, you would think he was a fucking
psychopath. Yes. Did you watch? She's not an elevator again. This woman does everything except
to operate the goddamn elevator.
Maybe she's in charge of elevator management or something.
She's Becky Thisson -Crupp.
I mean, look, she's asking to smell his breath
if he's been drinking.
Yeah.
She seems to hold a lot of clout.
And she seems to have no problem wearing that vest,
which is a real power move.
Yeah.
I can also picture Carl Winslow himself in that vest.
I'd like to see it.
I can also picture Erkel in it.
That was the good thing about Family Matters is an interchangeable wardrobe amongst the cast you know
You'd have to let out an Erkel for a carl to get into it, but yeah, but that was a trick
They did in TV back then. Yeah, they'd say we need we need a cast make the characters that they could all wear the same things
We don't spend a lot of wardrobe
Did you watch just the ten of us? Yes, you used to love just the ten of us. I loved it too
Bill smithrovich could have could have been a TV star in those days
That's how that's how lacks things work. I'm a sucker for a bald fat guy. Sure. He was the John
candy of sitcoms in my opinion. True. Did you watch a step -by -step, which I don't think I missed
an episode of? I like step -by -step and never in my life. Whoops. So these two women just walk through
the wall. Larry's subtle reaction from Larry. He's going crazy because he watched too many horror movies.
seeing things. Never in my life. Big eyebrow actor, Marklin Baker. Yes, look at him. It's all
in the eyes. Yeah. Did I want to have sex more with someone than Suzanne Summers in the
step -by -step years? Sure. Didn't care at all three company years. That's those step -by -step
years where she was like in her 40s and just rocking it. Yeah. Good. Lord Almighty. Balky
he just floated down from the ceiling.
Then you saw him sort of detached from the strings.
Yeah, and then Marklin Baker made his eyes
even bigger somehow.
Balky's working his brows too, though.
Balky's in a vest too.
Almost exactly like Mrs. Williams flows vest.
Balky keeps floating up and down.
I mean, it's, you know, so at this point in the show,
you're saying what is this all in Larry's head? Right. What do you think the explanation
is? Is it like that the worst cause be show episode ever where he eats the bad sandwich
and then has horrible nightmares all night about sandwiches? I never see that one. It's
like a season one. It's the worst that come episode maybe of all time. I would argue that.
Okay, I don't think that that's possible when you've got
There's a lot out there. Yeah, all right. There's a lot out there
You know Joe if you ever worn a vest at any point in your life
Yes, I sat at like a wedding
No, no like like socially no, yeah, I have a
School picture of myself maybe third grade wearing like a gray button up vest and a white shirt
Doesn't look bad. I look pretty cute
In fourth grade. Yeah, well, yeah, I mean a little child wearing it is fine. Right grown man with a
Adult vest. I don't think I pulled that off outside of like the marty McFly like
Lifejacket style this scene is at three vests both women and balky are have all been wearing a bit of vest and they're all very loud vests, right
Balky is pursuing Larry to take him to his home planet of
Mepos Mepos is not a country it turns out. It's actually another planet
That let look at those eyes. Yeah, on that. Larry
Just was really for kids. I mean, that's why I was asking about the fucking. I feel like kids enjoyed it more than adults
I mean they had a bachelor party episode of you know where there was a stripper and stuff. What would she wear full full front?
It was full frontal noodle. Yeah, there was the there was the full frontal scene that Mark Lynn Baker did
right around the time that the piano came out.
Okay, so he kind of advances on the stripper.
Yeah, yeah, no, but I don't think it was for kids.
I think it was just like, this is how sterile network TV
was then.
I think about how sterile it is now, you know.
Yeah.
You look at a show on ABC or something.
Like, if I watched, I'm not shitting on the show.
I'm just saying like, if I didn't know any better
and I watched the Goldbergs,
I would think that was like a Nickelodeon show for kids.
Yeah, that's true.
You know, that's true.
Speaking of which, horror fans,
Freddie Kruger making an appearance
for the Halloween episode of the Goldbergs.
Robert England.
Yeah, he's doing Freddie again on the Goldbergs
because apparently I guess they've done a lot of episodes
where they do homages to movies
that were famous in the 80s
so they're doing a Halloween one with he's coming in as Kruger.
But doesn't England like not play him in the movies
even anymore?
Well, they only made one movie without him was the remake, but he did say was he was done playing Freddie, but obviously
When the Goldbergs calls
He'll change his tune. Yeah, the
Balky's flying up in the air
Like a like a man witch
Not the sloppy Joe no
But in a very witchy kind of spooky way and he's he's saying I guess he's cackling that he's gonna take
because in Larry to plan it in Mepos, right?
They just showed the exterior of their apartment building.
It always made me want to live in Chicago.
I would have loved to live in Chicago and almost did.
I was debating between Second City and Chicago as a performer
or New York and being an NBC page.
That's what I chose.
I'm glad I did.
But a dream of mine would be to live in Chicago for a bit.
It's like New York without the shit,
the constant onslaught of shit.
Yeah, but also the worst winner of all time, but I love winter. It's what I want more of I want more of it too
I don't know that I want a Chicago winner. It's fucking cold, dude
All right, have you been to one I have I used to go there for concerts all the time
I saw the breeders there once tiny theater called the Metro great town
Let's talk about how out of
both of their leagues
their girlfriends are. Yeah. It is outrageous. Well, that's a sitcom staple. Yeah. I mean,
it's not even close in this fucking thing. No. The, uh, um, what's it called? Um, for
Christ's sake, what was it going to say? The, uh, oh, Chicago, no, uh, front, you're wearing
a vest. Oh, the vest is the bit. Everyone who has a vest is an alien in Larry's mind. Oh,
That wasn't intentional. It's a vest based episode. Okay.
Doc, he's still flying. We really missed that whole point.
Chicago. My friend was telling me that lives in Chicago. She was saying that she was like,
yeah, when the winter comes, we just stay in and drink. Yeah. Like, because it's so cold. I mean,
it's, it's like dangerous cold outside. Right. I like that. Uh, that's, that's a little too much for me.
I like not having to leave my house
That's a little too much for me
I think, you know, I don't need to fucking I don't I don't need to lose a finger. Sure. Sure. You know what I mean? I do
How cold would it get in St. Louis?
St. Louis it gets just as cold. I mean it's
Chicago's probably a little worse because there's water there, but St. Louis would get down to the zero area from time to time
Yeah, he had some birthdays canceled due to
Roads and temps. Yeah, that would
That I think that would kind of you know
Be sort of like those this bad as it would get in Pennsylvania
Yeah, I mean sometimes in the low
Single digits, but you know it never got below zero
Larry was dreaming the whole time ladies and gentlemen
What's your favorite costume you wore as a child Freddie Krueger? Okay
which is crazy that as children, we dressed up as a child murderer and it was fine.
You have knives in your hands? Yeah, my dad made me a glove. I mean, he made it out of,
he made it out of like... Chopsticks, dull metal. It wasn't like it couldn't, it couldn't hurt anybody, but
and then I got the costume glove like that they released that actually was plastic blades,
but it looked like the real glove. Yeah, it was pretty fucking cool.
All I remember was, I was Orco once and I don't even recall enjoying He -Man.
I don't even remember ever watching He -Man, but I was Orco, the little sprite.
And beyond that, I don't remember any of my costumes, really.
What made you choose Orco over He -Man, for instance, or one of the good characters from the
show?
Probably if I did watch it, the only character I related to was Orco, the little floating
dork. You also felt like a faceless underappreciated person with that a lot of
magic to give the world. Yeah. Plus, hey man, what am I going to go to school without a shirt?
No thanks. Here's what I don't give you. We had different body types,
me and Mr. Mann. My phone is buzzing here with news updates. You saw the Kanye
I did the Trump speech on SNL.
I was watching it, yeah.
And also the worst musical performance I've ever seen
in my life, dressed as a bottle of water.
Yeah.
So the next time...
Also, could we get Pete Davidson
into a few more sketches over there?
Cause he's a very diverse performer.
He really lands a lot of different styles of comedy.
Pete's my friend, is he finally in a lot of sketches?
He's in every sketch, yes,
because he's fucking Ariana Grande.
The Pete's my buddy,
So I'm happy that he's getting some face time, but it's it's but this is about Pete
Man, the man is not a sketch performer. This news thing is about Pete
All right, so Kanye leaves he tweets out
Lauren had a great time at SNL Lauren said I can come back and host by the end of the year right of the year
Then the next episode Pete goes on and says
About Kanye was being mentally ill is not an excuse tack like a jackass sure who's on who's telling the truth who's on whose side
I mean, that's all I want, that's all I want to know.
So learn, you know what I mean?
Learn goes, hey, we'll have you back.
And then he's also like, yeah, now go call him a jackass on air.
Or learn didn't say that in Kanye's nuts and lying.
Or...
Kanye is nuts.
I don't know if he's lying.
Lauren, I think, just loves anything that creates ratings,
even if it's bringing President Trump on.
Well, after the point, he was an established monster
right uh... and and watering him down from mass audience
perhaps destroying little you know at least laying the the bricks that would
soon uh... crumble democracy around us
right uh...
i think one of the ship bag
but i think he's a ship back to
i mean just the epitome of that kind of rich white
he sucks the episode just ended by the way is pat was ranting about our crumbling
democracy
We missed the completely missed the end of the episode.
Um, well, I think he's not an alien.
Larry would dream.
It's okay.
Belki's not an alien, guys.
Calm down.
Um, interestingly enough, even though we weren't watching very carefully that the subtext
of that perfect strangers was it was about our crumbling democracy. That's why I started talking
about this. Well, and it was a play on and I've never seen this. Yeah. It was a play on the idea
that a foreign person coming to our country is referred to as an alien. Actually might have been
an alien from outer space. Right. Right. I've never seen that joke done before. Nor have I.
I'd like to see it more. Yeah. It's good. It's about as fresh as he's standing right behind me, isn't he?
It makes me laugh every time he's a prick. He's a son of a bitch. He's standing right behind me, isn't he?
It's always funny. It is kind of always funny. It's always funny. That's always funny. The, you know, we've discussed this the guy. Take care, baby
We love you. Hangs up the phone. Schmuck. Yeah, that's always funny. Yeah, every fucking time. I like nope. I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it
There's no way I'm doing it hard cut to him on the camping trip. Yeah, and I guess I did it. Yeah, that
Also the version of I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it. It pays $200 ,000. Well, wait a minute. Yeah, where do I sign?
Yep
I'm not saying I'm above doing that joke. That's always a chestnut. Yeah. No, I yeah look it goes against everything
I believe morally I think it's wrong. It's disgusting. It pays 500 grand. Where do I sign?
And I'll tell you this, I'll tell you this, I'm still a sucker for, you do the impressions
of the people working, celebrities working normal jobs, yeah, give me a 7 -11 run by
Nicholson Cosby and Jane Fonda, I'm in, I want to hear this bit, wait, that's not a sitcom
bit.
No, I'm saying a bit, like a bit that's always funny to me is when somebody does an impression
they go, you know what I'm saying.
If I think it might sound a little something like this, yeah, I'll laugh at it every time sure of course give a shit
We're simple men who we're simple
Never did it all with the Joe. Well do it now because it's the end of the show
Well gang
I guess it's about time to get done with the show and at the same time done
with the Jonah of a lonely heart. Wow. Jonah of a lonely heart much better than the very good
in the clutch. Very good. We had yes tickets didn't go. Yeah. Yes it would have been dark. Let's
be real. It's hit or miss man. If it's the 50th anniversary tour there's 75 years old. Yeah
and it's hit or miss and as I said I have seen them on like DVD concerts I've
watched and stuff pull out a fucking acoustic folky version of Roundabout
that never kicks in yeah and I'm like if I sit through the whole fucking
concert and they do that I'm gonna be furious sure so anyway folks we'll see
you soon live October 20th at Oma ribs and if we don't see you there we'll see
you. Well, you'll hear us again. We won't see you at all, or hopefully we'll see you
someplace else. Joe DeRose a comedy on Instagram. And I'll be in Philadelphia headlining the
punchline Thanksgiving weekend. I am the Patrick Walsh at Instagram and Twitter. My show
The Cool Kids airs Friday night. And also on Hulu where they have the first two episodes
So it's up, live short, October 20th, I think that's all we got.
Gang, we'll see you next time, and we'll see you in hell.
I'll see you in the next video.