I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to Will see you in hell.
So it's a podcast you tune into sometimes when you want to hear about movie discussions
and movie news and movie reviews and once in a while a nice commentary.
My name is Joe D 'Arosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh and on this week's show we're discussing Tom and Jerry.
I really I don't even know how this started that this is something we'd even discuss reviewing
we're grown men but I'm sitting up last night late watching this thing and I was like maybe
this is the end of the podcast maybe that's it don't say that we're going to get messages
from people not in tears you know now we had to stop or you know we had to delay the
start for a second while my cat scratched her scratch box whoa whoa keep it clean you can
hear it there again cats do this to relieve anxiety whereas Joe and I might take a drink
you know but my question is the song cat scratch fever by Ted Nugent the Nugent actually the
only Ted Nugent song I've ever heard what does that mean what it what is when Nugent
sings cat scratch fever what is he referring to like a STD no I always thought it just
meant he was like horny like he's got the fever he's got to scratch the itch that's what
I thought it meant but I never believe it or not I've never scrutinized the lyrics I did
attend a symposium once that broke down that song in great detail but I felt asleep all
right yeah I don't know I think I think I think it just I think all of his songs are just
I'm horny yeah doesn't it one that's like she's slippery and 16 or something like that like well he
fully dated like a 14 year old girl I think his bride was underage when he got married Jesus yeah
different time different time different side of the tracks I feel like Nugent was a guy who a big part
of his life was needed to get across state lines yeah yeah so you said before we started well you
were talking about drinking you said yeah I said you look like you lost a little weight you said you
haven't had a drink yeah you know it's it sucks it sucks that you do lose weight when you stop
drinking like it would be nice to just have no nice effects I don't miss drinking part of that's
because I've been keeping up with the weed the way some do with the Kardashians or the Joneses or
the Joneses or the Steins if you remember that Jeremy Piffin movie about bar mitzvah planners I
didn't see is that what it's called keeping up with the Steins it sounds right yeah you're
mad you're thinking about him doing stand -up aren't you Joe you're mad I'm just thinking about him is
as an existence sure sure but yeah imagine the women he's groped that's how they think
boy yeah yeah so I I have lost a couple we also hear it at Walsh Manor got a peloton I got it for
the wife's birth or sorry the wife's Christmas and of course I use it as well we just started but
it's it's as great as you hear it's it's the class setting without the annoyances and the pink
eye of going to an actual one of these classes but I've done too so far we got it set up a couple
days ago so you hit play the first was a very sort of gruff woman doing a new wave class I like new wave
music I mean she's in there it was me and a lot of seemingly divorced women are these real
people in the class with you yeah I mean sometimes if you select like I want to do 45 minutes and you
pick your music then it gives you a bunch of options sometimes you do a live class with other people
sometimes you're watching a video of a live class but the woman yesterday was very into eye contact
and like and spurring you on by looking you in the eyes and I don't like that I see I think people
are going to start falling in love with these instructors like a sex dial type thing they wear sports
bras and how it started to talk about this every morning how you like can't do peloton because he
wants to go jack off and etc I'm not there but it's it's a great workout that it's the kind of workout
where when I was walking to like go take a shower afterwards my legs were wobbly okay
you know like when you get blown out by a hot babe yeah I you know I have I've thought of the
peloton if I live in New York though there's just no room for there's just no room for a peloton if
I didn't own a full -size Star Wars arcade cabinet I might be able to fit one in here but you got
it you got to prioritize you got to prioritize it is surprisingly compact but um I'm a fan and I
feel like in the long run you save money if you're somebody who likes going to exercise classes
definitely how big yeah what do we get again I'm really good to start asking you about details of
the peloton I love how when Howard Stern talks about the peloton he makes a million dollars
a morning and I'm just doing it yeah out of the kindness of my heart is it a pricey device
um you know it's roughly the same price as any of these if you were to buy an elliptical or something
but yeah you you pay for a monthly fee for these classes and see that's where they get you so
if Heather wanted to go do these spin classes you know you're talking about you know a month's
worth would be something like three hundred four hundred dollars this is forty dollars for a month
of classes but it's like everything now you're paying everything is subscription you own nothing yeah
yeah not to you I guess what am I talking about you don't own a spin class when you go to it
that doesn't make any sense no but but but there was a time where they'd say you buy this thing and
you get access to the thing and then and you're done yeah you know what I mean there wasn't this
constant paying right you know so I I hear you I'm gonna get I'm gonna get my workout in the old
fashion way uh pat I'm gonna get an old gray sweatsuit and I'm gonna jog with some some springs that I
stretch then you do the the big sort of rubber band around your midsection and then shake it right
yeah you hit a button works wonders yeah I'll tell you though the whole thing is I've been not drinking
and I've been uh uh on a diet I'm desperately waiting for the comment compliment to be returned to me
that I also look like I lost some weight I'm sorry I you look like you lost some weight
thank you it's like pulling teeth well how how much does that mean if somebody says it and you just say
it back like a robot that means nothing I want you to know that meant nothing just then but
uh but I but the only reason I bring that up is because I noticed I'm at an angle right now with my
computer well not flattering passable and I could live with it if it went out on the internet like
this right this angle two weeks ago I would have blown my brains out so that's how you know you're
making progress I mean that that's why it didn't occur to me to say anything Joe you literally have
the camera pointing up underneath your chin like in a horror film it's it's nobody's best look now but
considering not too shabby yeah what I'm getting at uh and I plan on making it better and better and
better how long are you improving do you have an end date or indefinitely I drank one time in the
last month I had one night where I drank well now it's more than a month now I'm at a month in a week
or whatever but but I drank one time in that entire stretch you have one of those number of things
in your apartment with like 67 days since an incident kind of thing what I do is I've a man come over
every morning and tattoo a line on my okay great inner thigh so we're we're at about 30 the money
or the money you're paying the tattoo guy could go to the pellet time that seems like a better use
you sure I looked at it as the money I'm saving on drinking goes to the tattoo guy but you know
whatever sometimes you gotta pay Peter to pay Paul you know what I mean mm -hmm Rob Peter to pay
but what's the expression who cares you got a Rob Peter to pay Paul is that just guys names or
that's supposed to be like disciples is it Bible shit I think so you know it's kind of like Peter
Paul and Mary there you I think it's biblical but I'm not sure you got a shove Mary to please Paul yeah
Paul I mean Peter Paul and Mary shit I can't think of a band I've had less interest in ever exploring in
my entire life the magic dragon god I feel like they were the only version of puff the magic dragon
where none of them were thinking about drugs they were just truly thinking about how wonderful a dragon
would be to be friends with is that a metaphor for marijuana puff long rumored to be yes I think
Paul Peter Paul and Mary drained it from that but but yeah I think it's like H &R puff and stuff
everything involved puffing and they all thought they were so clever I mean Jesus Christ dude yeah
I don't put I don't put the doors that far above this level of like drug discussion you know
you can totally imagine Jim Morrison being like I'm dancing with puff I hear you I like the doors
they've got their flaws but yeah I understand where you're coming from with that you know but uh
I mean on the storm if you listen to any robbery Krieger not Robbie Krieger sorry any who's the
keyboard player Rayman Zarek Rayman Zarek also X which is a truly excellent band but any interview with
Rayman Zarek will take you off the doors in five minutes I mean it'll make it throw your albums in a
fireplace yeah it's like hey we were out there man like it's so it's so awful yeah um what Jim
was doing I mean you know we were in awe nobody was doing what Jim was doing at that time
reciting poetry while people played music behind him it just wasn't done you know
writing a three -minute song that somebody would play guitar behind it nobody did it until Jim
came along without without us you wouldn't have your Demetri Martin's and your Nick Thunes
and your Zach Galafanakis's they they claimed to be pioneers of the comedy movement
no I'm just saying they all they all do jokes well they play music oh I see yeah yeah there you go
there you go um I uh I um think uh I lost it I don't know what I was going to say I don't know I
had something to say just then and it's gone wow it's gone what the that was excuse is that I've
been awake for 18 minutes it's 918 PM Joe got me up pretty early today to do this I have to you go
ahead Joe well I might have to go into the Salami house as I call it this afternoon the bathroom
yeah yeah yeah yeah my yeah nevermind I was gonna say something really gross uh so yeah we had to
start early today uh but but hey we get it done for the fans and that's how you do it oh and time
and Jerry the reason we're doing it yeah is because you we were talking about it and I said to you
I'm gonna just pitch this out to feel free to say no but should we do Tom and Jerry I hear it's a
train wreck and then and then we we laughed and both said yeah we should do it and then and then we
fucking had to had to do it and here we are Jesus Christ this fucking movie this so bad of goods it's
good stuff it doesn't hit when you're alone and 40 you know you're just sitting there watching
shit for two hours wanting to die it's not the fun of like being 18 with your pals watching the room
or something yeah it's uh well we'll we'll get to it yeah we'll get to it and uh in other news uh
and in cartoon news we'll just keep it in the cartoon world today sure pepula pew cancels
there's your news psycho I mean nobody liked pepula pew really no uh I get it I get why they were
like this is we can't have this in the movie of space jam too I mean look people before everybody
starts to pat Warner Brothers on the back about getting rid of pepula pew don't forget they are still
making space jam too you know which is an offense in and of itself uh way the the Warner Bros
executives here's how they go in it's not they go in and they're like hey we've heard some concerns
about this and like we we really agree whatever they go in eyes completely rolled and go like hey
some idiots complaining about pepula pew I mean they don't care either nobody cares nobody's acting
off of any sort of principles everybody's just caving into every demand that is made I don't think
even the people complaining about pepula pew care about pepula pew right so he's he's out and I get
I get the the problem with the past portrayal but I also I read an article and Warner Brothers stance was
you know he's it's a problematic character and it needs to be and it's guys he's not a real human being
just redo the character they're they're redoing the sexy bunny character for that reason yeah like
we don't want it to be sexualized we want it to be strong so you redo it that's that's I don't know
maybe how you kind of learned that things should be different uh but no just to get in here is one
gag of of pepula pew starting to hit on a woman and the the woman or squirrel or whatever
and that squirrel being like hey that's not how things are done anymore you make it funny pep he's
like oh I'm sorry I got better find another interest you know then he starts reading about Bitcoin
you got a timely joke yeah yeah oh boy and then pepula pew's new thing is he's a Bitcoin bro yeah
and then yeah and then you have him fuck the bit coins yeah he's like scrooge McDuck where he jumps
into a room full of bitcoins except they all have pussy's and he fucks him it would be is that
fun coins have pussy's my my friend keeps trying to explain it to me and we never get to that question
and I want to ask they'll both yeah okay um it would be funny if you did a thing with the character where
he became a proponent of women's rights or something you know what I mean like that would be really
funny man like or like like the brain gremlin and gremlins too with Tony Randall's voice just make it like
where he's woke now or something do something with it again and my whole reason for that is just
so we can learn like this this strategy of erase it because it's offensive is so dangerous to me it's
like no we have to teach people this is what the point of raising a child is just to say here's here's
how the right way is and that was the wrong way back then right but you need to have the wrong way
to show them that's the wrong way to you don't do that so anyway he's out there's a there's a back
lash now on on the internet it's jovial I believe I don't think anybody's dead serious but
people now are saying for and and and look it is a fair point there's calling for Miss Piggy to be
canceled now because they're like she sexually assaults Kermit constantly and also hits him
like sure she beats on him and I'm like all right well I guess if this is the game
we're playing yeah so but you know she she like malls him to the ground and all that stuff and
you know here's the difference and this is something that nobody really likes talking about
Kermit loves it Kermit loves being beaten but it's his little green cock hard right he likes yeah
the reason you'll never hear him come forward and be like yeah you're right this is this is bad for
me thank you for for saving me it's because he fucking loves it yeah he's into that yeah he's he's in
a piggy what do you think Gonzo likes I mean you got Gonzo on there who fucked chickens I believe
was the insinuation right certainly fuck the chicken that seemed consensual as well I'm not well
well how do the chickens couldn't speak and there were they had female voices you knew they were
women well thank god for that I guess they didn't say words I'm saying that they had like
they were present you know they weren't just like I remember as a kid thinking it was funny
because the joke was that they were actual like chickens they were just puppet versions of chickens
but they weren't like they weren't like humanoid chickens or whatever you'd call it yeah they weren't
like it wasn't like Kermit where it was like a chicken who had a personality of stuff they were just
fucking chickens but the point is it wasn't I'm not misremembering right it wasn't
simulated that he liked to fuck the chickens right it was it was heavily insinuated and not
it was a problem not just because they were different species but because he was their superior
that's what I mean they were clearly his assistants which brings something else into question
Kermit is mispiggy superior she's assaulting her boss
Kermit's not mispiggy's boss that's just simply not true what what would the job even be
I thought Kermit was the leader of the Muppets I thought he was everybody's boss
but the well the Muppets isn't a union or something like they don't you know come put
caulk around your bathtub or something they house Gonzo above the chickens that
Gonzo is above the chicken the chickens aren't even really technically Muppets but they're his
assistants for his his feats of daring do being shot out of a cannon or whatever I see okay all right
well who's a heavy time man it's a heavy time and when the times are heavy where can you turn
but the old past movie quarter oh good you know yeah am I wrong you're not wrong tell me you know
no you're not wrong at all all right then I'd like to start with a picture called
what what did I tell you I wanted to talk about on this show blame it on Rio blame it on Rio
oh man blame it on Rio you never saw it see this is a movie a lot of people I know a lot of people
in our age group watched on HBO because it was on five ten times a day it was on constantly
apparently on HBO the film is Michael Cain in his I'll do anything period and Joe Bologna who was
yeah in my opinion one of the least effective actors of all time he's not a good comedic actor he's
not a good dramatic actor I like him I think he's a good multi cam guy I think he's a pretty good
multi cam guy what multi cam was he on uh he was unmarried with children he got a spin off that that
bombed but but like that's kind of what he was suited to do was that sort of thing I think he's
isn't he the dad and clueless no no that's the Dan Hadea that's Dan Hadea yeah uh he's you know
he you know he's Joe Bologna you know no yeah here's the proud name wild name could that's the
reason he's famous Joe Bologna yeah uh Mike Cain is married to Valerie Harper and other sitcom
staple and the marriage is on the rocks she apparently was it is a nightmare by the way is she
well she left wrote or she she pulled some like she was married to her husband was her manager first
of all that's you're already off to a bad start sure and then uh she did a thing remember when she
got booted from the Hogan family where they're like take care of yourself it's because she tried to
pull a thing she pulled on Roda where she's like I'll walk out if you don't give me more money and on
Roda they folded and Hogan family they were like take care I prefer the Sandy Duncan episodes of Hogan
family yeah and there were like lots of jokes about Valerie Harper on other sitcoms like the Golden
Girls went at her a couple and I'm like this is clearly like inside baseball she's yeah she's a problem
well she she had she has brain problems now correct she's dead she's dead okay because she did a two
broke girls kind of near the end and yeah she was she was sweet but she was also not not all there
right I think she was very sick at the end yeah I don't know why she was doing the show she was not
healthy but it was cool to meet her sure anyway blame it on Rio Michael Cain and Valerie Harper
marriages collapse and Harper's barely even mentioned in the film but you you get the feeling things
aren't good Michael Cain and his daughter a young gorgeous Demi Moore are like we need to get
out of town let's leave the this this mom slash wife behind and go to Rio so Michael Cain and his
daughter and Joe Bologna and his daughter Michelle Johnson who is the lady from father the bride no
she's an actress I was unfamiliar with a but I guess your death becomes her she's in doctor giggles wax
work wax work yeah she's Zach Galligan's girlfriend and wax work I think okay they all go to Rio
together the first night if memory serves that they are in Rio Michelle Johnson and Michael Cain
fuck Michael Cain fucks his best friend Joe Bologna's 17 -year -old daughter different time as you said
earlier but it wasn't legal then either um those 17 is well depends on what state you're in as we're
learning from the crystal true true and why did you by the way tell mr. Julia again to do what he did
yeah the daughter is 17 now Michael Cain is conflicted in the movie of course they they're in like a
little cove off off the side of the beach and he's like I shouldn't be bloody doing this I shouldn't
be bloody but it also appears that Michael Cain the man is having problems with the scenes he's
being asked to perform um I looked it up here's here's the one piece of trivia the movie offers
Johnson who was 17 at the time of filming so not a not a 25 -year -old plank 17 had to receive permission
from a judge to appear nude in the film so there's like 10 grown men and a 17 -year -old girl in court
like please let us show this girl's tits wow this 17 -year -old girl is nude throughout the film
there are numerous scenes where Cain and Bologna go to a topless beach and just stand there as women walk
past them just dozens of women walk past there's almost no dialogue when the end credits start up they
re -show you the topless beach scene they put it in a little box during the end credits so you can
just watch the topless girls walk by again yeah well that's an exec going yeah we went to trial
it cost us 45 grand for this you better put that fucking shot in more than one we paid for I'm
get him up there yeah uh Cain can anyway you might be wondering what the tone of this movie is the tone
is light sex farce like what he comedy Cain is finding every opportunity to take this girl into a
secluded location and fuck her under the nose of her dad and his best friend then she takes a photograph
of herself completely nude Bush and all gives it to him in a public place and Cain's like all right
now this is getting out of hand now you're getting mouthy now you're showing off and then the whole
thing becomes how are we gonna keep this from from daddy they do eventually you know Joe Bologna
eventually finds out through a lot of like hotel room doors slamming one of those type of scenes
but it winds up being okay that Michael Cain's fucking his daughter because we learn that Bologna's
been fucking his wife oh I I wish it was the other daughter that's where I thought it was going
at some point it looks like Bologna is going to start trying to fuck Cain's daughter as revenge yeah
to me more but really to me more just looks uncomfortable well this is an identical plot to that to that
who's the lady from the married to live shriver what's your name he wants
this is an identical thing to that Robin Wright pen Naomi Watts movie where they bang each other's
sons right but that's like a steamy art house yeah it's always different with men and women and it's
like Naomi Watts is a young beautiful lady Michael Cain this was in Michael Cain in like Hannah and
her sisters days yeah yeah like you have expected them to show up in that coat you know the giant
glasses a truly insane movie I've learned that many many of my friends have a soft spot for this movie
this was their kind of intro to nudity we all need those movies for me it was you know a porky's
a hamburger the motion picture these were the movies that I first saw the boobs and
I write this later today to be honest with you this this movie is is nuts you can read ebberts
review of it which was really really funny where he just talked about how just gross it made him feel
and disgusting and um check it out you want to talk about a different time this movie would
would have you thrown out of America at this point uh I watched in my I'm sorry Rook I'm sorry Joe
I wanted to mention that it was directed by Stanley Donan who did singing in the rain
that was one last thing I wanted to mention it was like one of his last films the legendary Hollywood
director all right carry on yeah he's up there go permission from a judge we showed Garbo's crack
and they loved us for it oh boy um all right I uh
I'm gonna keep it light today yeah in my pursuit to go back to a simpler time
because that seems to be another theme of today cartoons in a simpler time uh I keep trekking back
through old sitcoms uh pat will not approve of this but it's what's happening I have started watching
who's the boss from the beginning have you started doing that in favor of news radio no I have news
radio still but I already talked about news radio and I and I do watch news radio and I'll jump
back and forth between who's the boss and news radio and I'm gonna say this about who's the boss
I never had much respect for it but in revisiting it Tony dances one hell of a performer
I can't argue that I put the smile on my face every time I believe in the tension between him and
Angela Judith Light the wonderful Judith Light who I met once after her performance in a play uh
called uh uh the football coach uh the packer's football coach um oh you're asking the
road uh son of the bridge deniro played him in the movie um paterno no no that's that was
Pacino that was the Penn State one uh i would ever that was a play about the famous green bay
packer's coach uh the dad from the wanderers played the coach Dan Laura yeah and then Judith
Light played the wife she was wonderful my friend Bill Dawes was in the play and I met Judith Light
afterwards and then went and drank with him in the hadaria at a at a like like a an actor's only
Broadway bar and morissa tome was sitting across from us she was in the show at the time it was fun
anyway I love the two of them kids are cute as hell cute as can be got a young elissa malano in there
young dandy pentaro adorable uh i i love Katherine helmond is the saucy moana you know i enjoy a
saucy older lady once in a while uh i i like this picture over this this tv show i'm enjoying it and
i will tell you this much much edgy year than you would think a lot of sex humor a lot of stuff like that
um and yeah once in a while it actually makes me laugh but it puts a smile on my face
all right fair enough i remember watching it all the time but i don't remember a single plot of
any of the episodes i don't even remember them leaving the hot the house on who's the boss the plots
they don't usually leave the house the plots are like it are like it tony gets angela to go out with
this best friend wally who needs to learn how to date again because he's too hung up on his ex -wife
and then wally starts dating moana and angela and then the mom and daughter compete for the guy it's
stuff like that nice work wally yeah yeah um folks i'm going i guess i'm going to go with crazy
movies as my theme this week um i'd love to talk about a picture called ken jitte
forbidden subjects ken jitte colon forbidden subjects starting Charles bratson
um it came out in nineteen eighty nine so from that tarantino uh Edgar Wright podcast
i found out about a lot of kind of crazy shit you know they were talking about some grine house type
stuff this was directed by jaylie Thompson who did tend to midnight which was the movie i talked
about last time where the serial killer would strip fully nude before killing each of his victims
uh and i just loved how insane it was this jaylie Thompson also did happy birthday to me which i've
never seen i own it i haven't watched it yet he's just a great he well he got to start with legitimate stuff
guns and avarone etc by the way i said chuck bratson was in guns and avarone last time he wasn't he's in
uh great escape and another stuff like that but um jaylie Thompson and i guess near the end of his
career was like fuck it if we can show nudity and violence he's one of these guys who was like
you know like hitchcock near the end where he's like uh let's just let's just show him everything you
know let's now be the another we can get away with all this the plot of ken jitte is is chuck bratson
has a again a young underage daughter i think his daughter is like fifteen um there is this guy
from in tokyo a businessman who watches a girl getting molested on a subway train this guy reaches
his hand upperskirt and fingers her while she's standing on the subway train she is too embarrassed to
tell him to stop and eventually climaxes while this creepy businessman watches and then it becomes
like an obsession for him he wants to do this okay we follow him we follow his freewheeling tokyo
ways where you can just grab a woman in a bar and make out with her whatever he gets transferred to la
he's on the subway and he decides well shit i'm gonna try molesting some girl like i saw that guy
do back in tokyo and reaches into the skirt of charles bratson's daughter she screams runs off the
subway and says the line and i'm apologizing in advance i am quoting but this is the line this movie
oriental just touched my holiest of holies okay all right this girl screams that to her friend
and i thought i mean if that's the kind of line that makes you sit fully up on the couch and just like
what am i even looking at here it was the name of my autobiography
colon and other observations i've learned on the long road through showbiz or whatever right they
made me well yours was that oriental touched my colon yeah yeah and then you put the colon
in the wrong place my ex so anyway that's i guess the plot is of course charles bratson wants to of
course kill the man who lightly figured his daughter um he goes into his bosses and his bosses are
well okay you say molest i mean did he rape her did he you know like everyone's given him shit
bratson asked to be taken off the case because of how much he hates Asians he doesn't think it's fair
that he should be allowed to pursue Asians well this was a thing this was now now this was a common
plot line up through the uh i would say the mid 90s because this was like this was like the
Philadelphia plot line it's like let's make the guy that hates the thing defend the thing right
what i mean so in Philadelphia it was i he was homophobic and whatever but they would do this a lot
back then with some kind of cop or lawyer that was how they create attention yeah they can hate the
person he's defending on a fundamental level and then and then they'll be drama well they have bratson
pull up inside of a downtown LA hotel with his partner and just starts there's a group of
you know extremely wealthy Asians going into this hotel and bratson stands up and starts screaming
at them basically go back to Tokyo kind of stuff and since bratson is your hero and since chuck bratson's
fan base is the kind of people who would definitely scream that at a group of actions it's really
weird because you can imagine that like in a theater people would cheer these lines it's not it's
it's not like he's treated as heroic for being racist but he's never really called out on it either
so it's it's very uncomfortable it's very sleazy i can't tell you how sleazy it is the opening scene
of the film and then i'll let you discover it's it's pleasures on your own if you want to watch it but
is it an enjoyable film million percent okay it may start watching other bratson vehicles i was
i've never seen much bratson so he's got a real track record man of problematic movies
this thing blew me away i mean it was like having cold water splashed in your face but when the movie
starts in the coal -eggert if you'll remember oh yeah when i was growing up there was a movie called
blown away yep gory ham and the coal -eggert and and then i just rewatched a bunch of clips from that
because i went down another film and rabbit hole on on youtube yeah and i was pulling up clips of
that and then that led me to scott bale yes and scott bale's twitter in the bio says you know actor
writer father falsely accused me to victim you know like he put her accusation in his bio wow
wow wow wow wow i forgot actually about that accusation but agger the first shot of the movie is
agger it's acid and a black lacy thong if i'm not mistaken but she is playing a 17 -year -old girl
and folks i can't stress enough that i was not seeking out material about underage girls
right uh these are both on amazon prime and they just popped now granted they did pop up in my
four u category where they thought i might like it but um agger is being taken up into a hotel room
by this kind of sleazy businessman type and you know one of those credits where they'll go like
starring charles bronson and then a quick flash of something then julyerland and then another quick
flash like it's like a like a stylistic choice yeah it keep flashing to this suitcase that appears
to be full of like weird sex shit and you start to see like okay there's a vaseline tub or whatever
this is how the opening credits are coming in charles bronson flash to a vaseline tub you know like
sex toys etc bronson kicks open the door stops them from having sex it's like a 40 -year -old guy with
mccoll agger the policemen come in they're doing their thing and then bronson picks up a dildo the
size of a loaf of bread out of the suitcase and plunges it into the man's asshole at the at the end
of the cold open that's how this movie begins all right now imagine a clinis would would never shove
something in a guy's at like bronson i guess we'll just like do whatever that's a lot to live up to
that's a hell of an opening you're gonna you got a lot to live up to i mean that's that's
imagine if a cheer is opened with that it's it's just that's what your cold openness like you have
to then top that somehow it's a crazy film congete for bidden subjects i mean when tarantino is like
yeah you're obviously not gonna out sleaze congete but you know they kept talking about it like
this is kind of the pinnacle of sleaze check the thing out i think it's a great double -fege with
tend to midnight if you like extreme grindhouse kind of shit okay well on a similar note my next
selection is the sitcom blossom all right i've also started watching blossom again wow we need to end
this pandemic folks i didn't really like blossom much as a kid except for the fact that i had a big
crush on six oh hell yeah and uh but you know other than that i wasn't that into the show
jeno van ooi yeah but uh jeno van ooi what what is what is there not to say about blossom
Joey Lawrence delightful my embalic delightful Ted was delightful met him directed a lot of
two broke nice guy yeah the kid that looks like a turtle delightful everybody's delightful in the show
and again heavy themes on this thing i mean it's here's the thing you watch blossom and then you watch
call me cat and you just it's just hard to wrap your head around how paper thin uh major network
entertainment has become because blossom was a show that when it was on kind of got made fun of
by other sitcoms for for not being that edgy and like oh it's the girl with that weird hats and whatever
you watch it now and it's like episode one it's blossom gets her period you know for the first time
and they're dealing with that episode two an older guy at the high school wants to take her to the
prom and her dad is like i'm stepping in and saying no because i don't trust this kid or with it
even these sitcoms from the that were tame in 1989 or whenever the hell it came out
or 90 are 20 ,000 times edgy or the meanwhile you turn on call me cat and it's like
i've got to get the money for this trip to bermuda like that that that will be a plot line of it you know
like so i felt that between that and the plot lines of who's the boss uh i was like i can't believe
i'm even saying this but these are these are edgy or sitcoms then anything you can find out
there right now and these are the shows that we kind of laughed about and made fun of a bit back
then for being way too wholesome a blossom actually there was actually a very funny bit on it one of
the things is that her mom left like that's why that's a single dad yeah i thought mom died okay
no she's like often you're up being a musician or something and like touring and the dad stays
home with the kids and he's a struggling musician so so they're split up but like that's
one big part of the first episode she's very sad that she doesn't have a mom she's like it's not
fair like i need a mom to help me through this time in my girlhood and um and uh she there's a dream
sequence where she goes into her kitchen and Felicia Rashad is in the kitchen with a cake and the gag is
she's having a fantasy that that misses Cosby is her mom it's very it's actually very funny bit
okay and even just seeing that i'm like once you couldn't even get a bit that quality on something
you know what i mean it's like so anyway uh am i telling you to go out and watch it no
am i telling you that i'm gonna stay in and watch it yeah um yeah i can't believe you start news radio
and then and then veer off into these other shows i'm bouncing all around some look you look it's a
finite product once that news radio is finished it's finished yeah so you know i you got it you got
to mix it up i'm throwing a couple episodes of taxi in here and there okay okay um
all right you can go uh joe i rewatched a film that i truly love that we've discussed on this show
and it's called prisoners i know i recommended it to you i've recommended it to many but um it's i think
it is the best thriller of the last ten years you know if we're gonna count parasite okay maybe that
but you know and i'm sure somebody could prove me wrong i'm just saying prisoners for its cast
for for everything great about it it is one of the most underrated movies of my lifetime it is a movie
that a lot of people just haven't seen they just missed and i don't know why or how that happened it
is a rough movie an unpleasant movie uh the violence when it comes is really extreme uh when
Hugh Jackman beats Paul Dano there are some shots of his face that are as scary as anything in in any
horror movie but i think prisoners is one of the great thrillers of my life i think it's maybe a
notch below silenced a lamp seven but it's not that far below jill and hall is awesome in it you know
you know we did a whole episode on prisoners right we did the show as an episode yeah we reviewed it
you talked about this scene you said dano looks like a pig person when they show a person i mean
i'm telling you i watched it again and i loved it yeah i know but you know you know you don't need
to redo the whole i'm redoing the whole i'm doing a standard uh bad movie corner review all right
fair enough um yeah i just think it is for some reason a movie that that has slipped through the cracks
and uh redoing the whole slipping through the cracks we had all kinds of innuendos going on over here
uh what oh the hole and then slipping through the cracks yeah sorry i'm a little more elevated with my
thinking sure yeah um i i love the film at this time what i appreciated more than i did before is
jill and hall's performance where i think he's almost doing like a controlled necklace cage kind of vibe
he's doing this like squinty thing i'm so glad it wasn't rough below in his part or one of these guys
who just you know like jill and hall there knock ruffalo i won't but i'm bored with him and
jill and hall's an interesting choice for this movie i i like that he's not who you think of as your
standard tough guy and he plays it as a guy who's kind of overcompensated it's total asshole throwing
a guy into a marvel movie will ruin almost any actor it's what happened to ruffalo if you watch
that second spider man jill and hall you're like what is this guy doing it's i find it to be an absurd
performance and then you turn around and go he's one of the best actors alive right now yeah there's
just something about seeing somebody in that in those movies that that that shines them up too much
in a certain way and it it kind of ruins it i don't know what it is couldn't agree more and it also
seems like the people who do them don't then go okay now i have eighty million dollars for the
rest of my life now i'll go do more interesting stuff like it's like they go do similar things
you know more ruffalo still challenges himself but like Chris Evans and a lot of these people are
just like i'll just keep doing movies where i kill people or go to marvel or whatever else and
man it's uh it's killing the business there's a lot of the swinging the swinging back and forth now
it's like you know it's like you're at some kind of superhero cinematic orgy like the way these guys
are now bouncing between the two universes yeah you know it's like it's just weird man it's weird
like i don't agree it's too much it's just too much um jo i need to grab my charger as i always do
at this time in the meantime do you do you want to talk about the plot of yeah i'm engineering
you're aware you can plug these computers in before yeah i just i just don't i just don't i think
that speaks leagues talk talk about tom and jerry if you know what the plot is i haven't done my third
movie corner yet do that corner uh my third in the themes of a simpler time and by the way pat pat
he's already gone he pat i'm here yeah you don't have to physically turn the mic off every time
you get up just go down to that mute button on your screen and click it and it's all right it's
well every time you turn it on and off it goes like that you hear it all right all right well it's
you know basic speed this is a man folks this man has worked in media his entire adult life
i've never seen anything like it doesn't know how a mute button on a screen works doesn't how to
share a photo it's outrageous anyway um in my thing it's a stick with my theme of simpler times
i watched Brian Regan's new special on the rocks which i thought was taped at red rocks
given the title but it wasn't it was taped so i think in Utah or something but it's at some big
outdoor amphitheater and like you know up in the mountains like a red rocks
um it was shot during covid uh the audience is fully masked um you you know that because you see them
occasionally but they don't show them that often because as i read in one critics review it you know
the point of this thing is obviously to to give you something to laugh about and take your mind off of
things and you don't want to keep seeing reaction shots of people and masks also to what probably looks
crap on camera to see an audience masked but laughing it probably looks weird anyway uh it's a
wonderful special i think regan is one of the best comics working today um i thought his last special
left something to be desired it seemed a bit rushed to me and that happens it happens with every
comedian this one i felt like he was he was back in full form i laughed out loud several times
throughout the special which is saying a lot because uh you know as a stand -up i barely laugh at
loud at all at anything anymore particularly stand -up but uh to watch a stand -up special that made me laugh
this much out loud it was really enjoyable it was a nice surprise uh he looks great
he kills you can hear how excited the audience is to be at an event and to see a live event again
and whatever and i think it's awesome that he did this and i think it's awesome that he did it the
right way and i think it's just great so uh i i really recommend that special very much if you
want to just have a few fun laughs i'm three fours done with it um for some reason i can't
i just can't watch much stand -up comedy right now it's not his fault but i'm not laughing at it
and i think i'm kind of like the man went through a divorce
to still not mention it in his act i'm just kind of like i want that regan façade to drop and to learn
about the man and not to do a five minute bit about raisins which is still very funny and i know
that's his thing but it's like i'm ready for the the guard to come down and to tap into the anger
that's clearly just below the surface of a bride and regan it's not his uh you know it's not
how he butters the bread what are you going to do you know it's like i don't ever want to turn on
look i think it's always sunny as the funniest show on television i hated nothing more
that they ever did was then when they did that serious dance
at the end of season tenor would it it's like guys what the fuck are we doing here man like
like this is not you're doing an interpretive dance to show mec coming out of the closet right now
like i'm so there's just certain things i don't want to cross into serious territory and brine
regan is certainly one of them i don't want to see him up there talking about his divorce i want to
see him being like hey dude you're coming in we're gonna have some stupid fun and uh and that's it you
i just think that it would be a whole new thing but like that level of anger coming out of him
about his life would be really fascinating even if i was just like
happen to be in the room where he was working it out you know maybe he doesn't release it
maybe i can get a i order a uh ten thousand dollar cameo from him where he talks about his divorce
for me personally you also realize too he's at a level where his fans expect a certain thing
and if he doesn't deliver that thing it will cost him money you know what i mean like he's got
he's got investors for all intents and purposes so my friend my friend was telling me she was at a
show a regan show and he made like the dumb joke of like studying a broad and he's like i prefer a red
heads or whatever you know right and he said the she said the audience groaned and he was like no no
i actually and he just kept like doing it because they were they were like getting weirdly offended
and she said it was crazy it was the most benign stupid joke right but like even that was too much
for like his audience it's like no dude yeah but i do like that it'll take shots at social media and
twitter i find that interesting sure you know uh that's which is a little heavier than you expect him
to go but uh or deeper rather but anyway watch the special is very funny he's one of the greats it's
just it's clean comedy isn't wetting my whistle these days because i'm i'm in a low place but um
speaking of clean comedy let's bring us to one of the pinnacles of the form the g -rated Tom and Jerry
movie i mean what is there to say where do you begin folks it's a movie about
Tom and Jerry Tom and Jerry are in the movie stop you're right there because i'm not even
sure you can say that yeah Tom and Jerry are you know they keep them mute which Tom and Jerry don't
talk fine but like there they seem to be very much supporting characters in their own film they are
they very much are uh the movie is really about and i know all of you have been pining for this
a character played by Chloe Grace Moretz trying to crack her way into the competitive field of hotel
management that is the plot her name is Chloe Grace Moretz oh sorry uh Joe's trying to make her a
spanish i always wonder i thought it was Moretz this whole time and i was always like man she is spanic
no oh Moretz um shit i never knew that yeah it there is a lot of plot here about her trying to get a
job as a hotel manager we're following the ins and outs of her job application process
Rob Delaney plays like the pompous hotel boss um Michael Pena doing that weird kind of
lisp exaggerated accent that he does in comedies is playing a hotel bell hop now he's like the
assistant manager of the hotel assistant manager because he's her competition he's like undercutter
throughout the movie he's the foil Joe's Colin jost and this other woman are getting married and
they're supposed to be like the royalty ish having a big wedding here at this hotel they never explain
that you're like are they instagram influencers they're just benign celebrities and this is how benign
films are becoming that they're not even giving you character details to describe you know who the
who people who characters are it's everything is so ambiguous and broad so that no one could possibly
take anything the wrong way they also do really awkward and bad jokes about how's oversensitive
everything is becoming and those fall completely flat because the movie has no edge or bite to it
either so why are they making those jokes but i was let's start at the beginning um a group it starts
with a group of pigeon cartoon pigeons wrapping they are doing tribe called quest can i kick it can i
kick it does nothing to do with the plot it's a great song it's a nice song to open a movie with
gets the energy going nothing to do with anything though and pigeons are wrapping it to the camera
pigeons flying and wrapping to the camera one of the pigeons voiced by the director of the film
Tim's story who gives himself the longest and largest voice credit at the end of the film so clearly
the guys some sort of ego guy yeah Tim's story let me just say right away Tim's story should never
be allowed to work again after this film that's the thing he there's a confidence to it and like
proudly taking a voice in the movie and all it's like anyone who is proudly standing behind this
has some troubles and should not be directing it's um what's crazy is that the guy did barber shop
and he's done other ride along and stuff and well though none of those were amazing movies they showed
a competence that this movie doesn't this feels like the first movie from somebody who'll never
direct a movie again and not that's why i think more and more they're just being made by
corporations this feels so soulless it feels like it's trying to address everyone's note
and in the process you have a movie with no conflict no real story no characters to root for
and i honestly was lost for big chunks of this movie i did not know what was happening well
let's start with the biggest problem in the movie every animal in the movie is animated interacting
with real people right it is never addressed it is never explained some of the animals can speak
some of them can't some of them can sing some of them can't people in one scene are interacting
with cats and dogs as if they're other people then in another scene acting as if a cat is just a cat
and it's not a person and has no personality or feelings or anything and then you're seeing on top of
it scenes at like fish markets where people are throwing dead cartoon fish around and you're like
you've spent the first 40 minutes of this movie acclimating me to animals being sentient beings
and now you're showing dead animals and it's disturbing it's like seeing a morgue scene or something
like what the fuck is going on here man yeah that's the biggest problem in the whole movie you don't
know what the fuck is going on so that they they at one point they hire Tom yeah at the hotel and you're
like what is happening right now that's exactly right it's like you know in a horror movie it's like
know the rules they're state state your rules the most obvious you know putting it in the text
example of this would be gremlins here are the three rules and you stick to them this movie creates
no interior sense of logic it makes you really admire what Roger Rabbit did which is a better special
effects 30 years ago better story by a billion percent and also you completely understand the
relationship between tunes and humans you understand that they all live in tune town but can cross over
it's sort of an interesting metaphor for racism you know that it's never done explicitly in
Roger Rabbit at all but it's definitely there's some prejudice between the two to even really say
Roger Rabbit while discussing Tom and Jerry as a slap in the face to that film this this is closer
to like that loony tunes movie that Joe Danty made but even that was way better than this because
it was made by somebody who loved loony tunes and understood the characters and yeah this is
no Tom and Jerry not that there's much to know but it doesn't capture any of the spirit of those
cartoons at all it's a failure on that level for sure this is like space jam six bad yeah a direct
clam shell VHS space jam sequel it's it's it's it's it's just a terrible terrible film the the competition
between Tom and Jerry is almost nonexistent there's a few sequences where they get into it a little bit
the entire crux of Tom and Jerry was was the was the constant torturous pranks they would play on one
another that was the whole crux of the show there was no point to it other than that right this
takes almost all of that away has a climactic sequence again which I'm sure you'll have all been
waiting for where Tom and Jerry work together nobody gives a shit and if it's not enough then
then Moritz has the line almost two camera if Tom and Jerry can learn to get along maybe we can
all learn to do the same that line and then the line that she says in the middle about when
they're feuding it's almost like you guys have been doing this for years oh Jesus Christ I mean
this movie is it's unbearable I had to watch it in sections and last night I was down to the last
section and it was 15 minutes and getting through this final 15 minutes I can't even begin to tell you
now here's my fear I often find myself and I'm not bragging but I often find myself at the
SNL after parties because they take place here in New York and I have friends on the show and whatever
I often find myself drunk at those parties and I have often found myself drunkenly talking to Colin
just uh -huh and I may or may not in those conversations have said a few dumb things to him that I didn't
need to say uh -huh my fear is that I'm gonna be in that position again and just be like bro what the
fuck were you thinking this money I mean of course money it's so bad it's so bad it is in a year where
it's just kind of everything is bad and disappointing um this stands out it stands below the other bad
stuff of 2020 and 2021 it's uh it's lazy as shit the what about the scene where they're being interrogated
and it starts putting words behind them like Batman style like a word will appear on the wall behind
them do you remember that no and it's like it's a cartoon it's like in Batman when you hit somebody
and it goes pal yeah yeah yeah but like they're they're super imposing words that they're saying on
the screen behind them I assume because somebody was like this is a cartoon why do you have
Jerry sitting in a chair being interrogated let's have some animated fun and they start trying to
put in words it's so other scenes so it's not a stylistic choice it's just like a nonsense nothing
makes sense it's so crazy um they look you know I know people out there are gonna be like look
you're worried about logic it's time and jade but I'm sorry yeah I get caught up on logic they
Tom they make a point to show you that Tom can't speak that's like a plot point that they go
back to and one point Chloe Gray says the silent thing is getting old yeah because she's trying to
figure out what he needs or how she can help or whatever but then they do a sequence in the middle where
he sits at a piano and sings and you're just like I don't understand what like what is the point of
there's a lot of also I didn't understand why Jerry was always like lounging to hip -hop every time
he went into his little mouse house which yeah because here's why it contemporizes it way too much
I remember when last Jedi came out I remember talking to Jay Ferguson on the set of the CBS hit sitcom
Living Biblically which would still be on the air had a certain character not been cut but
yeah I remember talking to Jay Ferguson afterwards or after we saw last Jedi and I said I said man
that call waiting gag at the beginning of the movie really fucking bothered me and he said there
should never be anything that connects that universe to ours and it's the same thing with Tom and
Jerry I don't want to see Jerry listening to heavy metal I don't want to see him listen into punk rock
I don't want to see him listen into hip -hop he's a goddamn cartoon mouse that needs to be timeless
and look if you're gonna have him listening to any one of those music types of music at least don't
have him listening to the thing that came out last week on Apple Music so we're gonna put a real time
stamp on this fucking thing you know what I mean where it's like auto tuned and whatever it's like come
on man what is this well at the beginning you see Jerry look up at a billboard for John Legend
and you get the feeling that I guess I'm sorry Tom Tomcat I guess Tom idolizes John Legend in
this version then he you know he imagined himself up on the billboard with him later on
Tom sings a song you're correct even though he can't speak but he sings with his voice auto tuned
yeah yeah Tom's voice auto tuned yeah so what the fuck is that yeah and they and on top of it all
they have them do this just for extra confusion they have them do the song at a real piano in a hotel
lobby yeah every no choice makes any sense no choice makes any sense it is all thrown together it is
paint by numbers if you do people like this so just throw it in there don't worry about if it tracks
or not it's crazy it's it's it's an insanely amateur poorly the Chloe Grace is lucky because about 10
years ago this would have been a career ender yeah all right nowadays this she got the slide
into the radio radar there's too much content nobody's gonna fucking crucifier for this but this is
like one of those you know I saw Dave Foley make a joke on Twitter the other day about the movie that
ended his filmmaking career that was so bad I can't remember what it was monkey bone yeah and it's
like it's like yeah man that used to be a thing yeah asked Brendan Fraser it's a thing you know
what I mean like and she's lucky dude this is a this is a career ender Tim's story I think it should
I be way more of a speed bump because this is not you're the director dude like you're the boss man
this was in your hand the guy who ever directed cats in gay 2 should never be allowed to work again
you you you're giving you're giving a hundred million dollars here uh agreed but again I this this
feels studio noted to to death uh I would imagine I would imagine it was a salvage job this seems
like something that was completely lost and they tried to fix it I have friends who were being paid
to write a time a Jerry movie 10 years ago so probably this went through eight drafts they were like
we've put five million dollars into this and we haven't shot a piece of film let's just shoot the
script that none of us think is ready and you know it's it's it's a it's a shame it's an ugly movie it
the jokes are are awful the animation look the animation is kind of pretty it doesn't really blend
in well with the the real world um I'm and I'm just scrambling just to say there's one
positive it's one of the worst movies I'll say something positive I'll say something positive there's
one I laughed out loud at one part oh wow there's a scene where the cat and mouse and then spike the dog
voiced by Bobby canna valley Bobby I'm a huge fan say no sometimes you don't have to do every single
thing that exists Jesus Christ man like if I was canna valley uh and I'm never getting that lead
roll with the huge payday I'm taking every part they offer me to no question
I think kind of valley he does get lead rolls and he's he's in tons of stuff maybe he did it for his kids
I don't know I don't know but anyway Michael Panna also he does cool movies it's like why are you doing
this man like but anyway whatever it maybe it's COVID maybe COVID fucked it all up maybe this
was supposed to be better I don't know but I will say the one funny part Delaney who gives a shit nobody's
expecting anything from him you know what I mean like very nice man though I'm not saying he's not
a nice man but it's like Delaney comes to astrophase which he wrote it's great show it's okay Bobby or
Delaney can pop up in a million bad things and it's like I don't expect anything Delaney's not
known for his quality work is what I'm getting at um you know no offense but it's true uh
Pania is a guy where I'm like no dude you've done like some really cool flicks
Chloe Grace Moretz is a woman where I'm like you've done some really cool flicks
she's also a kid still so it's like you know it's a little more forgivable um
anyway whatever I'm putting too fine a point on it the the funny part
spike the dog Tom and Jerry get into a fight in the lobby of the hotel and they do the gag from
cartoons where they're fighting so crazily it starts a tornado right loud and Michael Pania gets
caught up in the tornado cloud and he's flying all around the lobby with them and then that that
cuts to a scene where he's explaining to his boss played by Rob Delaney what happened yeah and his
he's his clothes are all messed up whatever and he looks traumatized from the experience and it's the
gag of he's he's trying to explain what happened and Delaney just keeps going I want you to take a
go on work rest uh he's like he's like listen to yourself listen to what you're saying which is a
really funny gag yeah and also would play way better if you didn't establish throughout the first
half of the movie then animals are interacting with everybody like people yeah yeah so but there
but he has a line Michael Pania goes the mouse and the cat are still here I saw them inside of the
animal tornado and and and Delaney goes would you listen to yourself go home and I was like that's
a very funny joke but again funny if if if if if these animals are acting like this when nobody can
see that they're acting like this which is what also what the cartoon was the cartoon was the mom
would leave and the maid would leave the store or go to work and then they go yeah so you know all
this flick had to be once again hollywood over complicates something it makes a terrible terrible decision
after terrible decision and and and and in turn a terrible product all this movie had to be was a home
alone they all they had to do was copy home alone the people go away for the holiday the cat and
mouse are in the house Jerry's trying to get in Tom is there to protect the house Jerry plays the
the the wet bandits Tom is in the McCauley Culkin position and the climax is the crazy
mouse trap you know literally mouse trap sequence of gags and events and that's that's that's the whole
there you go there's your movie that's all had to be I'd say I'd say that's a great idea except I'd
have the parents leave and then act one is Tom and Jerry fucking with each other in classic
Tom and Jerry's style then an act two a separate entity the wet band that's come in whatever it may be
and Tom and Jerry maybe do have to team up their knowledge of traps and stuff sure but you know
like I just think that at least keeps it going to feature length this movie and they even they must
have heard pitches over this over a decade tons of pitches if I'm sitting there and I'm an executive
and somebody is talking to me about Chloe Grace Moritz trying to get a job as a hotel event planner
I'd go wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute stop what is this fucking have to do with Tom and Jerry
and I don't think these people get the characters I don't think they understand I don't think that
anyone involved cared about Tom and Jerry I'm gonna be honest I don't care about Tom and Jerry
but this didn't really help me in any way it was it's embarrassing it's amateurish it's not funny it
looks like shit looks like an episode of ugly Betty and then also too you know the cardinal sin
of a film like this as you interact three and Chloe gets fired because she's not good at the job and
she ruins the big celebrity wedding or whatever the hell it is it cuts to a somber heartfelt sequence
where a pigeon sings a ballad and Tom weeps alone in an alley it's like what the fuck is going on
here guys yeah oh my god what a piece of shit hogs way down on Tom and Jerry hog so far down it's
as though it's never been up if you had to watch Veronica or Tom and Jerry for a second time you had
to which would you do Veronica Veronica I could I could jerk off to it in a bind yeah and Veronica at least
I was like I mean Veronica's terrible terrible dog shit yeah terrible dog shit but at the very least I was
like I can split this up into the three stories and the the batch it stuff was so batch it
that I was like like you know this lady's tits have eyeballs in them or whatever you know at least yeah
this was this was painful man this was like trying to watch like seventh heaven or something where I was
just like oh my god I don't give a shit about this at all it is it's it's almost impossible to pay
attention to they're giving you so little to to care about and latch onto it's a it's a hateful movie
it's a it's a shame that's our show folks check out the taste buds podcast sell volcano myself every
Monday drops 11 a .m. on YouTube on the no -press network channel also featured there is Hay babe
with Christa Stefano and Sal thank you everybody for your support on this show really appreciate it
you guys have been really amazing sticking with us via patreon send in the nice messages
and the emails and thanks thank you babe yes thank you so much we do read the patreon messages and
comments thank you for leaving those that is a great way to kind of get some information to us I always
go through and read them it might not be right after you send it but I always go when I check into
the patreon I'm on twitter and instagram kind of at the Patrick Walsh I'm casting on my buddy Jimmy
smagula's podcast baby mouth he is a man who has only eaten very few things in his life and he is
having friends introduce him to new cuisines I will be introducing oysters to him and that should be
up in about a week that's it our next episode will be regarding coming to america we will see you next
time and we will see you in hell