I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell folks.
It's the movie podcast where we discuss them.
We rate them. We talk them. My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh. And today we'll be talking about the Candyman who mixes it with love
and makes the world taste good. Candyman Candyman. This is the new version.
Obviously the the sequel to the original. Yeah, 2021 produced and co -written by Jordan Peele.
That's correct.
Productions. It was Blumhouse involved in this one at all.
I think they are right. I didn't see him at the beginning. I think it was a brawn joint.
I see brawn before more movies than anything these days.
There must just be a giant media conglomerate, but there are always in the list of
pre -movie things that goes by and directed by Neatacosta.
Yeah, it was interesting. I saw a lot of reviews say Jordan Peele's Candyman,
you know, and it's like, well, come on guys, you get a black woman directing a horror movie
and it's a big hit. Why are we talking about Jordan Peele?
Sometimes I completely get why people get upset about the way things are presented.
Of course. Of course.
But yeah, it's the new way. The custom now immediately onto the Marvels.
God dammit. Of course. Of course. God dammit.
I wonder, in some cases, if it's the goal, you know, now I know it's the agent's goal,
because you make so much money. But if from everything I've heard, it's essentially just
signing away your creative freedom and just, you know, letting them kind of direct over you.
Which is a shame. And these people probably all think they'll get back to doing one for them,
one for the bigs, but they don't. None of them. Because once you're handed $10 million as opposed
to $250 ,000 for making a movie, it's a little hard to go back for these people, I think. I get that too.
It's not helping us, you know, the old pipeline of like make a good indie and then become a brilliant
director, Spike Lee, Bart Scorsese, you know, the list goes on and on and on and on and on and on.
Now they go directly to Marvel. And I think it really sucks. If the Cohen brothers had gone to Marvel
after blood simple, imagine that, you know, imagine dark dark time from Marvel to back then. That's
what that was the period of the Dauflunger and yeah, the Roger Querm in fantastic four that never
got released. And, you know, it's still not out nobody's seen it. You can buy bootlegs on it,
like like trade shows and stuff. I don't think there's an official release. There's a documentary
called Doomed about it. And it's one of the saddest documentaries. You think it's going to be like
this funny, fun like everything went wrong. Look at this goofy moon. And it's like, God, it's like
these people thought that this was going to be like what made their careers and it's very sad. It's
the, do you remember a movie that for some reason has been rattling around on my brain lately called
The Giver, not McGiver, but The Giver with Mark Hamill. Yeah, so I do a very, yeah, very much so.
I never saw it, but what the hell was it? I mean, I feel like I saw it five minutes of it a hundred
times. I never knew what it was. It was a sci -fi movie. Hamill has lesser of a role in it. I think then
the box leads you to believe. Sure. I remember those seeing that as a kid, seeing it in the video
store as a kid and knowing the step down it meant for Mark Hamill. Sure, sure. It may be said,
which is why I'm so excited, Mark Hamill has had such a resurgence. I think it's great.
I hate that they botched it so badly with the Star Wars stuff, but yeah, but I'm glad he's like
back because he's, he is a charismatic actor and he's like fun to watch and he's really talented,
you know, and like, but I remember seeing that and being like, oh boy, man, oh Luke, what the hell happened
here? You know, meanwhile, I mean, that's got to hurt, dude, you know, you're, you're going to the
video store, you're seeing your movie next to like the full moon video stuff, and then you,
you know, then there's a giant poster for like regarding Henry. Yeah, you know, or whatever on the world.
Yeah, it's a tough town. It's a tough town. I always say I've never said this until now, but
the people in this town will cut off your balls and mail them to your grandparents.
They won't think twice, you know, yeah, but what I'm saying is they'll cut off your balls and
you're expecting that, but there's always another more horrible twist coming with what friend Jim wants
to, friend Jim Cargill wants to describe New York as you put your balls on the smoker and see if
they like the taste. Yeah, that was very funny. I'm looking here. This, the driver was co -directed by
screaming mad George. Do you know that? I actually know that name from something else. I don't know
what it is, but he did effects on big trouble. No China predator, nightmare three, nightmare four,
and then I believe he had something to do. Yeah, he definitely had something to do with society.
Well, folks, take a take a, we just praised Shutter in the last episode, but Shutter, take a note from
that. That's the kind of thing you let the effects guy direct, the guyver. You don't put him at the
head of one of the greatest horror franchises of all time. You let him write and direct half of the
episodes. Couldn't agree more. The guyver also spawned a sequel, which I called Guyver Dark Hero,
which I was unaware of. It's like a dark like superhero movie or something. What's new,
Joe? What's going on? We were talking about the Matrix at the end of the last one. I'm going through
them with my wife. We watched one and two, and I'm back on board. I do sort of feel like the fourth
is going to be a letdown, but a letdown from what? These movies let down people just as much as
the Star Wars prequels. Yeah. I remember enjoying two in the theater because it was so action -packed,
but now everybody I talked to says two is horrible. No, the action is incredible. I mean, the great
car chase is great fights. The action is better than one. It's just that one has this super tight story,
and it's very confident. There's a scene of Keanu talking to the oracle who's an old lady on a bench
that goes on for 25 minutes, and it's just like shot of Keanu, shot of the old woman.
And then the next scene will be one of the greatest action sequences you've ever seen.
So we're going to turn into like a little kid at the third in the third one or something.
I think we're going to watch the third one this week, but I don't remember liking it at all.
I remember there being an even longer long monologue of like a guy just rambling,
an old guy rambling in a room for what felt like an eternity. That's the second one. Isn't it
the engineer? That's the third one. Well, there's I think Cornell West might play the guy in the third
one. There's an old guy in two that's kind of cool that does a long monologue, but it's like I can't,
I mean, I know I want to brothers didn't do it. They're like, let's just let these guys do what they
want to do. They made a huge hit, but it's like somebody should have stepped in and been like,
guys, you can't have a monologue that goes on endlessly in the middle of an action movie.
It doesn't make any sense. Yeah, I never watched the anime tricks, you know,
they all animated series something, but I couldn't give a shit. Yeah, no, no.
It's just they got immediately too far up their own ass. And I feel like everybody wanted all
these answers. And it's like the answers unfortunately are like in philosophy books. They're trying to,
these guys are nerds, and they're trying to guide you towards like learning about philosophy.
It's like people think they're learning more about the matrix, like they learn about the force
in Star Wars or something, but it's like, no, these are these have basis in reality. It's really boring.
If you want to study it, study it, but it's like, this is real life. They got interested in this shit.
It doesn't mean we want to watch it as a movie, but yeah, it's like somebody,
like, it's like your friend who becomes obsessed with something and like won't stop talking about it.
And you're like, no one cares as much as you. Like, that's enough.
I mean, Jesus Christy, the wakowski's made two good movies.
The matrix bound. Yeah, that's exactly right.
They're amazingly gifted filmmakers, and yet everything they did is close to unwatchable.
They're, they're, they made some sort of loaded people hated it.
Matrix revolution people hated it. Speed racer. Who gives a shit? Clown out of speed racer.
It's got huge fans now, like every other piece of shit movie. People, people find their way to
these things. Sometimes cloud Atlas and Jupiter ascending were like laughable.
People, I know people who love cloud Atlas. I feel like they're just being condes,
are, you know, contradictory because it's really hard to even watch and racist in a lot of spots.
There's a lot of blackface in that movie that I can recall, including Tom Hanks, I believe. Yeah.
Blackface are like brown like white people playing like Indian people or something.
I don't remember specifics. I just remember a lot of like, why is Tom Hanks playing like an
Arab in the scene? Like a really weird stuff. And then Jupiter ascending is so awful,
but they give them huge budgets every time out. I mean, Jupiter ascending is madness.
It's just madness. Channing Tatum. And what does it Mieleconis?
I mean, any red man, Mieleconis should never be allowed to do anything except play
the character from that 70s show. She's great at that. She's great at that. When they can't,
I mean, I've talked about it before. When the castor is the wicked witch, I was like, what,
is this a joke? I know. What is this? I like you're in black swan. I don't think she's untalented,
but it's got to be like you're saying a part that's very much in her wheelhouse. I'd almost put her
with Reeves in that regard. You can't stretch her out of that. Like little things she does well.
Yeah. Well, what else is new? The Matrix. Did you see that? There are shows.
Any of the the Wachowski's like Netflix shows that they did. The one where everybody
fucks the whole time, the orgy show. Basically, I never watched.
No. What's that one? And are the Wachowski's both, they're both
females, correct? Currently. And they both have fully transitioned as far as I know.
Okay. Yeah. Sense eight is the show that I never saw. But I mean, these guys have done a lot of
stuff. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. These women have done a lot of, I'm looking at a picture of them
from the 90s right now. A lot of really expensive stuff that just didn't make any money. You make
something like the Matrix. You can kind of do what you want for the rest of your career. It's crazy.
Yeah. Well, there was a time. I don't think that could happen again. But
yeah, they probably had to go back to the well to keep getting stuff picked up. But
you know, so I don't know, but I have a kind of a cool scary stuff. I discovered something last night
that I didn't know existed. So I've been, so it's a double scary stuff. So number one, I've been
listening to selections from Night Shift, the Stephen King book on Audible. There are several,
you can't buy it all together as one volume. But there are several volumes
to the night shift book as audio books. All of them read by John Glover, which is great. Yeah,
he's great. He's amazing. So the first one is called like Gray Matter and other selections from
Night Shift. The second one is called the lawnmower man and other selections from Night Shift.
So anyway, I downloaded those two things and I was listening to them and they're great. John Glover
is just amazing. The writing, of course, is some of King's best. I mean, Night Shift is,
yeah, you know, you're getting you're getting quitter's ink, you're getting the ledge,
you're getting Jerusalem's lot, you're getting the I think the 10 o 'clock peoples from Night Shift,
you're getting lawnmower man, you're getting gray matter, you're getting sometimes they come back.
I mean, it's just loaded with the bookie man is one of the stories. So I highly recommend those
books on audio. Each one of them is well worth the credit. And they're like three and a half hours
long each, which is great. Because you know, the big problem sometimes with an audio book, it's like
17 hours and you're like, Jesus Christ man, I just kind of want to go to sleep to a little bit of
something. The stand, the stand was over 40 hours. Yeah. So anyway, it's worth getting the one
thing that pisses me off is with audible is like, guys, can you not cut the chapters? Can you not take
the time to cut the chapters properly? You know, it'll be like chapter four. And in the middle of
chapter four, the next story starts. So if you want to start at the beginning of that story, you have to
go to chapter four, skim through it, figure out where the other story and it's annoying. It's like,
guys, take 10 seconds and do this, please. They'll also, when you're listening in the car, it'll say
like chapter six on the screen and in the narrator, we'll go to chapter four. That happens all the time.
It's it's very. It's the only thing they do is put books online and they can't do it. Anyway,
those are worth picking up. But in listening to those, I went on Google and I was like,
is the, is the, um, book, the Boogeyman harm movie from 20, oh, five or something. I forget when it came
out. Is that based on the Stephen King story? I don't think it is. So I looked that up and it's not as
far as I could tell. Then I saw that there's another movie called The Boogeyman from 1983. I think it
was or 81 or something. That also was not based on the Stephen King story. Then I saw there's a short
film called The Boogeyman that is based on the Stephen King story. It's just 30 minutes long or something.
And I was like, what is this? Is this some fan made this? Then I realized it was from the early 80s
during that period where Stephen King was leasing out all of his stories for a dollar a piece.
Right. I actually thought he still did that, but maybe not. Maybe he still does. I don't know. Then I
saw that you could, that there was a video of it that you could buy and I went and looked and lo and
behold, found out there was a two volume VHS collection released in the 80s. It was called Stephen
King's Night Shift Collection. The first one has The Boogeyman and adaptation of The Boogeyman on it
and an adaptation of the woman in the room or something like that. I forget what it's called.
The second one has an adaptation of Children of the Corn on it, a short adaptation of that.
And then another thing that King didn't write, but it's a hard short that's supposedly pretty cool.
But I found both of these on VHS. These were official releases. And the reason these three
stories based on the King, these adaptations of the King stories were released was because these were
the three that King deemed worthwhile. They met his expectations and I guess you'll add them to be
released on VHS. So I immediately went online and bought two copies of the first volume and one
copy of the second. The Children of the Corn one goes for a lot more money.
And I was like, this is so cool. Like as a horror collector and as a horror enthusiast,
how can I not own these? You know, and it's good. When they arrive, you know, it's going to inspire me
to hook the VCR back up and break out some of the VHS tapes and stuff. But I was just really excited.
I was like, this is a really, really cool little thing that I never knew existed. And like,
what how perfect in time for Halloween? Some 1981 low budget adaptation of
fresh Stephen King stories. Like, I'm in. I can't wait to watch these things.
I'm curious to hear what they're like. I mean, I was the budget for them $100 or a million or what?
Like, that's what I'm curious about. No, no, no way. I can't imagine. I mean,
these days did win awards. The book, I think the Boogeyman won awards from the Academy of Arts
and Motion Pictures. But, you know, they're probably like, you know, I mean, tens of thousands of
dollars, you know, whatever, like, you know, I'm imagining they're going to look a lot like that Tom
noon in movie. What happened was sure. Yeah, like that kind of thing, you know. So,
but I'm excited to watch this when they arrive. So I'll keep you posted. But go online and check
them out. Like, they're not easy to come by. So I would say, what'd you get it for on DVD?
I bought the VHS tapes. Oh, the VHS. So DVD transfers didn't exist. I bought.
I bought. So for the first volume, I got one for like $11 .50. Like $11 .50. I got the other one for
like 10 bucks. The second one that had the children of the court adaptation, the most affordable,
decently shaped in shape copy I could find was like 20 bucks. Yeah. After that, they started
getting up around like 35, 36. And I was like, yeah, you know, that's a little more than I would
want to spend on something I've never seen. And also, both of these stories aren't Stephen King
adaptations. The second one, I'm completely unfamiliar with, but I found one for like 20. And I was
like, okay, they're also the kind of things too. If you like them on eBay or put them on your watch list,
I immediately got offers from sellers like because nobody knows these things exist. So they're
super rare, but they're also just kind of sitting there. So yeah, that said, I'd snatch them up.
I think it's worth it. I got I'm about ready to transfer my stuff that I have on sale over to eBay,
because Amazon has just broken me. I got an email the other day that was like we're removing
13 of your listings. They've been up for years. Why? Very strongly worded language like, you know,
you're breaking copyright codes by doing this. You need to write us an explanation so that we don't
pursue further legal action. Or if you want if you want to keep them up on the site, like on and on
on. I'm reading this. I'm getting nervous. I'm wondering what's going on. Then not even 24 hours
later, another email saying, sorry, we sent this to you in error. Your posts are back up. It's like
that's it. Okay. They just they're we enjoy we're talking the other day. Like if you click on vinyl,
if you're in the vinyl section of the app and you click on box sets, it takes you to a broken link.
vinyl box set and it has four years. Who's running this is one of the this is the biggest company.
There is. Wow. It's absurd. And anytime you list an item on the app, I go, I want to sell this
copy of purple rain. You click sell and a picture of a wounded dog comes up and it says, oops,
something went wrong. But that actually is confirmation that your listing has gone up. That's how that's
how faulty the Amazon app is. And it's nothing works, Joe. Nothing works. Yeah, I know it sucks, man.
It sucks. It sucks. Anyway. Oh, God. Well, anyway, that's all that's scary stuff for you.
Let me take you on a lighter note over to the movie. Corn. I rewatch. Cornhole. Cornhole. I rewatched
tombstone because I made an appearance on the Val cast, which we have discussed in the show before.
Joe did one as well. It is actually called We Love Val is the name of the podcast. And it is hosted
by Mike Greenwood had a super fun time chatting with him. Nice guy. Nice guy. It looks like the podcast
just started posting and airing. So I assume it will my end Joe's episode will appear in the coming
weeks or months. But yeah, I discussed tombstones. So I rewatched it. It's fantastic. You know,
and we discussed a little bit on that show, the kind of troubled history of it where the guy who
wrote it was going to direct it. He got fired a month into production. Kurt Russell said, I'm
going to direct this thing. Can we get a ghost director who can just put on the thing so that when
studio execs come by, they think there's a professional director here, but I'm going to direct it.
They'd be too nervous to let me do it, but I'm going to do it. So apparently most of tombstone was
directed by Kurt Russell, which is crazy. George P Cosmatos is the guy who's credited as the director,
the father of the guy who directed Mandy. And he was like on set, but apparently didn't do too much.
And look, whoever did it, it's kind of like the poltergeist mystery. Was it Spielberg,
was it Toe Bay Hoops, but it's a really, really good Western. I think one of the best
Westerns made in the 90s. It's not on a level of unforgiven. I'm not even sure it's up there
with quick and the dead, but tombstone is great. It's very old fashioned in a really good way.
Kilmer does steal the picture. He's great as Doc holiday. Fun fact for you, Joe. Willem Defoe was cast
as Doc holiday. And as they were about to start shooting, the studio said no because he had been in
last temptation of Christ seven years prior. They were like, he's too controversial.
The different world, man. Different time. Defoe would have been great too. But Kilmer is really
good. And that role made, I feel like that role made Kilmer. So that was for sure. It definitely
let everybody know, okay, this guy's a great actor. I also Mike sent me a clip of Cisco and Ebert
where they were talking, they were both loved the movie, but they were talking about how
annoyed they were that they had to chase it down because the studio wasn't screening it for critics.
Movie's gone on to become one of the few classic westerns of the 90s.
Even back then, they were pulling the bullshit with the screenings.
It's great. Every little part down to Billy Bob Thornton as a much, he's much heavier in the movie,
but down to him as like a drunk annoying gambler. I almost expected Heshie to come in and stab him.
It's a very similar scene to Casino. But yeah, down to the smallest part, you recognize everybody.
It's like there's an old man with three lines and it's Charlton Heston. You know, it's like
super overcast in a great way. You got Bean and you got Bill Paxton. You got Sam Elliott.
It's a great movie. The only thing that doesn't work is the Dana Delaney subplot where he's
Russell's cheating on his wife because she's a drug addict with Dana Delaney. It's awful.
But everything else is great. Check it out. He never saw it. Tums dumb.
I'll stick with episodic since that's kind of where I was at with the King video.
I watched the new season of Titans so far. They're releasing it. Based on the comic book,
The Teen Titans DC, which was Robin after, you know, it's kind of like Robin's side group.
So it's Robin Aqualad. Well, in the comics was Robin Aqualad.
Aqualad? Yeah, that was what young Aqualad was the Aqualad son was called.
They still call him Aqualad? He's not on the show. So now, okay. Superboy is on the show though.
The show crew is this third season. It's Dick Grayson has moved on from being Robin. He now
play in the He's not Nightwing. The Robin in this season is Jason Todd.
First episode opens basically with him spoilers with him getting beaten to death by the Joker.
And then spoilers. Be returning as the Red Hood, which is the death of the family storyline.
Beast boys in it. Star fires in it. Black fires in it.
Superboys in it. It's good. I really liked it. I like the guy playing Bruce Wayne.
I think this season's been awesome. I've only seen parts of the other seasons, but I always like
the show. It's very gritty, very dark, very hard R, I would say, which is so interesting,
because the Titans is a brand where they have this super hard R rated Titans.
Then they have an animated show called Teen Titans that's for like, you know,
tweens and whatever. Then they have a show called Teen Titans Go that's for like little children.
That's a comedy. So I can't imagine like you're a tiny child,
and you just saw the Teen Titans Go movie, which is absolutely absurd.
There's like cameos from like Beetlejuice in it and stuff.
And then you see this live action one. And you're like, Mommy, I want to watch Titans in your
mom's like, you're not allowed to watch this Titan. You just don't understand.
That happened to me as a kid with Tarzan. I felt so betrayed, because there was like the R rated
Tarzan that had come out. And then there was like the skin flick Tarzan that had like
tits in it. And then there was like the Tarzan I was allowed to watch. And I was so confused as
to why I couldn't watch certain Tarzan's. Also, what is it? There's Grace Stoke with Chris
Lambert. There's the one with Bo Derek, right, which is I think is like the nudie one, right?
It's off core. Yeah. And then later you get Phil Collins's animated Tarzan, which sucks.
And I think well, there's the Tarzan. There's like the
yeah, I don't know. Yeah, it's weird. So, you know, so I feel like if I was a kid,
that's how this week. But also too, you'd feel like this would be like that with Batman too.
You'd be like, well, I can't I watch the Batman movie, Mommy.
Right. And she's like, because he says fucking it and like stabs a guy through the neck.
You get these kids hooked on the superheroes and then they're demanding to see
suicide squad or whatever. It must be a nightmare. But I don't know. A lot of parents.
I mean, it's great. It's brilliant. Look, it's brilliant on DC's part because they're like,
hey, man, we're going to we're going to retain the as they grow older.
Yeah. We'll have we'll stuff stuff for every age group. Don't worry about it.
But but anyway, the new season is really, really terrific, very well done. Revenous and quite
reminiscent to me of the later seasons of Gotham, which I thought were stellar.
And the guy, I don't know what is the actor's name, but the guy playing scarecrow and this is
awesome. All right. It's played a great villain. So that's that. Check it out.
I saw over the edge, which was playing at the New Beverly. I just rented it cheap off Amazon. But
a lot of directors have cited this as a big influence. It was one of Kurt Cobain's favorite films.
And I had never seen it. It's done by Jonathan Kaplan, who did like the accused and unlawful entry
and broke down palace and a lot of thrillers later on. But this came out in 79. It stars an
extremely young Matt Dillon. And it was a huge influence on Dazed and Confused, which you learn
right away. They've got the exact same shots in some cases like the guy putting on the big headphones
in his bed was it's like they must just, you know, take a picture of it and done the exact same scene.
Excuse me. Sorry. No, it's fine. It's super entertaining. It's basically a movie about kids from
the wrong side of the tracks. They live in this kind of weird community where it's like mostly juvenile
delinquents, not really explained or if it was, I missed it. But it's just one of those teen movies where
they kind of go from party to party. And it's like doing the fly on the wall thing of just like showing
you teenagers as they are, hooking up, drinking, doing drugs, playing pranks on each other.
And then at the end, it takes on a much more serious tone as all the parents are in the school,
ranting and raving about their children. They just don't understand. And the kids pull up on their
bikes. And they're like, let's lock these assholes in here and burn this place to the fucking ground.
So the end of over the edge caused a lot of controversy. And the movie was very controversial in
its day because they were like, this is going to inspire kids to, you know, fight back. But there's
great, there's great stuff in it. I mean, at the end, look, if you're not a parent, it is thrilling to
watch a bunch of kids on on bikes to torment the adults, you know, like I'm sure if I was a kid,
I would have loved that a lot of those movie too. It's super entertaining and it's got a great soundtrack.
It's one of those, our 70s and 80s soundtracks where you can tell they ran out of money because
they'll play the same song like four times. But the songs are awesome. Like it's like cheap trick
surrender is one that you hear a bunch. The cars, the remones, definitely a great kind of slice of
life, little movie. You definitely feel the influence on days to confuse in a very big way. If you're
interested, check it out. I thought it was really entertaining. Did we review trick -or -treat on
this show already? No, I don't think so. Is that one we want to save for Halloween and maybe do it
as an episode and streaming? We could, sure. I don't even remember trick -or -treat.
I saw it. The anthology trick -or -treat. All right, I'll save it. I'll save it. Then in that case,
I only have one more. A little episodic project from the late 80s, early 90s, called 227.
Been watching 227 again and man, am I enjoying it? What a wonderful show, what a wonderful cast
was. A man has been off of 227 or the other way around? It's not. It's didn't either. It's just
everybody thinks that because one is Martha Gibbs, Martha Gibbs, and the other is Sherman
Helmsley. You think they must be connected in some way, but they're not. Everybody's wonderful
on the show. It's a great show. I never knew this. It was based on a play called 227. You can see that
in the first couple episodes because the first couple episodes, the sort of customs or culture
of the building and the neighborhood are a lot more prominent or present, like Rose and Mary
gossiping on the stoop all day to each other and Pearl sitting in the window all day. That sort of
thing, it's great. It really captures the community of a building in the city. This takes place in
DC. I just really like the show. I love the cat. You got a young, um, uh, for Christ sakes, my brain
today, Jesus God. I sucked. The woman that directed one night, Miami, Regina King, Regina King playing
the daughter. She's great in it. Everybody's great on the show. Yeah. Eventually you get a
Barry Sobel into the mix. I haven't gotten that far yet, but okay. He comes in later. I remember
that as a kid, though. Um, but let's stop beating around the bush here. You come for 227. You stay
for Jack A. I mean, he's hitting grand slams in every one of these episodes. I'm like, how was this
woman not a bigger comedic actress? She's, I watched an interview with her where they did like one of
those reunions on like good morning America two years ago, whatever. Yeah. And she talks about the,
it might have been Brendan Tertik, Tutikov, Tertik, whatever fuckers name was. I forget who the
executive is with that she said, but she said that like, like when they were doing the pilot, she was,
she started doing a little bit like, oh, oh, man, you know, like that stuff. And he was like, do more
of that. And she was like, are you serious? Because she was like, this is absurd. He's like, no,
do it. It's great. And he was right. And she nails it. And like, it's, it's an insane performance
that she sticks the landing on every time. It's up there with like, it's up there with red foxes,
Fred Samford. If you read Fred Sanford on paper, what red fox was going to do, you'd be like, you're
out of your mind. This is insane. This will never work. And it worked. Same with George Jefferson.
If you, like Sherman, Sherman Hemsley's walk, it's insane. And he said that was the whole
character. He found it with the walk. He was like, it's the walk. Like that's that guy. That's who
this guy is. Right. And Jack is right there, man. Like she like literally tiptoes around the set in
every scene. She makes these noises constantly. Yeah, it's crazy, but it works. And it's amazing.
It's brilliant. I literally laugh out loud when I watch the show when she comes in. I get excited.
And not that I don't laugh at anybody else, but she, I mean, she's just awesome. She, she won an
Emmy for that role, but still it's like, and she's been on TV forever. It's just like she works and
works and works, but she never achieved that like big star quality, which sucks. I mean, she's,
she was the had to shove her day for sure. And she never appeared in movies or anything like that.
She's in some movies. Well, she also said, too, that like repossessed, was she?
She's in ladybugs, but yeah, ladybugs, too, that she didn't want like she, you know, that
she wanted to be a serious actor and like it would disappoint her that everybody wanted her to do
that thing from 227. So that might have been a two that she was like, look, I'm just not going to
do it. Again, I'm going to go do roles that appeal to me. And maybe those roles just came in
in under the radar productions or, you know, right. Let's say I have things, but I've worked with her
a couple times once on two bro girls and then twice on cool kids. And she is that person in real life.
She walks on with all that energy, cracking jokes to everybody she passes,
anybody above a six walks by. She leans over and is like, who's this good -looking man right?
You know, I mean, she's, she's great. She's a, she just makes everybody feel good and special. And
I hope she works forever because she's. Did she play a, did she play a Sandra type character on?
Either of those shows or was it a different type of character? Cool kids. She played David
Hungry's ex -wife who was now married to Rick Foxx, the old NBA great. Oh wait, that's right. I remember
that episode. And then we brought her back and Rick Foxx back at the end. Tony Rock played their
son. But that was a little more of a, that was definitely more of a grounded type of. It was on
cool kids. She was, she was definitely, I mean, on bro, she was amputate up way more. But she's,
she's, she's the best. I'm a big fan. I'm excited to watch her M .E. speech, which I've just
bookmarked here on my computer because it's, I'm sure it's funny. Jack K, we love you. I saw a movie
I've long wanted to watch called Little Murders. I've not been able to find it. And it is currently
on the Criterion channel directed by the great Alan Arkin who has a hilarious cameo
and written by Jules Fifer who did carnal knowledge, which is a masterpiece. He also wrote the script
for Popeye, which is not a masterpiece, but which many people like.
Little Murders is insane. It reminded me of Where's Papa, which I talked about on the show,
which had like the five minute gang rape sequence that I talked about at length.
Made for comedic values.
Played for broad comedic values.
Where's Papa? People have been kind of catching up with after the death of George Siegel. I think it's
aired on TCM a few more times and stuff. But Little Murders is every bit as dark.
It is Elliott Gould who is playing a man who I related to so much who just has
zero zest for life anymore. He's not interested in anything. Super depressed and detached.
He's getting beaten by street tuffs and this woman runs up and stops the men from beating Elliott
Gould and he just gets up and walks away. And then she runs after him and she's like,
can I get a thank you for saving your life? And he's like, oh, I'm sorry. You know, like it's so dark
that it barely registers as comedy. But she is so used to men bending over backwards for her
because she's a beautiful woman that she hates that this guy won't give her the time of day and
becomes fixated on him and wanting to like make him a man who can feel.
So she brings her home to her family. Vincent Gardini plays her dad in a extremely funny,
extremely funny supporting role by Vincent Gardini. He also goes home to his parents. He's
basically trying to unlock this like why am I the way I am. He goes home to his parents who are
extremely weird and her parents are extremely weird. Wedding crashes clearly took a page from this
because they've got the exact same character. You know, that teenage kid who like might rape,
Vince Vaughn. Yeah, that's a very very strange comedy. It's just one of the most unnerving things
I've ever seen. Like I remember squirming in the theater in those scenes. That that character is
stolen a hundred percent from this movie, Little Murders. Gould's parents are played by John Randolph
who's the great actor who plays Clark Rizwold's dad in Christmas vacation.
Doris Roberts plays his mom who was also in Christmas vacation, but then she plays,
you know, she's on everybody loves Raymond as well. Wonderful. It is a who's who of great beloved
New York character actors and then at the end, Arkin comes in himself to do this like five -minute
monologue about what a disgusting cesspool New York City is and how he doesn't want to live here.
He doesn't even care who dies anymore. The body's just keep piling up. It is so nihilistic, so bleak.
In the moment, Elliott Gould decides, all right, I'm going to be a man who's emotionally connected,
a man who's checked in. I'm going to be the kind of guy you want me to be. The second he finishes
deciding that his girlfriend is shot by a sniper's assassin bullet and dies.
I mean, it's wild and then the movie literally ends with Elliott Gould and other characters
shooting out the window. And finally, Elliott Gould finds happiness in his life by firing a gun
at strangers on the street below. I don't know what else to say. Either you want to see that movie
or you don't. I want to see it. It's madness. It's on Criterion Channel. It's in the New York classic
section. You got to check this thing out and do it soon because it's been impossible to find my whole
life. So wild and very funny. You certainly get why it's hard to find these movies because a date
it doesn't even really cover it. I mean, they're antisocial movies, really. So it's something to see.
I'll tell you, I liked it a lot. All right. There's your goddamn movie corner.
Quick shout out to Mike Patton from Faith No More. One of my favorite bands of all time.
Apparently, they just canceled all their tour dates because he's dealing with mental issues that
were exacerbated by COVID -19 in the lockdown. And he said he does not feel he can give 100 %
and both Mr. Bungle and Faith No More, two of his bands that had tour dates planned support him.
But I'm sad to hear that, man. Very sad to hear that. Hope he's okay. All right. Candyman.
The Candyman. Yeah, I guess you're not near to costumes.
Right. No, it is near to costumes. It is in a way. It's a continuation of the original film and the
Candyman legend that certainly pops up in here. But it's also very much does its own thing and
definitely has its own kind of tone. There's some some comedic elements to it that I thought worked
even when they felt sort of off. But off from what the tone of the movie was, I'm saying like there's
there's actually like jokes and quips and the thing that feel like a gossip girl or something.
Finally, finally, a movie realizes that comic relief can come in the form in a horror movie,
can come in the form of a real character. Yeah. And not in the form of a gag that makes no sense.
That character in this movie is the, I don't remember anybody's name, I apologize, except for
Vanessa Williams who plays the, who returns from the original Candyman.
Not Vanessa Williams, Joe. No, her name is Vanessa something Williams. That's her name.
She's billed as Vanessa Williams in the credits. Because I remember I was like, wait,
Vanessa Williams is in this. All right. Well, it's not, then it's the different Vanessa Williams. I
guess. Yes. Okay. All right. Yeah. All right. I thought, I thought now you're maybe talking about
the lady from from sideways. You're talking about Vanessa. Okay. Vanessa Williams. Why wouldn't you
change your name? I don't know. By the way, that's, that's not the only minute. There's like a,
I think there's a third Vanessa Williams. Anyway, if there's a huge, and not only a huge actress,
but a black female actress named Vanessa Williams, I do not get what this woman is doing going by
that name. It makes she was first. I think, maybe she was first, maybe the other Vanessa Williams.
All right. Oh, yeah. She said, yeah, all right. She looked, I thought she was 30. That was
another confusing thing when she, when she goes to see, when he goes to see this woman, I'm like,
is this a supernatural touch? This lady's his mom because she looks like she's the same age.
Yeah. She looked in Christ. She looks like Jesus Christ. What are you drinking? Child's blood or
something? Anyway, um, point being, uh, that character comes in the form of the, the comedic
relief is the is the gay brother of the female lead. And he's great. And they make him,
they give him some funny business to do. And it's, but it's real. And it's grounded. And it's good.
It's, you know, and yeah, he's, he's very funny. I was even referring to the victims,
the early victims are all kind of extreme caricatures so that you want them to die. But there's
that guy who's dating. He's like a art dealer and he's dating this extremely young intern.
And they get back to his apartment. And he's like, we get it. You like joy division, whatever.
I mean, there were laughs in the movie, but they felt true to the characters. That's correct.
Yeah, I agree with that. Um, it does pick up, however many years after the original,
it is a direct sequel. Uh, and it does set the stage for a new franchise. Or to continue the franchise,
I should, I should say, but it is a direct sequel from the original, which crazy is,
I want, this is not it. They do not hide this in the film.
Which I don't understand why they didn't because I chose to watch the new one and then go
back and watch the original. I didn't want to watch the original first and then go watch the
one. You could do either. I liked doing it that way because in the middle, there's major spoilers
here in theory. In the middle of the movie, when you, it is revealed that he is, that the mother,
his, when he finally goes to see his mother, it's the woman from the original film whose baby candy man
takes. And then you realize he's the baby from the original candy man. That was a huge twist.
That was a huge reveal. But here's the thing. If you would watch the original candy man first and
went into the movie to see this, they call him by the same name through the entire movie. So it's
not really hidden or anything. It's, it's, you would know immediately. Oh, that's the baby from the
first movie. Uh, I was a little confused as to why do it that way instead of springing like a
twist for everybody. Maybe they thought it was obvious and they felt there was no need to hide it.
I don't know. I love that they tell the Virginia Madsen story at the beginning of this thing to connect
the stories. Um, and when you could do go back and watch the original, there is still that commentary of
you know, all of a sudden, there's an issue. The cops are interested in a murder because a white
woman got attacked. Um, and this, the secrets of this black neighborhood and whatever and the
neighborhood itself were, were, were buried. Yeah. Uh, by, by, by the white, you know, sort of patriarchy.
I thought those things are in the original. Um, they're a little more muted in the original, I think.
Um, they're, they're, they're pretty out there, not out there, meaning crazy, meaning out in front of
everything in this movie. Um, I think at times they handled the conversation of that very, very well.
I, I like that there's a, you know, right off the bat, the lead female is saying like, you know,
that's what, that's what these neighborhoods do. They, you know, they, they come in and they build
up these high rises and push all the black people out. And that's what happened.
Yeah. In the neighborhood that candy, the candy man's story is from. And then the, the white
boyfriend of her brother goes kind of like this neighborhood and then realizes, oh,
shit, I shouldn't have just said that. Right. And I thought that that was like kind of an interesting
balanced commentary. Like, hey, man, even people that are against this are, are in their own way in,
in theory, contributing to the issue, right? It's a very hard line to walk. You want to live. Yeah.
In a nice neighborhood, but by living in a nice neighborhood, you actually kind of contribute
to the problem in your own way. They also talk about that with artists too, you know, artists going
in and then address the hypocrisy of that very well. It's also like anytime in a movie I'm seeing
people talk about their art. I'm like, am I supposed to be talking about what I do in the, in these
self -important serious tones? Because they always do in movies. And me and my friends do not talk about
what we do that way. But maybe that's how you get people to take you seriously. I don't know.
I thought, I will say this. I thought that, now look, I understand that everything Peale's company is
doing is, is a commentary on society. Yeah. And in, in some ways, it's retribution and finally doing
what needs to be done for non -white dominated cinema that is not done enough. I get all that.
I did think that the white characters in this were a little cliched. I thought that they could have
been a little less over the top assholes that are being taught lessons throughout the film. I
particularly thought it was ridiculous when it was like the five high school, caddy, high school
girls. And they're doing the candy man thing in the bathroom. And the only one that leaves
because she doesn't want to be a part of it is the Asian girl. And then you're left with four white
girls. Right. And then a black girl comes in. And then they, they kind of bully up on the black girl
a little bit. And then the black girl goes in the stall. And then the four white girls get killed.
I was kind of like, guys, I get it. But like at this point, you're, you're, you're even breaking the
rules of candy man. Yeah, candy man doesn't seem to give a shit who brought him there. He's
there. And now he's going to kill people. Right. So, um, and then, you know, the white cop at the end is
like, so we're going to agree on a lie here, you know, and then he gets taken care. It's everybody is
kind of at their most evil who's white. But it's, you know, that's, that's the state of the world.
And I get it. And I, I'm the, the fate of black people and horror up to this day, including
quiet place two, the most notable example of bringing in Jim and Hansu to kill him in five seconds.
They probably wanted a little bit of, you know, hey, we're going to, we're going to treat the white
characters that way too. And good for them. But, um, yeah, it's, it has so much to say about race,
but it doesn't really pick a theme that it wants to focus on fully. So when people would say it's
trying to do too much, I was like, well, at a time when movies are doing so little, is that a bad
thing? But you see it and you do feel it. It's, it's, there's so much going on in it that it's hard
to really emotionally latch on to anything. But it's making a lot of good points. It's just not
making them in a super cohesive way throughout, even though I enjoyed the movie a lot.
I, there was, there was, there were, I really liked the movie. I think it was out of, obviously,
out of all the candy man films, it's second only to the original. You know, I tried watching
farewell to the flesh. I was not very invested in it. And I think I tried watching day of the dead
once. And I couldn't have cared less. Um, it's a great flick. Uh, it's something I want to own.
Absolutely. Um, and it's something I want to see again. Absolutely. I really liked it. I was my,
my, my one criticism is, well, it's, it's not one criticism. It was overstuffed, as you just said,
there was no need to bring in this new candy man that there was, there was no point to that whatsoever.
Yeah. Cabrini green, uh, which is the neighborhood where the original candy man dies.
This one suddenly there are five candy men, all who, all of which who have died in Cabrini green,
um, I get it. I understand the concept of the legacy of violence towards when they formed the
boys to men style singing group was when I really took issue with the, the tone of the film.
Yeah. I mean, it's, it's, I, I understand the commentary of that of like this is something that
happens throughout history to black men or black people period. I get that. But when you're trying to,
when you're trying to maintain a certain look in certain features of the candy man, meaning the
bees and the hook hand and all that. So just stick with the original candy man and make it that his
vengeance is for all violence before and after him to people in his position or whatever. There's a
simplified way to do it. Um, you know, it was, I got to kick out of the Tony Todd return at the end.
You know, that is a, a nice, a nice surprise. They CGIed the shit out of his face.
We didn't understand it because he's old. Was that the point?
Yeah, I guess they just wanted to make him look like he did in the first, the original film,
I guess, but and because he had bees all over his face. So I guess that's what you had that,
which in the original movie was real bees. Right. Yeah. How did you do that? He's like, I,
they put bees on me. Yeah.
So, but you know, like it was like, you just didn't need that. You didn't need this other candy man
character. And then when also, when you realize at the end of the film, that the point of candy man is
to be this anti hero who is the sort of, who is, who is here to bring retribution
or to avenge all the wrongful deaths in this neighborhood and all the horrors that have happened
in this neighborhood, you go, that's pretty cool. But then you go, then why is he killing like young
black children that summon him? Like the guy's sister. Right. Uh, the, the, the laundry man guy's sister
when he shows the flashback and you see that it's like, wouldn't he not kill? That doesn't make,
that didn't make the discussion in the original too. You know, like when I watched that, um,
horror noir, which I think is getting a sequel on shutter, which is a fantastic documentary about
the role of black people in horror. Um, they talked about that. Like why is candy man coming back
in the first one and killing black and white people alike? So I thought they would, they would
address that and update that and this one and they kind of didn't. But the big kill scenes for the most
part, the, the young artsy couple, right, the young girls, the, uh, the old snooty white critic. Yeah,
it made sense. It made sense. It made sense. It made sense for most of them. I didn't get, yeah. But,
but and then the other thing was, and this is just to me, bad writing, to have that
asshole cop come in at the end, yeah, sit in the car with the fiance of the guy who becomes candy man
and the main character in this who also plays Morpheus in the, in the, uh, right, new matrix.
To have the cop come into the car and do this James Bond villain monologue where he reveals all the
evil that they will do to cover this up was number one lazy writing. But then she goes,
can I look at myself in the mirror and she summons candy man to kill the cops, right? Yeah. Now,
again, two things here. We're not making any sense because the way this has worked throughout the
movie is if you summon him, he kills you and everybody around you, right? So we're breaking that rule.
For the second time in the movie, the first time is when he kills only the white girls
and not the black girl in the bathroom, it, you know, it just doesn't really add up.
And then you think that's a racial thing and then you realize it's not because he kills the black
girl in the other part who doesn't do anything wrong except as a 13 -year -old do a candy man summoning.
Yeah. But what my bigger issue with that was is like what the cop would not do this in the car,
he would do it in the interrogation room. Why the fuck is this scene not taking place in an interrogation
room where there's a fucking two -way mirror and she just ignores him and starts saying candy man
into the mirror and then your finale is the most awesome candy man ripping through a police
precinct finale like like in Terminator when he comes into the precinct and what's it all up?
Why would he not do that? Especially for this moment in time, the audience would be cheering so much
at the candy man ripping through all these cops, it would just be such a thrill to watch and it
doesn't happen. I agree. What I was thinking in that scene is why is she saying candy man so slowly?
She, the cop, after if she does it twice the cop goes, what? What are you doing back there?
Then she goes, candy man. He's like, hey, what's happening in that backseat? Why do you keep saying
the word candy man? It's like you would go candy man, candy man, you know, you'd get through it.
Also, lots of little moments that you're just like, what's going on? Why are you doing that?
Why are you doing that? Just take out also two. Guys, there are literally phone cases that have mirrors on
them. This woman works in art, she comes in in every scene. She is dressed to the fucking
nines and they also make it a character trait that she is very concerned about the way she is presenting
to these other people in the art world and that she's got to keep a face on because the commentary is
because it's harder for a black woman to work her way up the ranks and she's got to play the game.
Maybe have her just take her phone out and she's got a mirror case on it. And again,
ignores the cop and just says it five times into the mirror phone. I mean, this is like five minutes
of thought and brainstorming. It's going to be a three writers on it. Nobody caught this. Nobody caught
this. Come on, man, like that, that's just crazy. Maybe I thought maybe it's a budget thing. Maybe
they can't afford to do a precinct shoot. They got it. But still, there were other ways around this.
The movie had a $25 million budget, which for horror is huge in a world where Blumhouse is trying to
keep things five. But it's got a good budget. It looks great. I love like very well -directed sets,
you know, like even just like walking down a hallway in this movie looks visually cool.
I'm very excited to see what made it cost it does next. Cass was all really great when she does
Vax. The Marvels. The Marvels, yeah, we discussed that. The Coleman Domingo, who was also in
Zola recently this year, I've started seeing him a lot of stuff recently, but I think he's going
to be a big star. At least a great character actor, but he's the guy who played the laundromat.
He was awesome. He was awesome. Love that guy. Everybody was great. I love the lead guy. I thought
everybody was great in it. He's exactly who you want, like telling you the legend of the Candyman.
He's got a great voice, great vibe. Yaya Abdul -Mateen, the second is the name of Candyman himself.
Who is great? He's got a great presence as well. Everybody in this movie is good. We'll go on to
bigger things. He's just like, what's up? He's stung by a B. I like watching him deteriorate
too. I like watching him deteriorate too. It was really gross seeing the shitty dub his neck.
Nobody is saying anything to him. I know. He lives with his fiance. She's not like,
what the fuck is wrong with your hand and neck? Finally, one lady is like, are you okay?
And you're like, yes, why is nobody saying this? There's some weird choices for sure. He's sitting
scab like the entire, not that there was that many people in the theater, but everybody looked away
from the screen like it was hard to watch. But yeah, there's so much great stuff in it that you wish
it was a little bit better. And maybe we'll get a Candyman too. I think we will. I think we absolutely
will. Like I said, it was good enough that I thought it was a very worthy sequel to the original.
I really enjoyed it overall. You know, look, a lot of horror movies have some logic issues,
but these did not take me out of this one at all. I thought it was so well acted, so well
directed. And the horror scenes were so worthwhile that I was just like, I can get past the other
stuff. And to understand why sometimes people could see him and other times people couldn't.
But you know, it was also one of those things. I talked to a kid that saw it the same day I did
at the at a comedy at the stand in New York. We were just talking about it. And every point I made
of like, why didn't I get this part? He kind of had a, he had a rational thing for it. I was like,
okay, this is definitely one I need to watch again, because maybe it's one of those things where it's like,
no, I get it. Okay, I missed that. I didn't quite catch that or whatever. Well, it's 90 minutes. So,
like the these moments where you're kind of confused, it's like, well, maybe leave in another
scene or two in, but you never know the whole process of a movie. Maybe some stuff didn't work or
I don't know. But for me, I always love a 90 minute movie, but this one I could have gone for another
10, 15 where certain things were explained a little better. However, it all works great. The stuff with
the puppets that they show you in the trailer is, it's such a, it's a cool, cheap and like great
visual way to show you these flashbacks in a way you've kind of never seen before, haven't seen in
a long time. They do a lot of great stuff visually for sure. And I will say, as much as I thought the
new candy man, not the guy that becomes him, but the, the, the, the, like, candy man throughout the movie
until that happens. Yeah. Was unnecessary. You guys scary as shit. I thought he was great. Really
fucking creepy. And yeah. And I want to say this in watching the original film afterwards, it did
reframe the, this one and it didn't make it make a little more sense to me overall, which is why
you might want to watch them that way. And in watching the bonus features of the original film,
you know, as much as I can complain about like sort of thinly constructed white villains, Tony Todd
talks about how they had to cut the interracial kiss out of the, the first movie because that was
too much for audiences that was deemed by the studio. And he goes, as it was okay to have a black man
with bees all over him, but me kissing a white woman was too much. Yeah. Which is outrageous
to think of that in 1991, this is, I mean, you're, at that point, you're almost 30 years out from the
first interracial kiss on Star Trek for Christ sakes. Like, right. I mean, jungle fever came out
these year after candy man. So it's, it's so crazy. Anyway, folks, my hog is up for candy man.
My hog is up too. And I hope they do do a sequel because they set up a lot of great stuff.
The cast is great, the director's great. And I want to see it. Did you know, Joe, I wanted to mention
this before we go that there was in response to the success of Freddie versus Jason across over film,
candy man versus leprechaun was developed. Yes. Tony Todd rejected the idea after reading the script
saying, quote, I will never be involved in something like that. And this guy, you know, who probably
is a working actor. He's not a wealthy man. But yeah, it's, I'd love to read the script for that.
And it also helps you kind of realize what a bullet we dodged with his franchise. I mean,
candy man has been kept pretty classy and pretty contained. And yeah, I could go for two more of these.
I really could. I hope they, I hope they dig into this a little further. And maybe these questions
that haven't been answered for us are coming. Perhaps, perhaps, or maybe we're dumb. We missed it.
That's also always a possibility. Anyway, folks, that's our show. Thanks for supporting us. Thanks
for sticking with us through these tough turbulent times. We hope we bring a little light to your life.
Thank you, Emily for all you do. Thank you for the Facebook group for staying so enthusiastic.
Pat and I hope to drop into the Facebook watch party sooner or later when we're able to and we're
excited to see people coming together through the podcast and just brightening each other's lives
and, and, and meeting and becoming friends. And, and all that sort of thing, it's, it's touching.
We'll do a live show again as soon as we can as soon as all this madness is over.
And that's it for us. We'll see you next time. Yeah, love that love that you guys are doing that.
And I will just be just a cut off of a perfect ending. Just I got to do it.
I got to do it. Well, it's the ending we do every time, Joe. I mean, it's yeah, it's fine. I'll get to it.
Thank you for doing that. I'm going to drop in. I had plans in the last one. I do want to shout out,
even though I did it earlier, the We Love Val podcast. Check it out. It's discussing the man,
the movies. I had a great time doing it. Me and Joe are appearing on that show coming up.
And we'll see you in hell.