I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear that sweet talk about those
bad movies, not to foreshadow the opinion on today's movie, but we might not be that
into it.
Yes, we are returning to a classic.
I feel like lately because so much is getting, let's call it what it is, dumped onto streaming.
We always have new movies to watch, but you know, we've neglected a lot of the classics.
And today we watched one called Prominite Joe, was it your first viewing?
I own this film, and I had watched it once on DVD, and couldn't remember why I hadn't
rewatched it until I rewatched it, and I was like, oh, yeah, I had only seen oddly enough
Prominite 2, hello, Mary Lou, I had only seen the sequel.
Normally, I wouldn't do that, but I think Joe Bob did it, and I had heard it discussed
as one of those kind of so bad, it's good classics.
I never saw the remake 2008, didn't even know it existed.
The remake I believe has a 5 % on Rotten Tomatoes, it's one of the lowest scores I've ever seen.
Horror remakes, I mean, there are so, really, you know, we're doing Justice League this
week as well.
And I think there's been two horror remakes I can think of that were exceptional, and those
are the thing, and Zack Snyder's Dawn of the Dead, but I'm surely forgetting some, what
am I forgetting?
The Friday, as far as great ones, like there's just not many.
The Friday the 13th remake is often deemed as a very good entry into that franchise, a fun
one, sure.
It meets the standard set by Friday the 13th, you know?
Yeah, Christ, I can't think of one.
I mean, if you want to call the new, it's a remake, they're not as good as the mini series,
we've discussed that.
If you want to call the new pet cemetery a remake, it's terrible, obviously, we've talked
about that.
The new nightmare announced street, the remake was bad and boring, yeah, talked about that.
But I'm trying to, the shining, oh, God, the TV version of the ship.
See, here's the thing though, they call those remakes, and I'm like, and it's my problem
with this new Wizard of Oz that's coming out, which quit news cycle right out of the gate.
They're doing a remake of the Wizard of Oz.
Why didn't, did you tell me this, because they got, they had the whiz, and they already did
the terrible remake with Downey Jr., that Sam Raimi did, and God, that, that was James
Franco.
Downey Jr., you're thinking of the, oh, you're right, you're thinking of the doo little that
was like a high seas adventure for some reason.
Yeah.
No, I, Downey, are you sure Downey Jr. wasn't in the remake?
I saw it.
I despised it.
It's, it's James Franco, yeah, Zach Braff as a talking monkey, I believe.
Oh, my God, yes, God, that sucked.
In some of the worst, I mean, two of the worst casting choices I've ever seen was James
Franco, supposedly being like a wizard and like a sort of savvy con man, just horrific casting.
And then Mila Kunis is the wicked witch of the West.
I mean, these, I was like, what are you guys doing?
You've got Helena, I think Helena bottom, not Helena bottom card, Rachel Wise was in it.
It's like, you're not making Rachel Wise the witch, well, this has do with Kunis as
the wicked witch and Rachel vice as the wicked witch is what it says, wise is the East.
But Kunis is the one that turns into the green witch that we all know and love.
And Michelle Williams is Glinda, I mean, that clearly they were just like, this is not going
to be your father's wizard, but it's, it's for nobody Bruce Campbell as winky gatekeeper.
Don't remember that.
It's a, but that's a prequel though.
So that's not a remake and it's not a horror movie.
I don't even know how we got on this subject.
But we're talking about the new one, the new one.
Well, what I was going to say is so they're, they're making a new wizard of us and they're
calling it a remake.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I said to a friend of mine the other day, I go, don't call it a remake.
Just call it an adaptation, a new adaptation.
And then nobody's going to give a shit when it's not that good.
Right.
If they had just said this new pet cemetery, if they just said it's just a new adaptation of
the book, it would have been so much less offensive than, but then you double down on
it.
So now it's not only a bad adaptation of the book, you also called it a remake and it's
a terrible remake of the film that we like.
You know what I mean?
Just call it a new adaptation.
Like, like, it makes it worse when you call it a remake too.
It's just, it's just bad.
Well, and then you know, return to Oz attempted to do the sequel thing 50 years later.
They actually did have a pretty ground breaking and incredible sequel.
But then everybody's like, oh, good.
So it's going to be like part.
It'll be exactly like the first one.
And then it's nothing like it.
You can really shoot yourself in the foot with this shit.
I didn't see the Zoey Deschanel sci -fi channel Wizard of Oz TV show.
Lucky for you.
Yeah.
Tin man was called tin man.
Not the Tim Robbins car salesman movie.
Tin man.
Yeah.
And that did not have Tim Robbins.
Tin man was Dick Dreyfus and Danny DeVito.
Oh, okay.
No, Tin man was Dick Dreyfus.
And, uh, yeah, and Danny DeVito and Barbara Hershey.
Yeah.
I get confused with Wise guys that Brian Dupalma movie with Piscopo and DeVito,
which came out at like the same time.
And Lord only knows why Brian Dupalma would think he's supposed to be doing a comedy.
They're both okay movies.
Tin man is really good, actually.
I've never seen Tin man.
You're thinking of Cadillac man with Cadillac with Tim Robbins, Rob Williams.
Which is not.
But there's a Robin in there somewhere.
You're thinking of Robbie Williams, the British songster who sang millennium.
Bill Savler.
I have never seen the movie Tin man.
But without even seeing it, I can tell you it is a more faithful adaptation to the Wizard of Oz than
the Tin man, uh, mini series.
Zoe Dashinnell.
I have never seen somebody sleepwalk through a production in my life.
Like I was a, and it's one of these mind boggling things.
And this happens to me a lot with this particular actor.
Alan Cumming is in it.
Alan Cumming is one of our greatest actors.
He's, he's a Broadway fucking phenomenon.
He's in tons of great stuff.
He's an amazing actor.
And then he does these things and you're like, dude, I don't understand.
Like you work, man, you work a lot, right?
But he'll pop up and shit.
That's like, you know, like a, like a Judd Nelson directed streaming, like action movie.
You know what I mean?
You're like, what the fuck?
Cummings isn't getting the big roles he used to.
He's, he's just not.
He is a good actor.
I mean, when you, when you're putting them in the greatest of all time, I feel like you might be a little hyperbolic.
But he's great.
Um, I loved him in Josie in the Pussycats.
He's very funny in that movie.
Him and Parker Posey make a great villain duo.
Yeah, very underrated comedy.
I'm basing my praise of him on, on what he did on Broadway with, um,
a cabaret, which was astounding.
Oh, okay.
I didn't say it was astounding.
Um, you know, I never saw cabaret there, but they, they, it was, when I was in New York,
it was one of those constantly rotating star productions.
Right.
So like one, one week at the Alan coming and then the next week, it would be Joey Fattone.
Like you never, there was, then Wayne Brady, you know, like there was no,
it's just anybody who came by the, the stage got to go up and do a couple of weeks.
So I knew the, I knew the cabaret soundtrack with Alan coming, the backers and forwards
because my roommate, Jim Cargill was a musical theater major.
Okay.
And he would listen to it all the time.
And he was the one that was like, listen to this.
Like this, and the, and the soundtrack really does capture a lot of the show and the play
and like, and I'm just like, this guy is incredible, man.
And he's like, you got to go see it, dude.
You got to see it.
So I went to see it and I was blown away.
And only to find out the end of the show, it wasn't Alan coming that I'd seen.
It was, it was John Sakata.
Ah, Latin singer, uh, John Sakata.
He said, he's very good though.
You didn't know till the end of the show that this Latin man was an Alan coming?
I probably knew before that, but it's funnier if it's at the end of the show.
Yeah.
Oh, so he sang, um, we got to get his hit.
Make it through the day without you.
Yeah, that was him.
And then he said, yeah, I, I don't want to stay.
Yeah, that's the same song.
That's the same song.
Okay, okay.
Get trying to get out of another day, make it through the day without you.
So what's his other single?
I don't know.
I only knew him from, I mean, I knew he was like a singer and stuff.
I didn't know his songs really.
I only knew him from the Sinatra duets record.
He's only going one of the duets.
Yeah.
And I was like, yeah, that's that John Sakata guy.
It is perfect that, uh, that that's who was playing when you went to go see it.
While I'm listing off all the random people that were there, John Sakata fits in beautifully.
But was he amazing?
He was incredible.
Interesting.
Like, I couldn't believe it was him.
I was like, what the fuck?
Because the part that the MC is a in the Broadway, at least in this Broadway version, is a, um,
it's a Jewish person in Germany, but like, but like, um, you know, like a Yiddish person
or something.
Like, so like, it's a heavy accent and like, and it's, and it's a, and he, it's a bisexual
character.
So he's very, at times, flamboyant and then very like almost lecherous with the women at
time.
It's a, it's a, it's a pretty fucking dynamic role, man.
Right.
Absolutely.
The movie cabaret.
I love it.
Joel Brae is amazing.
The movie's great.
But this reboot on Broadway, really, they really darkened it up.
Yeah.
They took it like, like that thing, two ladies, this song about the three.
So like, that's, it's filthy on the, in the Broadway show now, you know, so it was kind
of, if you're darkening up a show about the Holocaust, that's, that's, that's pretty dark.
It's kind of like what Fossey did in, in, in, remember in Fossey, Viridin, when he wanted
to redo 42nd Street, but like, make it like crazy dark, that was like the whole thing.
It was like that.
It was like, I, it might have actually been something Fossey did before he died, and
then they just redid the Fossey version.
I don't know.
Go to bed.
Yeah.
Now, Joe, I don't know why it took me 10 minutes to notice this, but are you, you're sitting
in front of a inner city mural or something that, that, like the dare program had kids paint
or what's going on?
This is, I get this a lot.
This is my, I sit in front of this window when I podcast, now, I used to sit in my room.
This is my terrace out here, and that wall was painted in, with that graffiti.
The person who lived here before me had a graffiti artist paint graffiti all over it.
And when I moved in, they said, would you like us to paint over that?
And I said, no, I like it.
It's kind of cool looking.
I got some chairs and things out there.
It's a lot of color, and it's fun to look at.
What, what wall is it in the next door building?
No, that's my terrace.
This is my terrace, and that's my terrace wall, like that's the wall of the, it's a tall wall.
So, so there's privacy on the terrace.
So basically, people, I could like walk around on my terrace naked if I wanted to, nobody
could see me.
That's the point of the high wall.
And then also, no children can like fall over it or something, I guess.
It's a safety thing.
But then, how do you stick your head out the window and go like, shut up.
You know, we're like, how do you put a string with different pieces of laundry on it from
your window to the, the neighbor across the, unfortunately, you can't, I can go out there
with a string, but it's not, I'm not hanging it anywhere.
Where are you cool in your paws?
Out there on the terrace.
There's, there's, there's enough of a sill there, and then this blue thing like flapping
above me is a retractable awning that I, that needs to be replaced.
It's a, it's a bad piece of tarp on there, but it gets the job done.
I'll tell you, this has been a game changer, man.
When you, in New York City to walk into your living room and have windows of this size and
a glass sliding door with a screen door that you're going to open and, and step outside and
get some fresh air every morning and it's pretty fucking nice, man.
Yeah.
I locked out.
I figured you were not at home.
It doesn't look like your place.
Yeah.
You got to come visit the new spot at some point.
Well, jam the records and whatnot.
All right.
Speaking of which, Pat, I wanted to tell you this.
Yeah.
Have you perused tower records lately, the virtual tower records now?
I thought they went completely under.
They've got a website now, and it's, it's a media site.
They sell media, okay.
I am not getting paid to say this in any way.
I'm saying this to the fans of the show who are also collectors like Pat and myself.
The records, every record is like slash down in price and you can get vinyl really cheap
and, you know, CDs, if you still buy CDs and then they have movies and stuff.
But I just got the 180 gram audio file, whatever the fuck it's called, reissue of Faith and
Wars Alvin introduced yourself, which in a record store sells for like 35 bucks.
And I think I got it from them for $21 or something like that.
Okay.
I got, I got a bunch of stuff on there.
They had stuff that I couldn't find anywhere else.
What brought you to tower records?
I was googling a no effects record that I wanted and I couldn't find it.
And for some reason on Amazon, it was very, it was like, I was like, that doesn't seem
right.
This is too high price right now.
So I googled the record and it's a tower records.
And I was like, oh, yeah, I think they still have a website and I went to it and it was like
and I got the record and then they, you know, I tried, I tried to buy from the stores, but
sometimes Amazon or something else will have it for like $15 cheaper and you're like, it's
sometimes it's a little hard to justify the extra spending, you know.
Well, I am, as I told Joe, I have been selling so many of my albums.
Stuff I had an open stuff I was probably never going to open.
But for some reason, everything on Amazon has skyrocketed in price.
So I've been selling shit.
I'm well over, you know, what, where I expect it to be in like 48 hours.
I've sold so many things.
I got a big stack that I'm looking at right now.
So it's a real seller's market if you want to hop on Amazon.
The other thing I would mention is to check out Hamilton Book, which is a new website I found
for Blu -ray's books, CDs, et cetera.
The deals on there are absolutely incredible.
Look up Hamilton Book and the shipping's free or cheap.
It's like $2 to $4.
I'm bookmarking Hamilton Book right now because I keep forgetting to go back to that.
But I got something really good on there.
I can't remember what it was for very cheap.
Now, did you get anything on the Amazon 3 for 2 sale?
I got some things.
I do hate more and more buying from Amazon, especially so like I sell all the time through them.
I buy all the time through them.
And then today I open up this slick Rick album that I bought.
The great adventures, the great adventures.
And I'm listening to it.
I want to play that when the wife's home.
Yeah, but I'm listening.
I'm loving it.
I'm not super familiar with old slick enjoying it.
And then I go to put on album 2.
It's a two album set like many are.
And it's the same as album 1.
Or I should say I have two copies of disc 2.
So I call up Amazon.
And they just flat out say your return window is over.
We're not doing anything for you.
I said, could you look and see what I've spent there?
Sir, just immediately into that voice and I just kind of hung up the phone.
They won't help you.
Except sometimes you have an issue.
If you're within that window, they'll do whatever you want.
You could have bought a car.
They're like, don't worry about it.
Just have the money back.
Right.
But it's just I, you know, it's a lesson that you should open things right when they arrive to check.
But it's the not opening things that is led to me making a lot of money off old purchases
because then there's still a new condition you can sell them for more.
I say that's a small price to pay for all the deals you've gotten.
You're not wrong.
They just pissed me off.
Sure.
It's Jesus Christ.
Among this Hamilton books now, my God, how do they make profit?
It's ridiculous.
Remember that I shared this with you folks because it's the kind of thing where you're like,
should I be telling people about this?
Is this going to go away?
I've checked in once a day for like a month.
They don't update it often.
But from what I've heard, apparently they have huge dumps every month or two
where they'll just throw up a bunch of new stuff.
But it's blu -rays that go for 20 and 25 elsewhere going for $5.
Jesus Christ.
The Goodfellas 20th Anniversary Edition Blu -ray is $7 .95.
You put together in order.
Yeah.
You do great work.
And it comes to you quick.
It's nice.
And it's new stuff.
It seems like it's got to be off the back of a truck or something.
But it's great.
It's probably overstocked stuff where they get they have access to promo copies or something.
And then you get it really cheap.
I got some books and some Otona movies.
Yeah.
Woody Allen's Manhattan $5.
$6 for the Blu -ray 2001 $8.
Wow.
This is incredible.
Incredible.
They had all those steel books like the Carey Steelbook and the Return of the Living Dead
Steelbook that we're going for $5 .95.
And then they're all on Amazon for $35.
Well, I speaking to Steelbooks, I lucked out on the Amazon 3 for 2.
I got.
I've had speaking of Wizard of Oz and Steelbooks.
I've had my eye on the Wizard of Oz 4K for a while.
I never owned the movie.
And every review in the 4K was like you that you have to get the 4K like every single.
And I was like, God dammit, man.
Yeah.
It's like fucking $40.
You know, like.
So they they slice the price down to 24.
Then they put it on the 3 for 2.
Then I get which I fed my eye on for a while.
The My Bloody Valentine Steelbook.
They have both versions of the 81 version of the movie, Blu -ray.
The regular Blu -ray was like 30.
The Steelbook one was like 22.
And the Steelbook one is the collectors one.
And it has the uncut version on the second disc and everything.
Yeah.
So those are my two.
And then it's like, all right.
You got a free one.
What do you want?
I grabbed a Twilight Zone season two.
The peel one because it had a couple good episodes.
And I didn't finish the whole thing.
And I was like, I'll think that for free.
So I can finish it and not give CBS anymore fucking money.
Yeah.
They're shit streaming service.
It was a nice little score.
Paramount plus apparently.
Oh, I'm on that.
Whoops.
Paramount plus.
Good, good, good.
Good people over.
Paramount.
Folks.
Actually, they.
Comedy Central emailed me last week.
My special you let me down is streaming on Paramount plus.
You can get it on there.
And you can get the complete unedited version.
It is not the 45 minute televised version.
You can get the uncut version of the special.
And both my half hour specials are streaming on there.
So you can check all of those out.
Please go do so.
More streaming opportunities for you.
You know, I might actually get Paramount plus.
Because Paramount plus at least I had no interest in the CBS only thing.
But now if it's under that umbrella, then.
Yeah.
That makes a little more sense to me.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, I think people like it.
Okay.
I didn't sign up for it.
But.
You know, they got stuff.
They don't have any.
Frazier is going right.
Yep.
Frazier will be there.
A lot of shows coming.
I'll probably do it for like the godfather's thing
that recently fired army hammer and.
The godfather thing.
They're doing like the making of the godfather.
Prepare Mount plus.
Oh, like a like a biopic about the making of the movie.
Right.
Like Mank, but about the godfather.
And hopefully good.
Who was hammer going to play?
Pacino.
No, he was either Robert Evans or somebody in that world.
I don't remember.
But hammer got the boot from several movies just in the past couple weeks.
And now Disney is like.
You know what I'm worried about is that it's going to start.
I'm not worried about it personally.
I just mean, I feel like where we're headed is that if actors are going to be in these movies,
they're going to start vetting them like they do political candidates.
Okay.
Because now army hammer is the star of death on the Nile,
which is murder on the Oregon Express sequel,
which I can't believe that movie made enough to guard warrant a sequel,
even though I liked it.
But death on the Nile is the sequel.
And apparently army hammer is the star.
So there was a lot of talk about just editing him out because everyone just assumed they would.
They thought he was like one of 12 suspects or something.
But he's the Johnny Depp.
He's the star.
And he's the guy they cast because Johnny Depp was too problematic.
So Disney is like, yeah, we're probably just going to release it.
And see what happens.
But they essentially have blown $100 million.
Unless people just go see it and don't care, which is also very possible.
But this thing of we can't release the movie with that guy in it because that guy's an asshole.
It's got to stop.
There are hundreds of other people that were part of this project.
It's a shame that one of them sucks and is terrible.
So don't use that person again.
And get rid of it.
Don't penalize everybody else and then throw money in the toilet on top of it because a guy turned out to suck.
He sucks.
So don't use him anymore.
Leave it alone.
Like, it's just odd.
I mean, you know, we're not going back to seven and usual suspects and American beauty and throwing other actors in the Kevin Spacey roles.
You know, it's like just trust that people are adult enough to go.
Yeah.
This guy is no good.
But I think they're worried that it comes off as an endorsement of the person's actions and so on and so forth.
I mean, those poor Cosby kids because it's like every like they did that they made the example out of the Cosby show.
Yeah.
And every other canceled sitcom star from the 80s, they're all their shows are streaming just fine.
You know what I mean?
And it's like, yeah.
Jesus Christ, you know, that one made a little bit more sense to me because it was called the Cosby show.
But I mean, folks, we're not talking.
You're not going down to see Army Hammer's one man show where he plays like Albert Einstein, you know, at the Paramount or whatever.
Like, fine, maybe you don't support that, but.
You should support that regardless of your thoughts.
Army.
I've got one word for you.
Come back.
It's like that David, our cat Sherlock Holmes, we almost went to see in Burbank.
We should have gone to see in Burbank.
I don't.
I don't have a reason under this yellow son of ours as to why we didn't get shit faced and go see that.
All the nights we sat around complaining about boredom and I don't understand why we never went to that.
No clue.
I got to say, I think we probably would have enjoyed it.
I think we would have come away pleasantly surprised with the new respect for Mr. Arquette.
Yeah.
Yes.
You never know, man.
You never continued respect for Mr. Arquette.
Joe, let's go over to Pat's movie corner.
Okay.
And I'm going to make this a little special one because I, for the first time in well over a year, saw a movie at the movie theater.
Oh, wow.
I'd think pretty sure the last one I did was the invisible man last March.
That was my last film, too.
First or something.
And, you know, AMC movie pass or whatever it is, not movie pass, AMC stubs.
I'm driving distance from like four AMCs.
And I was going to three movies a week.
It's $20 a month.
It's a great deal.
And they give you a bunch of perks.
So they email me but they've been very respectful.
The day the pandemic started, they paused everybody's membership.
Then now they say, come back whenever you want.
But we are going to restart you in July.
And start whenever you want, which I think is a nice way to handle it.
I look yesterday.
I'm like, what time are, what does the theater look like for nobody in a half hour?
And I looked.
There was one guy sitting over in the corner and he was surrounded by X's.
So the second you select your seat, they surround you with X's.
And nobody can buy any of the seats around you.
Very rude.
They bring only your X girlfriends.
I mean, he needs that.
Come on.
Right there.
They fill the theater max of 40%.
So I was going mid day on a Monday.
It was me and two other people and we sat a mile from each other.
I wore my mask.
I felt very secure.
And I would say, still look ahead.
If the theater was 50 % full, that's still a little close for comfort for me.
But I felt very happy with it.
I'll probably do it again.
And nobody with Odin Kirk is awesome.
It's everything you want it to be.
Here it's great.
It's really fun.
It's directed in like almost like that atomic blonde movie with Charlize, which I liked a lot too.
But where it's just crazy fight scenes and like weirdly like weird music choices,
a lot of weird music choices like 80s songs and then like old 30s music,
you know, kind of ironic type music, which has become more and more popular these days.
But Odin Kirk is awesome in it as you as you would imagine.
It's not a comedy, right?
But it's lighter than I expected.
It's like, you know, I don't want to give too much away.
Here's what I'm saying.
I've been watching the Death Wish movies lately.
And there's something I love about just a guy's family gets hurt.
And then he's like, I'm going to kill all of you.
What I don't like is the backstory where they were a mercenary for the CIA.
I didn't like it in WIC, the secret society of assassins.
Right.
And I don't necessarily love it here because it's like, I'd rather see a put upon a cook husband,
finally snap and take everybody out.
I don't like him having ties to the CIA and all this stuff and blah, blah.
But it's a small quibble because as far as action movies go, this is the best in ages.
It's really good.
But it's probably the best since WIC that I can think of.
Who would have thought?
Oh, yeah.
Crazy.
It's great.
And you know, my buddy works with Odin Kirk and he talked about how Bob got into,
took him like a year to get into his shape for it or whatever.
And then this is what it almost made me get emotional.
He takes his shirt off at one point.
They still won't shoot him below the tits because he doesn't have action star body or whatever.
And he looks fine.
And when my buddy told me that he trained all this time, I was like, oh my god,
like that's so depressing to me.
Conan O 'Brien used to say that when I was the page on his show,
he would come like drenched and sweat from the gym.
And he's one of the few times he ever like really talked to me.
He would be like, you know how horrible it is to spend 90 minutes every day working out.
And the end result is this.
And he grabbed his stomach and was like shaking it around.
But it's, you know, it's genetics, you know.
Odin Kirk was never going to be either go the steroid route or you don't.
And he clearly didn't.
He looks thin.
He looks sharp.
He's, uh, he's believable completely in the fight sequences.
Um, the movie is stolen by Christopher Lloyd, who is for some reason not even in the promo,
but he plays Odin Kirk's dad.
Oh, okay.
I will not spoil his journey, but my god, he's still, he is back in a big way.
He's so good in it.
And really, you know, uh, well, again, I'm not going to spoil anything.
I'm going to say it's a lot of fun.
And if you want to see Bob Odin Kirk, Christopher Lloyd and the Rizzah.
Oh, yeah, kicking ass, then go see it.
And I, and if you don't want to see it, you probably don't want to be friends with me.
So it was very fun.
See it.
I will see it.
I think my first one, I might this week, uh, at some point, as a first one back to Kong,
Godzilla, Kong, just to go back with a full on popcorn.
Okay.
You know, huge movie.
Yeah, I'll probably do it.
But I don't know.
It's, it's from the writer of the wicks.
I mean, so clearly this guy has like a, has a, uh, a niche, a niche, uh,
and the director of Hardcore Henry, which I didn't see, but, uh, yeah, I never saw that.
It's directed in a, in a really cool, fun way.
I liked it a lot.
And it's 90 minutes.
Exactly.
Good.
Uh, well, speaking of Bronson.
Per your heavy recommendation.
I watched Kinjitay.
For hidden subjects.
Yeah.
I watched it.
Holy shit.
First of all, I thought when you were describing it, I thought this fucking thing took place.
Like, was shot in the 70s or something.
I turned it on.
It's sort of like 1993.
It didn't really do.
It came out like the same year as Jurassic Park.
It's, I believe a Canon film.
If I'm not mistaken.
Of course.
It's at the tail end of Canon, man.
It's like right at the end.
Like, they were just, it was full on paint by numbers at this point.
Over at Canon pictures.
Uh, as Pat pointed out to me.
Uh, over text.
I can't remember if you said it on the show or not, but.
You know, uh, you know, uh, uh, Bronson is just sleepwalking through the, through the movie.
Like, he's, I don't, I texted you at one point.
I said, I don't even think Bronson knows what movie he's in right now.
Like, yeah, he's just like, he, it was just outrageous.
Like the, the, the, the lack of commitment and just mailing it in.
And, and it tries desperately.
First of all, it's an action movie with a, I'd say zero action.
Yeah.
Well, there's a very interesting thing that I, I heard, I was, I, I've been.
Uh, spending a lot of time on the Bronson Wikipedia and the J. Lee Thompson and the Michael winner who are these sadistic directors he worked with.
But he talked about how he worked with certain directors like this J. Lee Thompson guy so much near the end of his career.
Because he'd only make him run for one take.
If the take involved running, he, he would say, will only do one job.
And, and it feels that way.
Like when he's running from point A to B, it looks like an old man struggling to run.
It, uh, it's a deadly serious film.
Uh, there's no fun at all in it.
I mean, given the subject matter, it's basically about a child prostitution ring.
That gets all criss -crossed like a sign filled episode where the guy that, a guy, Gropes, Bronson's daughter and then Bronson is trying to find the, that guy's kidnapped daughter, but he doesn't know.
And it's just, it's just insane.
And, um, but then in the middle of it, there's like this, there's like a WC fields level broad joke where they're hanging a guy off the balcony.
Yeah.
To scare him and he falls out of his shoes and dies.
And the, and the, Bronson's partner looks at him and he goes, what do we do with the shoes?
It's a bad movie.
It desperately tries to make some sort of commentary on racism.
Like it's not a, it's not a like, it's not a pro racism movie.
It's trying to make a commentary on racism against Asian people.
And it fails so horribly that it feels racist.
Yeah.
It's like they're, it's crazy.
It's a crazy fucking movie.
When your hero gets out of a car and starts screaming at a bunch of Asian tourists going into a nice hotel for a gala,
Yeah.
You're, your message is getting a little confused, a little muddled at that point.
And they, they never set up why he's racist.
Yeah.
So one scene in where, you know, a flashback, something happens to him and he's, he's racist.
And then he redeems himself.
No, he gets any of that.
He gets, his racism gets activated when the Asian man feels up his daughter.
That's what starts it.
That's what at least inflames it.
Yeah.
Then the daughter's racist too.
Well, as you remember, she gets off the bus and says that Oriental touched my holiest of holies.
But then one line of dialogue.
Yeah.
But then when she's being interrogated, she goes, again, this is like a sign felt scene.
She goes, the lady goes, the cop lady goes, are you, was it a Japanese man or a Korean man or Chinese man?
And the girl goes, how can you tell?
And then an Asian cop comes in and goes, oh, because we all look alike.
Wait, let me stop you.
Let me stop you because I thought that that scene was insane.
Actually, what he does is he said he agrees with her.
He stands up and he goes, no, that's right.
He's like, we're all, and mentally you're like, well, of course, he's offended by this.
But I think they put him in to say like, hey, this, this white girl saying that's kind of racist.
Have the Asian guy agree with her that all Asians look alike?
Because he's an agreement.
I took it as the, to me, that played like that sign felt mail man scene.
Like, excuse me, sir.
Do you know where the Chinese restaurant is?
Right.
And the mail man freaks.
I was like, I know.
Yeah.
Hey, they're American joke.
So can you just point me towards the hamburger hotdog stand?
Yeah.
What are the great sign felt lines?
I'm Jewish.
I don't go flying off the handle.
So many as we would direct you to Israel.
Yeah.
I mean, it's it's it's a fucking crazy movie, man.
I have really been enjoying watching movies that are that could not be released now,
which is most movies made before 2010.
But something like Kinjitay feels like it's just from another world now when you watch it.
It's, you know, as I said, Terence, you know, was the one kind of talking it up.
I've heard all these people who deal in sleazy movies described as one of the sleasiest movies ever made.
And it's if that's your thing.
If you want to watch Charles Brownson shove a dildo into a man's ass in the first two minutes of a film,
check out Kinjitay.
Yeah, which great scene.
And I texted you about it.
He comes home from work beside himself because he raped a man with a dildo.
Yeah.
Who who was about to have sex with a minor.
And that's how Charles Brownson justified doing it.
And he comes home from work just a shattered man, like, what have I done?
What am I becoming?
Right.
And he says to his wife, I did something today and he won't say what it is.
And his wife makes him feel better by going, you're a good cop.
You didn't lie.
And he's like, you're right, honey.
And then that's it.
That's it.
It never comes back to bite him in the ass.
There's never any repercussion.
Nothing.
It's just right.
If I know anything about you and then he steals that man's watch and blows up his car about 10 minutes after that.
Yeah.
He plays by his own rules.
I mean, he makes the pimp guy eat the watch.
Remember, he makes it swallow the watch, which is crazy.
Not even crazy because he's making a man swallow a watch.
It's physically impossible.
It's the biggest watch I've ever seen.
I'm like, this is ridiculous.
Yeah.
But it's a flavor flavor to choke down his neck.
All right.
That's good.
It's something.
And I'm going to do a little bronze in feature coming up.
I've been watching the death wishes and his lesser known films.
And there's a lot to go off of.
I saw Tina on the home box office network.
It's on HBO Max as well.
It's a documentary about the life of Tina Turner.
I have always really liked the music of Tina Turner.
I think her vocal performances, you know, unfortunately with the abusive Ike Turner are amazing.
I mean, she what she lacks in like a wreath is range.
She delivers with just raw power.
She's a rock singer.
And I've always been a big fan.
I've loved her.
My mom listened to her 80s stuff relentlessly so I know all that stuff as well.
What I didn't know was much about her aside from the fact that Ike Turner beat her up a lot.
And I've seen what's love got to do with it.
This is a really, really, really good documentary.
HBO has been thriving with music documentaries and shitting the bed with all their other documentaries lately in my opinion.
But it's very good.
It's a survivor story.
She basically announces halfway through.
This is her last public appearance.
She's found love.
And when you find out that she's found love again, me and Heather, my wife cheered.
That's the kind of that's how much it makes you feel for Tina Turner and then this thing.
But God, what a life.
She had a rough go.
And then when she finally broke free of Ike Turner,
she's like, all right, I'm looking to have this solo career.
And no one would give her a deal in the Turner.
Everyone was just like, nah, then sure enough, one guy took a chance on her.
Gives her what's love got to do with it.
She became one of the biggest stars of the 80s.
She's in Mad Max, et cetera.
It's a great story, a great doc.
And it will much like the Bee Gees documentary.
It'll lead you towards some of their music that you might not know.
I'll highly recommend.
My second film was a rewatch of a movie that is not racist and doesn't deal with racism.
But the title does sound like a racial slur.
Go on dark man.
Yeah.
It's not a racial slur.
It's the name of the superhero in the film.
This is the Sam Raimi superhero epic.
I had watched it in years.
I rewatched it.
It's fucking great, man.
It's every bit as good as it always was.
It is awesome.
It's so fun.
Sam Raimi made this movie because he wanted to get a deal to do Batman or the shadow.
Yeah.
Couldn't get the rights to either.
So he said, I'm going to do a superhero movie that also that also traipses along the
same path as the universal monster movies that I loved growing up as a kid.
So he kind of mixed the two together and came up with dark man and it's just an awesome movie.
Liam Neeson is great.
He plays it real hammy, which makes it fun.
Francis McDormand is great.
You know, she.
She refers to the role in this movie as the only bimbo I've ever played.
I don't know why she thinks this woman is a bimbo, but she does.
She's not at all, but it's certainly a let it's more of a girlfriend role than you'd normally expect her to have.
Yeah.
And then, you know, the show is stolen by Larry Drake as the.
As Dr. Giggles.
Dr.
As Dr.
Giggles in the.
It's crossover film.
What's his name?
The Durant.
That's his name.
Yeah.
I've never seen the sequels.
I almost.
I almost just bought them because I'd never seen them.
And then I started to like, yeah, I started to watch trailers and.
I just was like, yeah, they just really wreak of that like early 90s straight to video, whatever.
And they just, it's a different guy.
The guy.
It's the guy that plays.
The punisher and the punisher sequel plays dark man in this and.
Drake is back in the second one.
And then by the third one, it's like he's got to stop a CIA ringed, you know, some shit.
But one of the things I like so much about the movie aside from all the cool camera stuff that Sam Raimi doesn't it.
And all the cool themes from genre films that he ties into it.
I really like the idea that dark man is a pretty selfish, selfish superhero.
This is not a guy that something terrible happens to.
And then he has to go.
And he just stops, you know, perch snatcher, perch snatchers and stuff like that.
He just goes back and kills the bad guys that killed that hurt him or tried to kill him.
And I just, I like it.
I like that it's a revenge movie more than a superhero movie.
But if you just look at it on a surface level, it feels like a superhero movie.
And the makeup effects are insane.
Like he looks horrible.
Yeah.
Which is also confusing because by the third movie, he still looks like that.
And you're like, what would have healed a bit?
You know, sure.
But, but anyway, good flick worth worth checking out.
I'll probably buy it at some point.
Yeah, I got the screen factory or whatever.
I love dark man.
I saw.
Oh, you know what I watched speaking of screen factory because it was one of the items I sold.
I gave certain things a goodbye listen or a goodbye view before they go out the door.
And one of those was poltergeist to the other side.
Not great.
I had always thought not great, but it's terrible.
It's, it's, you know, like I never realized poltergeist is one of the movies I know.
I know almost by heart.
And I never really noticed how much this movie rips off every single moment and beat of the original.
When it's not just showing you flashbacks of the original, which it does a lot,
it's just going through the exact same motions.
And because they don't have the old lady Beatrice straight that was in the first one,
she's not there anymore.
So they bring in Joe Beth Williams mom.
It's like down to that they have to have every single beat be exactly the same.
Will Samson, the, the guy from Cuckoo's Nest is playing the Native American sort of spirit guide.
He's playing the, the new version of Zelda Rubenstein from the original.
But she's in it too as like a researcher at the original house site.
Yeah, she comes back.
Yeah, she's in it.
But man, it just sucked the, there's two sort of major freakouts that I remembered from when I was a kid.
The first is that the kids braces attack him.
That is really just sort of more stupid than anything else.
But I'm sure it gave a lot of kids horrible nightmares about getting braces.
And then the other scene is where Craig T Nelson drinks bottle of tequila.
Accidentally drinks the worm.
The worm is demonic and it makes him like possessed.
He attempts to rape Joe Beth Williams, which I had completely forgotten about.
And then he violently vomits up this sort of worm demon creature that looks like the grabboids in tremors two or three when they were walking around on four legs.
And it has the face of the preacher.
Yeah, I liked that part.
I thought that part was pretty fucking cool.
It was intense and the preacher is great.
The preacher is awesome.
He is doing a lot of work scaring you that the movie is just not doing.
Julian Beck is his name.
Yes.
Yeah.
Great.
I have to imagine he's dead as I think he was nearly dead while filming this movie.
I believe he was 157 years old when they made that movie.
He's one of those guys.
He's like Bill Hickey, is it?
Is Bill Hickey the guy from...
Yeah.
He's like Bill Hickey.
Bill Hickey died.
I was like, what was he?
98?
He was like 61 or so.
He just always looked really old.
Well, fun fact.
Julian Beck was actually discovered on the set of the first poltergeist.
He was one of the skeletons in the pool scene.
Oh, wow.
And they sort of reanimated him and cast him in two.
But yeah, the movie is stupid as all get out.
And then it takes an even further step down with part three,
which I don't think I'll ever watch again.
I just remember them going into mirrors.
The director is ashamed of the movie.
He wishes they hadn't released it because the young girl passed away, of course.
If you've never Googled the poltergeist curse, you know,
there's also a documentary about that on on shutter.
Um, look, the guys three is at the bottom of the Tom Scarrett bought a barrel.
Would you sing a lot?
Yeah.
That's like, that's real low rent Tom Scarrett.
And that's saying a lot.
I think the poltergeist remake with Rockwell might be better than three.
And it's fucking awful.
So I think the franchise that should have ended with one masterpiece.
I mean, they just didn't ever get it back.
Three and two, I'll say this.
I don't agree about the remake thing that you just said,
because I think that three and two are passable on a pinkstone said this to me once.
He said, I was, he goes last Sunday, I was in the mood for a nap,
but I wanted to turn a horror movie on while I took a nap.
And poltergeist three was streaming.
And I was like, this is absolutely perfect.
So I think, I think it does have those sequels have some redeeming quality in the like.
You know, if you were to kind of take it back to the old days where they'd run a horror movie on a Saturday afternoon on Channel 57 or whatever your local affiliate of whatever it was.
Sure.
You know, like in that sense, they're just fun enough, but it's a real like,
you're cleaning the house while you watch it kind of thing.
You know, like, I don't even think the remake had that much even had that level of fun to it.
You know, I don't want this on at all.
Yeah, it really upset me.
I remember driving home very angry.
But there we are.
It's a mix bag this week, but some good stuff in there.
I don't need to do a third one, but I'll leave you with this.
I can't stop watching the smurfs.
What?
It's on HBO Max.
The original.
Yeah, the cartoon.
There's nine seasons.
Nine.
Did you used to watch it as a kid?
I loved it as a kid.
And I, I just one night, I was in one of those pandemic moods of, man, I'm just,
just, I want something that just takes me out of it completely.
And I was like, I'm going to put on this.
I'm going to see if the smurfs is still kind of fun.
I bet Gargamel is still pretty fun to watch.
And he is.
And I enjoy it.
Do I feel challenged?
No.
Have I learned anything?
Not really.
What are the stories in an average smurfs that?
It gets a little bit into more, more into wizard, wizardry and kingdoms and stuff.
You know, fantasy stuff that you'd think it did.
But, you know, a storyline will be like.
Gar a, you know, clumsy smurf finds a wand that can put a bubble around you.
Okay.
And then pop a smurf takes the wand away from him because it's dangerous because.
If you're not inside the bubble with the wand, you can't pop the wand, the bubble.
Then you just be stuck in the bubble.
Only the holder of the wand can pop the bubble.
And then I think Gargamel gets the wand and he's going to use it to trap the smurfs so he can eat them.
That's basically every episode is he.
Gargamel is going to eat the smurfs.
Right.
And says things like you're, you know, you know, not only is your nap over,
your life will be over soon.
You know, it's, he's pretty sinister, but a fun character.
Are they supposed to be extra delicious to him or nutritious or he just hates them?
I guess I used to watch it too, but I don't remember.
They never explain that.
He just wants to eat them for some reason.
In one of the newer movies, the animated movie, the lost forest or lost woods,
whatever the fuck it was called.
I read that the storyline was that Gargamel wanted to steal their magic,
which makes a little more sense.
But I thought if I ever remade the smurfs, I would make it that he's actually afraid of them for some reason.
Maybe there's some, like, like, kind of like the skexies with the gelfling.
There's some prophecy that says the smurfs will.
So he's hell been on eating them to make sure that that never happens.
But the smurf wants cucked him like a smurf fucked his wife in front of him and tied him up and made him watch.
That's possible.
Maybe he tried to hit on smurf at one point and she was, they did actually,
there was a very funny episode where a woman is scamming, a fairy woman is scamming Papa Smurf.
Yeah.
Because the only way she can escape from this evil magicians imprisonment is if she brings him Papa Smurf in trade for her freedom.
Uh -huh.
And so the way she tries to trap Papa Smurf is she wooves him with her feminine wiles.
And he's in love with her and then he gets self conscious about being old, two old.
And there's a scene where he comes to the door to answer the door for smurfs and his beard is brown.
It's kind of funny.
Yeah, they're like, what happened to your beard?
And he's like, what did nothing?
Nothing.
I was like, it's a pretty heavy joke for a show for six year olds.
But how would he fuck a smurf?
I mean, like, I guess they just assume kids won't ask these questions.
Well, it's weird.
They had a baby episode season two episode one.
A stork brings a baby.
Okay.
A smurf, a baby smurf to smurf village.
And then the smurf, the stork takes it away because it's like, sorry, wrong village.
And I was like, wait, there's other smurf villages.
Like I thought this was the only one.
But I guess there's like other smurf colonies elsewhere.
But anyway, I put it on when I go to sleep and stuff, you know.
It's like nice to go to bed too.
I'm reading about the smurf movie.
There's been three.
Yeah.
But we got Neil Patrick Harris.
So there's is animated with mix of real people.
I don't know.
It's live action with CGI smurfs.
Okay.
But you know who's playing gutsy, your boy Alan coming.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
He is.
Yeah, he's in those movies.
I never saw them.
But I read that online.
Hank is area as Gargamel.
He's pretty funny if you YouTube the Hank is area Gargamel scenes, you know.
He's Hank is Hank is area.
You can only get so bad, you know.
Katie Perry is smurf at Jonathan Winters this Papa.
Mm hmm.
Good cast.
You'd think the movies would be good, but apparently they're fucking terrible.
Yeah.
I tend to avoid kids entertainment.
I usually catch up to the Pixar's eventually, but I figure at some point I'll have kids
and I'll have to watch that shit all the time.
I'll just wait until then.
I don't like it.
So well, I've been writing some children's fiction.
So I've been delving a little bit more into that stuff again, just kind of like.
I guess you could call it research, but you know, just kind of get you in the headspace
of like, but I, but my problem is I'm also watching all this children's entertainment
from like 30, 40 years ago.
Right.
You know, like I don't know if it, I don't know if it could, could you still do this?
I don't know what the fuck do kids like now, you know, I mean, I don't know.
I'd have to imagine it's changed drastically.
Probably.
When you watch Sesame Street now, it's largely the same as it used to be, but I don't know.
Let's get to our movie, Joe.
Our movie today is called Prom Night.
This is a film that, as I said, I had not seen, but I always thought of it as being like,
Halloween is of course Jamie Lee Curtis's horror classic, but that Prom Night was like a wonderful second tier,
like just just below.
And that certainly is not the case.
Prom Night, as far as I'm concerned, is a really pretty terrible film.
You got Leslie Nielsen in what Wikipedia says is his last serious role.
So after this, it was just fully into the comedies with airplane and onward.
Yeah, and you, and I'll tell you that you can't, you can't go back and watch Leslie Nielsen serious now.
No, because it only reads like he's trying to be funny.
There's especially when he's dancing with Jamie Lee Curtis.
Yeah.
I was like, boy, this is classic little Nielsen.
I was laughing out loud.
Yeah.
There's a scene where he walks out in a tuxedo and it just gives you like naked gun party at the Queen's house.
Flashbacks.
You're just like, come on, man, you're killing me here.
Yeah.
No, it starts effectively.
It starts with the kind of the horror trope of the flashback.
There's kids sort of tormenting this young girl and then she falls to her death.
And we see a shadow we figure has witnessed all this.
Then I, it's sort of a who done it, which is never my favorite kind of slasher because I always sort of just feel like who cares.
I felt like that in this one for sure when the reveal came.
I was like, that's pretty much who I thought.
The movie uses, let me say this really quick about the who done it factor.
It's, it's almost not a who done it.
They just try to make you believe that it's this escaped killer who was blamed for the death of this little girl at the beginning of the movie.
The death was actually caused by her friends.
They were playing a game.
It was an accident.
But they covered up and this guy gets blamed and sent off to a mental asylum.
And the entire movie, they're just playing off of the guy that killed the girl 30 or 57 years ago, whatever it is,
is has escaped on this stormy night.
That also happens to be sort of a holiday, prom night.
Right.
And he's coming back for the ones that he didn't get.
And you're watching this thing that stars Jamie Lee Curtis.
Yeah.
It's her sibling that was killed and you're like, this is like a fucking paint by numbers Halloween rip off.
Like it's, it's crazy how close it shapes to Halloween.
Yeah.
When you read the story of it, they, they flat out say we were trying to do Halloween down to getting Jamie Lee Curtis.
She said, this is the first movie she ever made and any money on and she made 30 grand off it, which is shocking even though even with inflation.
But they talked about how they were basically doing that and carry and the ending you'll feel it's essentially the same thing as carry.
There's a plot going on in the background where they're going to fuck with people at the prom.
But apparently the trailer was cut by the producers.
They said cut the trailer beat for beat exactly like the carry trailer and they did.
Yeah.
I read that which there's a similar story about that very recently with the Cruella trailer apparently having been cut to match the Joker trailer.
They match up exactly.
But this feels super derivative and it wasn't that far along into the slasher genre like it wasn't like when it's like 1989 and we've seen every, I mean they they had pretty much license to do anything.
There weren't a whole lot of slasers happening and it's just feels tired paint by numbers.
Neilson vanishes about halfway through. He's not even really in it very much.
It becomes just this disco dance thing to the extent where you watch full songs.
Yeah.
And I think good.
Well they're just songs that they said they dance to the originals like they dance to let's say go on now go walk out the door.
They'd all dance to that when they shot it and they didn't have the money to buy the song.
So then in addition they paid musicians they had 24 hours to come up with like five disco songs that sounded exactly like the songs they dance to.
So the whole movie is a rip off.
And when you're watching Jamie Lee Curtis sort of dance awkwardly for five minutes.
The movie's only 85 minutes with no suspense.
You're like guys this doesn't even really count as a movie at this point.
It's got some it's got some interesting choices.
I did appreciate that it's more implied violence than just straight out splatter fest.
I'm not sure why they did that. I feel like a couple of good graphic practical effect kills probably could have elevated this thing a bit.
But hey I guess there were you know trying to be more hitch cocky and or something about it, but you know I.
Neilson does disappear halfway through the film and I got to tell you I think they did that on purpose for this reason and I fell for it.
Toward the end of the movie as murders are still happening a cop comes in and says we captured the guy that escaped 50 miles from here and that's the one you realize that's not who's killing everybody which you kind of suspect is probably coming anyway.
And I thought oh it's going to be Leslie Neilson that's why we haven't seen him so they did actually get me with that it turns out it's her brother who cares.
And also odd choice I don't know what the fuck they did this for why is he wearing a glittered ski mask it's got glitter on it.
Well they literally do this Scooby Doo thing it ends with pulling back a guy's mask to reveal who he is yeah then he plays it so tortured and sad that it ends the movie on this really bummer note.
The violence the director did say he didn't want to kind of still have the you know the gross kills and he wanted to be a little more classy and respectful.
And then of course the producer saw it more like you got to go back and add this be heading at the end be heading doesn't look particularly good either.
I thought that looked good I actually like to be heading that was like when I saw that I was like oh finally that was kind of cool.
It comes off very cleanly I'll say there's no blood or anything like that but the scene where Curtis the killer and and someone else are out fighting on the dance floor is one of the most awkwardly choreographed fight scene they've ever seen.
It seems like they don't know how to fight and the camera person doesn't know where they're supposed to be.
And at that point I was just sort of completely out there's no suspense I didn't care who made it.
Also with Curtis is gorgeous you get I mean Curtis at any stage is worth the price of admission but Curtis back then is astoundingly gorgeous young woman.
But I mean and she's good and she's convincing I mean you know all the actors are decently convincing and it's just not a good movie and then what really doesn't make sense and they're trying to do some sort of Shakespearean ending on this thing.
She before she knows that the killer is her brother because he's still masked to save her boyfriend who also is one of the kids that killed her sister that's never there's never any you know redemption with that that never is brought up it's never she's never realized or confronted she hits her brother in the head with the blunt end of the X.
Yes and he's you know he's delirious he's stumbling around because it would you know it would knock you sideways.
And then he falls down and she she unmasks him and realizes it's her brother and then he dies in her arms and it's like why would you not have her accidentally at least land a real explode to like his chest.
Yeah then I'll buy it that he dies outside like why did he just die like it doesn't make any say he got hit in the head and he just died it's you wouldn't die from that it's fucking crazy.
It's also more interesting if she brutally kills this guy and then reveals it's her brother that's right juicy ending right right yeah not a good flick man and a lot of.
It tries to do this stuff with imagery with like shards of glass and yeah and it just doesn't mean and it doesn't work it doesn't do anything it's just it's just kind of goes nowhere and also it's also another one of these movies from the early 80s where the blood looks like you know like they squirted raspberry fucking filling all over the floor.
I mean it's bringing the donuts yeah it is bonus ridiculous how read the blood is it's stupid looking.
Yeah this guy you know it's this is the only movie on his list that I recognize at all he directed a bunch but they're not names that are familiar to me I think this is a Canadian production if I remember correctly.
The one kind of interesting fact from the Wikipedia that I read is that they just used a couple deleted scenes they had the editor go back and put in some deleted scenes remove the two nude scenes and aired this on NBC nine months after it left theaters which was like unheard of at the time.
Yeah and apparently it did very well yeah well the movie made 15 million bucks in theaters and then NBC paid 300 grand air at three times or something so it made 50 million it made 50 million.
I think I'm I saw 15 on the side but 15 back then is 50 million all right yeah yeah 50 is all right sorry good yeah it's just I think it's one of those that was on cable a bunch and people have
this affection for it but watching it especially having never seen it just now I mean it doesn't rank it's way below most even slasher movies which is a pretty low bar.
But I did like prom night two hello Mary Lou more for its ridiculousness factor it's fun to watch with Joe Bob if you have shutter but it's a way more interesting and entertaining movie than one which is rare but.
And then three is like a satire it's like a deconstruction I never saw I never saw it either I never saw two I like the two I don't I never saw but I like that it has a supernatural element it makes me want to see it maybe I'll go watch it but.
You got a prom Joe yes yeah ladies name.
Which part Nora was my senior prom.
And my junior prom was Maureen okay those were the names what about you.
I went to three the one was this girl named Jess who had a seizure.
She's at the prom.
This junior year was another girl named Jess who's brother used to kick the shit out of me all the time.
The tuxedo place gave me a tux that was 12 sizes too big and her father tied a piece of extension cord around my waist because the belt was not keeping my pants up.
And the senior year prom I went with my my girlfriend Elizabeth at the time which was lovely.
All right very nice it's good after my senior prom was the first time I ever got drunk ever really yeah we drank screwdrivers and had a black we camped in somebody's yard wait a minute was more no Maureen was my senior prom Nora was my junior because we went back to Maureen's house I believe and her mom let us camp in the backyard and she didn't she didn't know we were drinking and then we drank we made screwdrivers with orange juice Donald Duck orange juice.
And I remember it was me and Pinkstone were drinking basically for the first time together and we were like this is so cool like this is delicious it goes right down and then you know I remember waking up the next day in my car so sick and freezing it had gotten so cold overnight it was just like the why did I do any of this.
Yeah my after my prom I had a girlfriend for high lot of high school and early college who wanted to remain a virgin until marriage and did so but I remember not being able to sleep and the other couple that was staying over at her house thought we were asleep and I watched you know not watched with popcorn but definitely saw him receive a hand job
and just sort of felt like trapped like I didn't know what to do but I witnessed a whole hand job go down to completion all right Nora was the senior prom where he was the gym I think Jesus Christ I can't remember it's they're not listening jokes anyway folks that's our show Twitter and Instagram the Patrick Walsh I'm on my buddy Jimmy smagula's podcast baby mouth where he he's never tried a whole bunch of foods that that most people
have tried I introduced them to oysters it's a funny show check her out Joe Joe to Rosa comedy on Twitter and Instagram Joe to Rosa comedian on Facebook doing the taste buds podcasts with my buddy Sal Volcano comes out every Monday 11 a .m. on YouTube on the no press network channel
thank you for supporting it and thank you for watching and thank you for supporting this show and thank you for listening we appreciate it and we'll be back in just a few moments with Justice League the Snyder cut see you next time and see you in hell.