welcome to we'll see you in hell folks it's time
to get busy. And if I don't mind saying so myself, jizzy. Okay. We're gonna, I guess we
could do sort of a circle jerk over zoom. A zoom around babe. Just stand up. I'd rather
not have my face in the shot. You know, I know how this shot of the camera or my genitals.
Both. I don't know if you've ever seen the fapeting website, but I don't need somebody
taking stills from from me cranking it with my face in it. If it's not, if it's just my
dick, I can say that's anybody's dick and the only people who could support the alternate
viewpoint would be the few people who have seen my penis. I wouldn't even fathom going
to the fapeting website as I would never intrude with another person's sexual voice. You know, I
have just like let's say I'm watching a movie and I see a pretty actress. I might go pretty actress
nude and then image search and nine times out of 10 it's gonna bring you to the fapeting whether
you want it or not. I agree. I've been on the fapeting for that exact reason. Yeah. And that exact
reason only outside, of course, if I am speaking to a female person in show business who I would
like to see naked. Right. Right. And I can't ask that person to be naked. No, I'm kidding. I don't
do that. You could romance her for one to two months until you've voluntarily showed you her
nudity. Yes, I could. I'm just making a joke that I'm running off to the bathroom as I'm mid conversation
to see to see Anna gas tires breasts I couldn't take anybody.
Anna gas tire was always naked as Martha Stewart. They would blur out her chest and should dance
around. That was very funny. Yeah, that bit. Yeah, I can go in and out when I go, but when I revisit that
era of SNL, which is funny, because we're gonna be doing today. We're doing Elvis. The next episode
is nope. And in nope, they reference this specific era of SNL. But yeah, very just a scene where
they decided to be a P and Piel sketch after two hours of a intense sci -fi drama. And then just
decided they'd go for broad, broad comedy. Interesting. You know what? Let's just flip it. Let's just
do no. Let's just find a do note. I don't think we've made it announce me yet. We're doing nope.
We're doing nope. Let's do no. Yeah, that is a weird scene in the movie where the
Asian character is speaking about, we'll get into it, but he's referencing a sketch on SNL for
particular reason. And he yeah, he rattles off all the, and then he goes, and of course, in the role
of the monkey, Chris Catan, and Catan is killing it. And I'm like, this is Piel making fun of Chris,
or is he saying he was a huge fan of the monkey thing Chris Catan used to do? No, here's what
that was in a movie that is sort of at most half -assed. I'd say eighth -assed about what it's supposed
to be about, which is that the entertainment industry fucks people up, very novel theme to chase.
In a world where that is the theme, they're also taking five minutes out of the movie to make fun of
a celebrity who's had a really rough time. Chris Catan, that's what they decided to do.
Hey, isn't this kind of against what we're trying to do, making fun of an actor who's really struggled
for about 25 years now? Oh, well, let's do it anyway. Very interesting.
Very interesting. A lot of a man who's been kicked to the point where he barely can stand up anymore.
Very interesting. I read his book, Chris Catan. The baby don't hurt me. Yeah, I can't tell if he's,
I've heard stories that he's a little bit difficult, but he might be difficult because he's in a
bad way or he might be in a bad way because he's difficult. I don't know. Yeah, look, I mean, I
forget that Peele was on Matt TV. Maybe he crossed paths with a young Chris Catan and he was a son of
a bitch. He seemed like an asshole in his book. I just, you know, I hear you. You make a good point.
I was going to say where we're always talking about you can't punch down. You can't punch down.
Here's a five -minute segment in a 2022 release where we make fun of Chris Catan. Interesting.
It's all I'm saying. When I was going to say about that era of SNL is when I revisited,
I find myself, and I never was at the time, but I find myself very attracted to Marley Shannon.
Sure. In that period. In that breakfast with Molly Shannon. Well, what's that, what's that insinuating?
We met at the breakfast, so I didn't nudge her in the morning and say you want to go grab pancakes.
Yeah. You nudge her, but it's just in public. Yeah, exactly, sir. Yeah, she was married at the time,
but yeah, yeah, attractive lady. Funny, charming, very nice, very funny. I did a pilot with
Sherio Terry. That was the first thing I did when I got to LA, an animated pilot, and I only had one
scene with her, but she, I remember the day she came in to do the scene, they asked us to rift some
stuff, and she was very nice, and we rifted and she was really funny, and then they were like,
that's good. We got it. She was like, all right, glad that's over. That's nerve -wracking.
And I was like, you're like a man. This is like what you do. Right. That was very surprised to hear
her have that take on it. By the way, the zoom 40 minute countdown clock is begun. What the
fuck is going on? Why does it do this all the time now? Because nothing works anymore, Joe, because
nothing works. Well, I, I don't even want to get into why I was late to the zoom. Let's leave it
out of the mix today. Let's keep things positive. I got a lot to say about nope. I almost feel like,
if you're ready, we can go right to the movie corner, and I can, I want to dig into nope. I'm
chomping at the bit here. I didn't realize how much I was as well. And, and I got a lot of shit to
say about nope, because it's like the, you know, if a kid's a bad egg from the start, you're like,
get this fucking kid out of my fucking face. It's fucking loser. But this is a kid that shows, it shows a
lot of promise. But just kind of keeps letting it down. That's how I felt about nope. And that can
be more frustrating than just a bad one. This is a movie that would lurch to life once in a while,
and then just kind of lose it again, in my opinion. I will say this before we get to the proper
interview. Yeah, or review, excuse me. It was, in my opinion, 500 times better than us,
because it was at least a linear plot that made sense. And it didn't have a very heavy -handed
bogged down, multi -tiered message in it, that it was desperately trying to tell me. It had a
message, and the message was there to take it or leave it. And if you weren't really paying
attention, you would have missed the message, which to me is how a message should always be in a movie,
unless you're dealing with a movie, you know, if you make a movie like colors about gang violence,
and obviously you're going to lean into the message a bit. But, you know, my point is is that gang
violence is a fun and healthy way for America's youth to get out of Grush. Yes. And colors
also, a movie that talked to the extensive SNL Congress scene in it. I didn't, I'm just joking.
Oh, okay. I have seen Dennis Hopper's colors, and I liked it quite a bit.
But anyway, in that sense, I thought this was far, far, far better than us. But also in that sense,
this was so point A to point B, without any ice cream or treats or anything in there,
to really, you know what I mean? Yeah. You got to have a simple story, but, you know,
we're not doing a Sam Shepard play here, like juice it up a bit, you know.
So we've got much to say. Anyway, I would love, if I may, to take us down to the movie corner,
everybody on letterbox talking about this movie, Pray, the new predator prequel, to give you a
lot of alliteration there. Don't worry. We're doing Pray, but we just didn't happen to watch it the
first weekend. It was out. We're going to do it and get to you about it. So watch Pray, get ready
for that. I watched a documentary called Clark that is new to streaming. I had a bunch of Amazon
credits and got it for two bucks. It is a documentary about Kevin Smith and thank God because there's
no information about the man available on the internet. It was done by someone named Malcolm Ingram,
but clearly done with a heavy dose of involvement from Mr. Smith himself. This is one of the more
faunting, dick -sucking documentaries I've ever seen in my entire life. It's as though it was edited
by Kevin Smith. It tells you the story that everyone knows about how he got into this business.
Everyone knows that story. It tells you basically movie by movie. It goes through clerks,
then everybody hated mall rats, then everybody liked chasing Amy, then everybody loved dogma.
At some point he just stops going movie by movie when things get shitty, then they stop doing that
and just jump forward a bunch. But essentially it's walking you year by year through the man's career
with interviews from Kevin Smith. They've arranged from funny stories you've heard before to really
annoying stuff. At the end we get a long segment about how Kevin Smith donated all of his
residuals from his movies to the women affected by Harvey Weinstein, which is like included as part
of the documentary, which feels gross. Then we just get into a chunk about how he's a nice man
and everybody loves him. It's a worthless documentary. I am a Kevin Smith fan. You sound like what?
You get to hear from a lot of people, Joe's favorite Justin Long. They bring Ben Affleck in
to talk about Jay and Silent Bob reboot, but they don't ask him about mall rats, chasing Amy,
Jersey girl. It's very strange in that regard. There's no Jason Lee, there's no lots of people,
there are some people talking at length. Jason Lee defected to down to Texas as a Scientologist.
I think he has since left the church, but he divorced his first wife by having a letter brought
there from the church of Scientology. I believe that's how that happened. I just started putting
together how many Scientologists coast are with T Cruz in his old movies. Like he's got Jason Lee as
his best friend of Manila Skye. He's got, who's the other guy? He's just, he's always surrounding
himself with Scientologists, something I've noticed. Beck always popping up in the Cruz movies.
There was, there was another really good example that I just can't think of.
Well, I just realized I have nothing for the movie corner because I have three, and I'm going to
episode. Okay. That's fine. I'll talk extra about nope. We'll still give you an up here. The one
thing I will talk about is I have gone on a multi -night rabbit hole dive of Tom Cruise interviews.
Okay. On YouTube. And quite frankly, it frightens me how much the man's philosophy is starting to
make sense to me. Now that is also the Scientology philosophy you're aware. That's what I'm saying.
That's why it frightens me. But I'm watching clips of him with Matt Lauer when he's promoting war
of the world's going like, back, you don't get it. Yeah. There's no such thing as a chemical
enbalancing. I've done the research and I'm listening and I'm like, it makes a lot of goddamn sense.
I've gone off my meds. Guess what? You off your meds? Problems right back there right again. Yeah.
You know, like, yeah. So I don't know. Maybe I'm just getting older. But the man seems to have
done well for himself. God knows what happens behind closed doors. I think a lot happens behind closed
doors. I don't want to know. And if I do have to know, don't tell me until that last mission impossible.
Let me get through the first two. Then tell me, but let me enjoy him out of the gate.
Are those final two? The final two? Yeah. It's a two part. That new Hollywood trend where
the final movie is two parts. Okay. Yeah. I don't know that I like that trend. You know.
Anyway, I rewatched a classic Boogie Nights early in the lady who had not seen the film.
And I just, I watched this movie pretty recently. It still feels fresh every time.
I noticed this time out how plotless it is. It's a lot of just kind of collections of seemingly
improvised scenes, but it all holds together. There's a through line. It seems to have been modeled
explicitly on good fellows almost moment to moment. It doesn't matter to me. He goes back to
the end of that film. Love sort of, you know, we're losing a lot of people in that age bracket,
which I don't care for. But Boogie Nights is a classic. It's Mark Wahlberg's best performance.
And I just can't get enough of it. Highest recommendation. And I think he bettered himself with
Magnolia by adding emotion to the mix. Mags. I liked it. I never watched it ever again. I didn't
have it in me. Yeah. Take cruise again. It's God. That's a heavy. That's a long, move fucking movie.
But yeah, you could do it over two nights. A good movie. I just, I just, I didn't rewatch Boogie Nights.
It's funny. Imagine I watched a few clips of it again on YouTube. And I enjoyed it. It's a great
movie. It is good fellows. You're 100 % right. Even down to the last scene where, you know, in good
fellows, it ends with Leo to, you know, I get to live, live the rest of my life like a schnuck. Right.
And in good fellow, I mean, in Boogie Nights, when he goes back to do the thing, he's still kind,
like he's still an asshole. Yeah. Well, that final scene when he takes his dick out and does the
monologue. That's actually raging bull. He couldn't decide which course is he was going to rip off.
Yeah. But he's still, like he's going back to play that like really gross character, Johnny.
Well, the character, what the fuck is the guy's name? He plays the cop's name, the cop character.
Oh no, I was going to say Johnny Ringo. There's a bunch of them. There's Johnny Wad,
who's the kind of guy he's going up against. Yeah, he, yeah, it is a Brock Brock,
Brock Landers, Brock Landers. He says, you know, we don't want to do what John,
Johnny Wad does, which is, you know, he's hitting hitting women and it's misogynistic,
it's gross, we don't see that. And then their characters start to do that. Yes. And then at the end,
when he goes back and, you know, it's sort of a redemption scene, but you can just tell
he's just tainted at that point. So it is sort of like the end of Goodfell's where it's like,
he got away clean, but did he? Yeah. You know, there was a price to pay, which is weird by the way,
it's always bothered me that they bring up Johnny Wad because the movie, the story of the movie is
loosely based on John Holmes. Right. But then they're mentioning John Holmes, which is odd,
they did that in that comedy store show on Showtime, where Al Madrigal's character was clearly based on
Freddie Prince Jr. But then they would talk about Freddie Prince Jr. And it made no sense to me.
But yeah, no, I'm in agreement. I don't like it. I saw a great new movie, really great, and you would
love this movie, Joe. It's new to Hulu called all my friends hate me. I'm not saying you'd love it
because that's true, Joe. Take it. It was directed by and starring an actor named Tom Storton,
who is a British actor that I was pretty unfamiliar with. I was unfamiliar with everyone in this film.
But what it is is a guy who was, it's a British movie. He's going to hang out at a big rented house.
For a weekend with his best friends from 10, 20 years ago.
The expectation is they're all going to drink and party and have fun, and he gets there and
just things are tense and weird from the jump. His fiance, who he has not yet proposed to,
is going to join them halfway through the trip. He gets there to find that a woman who he used to
up with, who his fiancee doesn't know about, is very much still into him and has recently
attempted suicide. So that's a complication to the weekend. And then there are multiple
other complications when his friends, nobody's there at first and they all come back from a local pub
and they've picked up some weird guy who is very aggro, very annoying. His like second scene in the movie,
he tries to grab our hero's dick while he's taking a bath and you're like, okay, it's just one of
those where you're like, what the fuck is going on? And if these are this guy's best friends, why are they
all acting like this? And it functions just like a great fucked up black comedy that slowly becomes
horror and really sort of a psychological horror. And I won't say any more than that, but I thought
it was really interesting, really well done and feels real. It feels like those weekends you have
with your old friends were like weird secrets kind of bleed out and people hook up and etc.
I really dug this movie, especially because I had never heard of it and the title just grabbed me
because it was clearly designed to stick out and it's well worth watching. They've buried it on Hulu. You
have to search for it. You'd never find it otherwise. It's a great new movie. Check it out.
I started re -watching the golden palace. Just desperate to find some good moments on Hulu in the
golden palace. It's not as bad as I thought it was. It's not great, but it's not as bad as I thought it
was. What are the stories, faulty towers, style, where they have crazy tenants each week? Exactly. It's like
we have a lawyer convention here. They're all ambulance chasers. And we have to pretend like we didn't
lose our insurance. And if any of them get wind of it, we're dead because they'll sue us and we'll lose
that. It's stuff like that. All right. There is a two -parter where Dorothy comes back. But they kind
of and it has its moments, but they kind of ruin it because it's her wanting to take Sophia home with
her against Sophia's will. And it makes Dorothy look kind of like an asshole. Yeah. But it's got
its moments. The saddest part of the show is that Estelle Gettie is clearly at the beginning stages
of dementia. Her energy is off. Her delivery is slow. You know, like you can just see that like
something's not right. And it's sad. It makes you sad to see it. It's not like it's devastating.
You know, it's but you know, it's a bummer. Anyway, I have a I have a scary stuff before we get into
note. I got one of the arrow. I mentioned this on one of the episodes. I forget which one. But when I
was out in LA with you, our friend and Helian who well, I don't want to say I don't get any trouble
and anybody in trouble. But a guy we know works at a place. And at that place, I bought a blue ray.
And it was Filipino teens.
Scissoring. It's going to say he gave me the sale price after the sale ended. Yeah.
The Scissoring teens part didn't even occur to me that that might be the problematic aspect of
the story. I think so too. Yeah. No, he got some arrow DVDs and well, blue as excuse me. But
I'm so shout outs to you, sir. But I most of these I'd seen a few of them ahead. But one of the ones
I bought for nostalgic purposes and I am so happy I did was the last starfighter. The arrow edition
of the last starfighter. What a great job they did. What an awesome nostalgic movie. What a
fucking cool movie. One of the first movies to ever use CGI ever like computer generated ships
and everything. Can we harm in a voice in the last starfighter? I've never seen the film. I own it.
He might be. I don't know. If he was, I missed it. Think of one of those. Is it Robert Preston involved?
Robert Preston plays an alien named Centauri who's like a shuckster based on his character from
the music man. Yeah. You know, as you would expect 4K restoration scan, high definition,
blue rate entity, P, all the audio specs as huge that you usually get. And then tons of special
features. If you've never seen the movie, it's about a kid that lives in a trailer park. It's
very similar to Star Wars. It's about a kid that lives in a trailer park who gazes up at the stars
and dreams of a better life for himself. And everything is going against him. He doesn't get the money
he needs for college. He has no hope of getting out of the trailer park. You know, his girlfriend
who he loves very much doesn't really want to leave because she's scared to leave her mom behind.
He's just, he's a broken soul at a young age, which I could relate to.
And the one thing he has gone for him is there's this video game called The Last Starfighter.
That's very much like the Star Wars arcade game. And he plays it and he's awesome at it. And he
like breaks the record on it or whatever. And then it turns out that the game is actually a test to
be recruited to actually go fight in the Starfleet against this alien race that's trying to conquer
the galaxy. It's just such a cool story for a kid to see. It's from 1984. You're writing that beautiful
pocket of fun 80 sci -fi cinema stars Lance Guest who played a, I don't I mean, he's in a bunch of
stuff. The thing I remember most he plays young Clark Kent in Superman, the movie.
But here's the wild part. So Arrow gives you the reversible cover.
So the front cover is their new take on it, right? And it's got a great
graphic here and a rendering of the kid playing the game. And then it just says the adventure of a
lifetime is about to begin The Last Starfighter. Pretty cool. You know, to the point vague but cool.
You open it, you got the original cover from the movie theater, which to me is a cooler looking poster.
You ready for the text? I'm ready.
Alex Rogan was a small town boy with big time dreams. But in his wildest dreams, he never suspected
that tonight he would become The Last Starfighter. The Last Starfighter.
It's a full paragraph. Yeah, no, that's too much. Which they used to do. Like I noticed that
along these arrow things, like, it'll be like, they would put like a full paragraph on the poster in
small print. And you're like, that's the whole pitch line. Yeah. You know,
they didn't want any confusion going in there. Wild. Anyway, check it out. It's worth it's worth seeing
the movie. The transfer looks amazing. And the blue rays a lot of fun and support arrow.
Maybe I'll watch it tonight. All right. No. No. Jordan Peele's latest and greatest question, Mark.
Uh, you already know that the hogs aren't quite up for this one. But what is Nope about Pat? Tell
us a little bit about this. I'd love you to tell it, Joe, because I don't know that I do know.
Well, it's about, uh, wait a minute. I'm sorry. Before we start, no, this is what I was sort of looking
for in the background on my computer. My buddy, Scott Weinberg, who does several great movie podcasts,
posted this years ago. This is the tagline for neighbors with John Belucia and Dan Acred. You
ready? Yeah. Earl Keese, a man who leads a routine suburban life, sits calmly waiting for his dinner.
Little does he know this may be his last homecooked meal. For somewhere in time and space exists a
world, a comic nightmare world where anything can happen. A world that this reserved hard
working homeowner is about to enter. In the next 24 hours, he will experience things he has never
experienced before and leave behind things he will never experience again. And somehow his life will
never be the same. For Earl Keen is about to meet the neighbors. That's on the poster. Is this
correct? What a terrible movie. It is, it's a very bizarre film to say the least.
Jesus Christ, that is insane. Yeah. So, so no.
God, the real estate. I mean, I'm looking at a house. They call you a lot, but all right,
that's neither here nor there. Anyway, it's about a brother and sister who are a little bit of
estranged. They don't explore that too much, but that's fine. They establish it. Their father
played by Keith David died. The brother and sister are Daniel Caluia from Get Out and also Kiki
Palmer, who I was less familiar with, but is very charming and funny. She's very funny. He's great.
They're, they're great at it. I would actually say of him. Why, why was he not a character? Why was
one of the biggest problems with the film? Very boring character and a very boring performance.
In my opinion, I felt like he was, I felt like that was the point he was extremely focused.
Yeah, I didn't have a lot to say, but was a man of action, which they show as the movie goes on.
So, that didn't bother me. I liked him a lot in it. That's Kiki Palmer, very funny.
Keith David, their dad has a, they, he owns a horse ranch. The ranch supplies horses for Hollywood
movies. Interesting, because the whole thing is sort of about entertainment and how Hollywood neglects
artists, particularly artists that aren't white. And they showed in the trailer that the first
piece of film ever made was the black guy riding a horse and that guy never gets the credit.
So they established that that's, you know, what this is in the trailer.
I'm listening to the David, what's his name? Al the, I never remember the fucking guy's name.
From the IT crowd. Oh, Ioday. Ioday, it's called Ioday on Ioday, a cinematic journey or something
like that. Or cinema. Yeah, a cinematic odyssey. Okay, but it's basically another book where he
decides to dissect himself. It's real, it's an audio book. It's really fucking funny. Okay,
but he does the thing about the first movie ever made. And he's like, he's like two men in a pool,
six seconds, three men of three men in a pool. After test screenings,
audio, the studio, the studio implemented heavy notes and rewrites.
This is on YouTube. No, it's on, it's an audible book.
Oh, audible. It goes, the sequel, some say rushed, three men in a lake was seen as derivative.
Yet, one of the characters was given his own spin -off franchise. It's really, it's really
fucking funny. Anyway, check it out. Then he was out there. So
their dad dies early on. They have to take over the business.
Kiki Palmer's character is very ambitious and sort of pushy.
The brother is, as I said, much more reserved. And, and he does not like that she's like that.
But they come together under this within the circumstance that he has seen a UFO on the property.
And she gets excited because she says, we're going to videotape it. And we're going to get on Oprah
with the video clip. And that's kind of the, again, the theme of the movie. Like, we're going to get
recognition as black filmmakers for getting something on tape. A clip about the same length as
this first movie that was ever made of something amazing that will bring recognition that we deserve
and our family deserves. That's as deep as the message goes, really. And then it goes from there.
And from there you get, it's, look, let's call it a, this movie is signs exactly.
It's exactly signs. I saw a bunch of people compare it to jaws. It's like, not really.
No, it's similar to close encounters and very, very similar to signs.
You've got a strange siblings. Yeah. We're siblings with, with problematic problem, right?
Yes, signs. You've got a guy whose legacy is in peril and has lost his way
in signs. It's Mel Gibson as a man of the cloth. And this, it's the son who fails to be able to
handle the responsibility of his father's legacy in this horse ranch, right? Because the first
job he goes on, it fails miserably. You then have quirky outsiders coming in
into the family. It's signed. It's literally signs. And it's about a rural family
being brought together again through what a sort of sinister alien invasion. Now in signs, it's
actually, this is going to be spoiler ridden. So if you haven't seen this and you don't want to know
whatever, turn it off now. But in signs, it's actually aliens that are invading.
And this you find out the ship itself is an alien entity that just looks like a ship.
But it's, it's, it's not a ship. It's an alien that looks like a ship, which as soon as they
reveal that, I was like, I don't care anymore. That's not that interesting to me. Like it's sort of a,
it's a unique, it's a very unique take. And I was like, oh, there's nothing really done with it.
There's nothing really interesting about it. And actually the first glimpse of the alien
is kids dressed up for some sort of stage show that Stephen Yoon puts on in a very odd B or C
story that's kind of runs throughout the movie. But that was a very chilling moment when you think
those are actually aliens. I was like, oh, this is that signs moment where everybody freaks the
fuck out when you first see it on the little videotape. That part was awesome. And I was in that moment,
I was like, here we go. Here's the mother fucker from get out. This is the, this is the
fucking guy from get out again because I did not have one moment like that enough. There was no one
moment that I was like, here we fucking go. And even when it turned out to be kids dressed up, I was
like, all right, you got me. But we're here from the real aliens now is what I thought. Okay, great
fake out. Now here come the real ones than we never got. I thought with Stephen Yoon's character.
So Stephen Yoon plays the owner of a tourist attraction ranch. Yeah, this is where the movie starts
to become problematic. And I don't mean offensive. I mean problematic with its execution and its structure.
You, there seems to be some sort of rivalry. And it's, I say, a parent or see, it seems to be
a rivalry. They, they never, there's like some weird cryptic discussion they're having about
him selling his ranch to Stephen Yoon. And you get the, you sort of get the idea that the price
that Stephen Yoon is offering is too low. But then like, but, but that's it. Otherwise, he's like
super nice to the brother and sister. But then there's this scene where Kiki Palmer
returns to the ranch with these plastic horses. Yeah, she says she's going to use as, you know,
decoys to draw the alien in because you, you realize early on that the alien for whatever reason,
like sets the horses off or takes them or whatever. And then it turns out she stole the horses
from Stephen Yoon's place. And you're like, why would you do that? I don't understand. Like there's
no reason for you to do that, especially after he was really nice to you. And then that's why he
sends his kids there dressed as aliens to like let all of their horses loose. Or no, to steal one of
their horses. They're actual horses. I'm like, what the fuck is going on here? Like, did I miss
something? Yeah, there's clearly tension going on in all of the relationships, but it's never really
clear and you don't care. Then we have to talk about the most effective scene in the movie, which is,
of course, has nothing to do with the movie really outside of thematically. But the Stephen
Yoon character as a boy had to deal with a lot of trauma. He was on the set of an alph -type
multi -cam with a monkey in the place of alph and a frustrated father character. We know something bad
happened. We see flashes of it throughout. And then we see a full, very effective, very suspenseful,
scary five minute segment where this monkey wreaks havoc on the set of the multi -cam while the
Stephen Yoon character watches as a boy. It brutally murders this woman. The father, for reasons
unclear to me, comes out of hiding to yell at the monkey, even though he just watched it beat a
woman savagely for 10 minutes. And then of course, he's beaten savagely. The boy sits and watches.
And it's all really cool and effective. And I guess makes his point that the entertainment
industry doesn't care about the people in it. But to what end? Oh, I didn't catch that. That's
interesting. My takeaway from it was that it's about how predators act. And this alien is a predator.
And versus predator. But then the alien kills Stephen Yoon, like he's one of the first people
with kills because Stephen Yoon is like way too arrogant with it. Yeah. Which was furtherly confusing
to me because I was like, but he's the one that seems to understand how predators then why did the
monkey kill him? I don't know. Yeah. It brings up a lot of points. And I'm sure there's some
fucking annoying nerd probably one that listens to this podcast who thinks they got it all figured out.
But what it really is is a jumble of thematic shit that lands occasionally, doesn't land more
often than occasionally. There's certainly no consistent clear through line that you're following
thematically. But aside from that, you know, get out as a classic example of a movie that is scary,
but also has a razor sharp through through line thematically that works beautifully.
I think Peele is now trying to be a little more esoteric, a little more weird, a little more.
You figure it out, but he's not really in command of his skills yet. If I may, I think he could,
like when when Shyamalan fucks up, he's got amazing suspense sequences in there. You know, even when
the movie sucks, Peele, this movie would have great suspense outside of the monkey scene for like
literally 10 seconds, and then just abandon it. Then 15 minutes of just dry, not particularly
entertaining, often confusing story. Then there'd be a little more suspense. That's not how a suspense
movie should work. You know, you can't build suspense when you're immediately abandoning suspense
at every turn. For me, I just felt frustrated by it. It's like someone grabbing your dick,
jacking it off furiously for 10 seconds, and then leaving the room is how the whole movie
felt to me, and I felt annoyed and frustrated by it. It's, it's, yeah, I mean,
I agree, I agree. It did the thing that Godzilla, the first, you know, the first of this new
series of who gives a shit Godzilla versus movie. Yeah. It did the same thing that first one did.
It would like get Godzilla would step into the frame with the other monster,
and you get all excited, and then it would cut away. Right. And it just kept doing that and doing
that and doing that, and then expecting you to really save up all your excitement for the last
seven minute showdown. And no, you just, it doesn't work like that. This, this, just, aside from
the sequence where the kids play the prank on him, this never had, and I think signs is not a good
movie. I think signs is a passable movie with great suspense sequences and an ending so schmaltzy.
It makes me want to fucking puke. By the way, by the way, signs dead wife in this dead father.
It's signs. But anyway, I think very often, and I have talked to screenwriters who do this actively,
a screenwriter or director will just watch a film and have it on while they're writing a film,
and essentially just copy the entire structure of it. It happens more often than you think.
Sometimes people catch it. Sometimes people don't. Well, it's one thing if you do it, and you go,
you know, hey, man, you know, there will be blood. If you look at it, it's the Godfather. Here's one.
You don't even know whatever, right? I'm not saying it is, but you go, oh, that's interesting,
but they made it about oil, and then that threw me off the scent. Right. If you do it with this,
you go, I'm going to model a movie about aliens. Yeah. Exactly after a movie about aliens that was
also the third movie in this breakout director's portfolio that was also that director's leap at
doing a summer blockbuster style. It's like, you can't mirror every aspect of it. Yeah. So,
well, you can. It's just going to be obvious. But anyway, you know, I only saw signs once I own it.
I like to revisit it. I found this to be a bar and fear your movie to signs. Well, what I was
going to say is it never has that thing like there's that sequence in signs when the alien is the
guy's hiding in the cupboard in the kitchen. Yeah. And the aliens walking around the kitchen. And you
know there is real danger. He is in trouble. That's when he gets like its finger by accident. Right.
Like that scene was so freaky. And I remember the scene in the theater when they they show the news
footage from like Argentina. That was that was a flip out. Like I've rarely seen it a movie. Yeah.
And the alien walks through frame. Well, I just got chills talking about it. I remember the entire
theater screaming like that. And there were moments in this. Again, it was when the little kids
stand, you know, or in the farm. When that little first little kid stands up, I remember everybody went,
you know, and it was cool. And I was like, okay, this is cool. And then it just never got back to
that. The scene where the entire horse ranch show gets sucked up inside of the alien was sort of
interesting and creepy. But when you saw like the woman like in a tube, you know, like getting sucked
up, that was like a weird couple of minutes scene where it was hard to even tell it was going on. But
that was unsettling, you know, that was a creepy little moment. Yeah. Yeah. But the thing is, is like, so
which is the last name, David? What? The main character. David?
Isn't this first name, David? That actor Daniel Collouin or Daniel, sorry, Daniel. I can never
remember this. But when Daniel, forget his character's name too. But when Daniel says, you can't look
the predator in the eye. Like that's what's going to keep us alive. You're immediately you're like,
no, you can look the predator in the eye because I saw the little Chinese kid look the predator in the
eye. Korean. But yeah, sorry, Korean. Sorry. You know what I'm saying? Well, I saw that guy look,
so, so, so right away, you're like, well, I don't, okay. And then he subscribes that philosophy through
the whole movie with every encounter. And then in the end, he does look it in the eye. And you're like,
okay, okay, okay. So you could look it in the eye, which is what I thought because we saw the little
kid look the monkey in the eye, right? But why the fuck did the monkey let the kid live? And why?
I guess it's, it's the, it's the predator's way of saying tell my story.
One the others that this is a danger that I'm out there. I guess I couldn't find this. I didn't
understand what it was. It yes, the predator picks one to, to, to spare. It's a real sign when you sense
that there's something going on that you're not getting. And, and you don't really care enough to
even look like I was going to read some theories and stuff. And I'm like, you know what, this movie did
not do enough to make this a complete experience for me. And I also don't care. When this movie ended,
I wanted to not think about these people anymore. They bring in the guy from Fry's electronics
just to have somebody else in the mix and out here. Brandon Pareia is the name. They bring in this guy.
He was kind of funny. And Scott, who was a, you know, I guess, supposed to be like the hard -ass.
Michael Wincott is in this thing, playing like Tom Waits dehydrated, right? Wearing like a literal
cape or Mark, what's his face? The clear character is that OJ, which is obviously supposed, there's a
lot of that. Like, okay, but what does that mean? Why, why would you name a black man OJ? What is your
point? You know, like there's a lot of that. There's something, it's a symbol for something, but I don't
care to know. And I also don't know if you know, and I don't think it's as cool as you think it is,
basically. I also thought the OJ thing was like a cheap, because you're supposed to,
it's like that moment where that white lady is like, your name's OJ. Like,
and it's like, I get that that's supposed, I guess supposed to be some sort of racial commentary,
but I'm like, it's not. It's crazy. I feel like anybody named OJ, a person would be like,
your name's OJ. The name at this point is worthy of comment. But, but especially when you can go by
awful or whatever the fuck your name is, why are you going by? And Mark, I thought for a minute,
did they name him this because we're supposed to think the entertainment industry made OJ do what he
did? These are the connections I was trying to make. Honestly, that's not that far off. It might be,
that might be what it is. Mark Lennigan, that's what I was trying to think of. I wish Mark Lennigan
played the part. But, but he comes in. What a corny, hacky cliche character this guy comes in,
Michael Wincock. And, you know, he's a DP. And they make it look like he's worsened fucking wells.
And all he's doing in his spare time is cutting footage of animals, eating other animals. Like,
he just sits there. And then, so they call him and hire him for this or try to hire him for this gig.
And he's clearly not interested. Number one, because they have no money to give him. And number two,
he's like, that top, that space on the top of the mountain where you're trying to go, you never
get to walk down from it or something. It's like a life lesson. Like, let this alone. It'll cost you
everything kind of thing. And what's being insinuated in these scenes when they talk to my
Wincock is that he knows about the alien. And is staying away from it, which is so insane,
that that's, that this is not explained, at least in one little moment where you see him see it
and you see him walk away and go, fuck that. I know better. There's no moment. I had read that there
is a much, much, much longer cut of this movie and longer assumption. I know, I know. Because to
me, it felt super claustrophobic all the time. And it's two hours plus, of course, all of your time
is spent on a fucking horse ranch. Like, it starts to get to me claustrophobic. I wanted to branch out
at some point, but there's a much longer version apparently. And I think that some of those cuts just
led to big narrative gaps. I mean, there's no, there's no real build to an exciting conclusion.
I like Kiki Palmer, you know, us tracking her on her motorcycle, driving through. That was filmed
in a really cool way. I like the final moment of triumph for the OJ character. And yet, it just left
me feeling empty. There was really a quiet disappointment as everyone kind of trudged out of the
theater. And it did not feel like the summer blockbuster it was trying to be at all.
It didn't feel exciting or fun or anything to make. It could, it could have. Yeah.
There were full moments. There were full ideas that were not executed fully. So
you got the kid from fries when the aliens hovering over him.
And it took me 20 minutes to understand what the hell he did. And when I understood what he did,
I was like, that's cool. That should have been a moment. But he wraps himself in barbed wire.
So when he gets sucked up, he'll get spit back out. That should be like a hero's moment.
You should see when he notices the barbed wire and there's suspense for him to get to the barbed wire.
And he does. And then he's wrapping himself. And then when he gets picked back out, give us a,
you know, suck on that motherfuckers. Something had the alien go, oh,
yeah, in a Walter Mathau voice. Give us the moment. Yeah. But instead it's so passive. And you're like,
you're like, wait, why did he wrap himself up in barbed wire? What was that? I didn't understand
that a guy who's clearly such a movie buff and grew up on the 80s movies and etc. Just can't do a
standard set up payoff. And he was, look, again, get out as a masterpiece of set up payoff.
When Lowell comes in at the end, you're cheering, you know, but it's yeah, he's lost something here.
There's there's something that just doesn't it ever take off. It never pushes the gas. A critic said,
a critic said he's not the next hitchcock. He's the next Shyamalan. I agree with that 100%.
He came out of the gate with a masterpiece that was so start to finish simple and brilliant,
but it had it where it needed it to keep you on the edge of your seat. Yeah. He then came out
with a very polarizing follow up film. Some people love it. Some people hate it. Yeah. Then he came out
with a summer blockbuster about aliens that was kind of corny and you just walked away going,
all right, I guess. And so so nice to be the true disaster lady in the water time. That's when
things really fall to shit. But this is what happens. This happened with Shyamalan. And we're not
picking on peel. This is what happens. Shyamalan got so high on his own supply. He goes,
my next movie is a story I made up night by night that I would tell my son at bedtime. And you're
like, wait, that sounds right. That's what lady in the water was. And you're like, what are you talking
about? Yeah. And then he did it. And you're like, oh, boy, Jesus Christ. So, you know, man.
And then there's the thing. Oh, here's another one of these ideas that was cool. And then they
didn't, whatever. When when the Tom Waits guy takes his camera and literally marches up the hill
to get right underneath the alien. So it's the metaph, it's the physical version of the metaphor
that he's talking about the entire movie. And knows he's going to die, but does it because he's
going to get the shot. And I'm watching him do this. And I'm going, this is so awesome. He's going to
get them the shot that nobody else can get. And he's going to sacrifice his life for it because that's
how much he cares about cinema. And then the thing won't be able to digest the camera. And it'll
spit it out. Well, he does get sucked up. He gets half the shot because they showed from his perspective.
The camera shorts out because he takes an electric camera after they go out of their way to set up
that he has a camera that doesn't use electricity. 10 minutes of the movie spent setting that up.
Um, he gets sucked in. The camera gets spit out. And it's never referred to again. Yeah. And it's
pointless. And then the thing that does get the picture that they need the entire time is the
contraption that's at the Wild West thing that Stephen, uh, what's his face owns that it's a well that
takes photos or it takes photos from within the well. That might have electricity. I don't think
it does. I didn't understand. No. But then you're like, what was the point of of the guy coming in with
the non -electric camera? That was just a stall to get us eventually to the point that she takes the
picture with the well camera. Uh, and the well camera had no significance. I mean, talk about a
missed opportunity. Talk about a missed opportunity. Tom weight shows up and he goes, I have a camera
that doesn't use electricity. By the way, how the hell does he know that this thing shuts down
electrical fields? And you don't know that because they never established it. But anyway, he shows up
and he goes, I have a camera that doesn't use electricity. And here he is cranking this thing,
you know, like not shooting us for a lot of two types of shit, right? Yeah.
Furiously cranking it to get the footage and you're watching it and you're going, oh my god,
they're getting the shot she's been talking about the whole movie on the type of camera that photograph
their great, great, great grandfather. And then in the end, it's like, no, actually, they're going to
something made up just for the movie. Oh, well, Cam, that their enemy had on his ranch thing,
there is his tourist ranch. And you're like, oh, so I guess it was supposed to be like,
Ha, ha, we got the glorious thing you were going after with your own stuff. And you got killed trying
to do this other way to do what? Why? Ha, ha at the Steven Union characters. He's not a villain in
this thing. He's a kid with trauma who grows up to be a, but seems like a nice man, an entrepreneur.
No, well, in that thing where he's going to like bring the aliens to the people, you see that he's
an asshole suddenly. Because when he, when he, when he, when he recalls, when he's prepping for that,
and he recalls the monkey thing, yeah, because that's when you see it fully, when it cuts back to him,
he's smiling because he's like, I, the predator, let me go as this one will, too, because I am special.
I mean, what, what's sort of a bizarre arc is that for a character? You know,
I think it doesn't even make sense. I actually thought it would have been really cool.
If I thought it would have been really cool, if when he was saying his wife,
he's talking about his wife and he hadn't seen her. Yeah, I was like, oh my god,
the lady they show in the commercial with the face that's all ripped up.
Uh -huh. Holy shit. That's the little girl that was his co -star. She got attacked by the monkey.
That's going to be his wife. Right. How beautiful. He's going to feel, he had carried such guilt.
Yes. That he was the star of the show and the seven that he married this woman and loved her
for her bravery and spirit and whatever. And then no, there's a great story. Yeah. And then no,
she's just there as a friend. But then he says, my first crush.
Yeah. So you could have made the connection. Yeah. And made the story kind of beautiful and
interesting. And maybe they'd die in each other's arms. Nope. Nothing. So what I was thinking,
guys, that poor bitch, that poor bitch dies after all she's been through. She gets sucked up into
what she still goes to see her friend for like a nice afternoon. And then she winds up dying after
dodging death all those years ago. But, uh, if you'll recall, Joe, 15 maybe even 20 years ago,
there was a woman on Oprah. Oh, yeah. And her face ripped off by a monkey. And it was a big
national, national news story. Yeah. Did this have anything to do with that? No.
You're sure it wasn't some sort of inspiration for this or? Well, that lady, I guess,
well, hey, no, because here's why there could have been, and maybe there isn't this longer cut,
some commentary on now this poor woman's claim to fame is not her acting work, which was her dream.
But the fact that she was disfigured by a monkey. Yes. Because that was that woman's claim to fame.
She, I don't think she wanted to be an actor. I think she just, she just got fucked up. She just
wanted to be a lady with a face. And who can I remember? Yeah. But I'm sure that the idea came
from that like, like, oh, what if you did a thing where a monkey did that on the, this is the thing.
And we got to, we got to wrap up. But, but this is the thing I'll say. And then I'll shut up. And then
whatever the hell you want to say, Pat, please, uh, peel, it's, it's a lot, and you're seeing a lot of
this in, you're seeing a lot of this across the board and entertainment now. But where I'm seeing it
the most is, is, you see it a lot from Star Wars and the way they're writing things. But peel to
me is becoming a guy who is, and he, he has massive admiration for John Carpenter. And John Carpenter
did this with Halloween. Uh, Argento's another guy that did this. He's becoming a guy that writes down
really interesting ideas in a notebook. Here's one here that's circled. Here's one over here.
And then he starts, I'm assuming he starts playing Connect the Dots. And you can't always write
like that. There has to be, you have to pay things off. Things have to be there. They don't have to be.
But then to me, it hurts the movie. I think, I think most of Argento's movies as movies,
suck as visual experiences, brilliant. They're brilliant. They look brilliant. They're freaky. They're
all bunch of things, but they're not good movies. Right. They're just not. I'll agree with that. I
wash them all. And I'm like, you know, maybe on the big screen stone or something this would be
having more of an effect. But here at home, I'm bored. And I like what I'm seeing in terms of like
looking through an art book. But I'm just not that entertained or intrigued. And you are not paying
off the stories. Peel, you know, the one interesting self -aware moment to bring it all full circle
in that clerk documentary was Kevin Smith lighting up a giant joint while they're interviewing him.
And he goes, he can't. Yeah. Okay. And they said he's been high every single day since he started.
He's never won. But he's like, people ask all the time, did we kill my career or did my career
really start poppin when I started smoking weed? And I'm like, nobody really asked that question.
I don't think Kevin. And we all know the answer. Yeah. In his mind, he's like, this is what saved me
and allowed me to keep working or whatever. There is an element of these peel movies that feels like a
guy with a surplus of ideas, getting high and not making the proper connections between story points.
And a lot of times you can get away with that by saying, like, oh, you know, I was trying to be,
you know, thought provoking or trying not to spell everything out for a viewer or whatever. But at the
end of the day, especially when you're making a blockbuster, you just simply have to correct your
story points or you're not doing your job as a writer. And I, you know, it's a harsh criticism.
But it's only out of my love for Jordan Peele himself and get out. I feel like this, we're
getting into he might be a guy who can't spread himself over 10 projects because the projects aren't
coming in good. He's not the guy and he needs to buckle down and finish something. He's not. He can't,
it's obvious at this point. He's got to focus on one thing and make it great. And then I'm that way,
some writers can do a really prolific thing. But when you look at the twilight zone and you look
at these movies, it's like, come, like, come on, man, we're all pulling for you. And I think people
are reviewing the movies that they wish these movies were us and no, but they're not. They're just not.
Anyway, folks, my hog is pretty slanted down on this one. I'll give it that you could watch it once
enjoy it to a certain extent, but then you're never going to want to watch it again. That's my take.
It's not feverishly down, but it's pretty down. I got to go, Pat, what do you think?
Yeah, my hog is, I would say, you know, it's, there's blood in it, you know, it's longer. It's not,
it's not like a cold shower, coiled up frightened tadpole or something. It's hanging there,
but there's certainly no rigidity to it. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
The premiere of season two of the Miss Pat Show is August 11th, which is tomorrow. Highly recommend
watching it on the BET Plus app because you get longer and certainly filter episodes.
Joe DeRosa, comedy on Instagram and Twitter, Joey Roses NYC for all things Joey Roses and
Joe DeRosa info for my upcoming dates and shows. We'll be back with Elvis. Thank you, folks. We'll see
you next time and we'll see you in hell.