Welcome to we'll see you in hell here we are down in hell
with the flames all hot making you sweat and get horny look who it is too horny
little devil oh no I don't want any part of this folks stuff you're in hell you
have to hello what was the first use of horny little devil was it oh God you
devil I mean what why did this start horny devil I think Christ said it in the Bible you saw
see little minks yeah Jesus is trials in the desert yeah when Satan tempted him yeah I don't
know who said it no definitely wasn't I had a couple trials in the desert too last time I went to
Vegas I only exist out here because of me I had a good folks show up the other day to my friend
who was diagnosed with cirrhosis of the liver due to alcohol yes usually what doesn't yeah and I
said I said Brian the good news is the cirrhosis is manageable unfortunately your personality is
terminal using the man's real first name here on the podcast he doesn't give rats ass trust me
but I know a million brines okay for all you know it could be a could be Brian he ran it could be
Denny he Denny he probably died with cirrhosis of the liver could be post sane oh boy could be a that's
all the famous Brian's I know Denny he actually got sober before many years before he died because he
told a story of I think a holiday dinner and he said his small child looked over at him he was like
three drinks in and like getting ramped he was ramping into it and he said his five year old son looked
over at him with an expression that just said oh no daddy you're going to be drunk again he said
that's what got into quit yeah that do it for me too Brian that would do it for me as well yeah so
anyway Joe what's going on in the world I mean are you watching the new domino challenge which is
hosted by the fat guy from modern family domino the the you mean the domino's pizza challenge are you
are you watching the new domino challenge you sent me with that I love it from modern family
what's that guy's name Jesse Brian no idea the fat one the fat one I'm sure he loves
when the people say that well we the first time he came well I liked modern family early on for sure
I know when I dropped out it wasn't that it had gotten bad I just had tired of the show but
we writers room once all listened to him on stern as he talked about I shouldn't share I'm
not going to share the story I'm just going to live next time you see me probably was a stern who cares
yeah no true well no that it was a girl who was like I'm worried he's going to talk about our date
together then he talked about how bad her breath was on the date on stern he wait he we say he
talked about how bad her breath was that's correct it says this co -worker and we're just sitting
there listening to this famous person talk about how bad her breath was on on Howard Stern
oh in your co -worker yeah oh I see okay now maybe that started it you know I was just like
what an asshole well I mean he didn't you know that's not that that crazy of a story to tell like
hey why don't the girls breath was bad by the way could have been talking about any one of
a hundred girls maybe he was dating the true you know that's true by the way famous this girl's name
was halitosis Jones I should say that was the original script title for osmosis Jones yeah
it was greater change because it didn't make sense who was in that was Orlando Jones osmosis Jones
I think Chris Rock was Orlando Jones and Bill Murray was the host it was kind of an interspace
thing without any of the laughs or story or goodness god almighty up there with Pluto Nash it's
pretty bad Jesus Christ pretty bad uh yeah well speaking of pretty bad good let's talk about I got
a news psycho terrible transition just terrible oh like yours are fucking good I say I say bad and
you go speaking of pretty good we got my son this is of good nobody speaking about my son this
is your bother me doesn't even count as a transition you're just saying the opposite I don't give a
shit do you think the transitions are seamless seamless Joe Jackson over oh god
what where do they where do they find talent like you in the television business how hard is it
the the the most seamless transitions since Caitlin Jenner Jimmy fucking the most seamless transition folks
since Kate Jenner that's a cancelable Joe okay hey hate to break it to you it's a seamless transition
I'm complimenting it the uh uh Disney plus finally dropped the Obi -Wan Kenobi trailer and it is
awesome it's everything I wanted it to be I'm super excited you and what happened here they cut
they cut Darth Maul is that was that some news he was in it and they cut him
uh I don't know I saw that article right repeatedly it was like Darth Maul cut from the the Obi -Wan
well I mean he falls into that storyline if you follow the animated shows which I do
which I don't yeah I know that but but the animated shows established that Darth Maul is hunting Obi -Wan
he doesn't can he never he doesn't confront him until a very specific moment which this show would not
be able to showcase uh but anyway um show looks great if you're a fan of Clone Wars and particularly
rebels they've got the inquisitors brought into the live action realm now which is really cool um
you and the Obi -Wan and what age this is so this is past the the prequels but pre the sequels it's like
eight years after revenge of the Sith because they show a young Luke Skywalker and he's like probably
six seven eight -year -old kids somewhere there still played by Hayden Pantanare from Heroes
no are you still played by Hayden Christensen that's Anakin Skywalker that's not from Shattered Glass
yeah I love to play by uh Shattered Glass an amazing film yeah uh so who plays is Hayden
Christensen evolved yeah he won't plays Darth Vader okay that's I was referring to an eight -year -old
Luke Skywalker and we're talking about two different characters here who plays Lil Luke is a Jonathan
Levin a little boy is it a hologram of Jonathan Lipnicki and German wire
and he's saying the uh the human head weighs eight pounds day unless it's got that big black
Vader helmet on it they brought in uh the kids all three kids from home improvement to do a rotating
Zachary Ty Bryan Jonathan Taylor Thomas Tim Patricia Heaton yeah and in a very bold move they're doing
and I'm not here style thing where they're all playing different versions of Luke in different scenes
and at one point and very controversial a lot of fans do not like this but Vader apparently takes off
the helmet at one point and goes oh oh oh oh oh oh oh even though the uh Tim Allen
uh hog house in a while yeah I hate it yeah um Tim Allen one of the most unlikely movie stars
there ever was you know when I did Vine I think I might have talked about some here I used to get
is this Tim Allen as a comment all the time and it made me so self -conscious meaning like are you doing
another just people who thought that I looked like Tim Allen and nothing like Tim Allen
well I don't think so either but especially since I was doing that when I was like 30 I was like
this is really traumatizing to me these people think I look like Tim Allen crazy Tim Allen is a
square jawed brunette Roger Brooks you're more of a soft oh shut the fuck up you started with me
lost a good deal of weight you look wearing a bag you see it I didn't see you didn't look good I
look said I looked soft I'm joking with you you started pushing my buttons I'm pushing them back
I uh I look how did I push your buttons I did take a terrible transition you said you didn't want
to know part of my hot and horny intro oh I'm sorry I said I'm sorry you didn't get me hard Joe
no before we started recording this one Joe's picture froze as he was cupping his bosom
both hands and I had to send him a photo of the shot it wasn't a flattering shot but I uh
oh yeah yeah all right so the Obi -Wan just one more thing yeah hating Christiansons back
Joe Edgerton who you used to hate with a passion I hated Joel Edgerton there was a time where
in our private life Jason Bateman is this is way before the gift but there was a time in our private
life where you want to discuss Joe Edgerton you had a real dislike for me I couldn't I couldn't
make header tails out of it I was like I don't understand why you don't like this guy I'm I uh I don't
love or hate but he I liked his film the gift I'll say that he's Joe Edgerton to me is the better
looking Jesse plements but not quite as good an actor but he's a good actor plements to me is as close
as we're gonna get to somebody as magical as Philopsy Moore Hoffman he doesn't get there actually
when he really started kind of getting there was in Friday night lights I knew that kid was special he
was the 18th lead on Friday night lights he played this nerd who was always crushing on really hot
girls out of his league uh he was in like a cookie monster death metal band he was a great great
character and they kept writing him more and more as the season went series went on but um I
always like him I like I think wait plements are you back to Edgerton plements I couldn't give two
shits but Edgerton but I I don't know why I would have said I hate them you you you said he was one
of those actors where it didn't make any sense that he had a career that he brought nothing well there's
tons of those there's tons of those I might have been talking about Sam Worthington that's a guy that
can maybe get my bander up Adrian Grenier can get my bander up Worthington still is one where I'm like
I don't understand but by the way Worthington is he's gonna be on all these avatars he's just gonna
he's so he he's struck out god bless he was in the biggest movie of all time was unable to parlay that
into superstardom and now he's got employment for the next 25 years because he's like a honestly he's
like a Mark Hamill you know and I love Mark Hamill but you know it's very similar no you're right
very similar but I've never liked a Worthington character as much as I've like Luke Skywalker ever
right ever what it seems like to me now like Worthington isn't an offensive actor or something but like
there were so many actors in the 70s 80s I'd even go 90s where you love to see them they had their
own thing they had their own vibe they were you know like they could release a picture everybody
now and especially in comedy which I've talked about multiple times we don't have movie stars anymore
we just don't have them I agree the people who are like so Harrison Ford is beloved by dorks
uh cool people black people white people Asian people everyone can agree on Harrison Ford that's a
star we don't have those anymore you'll have like this guy Sebastian Stan that I talk about in the
last show he's in everything now he's hot he's in all the Marvel movies he's got like 10 million
Twitter followers have you ever heard anyone Joe in your day -to -day life talk about Sebastian Stan
no that's not a movie star it's not a star I'm sorry I agree I agree you know the one I always
go back to is Jason Clark you know my beef with this guy I just saw him and something actually
I don't remember what it was I turned something on last night oh god damn oh it was the terrible HBO
show uncanny yeah one fucking candy I go this this this this this LA Lakers series looks okay
Adam McKay how are they not ripping this thing apart how are they now I turn the goddamn thing on
opening credits I see Jason Clark's game I go this does this mean it's gonna suck and five minutes in
John C rally breaks the fourth wall starts addressing camera in like one of the hackiest turns
well that's Adam McKay's whole style right it was like fuck this I turned it off it was terrible
it is I mean the fact that Adam McKay walked away from anchor man stepbrothers
tell it egg and eggs that world of like hard hitting fucking great American companies one classic after
another and he is now doing this it's very sad to me he's chasing that Oscar you know and
look I lumped I lumped don't look up and there as well the fact that's nominated for best picture is
one of the more embarrassing nominations in the history of the Academy Awards it's really it's crazy
that that's nominated for best that that is a two and a half hour sketch about global warming that
if it aired on SNL would not be the best sketch on SNL and I think it's a disgrace but anyway that
excuse me that show about the Lakers and I'm no basketball fan but I was riveted by every second
of the last dance the Chicago Bulls thing sure I mean I was riveted I watched it twice all 10
hours of it I watched it twice and I have no interest in sports or basketball yeah this thing is
so bad and he's doing like rip off Oliver Stone shit it's terrible and he's doing it like there are
big chunks of this thing that are completely out of focus he's trying to do the 70s grain
but they went too far and I'm not kidding when I say 10 % of every episode is out of focus I watched
one and a half and now I'm done it's it's a bad show I'm out I couldn't do that that that monologue
that Riley gives to the naked woman in bed which is basketball is sexy yeah look at these I mean it's
just it's embarrassing it's theater it's theater major shit yeah anyway show sucks but but Joel
Edgerton is back in Obi -Wan playing Owen Lars yeah we got a little off top uncle Luke Skywalker
which I'm excited to see I'm excited for the show anyway let's get to the movie corner before we
get to sidetracked here actually thought we were in a movie corner that's how lost I got
oh boy that's that edibles hitting yeah well no you've been talking about this NBA show for 25 minutes
no we we were talking about bet we spun into bad actors from the Obi -Wan thing and then I said Jason
Clark and I said I knew the show was going to suck when it said Jason Clark was in it yeah no Clark
yeah from zero dark 30 on he's just a presence that I don't get I don't get him annoying face too
just annoying face he does I don't know what it is I don't know what it is he looks like it looks like
a lot of high school bullies frankly face is too bunched up yeah there's a lot going on all right
I saw I'm gonna go with TV shows because I think I'm out of movies I watched impeachment
American crime story or American crime story impeachment whatever it is called it was on FX and
usually FX shows go right to Hulu but this one they knew they had big money so they kept it off Hulu
for a long time it just dropped I think and this just kind of snuck up on me this realization but I
think American crime story is one of the best television shows on TV the OJ Simpson American crime
story is one of the great TV accomplishments of my life I think I loved it I can't I think that was
the last show that I was riveted to that I was desperately weighed it refreshing waiting for it to
air each week loved it and they got you know they got movie people they got the guys who did Ed
would to do that show and I think it really shows then they did the Versace one a step down but
fascinating and just like dark and fucked up and sexy and weird and I like that a lot too now impeachment
is the first one that I felt like I knew a great deal about the case because I was 13 or whatever
when this impeachment stuff happened and I was reading all this shit but they uncovered a lot I
didn't know they got Sarah Paulson playing Linda trip and I know it was controversial because they
got her in a fat suit or whatever but they made her look way better than Linda trip actually looked
Linda trip is one of the greatest monsters of all time I mean in American politics recording her
dear friend in a food court to rat her out just because she like wanted attention so they make her
into this really fascinating character in the show and I loved how Sarah Paulson played her she was
great the role of Bill Clinton is played by Clive Owen which at first you don't get it doesn't quite
make sense they give him a big prosthetic dick nose like Clinton has but by the end of this thing
Clive Owen who is just one of the great actors I think he's so good as Clinton it takes a minute to
adjust to it but he really gets into this guy and portrays him as a man I took it with no soul
and it's really fascinating how critical they are of both Clintons in this thing love that he's great
Eddie Falco plays Hillary Clinton and honestly the role links up a little too much with Carmelo
soprano she's an actress like Julie Louis Dreyfus where I don't like seeing her and things other than
that signature role so yeah I thought everybody was fantastic in the show I thought the writing was
exceptional and I really do feel three seasons in even though it's not a traditional series
but this is one of the best shows on TV they take big cases that everybody kind of knows about or
thinks they know about and shines all kinds of new light on them dramatizes them and packs them
with amazing casts down to really lower level people so there's other Ryan Murphy stuff American horror
story or ratchet and all that it doesn't interest me but this series I think very much works and I
love it I recommend it impeachment is just as good as the other ones OJ is the best but it's a great show
I love it all right good I'm for those of you that are unaware of what's happening on our end
uh this is now the third time we've had to restart this because of the zoom crashing on my end
brand new MacBook Pro best internet speed that time Warner or spectrum rather offers
doesn't doesn't fucking work I'm two feet from the fucking modem the fucking thing doesn't work
does anything work anymore does anything just fucking work the way it's supposed to anymore
no the answer is no the answer is simply no god damn it I'm furious right now anyway
all right I rewatched black man speaking of Joel Edgerton
yes wonderful performance by Joel in that film wonderful performance was that was at the last
big Johnny Depp release I believe the the turn down yeah I believe so he's fantastic in it
Edgerton is fantastic in it Kevin Bacon is fantastic in it um what's his name Sherlock Holmes is
fantastic in it Benedict Benedict Comper Batch um who else you got it oh you got Jesse Plemons in
there who's great um and then Peter Sarsgar coming in playing a wild co -head and he is
tremendous in he's tremendous he should always love Sarsgar always love Sarsgar he deserved the best
supporting actor I think for that part but yeah also in the Batman and a small but pivotal role in
yes similar role actually yeah I love black mass I just bought the blu -ray I'm a big fan I'm on a
real gangster movie kick um and I wanted to see this again I hadn't seen it in a while wasn't
streaming anywhere and I was like you know and I should own black mass it's great and no regrets in
buying it it's an amazing story about the rise and fall of whitey bulger Boston's most notorious gangster
so I really and his his is uh unholy union as they put it with the FBI but uh I really like the movie
quite a bit good name for a male stripper whitey bulger maybe that's that will be mine when I when I
take the stage my I was gonna use ray bulger but uh the tin man oh I'm no no scarecrow bulger scarecrow
uh scarecrow and burt lar was the lion yeah tin man I can never remember his name
ebson buddy ebson maybe from uh no I'm gonna look it up now folks I saw a show with just a terrible name
so yeah we got ray bulger as the scarecrow jack haley is the tin man that's right never would
remember I watched a show with a title that made me cringe called life and death just like a
standard 90s rom com starring jenny mccarthy kind of a title direct to video but I was like you know
what michael sarah never acts anymore I find the kid funny by and large I like what Amy Schumer
is giving me and then joe tells me he's in the show so I'm like all right yeah supposedly so I wound up
watching over the I am trying to keep myself very distracted at all times due to my extreme depression
but sure I watched 10 episodes of life and death uh even though there were several points where I was
playing like a farmer in this thing just wildly miscast but he's playing this autistic guy which is
from what I've gathered from interviews with her very much based on her husband it's her story
to a very large extent but it's fictionalized and it's you know it's kind of her attempt at like a
Woody Allen type thing she meets michael sarah I believe three episodes in which is really when the
story starts the first two episodes she's with the wrong guy it's the kind of project that only a big
star can get made uh no matter how perfectly you did this you would never get this made now unless
you were a star on her level because it's very self indulgent it's thinking that her story is
is something that people will want to watch but it's not that interesting it's a woman who falls in
love with an autistic guy and it's I don't know it just wasn't done in any sort of fascinating way and
then to a to a to a to a to a fault the show is avoidant of comedy because it if I could tell that Amy
Schumer felt like if I'm gonna get Emmys if I'm gonna fit into today's comedy world I have to not
really have jokes you know so when there are big funny moments and there are because Amy is an
undeniably funny joke writer comedian writer would everywhere call it they feel out of place because
the rest of the show is trying to exist in this very like shrill hula original series kind of mode
where they don't ever really try for a joke because that's not popular anymore so it's very frustrating
as a lot of modern comedy is to see somebody funny consistently try to avoid comedy and then once she
has big jokes in it they seem so off base because the rest of the tone is so dramatic I don't know
what to say I think comedy is broken beyond recognition the show is fine and the darkest aspect of
the show is that Joe never made an appearance I'm looking on the IMDB now I watch this thing 10 episodes
looking for Joe and I didn't get I play a stand -up comic it's not a huge role who's really offensive you're
not on the show Joe yeah out on the show I want I'm playing on the TV while she's in bed with a guy maybe
you missed it that scene doesn't happen well I mean well I'm not listed on the IMDB so you're not in it
well Amy put me in it and here we are no look I I have I have liked her stuff in the past
more good news today yeah exactly I like train rack more than your average Joe I have issues with it but
you know I I loved her series I'm a fan but this is just not the best showcase for talent this is
the this is the problem it sounds like that after life had with your vase it'd be like everybody needs
to be serious everybody needs to go I want my Emmy thing they're never gonna get it but that is
because they're they're working in a medium that is not their own it is not their
a medium there they should be thriving and they're competing well and that's the thing they saw
everybody saw Woody Allen do it they went though that's what you're doing it's exactly right was the
only one that was good at it so but yeah it's the same problem with after life because it's like
you know he's like weeping in bed to his dead wife and wants to kill himself and then like it cuts
like his psychiatrist being like did too much Chang last night was getting a little minge you know like
this doesn't fit at all yeah and all you want is the whole show made up of those moments i .e. the
office x -rays etc and I don't know everybody's just obsessed with being claimed you know and it's
the death of comedy it really is mccays another example sad comedy is a is a big thing right now
you're i mean jarard car car car car car car Michael who's a for a pal of mine i've always been very
friendly with him i like him a lot the trailer for his new special it's like it's depressing
i have HBO is almost exclusively now only doing sad stand -up specials where it's like yeah
this somber like like very stark cold like synthesizer music playing and then like
it's a voiceover of like my whole life was a lie until i figured out how to tell the truth
and then it goes to like some dramatic reveal of the title you know and you know guys there's a trailer
for a comedy special there's not literally no laughs in it i don't mean like you attempted to laugh
and fail i mean you purposely didn't purposefully didn't put laughs in this yeah and then he's hosting
s &l in two weeks it's it's all strange well s &l also just had the Ukrainian choir on or whatever
the hell they did you know maybe take a week off warn yeah how about that maybe take a week off
if it's so serious that we all need to take a breath that have a moment of sound maybe take a
off of the show how about that they'll never do worse than Kate McKinnon dressed as Hillary Clinton
singing hallelujah is when i think about that i break out and do a cold sweat
it made me lose all respect for Kate McKinnon and she she introduced this one too like like she's
i was like fuck you like that's it like yeah you it's not like you reluctantly did this you wanted to
do this yeah and that's it you're that's it you're done in my book that i can't respect it anymore
i just can't it's like you know blessed the kids heart drew Michael i mean my god almighty you know
that's actually i mean it's always been nice to me but it's like i have zero respect for him
as a comic anymore it's like dude what are you doing i would like a lot of way by that special i like
i didn't watch it but the trailer for it i was like we're entering a world where like it's almost
like the start of a trailer for a movie where comedy is not allowed when i watch these trailers it's
that's what it feels like to me like a sci -fi movie where comedy is not allowed i saw Doug Benson it's
out by Southwest and he was coming from the Nicholas Cage movie yeah and i said i wrote it can't
wait to see it yeah yeah i said that was he said it was awesome yeah and i said just to answer me one
question without any spoilers is it a comedy and he was like oh yeah no it's a comedy all the way
through it's not like they're he gets serious journey i mean he's like it's a comedy you know i was
like what a fucking relief because you because you you see trailers like that now and you go into the
theater and you're like what the fuck happened to the comedy like that i was promised what is this you know
yeah i got no energy we we're still in the movie corner out way yeah i got one more and then that's
all i got left for this week but uh i got my turn i think okay go well yeah i'm not go well did you
start no i did impeachment i did some other show you did life and Beth life and Beth now it's back
to me okay yeah and i'm only gonna do one more than you can close it out uh i watched rewatched courtesy
of the criterion collection i was actually on the podcast talking about this i was a little on the
fence about buying it but i did a face in the crowd starring Andy Griffith i was so happy i bought
this when i started watching it man i was like well man i can't believe i wasn't by this what a
fucking masterpiece Ellie Kazan Andy Griffith i mean that's it that's that's what i'll see in
eight you're you're in you know Andy Griffith playing a cock sucker of a human like just the worst person
you know rotten salacious movie salacious movie especially for the time it was released
uh uh Griffith plays a guy named Lonesome Rhodes who has a sort of mysterious past that a radio show finds
in a jail cell then the drunk tank he's basically a drunk uh but he can sing and he's charismatic
and he's got a lot of stories and as the movie goes on his fame and star rise
and you start to see who he really is which is a sort of self -centered
egotistic goal man you know maniac uh and that he might not be so truthful about his past uh
and it kind of just goes from there it's a commentary on the meshing and melding of entertainment
and politics and big business uh it certainly speaks to the current state of everything in our climate
particularly politics uh Walter Mathau shows up uh as a writer for the show uh it's for for for
for Lonesome Rhodes TV show that he eventually gets it's an amazing movie and one of the only
criterians that had a worthwhile supplement on it which was a kind of a look back on the movie
where they interviewed the actors now talking about it and they got into Elliott Kazan's you know
involvement with McCarthy hearings and how he named names and how that got him blackballed by the
artists but not by Hollywood itself they get into all that stuff it's very interesting it's again
speaks to the the the themes of the film itself um but the craziest part is is Andy Griffiths is
telling a story about when he meets the scene in the movie where he meets his second wife and he's
sort of like leering at her and he goes uh he goes Kaz came up to me before he yelled action and he
just goes and he and this was his only note he goes Andy fucker fucker and if you look at my eyes
that's what i'm doing and i was like holy shit i just heard Andy Griffith say fuck that was weird
they don't beat it or anything but then the other supplement on there which i texted Pat about
i found the the portion after that where Andy mimes fucking her where he gets up on the interviewer's
table and just starts thrusting i found that to be a little off -putting yeah and then explains this
was his technique in any scene with Don Nott's yes yeah uh he's fucking her in that white suit then he
takes his his uh his handkerchief out and his mopping his brow as he just plows away like matlock style
and it's a shame this is the movie that launched Griffith into stardom it's pre the Andy Griffiths show
i didn't know that because what a treat it would have been to know the Andy Griffiths show which i
guess i did that's how i you know i saw it this way but at the time to be a fan of the Andy Griffiths show
and then this movie comes out and you go see it you're like holy shit yeah this is so dark that would
have been kind of cool uh to see the guys acting range but uh it's not it's the it's a satire there's
some really really funny moments in the movie but it's not a comedy funny stretch um and nor does it
present itself to be it's not supposed to be um but so it's not like what we were just talking about
which is one of comedian tries to make a comedy but they make the comedy sad that's not what this is
this is not a comedy movie and also he didn't make it he just accident but um it's a great flick uh
and then the other supplement on the disc which i texted you about Pat is an interview with an Andy Griffiths
expert yeah that the best day of that guy's life was what criteria i called him
such a crazy thing yeah i don't even know how you do that but these are the story about Andy Griffith
anyway check out a face in the crowd you'll want to be a face in the crowd for a face in the crowd
i love the film classic i'm do a rewatch myself and i would like to close by sharing
this special moment with Joe to say that i for the first time in my life and maybe i had done it all
piecemeal because i watched a lot of this show where my grandma's house throughout the years but this
was the first time i watched it all the way through start to finish the golden girls oh yeah
and i know that this was the last time i saw the last two seasons of the golden girls because nothing
was ringing a bell i did not know lezzanielson was a part of the show um but i texted Joe lezzanielson
should have come in way sooner he was riding the high of naked gum when he guessed it as
be Arthur's kind of final love interest but he fits in so well to the world
the show is great you know the show is a it's it doesn't have the greatness of the all the families
and so forth because its issue episodes are so like they shine the light we're an issue episode where
like you know rose things she has aides for example or whatever it's very tightly written when they
get it it is yes they do a lot of like sappy freeze frames at the end of emotional episodes in
the middle seasons that don't work it it goes a little too maudlin at times however the jokes are
very rough like i mean the amount of time they spend telling be Arthur how unfuckable she is how
man she is i can't imagine be Arthur didn't have a mental breakdown but uh to me the show has always
been about Dorothy be Arthur her reactions are funnier than anything anybody else is doing but the
characters are so well written the show is so well cast the my only real grievance and this is
a grievance of sitcoms in general up to the present day i don't like a sitcom where
everyone is always doing their one character trait at all times and that that is what a sitcom is
but if anyone says anything about sex they all look at room a clan of hand
and make slut jokes if anything is ever about being dumb it's always about Betty White they're always
their character to a tee to a fault and to me yes it is kind of fun to like know what somebody's
going to say but it makes the show a little predictable that is what that's what a sitcom is
but uh there's sitcoms that exceed that but yeah here they do that said that is also what is most
comfortable and soothing about the show at a very stressful time my life i'm in the middle of nowhere
in Georgia especially this current bout i'm on i rented a house in the middle of nowhere
because basically you can get an apartment in like fun midtown manhattan or get a house in the middle
of nowhere i tried the house it's deeply depressing and i've been watching a lot of golden girls i
watched like a season a day last weekend but uh there's something reassuring about it even as it's
kind of creatively frustrating these four women are they are sitcom acting to an absolute tee
to a perfection they nail every punchline they are so funny they're so good the show is one of the
greats however it's also not one of the great greats you know what i mean it's a great joke machine but
there's there's something kind of lacking from it it's just a it's you know look it's a dated uh it's
of the error it's of the time i love i think you could get me wrong no no i hear you my argument that it's
one of the that makes what makes it one of the great greats is that it's a celebration of women of
a certain age absolutely and you weren't seeing that and for that for to be that celebratory without
putting too much of a focus on age yeah you know even the problems they're encountering are not
often very age related they're just life related and it puts people in that of that age range
into it it's it's the thing that made me want to ultimately write about old people oh they're not
that they're old but you know what i mean senior citizens you know where people approaching senior
citizenship it's what i want to write about more than anything i i think it's an amazing
age range and eight time of age and i think it's in a fascinating period
because the angst is gone the bullshit is gone you've seen life you've seen what's really important
you've experienced real loss and you're at a point where you're you're trying to to focus on what's
right unless you failed and you're just stuck in your ways which is also a very frustrating thing
to encounter but a very funny thing at times to watch so that's that's what i love about the show
but as far as i said look that's show with anybody else in the parts would have in a season would have
been gone it's the casting director of that show i hope NBC just gave them so many gifts throughout
the years because it's just it's beautifully cast and it's still getty being the youngest is
still fascinating to me she is i mean they call her Yoda on several occasions i mean she really is
just like almost like a she's like the crib keeper at some point the character of Sophia but she is
so relentlessly funny and they never without softener here and there but like man she comes in they
these people say such mean fucking things to each other on the show
yeah it's wow it's it's a whole different kind of comedy and like
the it go you were told now because these old actors and i've heard stories about the Golden Girls
they weren't fun then either but i can't imagine these actors weren't bothered by a lot of these jokes
like be Arthur will look at room of clan of hand and tell her her ass is getting fat you know
like this this kind of thing happens all the time on the show so like if you're calling Betty white
dumb Betty white goes home not bothered by that she's not a dumb woman
they're calling be Arthur a man -ish ugly woman who nobody would ever want to fuck it's in the book
that you bought me the man it's tough it's tough date she talks about like they talk about like how in
the later seasons she would complain like oh great more dorthy bashing for that very reason yeah
because personally she's the funniest and in my mind and this might seem crazy to people
i find her the most attractive i was always a Betty white man and look in the looks department
sure uh but but be in the comedy department
who in the acting department i find her performance in that show it's incredible she is that woman
it's like it's wild when you see i met her in real life right before she died she was at a show i
did it was pretty cool to meet her but uh you i was like she's not the same person it's like it's like
it's like talking to Pacino and then watching Scarface or something yeah who is this man in this movie
like it's fucking wild but she's she's really excellent there i love them all and then of course
just don't get it it's incredible but i love them all and then like
what the other thing i like about the show is i feel like they'd be
proponents now of true liberalism which is human rights and that sort of thing
but also proponents of comedy and protectors of humor
yeah it's it's hearts in the right place and they'll they'll also make like
fucked up gay jokes you know fucked up lesbian jokes but at the end of the day their heart is in
the right place it's it's uh it was it was a real treat for me i and i didn't notice any sort of quality
drop off along along the road either i thought there are gyms would suck but it was all good no that one
where they go to the murder mystery place is one of my favorite episodes yeah that's great that one is
amazing uh yeah just killer gangster lines you know like you know what would uh when they're
taken the class about being positive and still get a sound that story about fucking Pablo Picasso
and Dorothy's like mom you're lying and then anyway it's like Dorothy be positive all right i'm
positive you're lying yeah it's like it's uh it's it's it's text books that come right in that show
it's it's it's it's one of the best of the classic sitcom it's not reinventing the wheel
and yet its subject matter was kind of revolutionary it's a great great show uh my the show
runner on this miss patch show was obsessed with it and he also raves about the golden palace so
i might give it a try i did not like golden palace because it's not fun to see for the reason i
like jack asked forever it's not fun to watch it without be Arthur being there but does it have
Joe that's what i told him i had no interest the pilot is good enough like Susan Harris i think
wrote it the creator and then there is a two -story arc where where b comes back which is great yeah
and that's awesome to see but like you know for the most part but young don cheetle very interesting
young don cheetle getting his start you got a cheat man in there it's not terrible it's just like
you know you're seeing half the band and it's a bummer that's all you know yeah it's new that's new
to hulu i might roll the dice but i like ending it where it ended it was it was a it was a good ending
to a great show i and like you know marrying b Arthur off to somebody who you've seen for two episodes
is a little unsatisfying but the fact that it's Leslie Nielsen i'm like i'm happy with those two
together i don't need to see any future adventures i mean i want to think of her as being with Frank
Drappett and happy yes yeah so all right great show great show well let's talk opposites of great
and i'm surprised to hear you say this joke because you're a DC man but not a DC man
no not a DC man this is the Batman the i mean the umpteenth version of this Batman story
excuse me yeah and yet at this point we are somehow seeing a three -hour version
so we've seen multiple multiple two -hour Batman movies we've seen a four -hour Justice League involving
30 heroes why all of a sudden we need a three -hour version of the Batman legend i don't know you feel
the length a lot i would say in the Batman i was most excited about the cast it's a very deep bench
i like Robert Pattinson but i tend to like him more in artsy roles the lighthouse
what's not on kajim with the one before on kajim good time i think he's a great actor but he's
clearly bored here he sucks as both Batman and Bruce Wayne he speaks only in the monotone
for some reason they have Jeffrey Wright speak to him in the exact same voice to the point where it
almost seems like parody most people in this movie speak in the Batman hushed whisper for three
hours yep and this stacked cast of Paul Dana Colin Farrell, John Terturo
what's the Jill and Hall gentleman's name uh that we just talked about Peter Scars guard
i mean it's a stacked cast yes but is anybody given anything great to do
no Colin Farrell is doing it the neuro impression to me clearly that i guess is kind of funny
it might be funny on s and l but we don't ever see the penguin come to fruition we don't we also
don't ever see the riddler come to fruition it's still just Paul Dana throughout i thought Paul Dana
was kind of weird and fun but the fact that in a three -hour movie we're never seeing the villains
be the villains is a problem i would say uh it just left me it was it was a movie equivalent of being
edged you know everyone likes being edged but that's because you know at the end you're gonna come
i didn't come at the end of the Batman Joe i did it i still hated it uh no i i i have a lot to say
yeah uh tell us the plot you know i was initially excited about the movie because i love Batman
and i love dc and i love a dark dc movie and by the way i think that Reeves is a fantastic action
director up to and including the Batman he's a good action he's he's okay he doesn't know when to stop
and i think this was part of it uh but but i'll say this in a world where every action sequence
is kind of nothing because you don't even know who's fighting who he knows where to put the camera
to give you a satisfying action sequence to some of that that you can't say about everybody
i i i i would even disagree with that but but uh i like the i like the second two
plan of the action movies he did i thought the first one was an abomination um this uh i doggal i doggal
this two um i started to worry i thought the first trailer was great i like that they were going
this dark route with the ridler it's been done in the comics it's pretty cool i started to worry when
they started saying things like Bruce Wayne is based on Kurt Cobain i was like here we go
and by the way so he's not so there's no similarity so um the so anyway so
that was that was when my antennas went up and i was like all right i don't know about this man
what are they going to do here um and then i talked to some people that saw it before i did and they
were like dude it's not good and i was like well wait a minute i am hesitant about certain things
but you tell me it's not good they're like just go see it you know say the first 20 minutes amazing
and then it's going to fall apart after that and i was like all right but i was still excited to
see it i went with Keith Robinson good friend of mine big comic book fan we were excited to go
sure enough first 20 minutes establishing who the Batman is showing Bruce Wayne walking through
the streets eyeing people saying things like i can't attend to every crime i have to pick and choose
all that was really really cool and that leads up to his first confrontation with a bunch of
guys in clown makeup which in the trailer everybody theorized this is going to be linked to
Joaquin Phoenix's Joker movie because they look like the Joaquin Phoenix Joker movie well guess what
they're not they're inexplicably just painted up like clowns for no reason and if you're going to
pay that off later well they're you're not going to pay it off later because you think to yourself
well maybe they are still linked to Joaquin Phoenix they're just not going to reveal that yet but then
when you learn more about who Thomas Wayne is and the history of Batman you go well that's not the Thomas
Wayne and the Wayne's from the Joaquin Phoenix movie so clearly this isn't linked to it so you
did just have a bunch of guys dressed up in clown makeup and this makes no fucking sense it was always
my biggest gripe about Batman returns why does the penguin have a gang of clowns with him when you're
following the Joker movie you don't do that well it doesn't make any fucking sense anyway
they don't they don't go to the to Wayne manner or maybe they do and I don't remember
they don't explain why the Batcave is in a subway station in the moment that you see it you're
like oh that makes sense that's kind of cool that would be like what a real life Batcave would be
but they don't explain how it connects to the mansion or why it's that
and things continue to just get sort of grittier and grittier and grittier as you're watching it
you've got Paul Dano in a puffy coat with a ski mask on playing the ridler who still has to wear his
glasses over his ski mask which looks absurd you've got well Dano's Dano's whole vibe in this
and the movie so as much as the dark night owes to heat and Nolan said I based the bank robbery scene
and many other scenes on heat uh this movie owes to seven it's very much trying to be
david ventures seven and a serial killer movie and it's very well shot you know and looks good
Dano you know was the movie R or PG -13 PG -13 it looks like PG -13 so like the movie was packed with kids
when I saw it and Dano's riddler stuff was horrifying the children which yeah in my mind was kind
of like okay that's what Batman Returns did as well I remember seeing that at the dollar show and kids
screaming and crying because it was way too dark for what they were expecting but Dano in this trying
to do the seven thing it just like the rat traps which also felt a lot like saw to me yep the trap
with the rats eating whatever I was like you know this is horrifying the kids but for me this feels
pathetic I thought Dano was terrible in this terrible yeah I thought Jeffrey Wright was terrible in
this I never thought I'd see a movie where I thought Jeffrey right Jeffrey right is embarrassing in
this and he must have been directed to just match it was Patent's energy I don't know what's going
on but they talk in the same boys Zoe Kravitz is Catwoman it's pointless it's a pointless character
it serves no purpose to the plot you're talking about one of the sexiest women working in film today
not really given an opportunity to be sexy and I don't know what they were doing with this catwoman
also too also too enough with the catwoman already there are other female characters we could explore
here and they're not doing it poison ivy they do the same villains again and again and again poison ivy's
the one I keep bringing up when I talk about this to people poison ivy kills people who put
puts mainly men into a trance yeah and kills them like they did it terribly and as I'm a
thermite not her fault but they did it terribly so poison ivy and she does that because they're people that
have put a purge out on the earth and on nature and whatever and she's she loves the she loves
trance and trees and all that stuff and she that's her revenge on man and man's mistreatment of the
earth it goes hand in hand with what Dano is trying to do and they had a real chance here because Catwoman
is supposed to be this weird anti hero where she's somewhere between Dano and Batman if it was poison
ivy it would have made so much more sense to have this bridge character between the two of them
they didn't do it doesn't matter point is this penguin catwoman dad ridler they've all been grounded
to the point that they are completely believable character completely believable those real people
they live in Gotham city which is just depressing and awful and horrible and gritty and drab and whatever
the entire time it becomes so out of Gotham square garden yeah really bothered me it's going to
stupid but like you're talking about they bring it so down to earth and then go through the earth and
bring it down into into underneath the dirt to make this thing so real that when you see a guy walking
around in a I remember thinking the first time I saw Batman in daytime I was like really he's wearing a
this guy's wearing a in this Gotham city there's a guy walking around why does he have a cape on
this is like this stupid it doesn't fit in and then you learn in a later scene which almost was cool
and this is why I disagree with you about Matt Reeves knowing where to put the camera there's a scene
where he's he's outnumbered and he's and he runs on to a rooftop and he almost he comes to the edge
and almost falls and he gasps and I was like oh that's really cool like he's like a new Batman like
because every time Batman's on like a cliff he doesn't give a shit he's finding it I was like that's
really cool like he realizes like Jesus Christ I could have just died and then you realize the cape
is like a flight suit and he does the flight suit to fly down and then Reeves puts the camera on
Pattinson's face so close it literally looks like one of those skydiving videos you do when you go on
vacation it's it's stupid looking it's just stupid and I'm like I don't know why would you shoot it like
this so that brings me to my next point there are two elements in the in this wants to desperately be
the darker Nolan version of Batman and this is why it fails there are two things in the Nolan movies
it that are that are put out in Batman begins that that justify the entire trilogy the first is
Lucius Fox played by Morgan Freeman being a part of Wayne Enterprises and part of their military
defense division and showing that's where Batman gets all of his equipment from and everything
and showing like why does he have a cape oh because it's memory cloth and that's why he uses it why
does he have the suit because it's bulletproof that you know what I mean they justify every fucking thing
he has on and you go okay this is why a guy is dressed up like this the second part is when he's
divine when he's making the cow whatever and uh uh Michael King goes why bats master Wayne
and and Christian bell goes because bats frighten me Alfred and right there you're like
guys are gonna dress up like a bat like it scares him there's none of that in this so you've got
this like hard -boiled detective movie happening that again like you said it's supposed to be like seven
and then you got a guy in a bat suit walking around the crime scenes yeah he's stupid he looks
ridiculous the suit you know all these movies have updated the suit and updated the bat mobile and
so forth and that was a big part of their charm I remember you know being nine years old and so
excited to see the new bat suit and the new bat mobile or whatever this doesn't do any of that there is
not an original bat suit there's not an original bat mobile there's not an original bat wing
there is no prince on the soundtrack there there is no attempt to make this movie a fun
new interpretation of the material the only thing they're really doing is giving you a grounded
which is every every executive's note nowadays grounded version of the Batman story and all I can
say is it makes for the least fun version of Batman you could ever have you basically have a crime drama
where your hero is not good because Pattinson is not comfortable as Bruce Wayne or Batman he's not
good in either role it's by the way let me interject really quick they do the corneous stupidest like
Superman Christopher I love the Christopher Reeves superman I'm not shitting on them but it doesn't work
with this kind of batman movie but they do the Christopher Reeve move in one part where Bruce
something happens where Bruce Wayne is in attendance and he slips out the back door and then returns
five minutes later as Batman yeah where did he have the suit what is going on here yeah
you know no for sure for sure and that to me and all I can speak of is for me and I'm not the
diehard comics fan and I'm coming as at a different voice than the guy who's loved Batman for his whole
life or something but the reason that I would prefer say Michael Keaton to Pattinson is because Keaton
had a fucking pulse and he played something other than like morose depression throughout the entire
thing which is boring on screen but also if you're gonna show me catwoman the penguin the riddler
and we're not seeing any of these people in their costumes we're not seeing any of them really acting
like their character we're just seeing Colin Farrell doing it the near one impression is no different
than having the near one the movie it's just kind of a boring expected thing Zoe Krabitz is very attractive
but she never really fully goes catwoman there's no real cat aspect to her personality and
uh the riddler and then in the end spoiler alert the joker all they really do is focus on their
laughter but Dano's character is just your run of the mill Columbine terrorist and to me that's not
why I go see Batman it's just like we're here you have a three hour version of Batman and your villains
are all people that we could see in any generic direct -to -cable thriller it's it's it's it's yeah it's
it's uh it's like a prisoner it's like he's trying to make prisoners except with Batman and it doesn't
make any prisoners a fucking masterpiece well I agree um but Dano just when you think Dano is playing
like this sort of koi stoic sociopathic riddler he then incorporates half with the movie this cackling
laugh which is the Achilles heel of almost anybody that plays a Batman villain they play it like
the joker it's yeah doesn't make sense it's not original it's stupid um so then in the end when you
do finally meet the new joker which is fucking dumb too which there's nothing left to do with the
joker guys enough enough that's another thing it's like enough with the joker enough with catwoman you've
got one of the deepest benches in comics I don't know comics and I know that Batman has a deep
fucking bench of villains and you're going back to the same people every time it's just exhausting
man which you know this was my biggest problem with the entire movie this did not feel like an organic
script to me this felt like a script that came out of a boardroom over at Warner Brothers that was put
onto a white board like a football play and said we need to launch these tv shows from this movie
how do we do that yeah they they have a penguin movie or tv show in production well into production
which is now serving as the sequel to this for the penguin storyline with Colin Farrell right yes
yes they have a Gotham PD tv show in production which centering on Jeffrey Wright as commissioner Gordon
they are obviously going to do a catwoman thing which is why she rides off to go on her own at the end
and doesn't stick around Gotham city and they're clearly going to do a sequel to this yeah oh yeah
you know it's it's just a it's just sucked man I hated it there's one line in the entire movie
that isn't brooding depressing mopey bullshit which by the way
25 minutes into this something in the way by nirvana starts playing and I was like oh here we go
we're in trouble now playing a couple times yeah obvious choice of well I was trying to tell Joe
it they played that in either justice league or something similar but yeah within the last couple
of years that that song has been used in another superhero movie but they play that and then the only
line where there's a good liver of a smile for a second is when Pattinson's a catwoman's apartment
he just goes you got a lot of cats again for a second it's like kind of funny and human for a second
yeah and like I don't want you know I don't want comedy in this in these things but for Christ's
takes guys like like even the Nolan ones had the moments where like you know where they're on the jet
and Alfred leans because he now owns way all the way in the stadium he leans back and he's like you
could use the rose master Bruce if just asked by the keys and by permission you know they had like
little moments like that where you were like you want to get nuts let's get nuts yeah you saw
like the you saw connect you saw a connection you saw the human side of people this is none of that
Batman looks as if he's going to faint at any well the Alfred's a great comparison so the Alfred
and the original Batman with Keaton was of course fantastic Michael but Michael Kane I forget his name
they were like Michael Gaul or Gaul I really want to say it was fantastic but they knew they had
to do better and they did Michael Kane in that role like people shit on the third of the dark night
rises the third of those Nolan ones but I love that movie and that the the wrap up to Alfred and that
is almost tear jerking for me I think it's so great and Michael Kane just gives that role so much
so to then cast Andy Circus the the guy who puts fucking ping pong balls on himself
to do these part as Alfred it's like I'm sorry you've you've you've traded down Christian
bail for Pattinson trade down Fyfer for Kravitz trade down uh Kerry for Dana trade down
well everything is a is a big step down and it just kind of frustrate I would like to
Joe I would like to have seen Circus playing a monkey butler yes emotion capture gorilla butler first
that I would like to know of course uh I liked it more than Joe I did but I thought it was an
average Batman movie and I'd probably a better than average superhero movie because I think
they're all so bad but I always like Batman I think because he's closest to real and I can I get
I can relate to a guy who's depressed and angry and trying to get vengeance whatever it's like death wish
or something that was stupid to everybody kept calling him vengeance oh yeah god that was terrible
there's a lot of stupid shit like that in this movie oh this is the last thing I'll say and I
said this to Pete Holmes and I said Pete the entire god damn movie is supposed to be real
and then you get to the plot line about the drugs yeah that everybody in Gotham is doing drop
yeah drop their export their importing drop into Gotham I hate drop heads just make it heroin or cocaine
make it a real drug every part of this has been real at least the original Batman gave you that that
cosmetics scheme which was original and fresh how many movies have done the drug that there's a new
street drug that's killing people and we call it hopper to do oh my god it was terrible that come on
guys the world's greatest detective doesn't know basic Spanish yeah you know you got the penguin go
don't you idiots those Spanish I mean it was terrible I fuck this movie I hate it I hate it my
hug is get more down than it's ever been possible it jeepers down on my hog right now I like jeepers
creepers and my hog is I would say we've kissed a few times and the hog knows that maybe getting
hard is in the future but for right now we don't feel there's any real need to get hard so we're
staying in a down position and look that could be the case I hated rising the plan of the apes I
loved dawn and war maybe he comes back swinging in these next two you know we'll see I don't like
to all of them I think he's a good action director you know the scene where he where you kind of see
the firing of the machine guns kind of you know with clearly very much like a set piece type thing
of Batman like fighting people in the dark or whatever I thought was kind of cool but the run
time on this you know it is absurd it's just absurd because it's telling a story that we all have
seen so many times and I do think that Robert Pattinson is a great actor but only in character roles he
is the modern day Brad Pitt where he comes to life in a flashy weird supporting role but in a lead
role honestly he's very very boring and in the scenes of him and Jeffrey Wright whispering to
each other are embarrassing they I was laughing out loud at some of them because they're so devoid
of any sort of human feeling or suspense or emotion yeah like how did you think this was the take
to use you know by the way you left out an Alfred our last Alfred was Jeremy Irons narrow and
justice like yes that's right Andy circus all right folks we'll be back next month with something
or other I'm not quite sure yet what it's going to be I think do we know no we probably X right we'll
be one of them I have seen X and can't wait to talk about it and we'll add whatever kind of the new
big movie coming out is we get one a month these days at least so we'll see but yeah definitely
check out X because that'll be one of the next ones see you next time and we'll see and how