Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Reward subject to expiry. Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
howdy folks welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast brought to you by the
Fingoria podcast network you know you want some info about the network or this
podcast or other programs how to find episodes of anything including us go
visit fangoria .com. Pat washed to my right. Hey here for another contentious. Maybe not.
We as you mentioned before we started this is the first time we're going in not really knowing
the other's opinion of the movie we're discussing. Yeah I don't think I said anything to you and
I didn't even know you saw it until about 10 minutes ago but we will be discussing don't breathe.
Yes, which is I
Guess with lights out and all these at which I didn't see yet unfortunately, but
So many titles like that that every time I want to say the title of this movie
I either say it wrong or forget what it is. It's a very generic horror title
I something just dinged. I think my text message came yet. There we go. Okay. Oh
Louder hear that do you hear the dings? Of course I do. I love this man
I don't you love when people what is the thing now?
Now you heard three things because I forgot to mute the speakers here and the podcast
or the text messages I was receiving were coming through the speakers, but you heard
three things because these people these days, these goddamn people won't consolidate their
text messages.
What is this shit where it's sentence and then a word and then another thing and then another
the word and another sentence, put it all in a, think about what you're writing first.
What this guy was doing is correcting because he auto correct corrects everything.
So when people be like, I meant this, I meant this, I meant this, I meant this.
Just assume the other person knows what you meant unless it says like, I want to finger you
and it was supposed to say like, I want to talk to you.
But yeah, I have friends who will send 10 texts to say something that you should say in
one.
I if I got a lot to say I say it in a giant paragraph not everybody has the the all -inclusive plan
I'm sorry. I'm a man of great wealth and taste, but many don't
But it's absurd it's it's come on I agree come on I agree about the goddamn thought first
We don't need a I hate texting I hate it phone call we're in and out
It really repaired my relationship with my father texting you don't the talk
It sounds, it sounds like it's repaired for all the wrong, and all the wrong ways for
all the wrong reasons.
Yeah, you're right.
You know, it doesn't sound like a good repair to me, it sounds like an old Band -Aid fix.
Yeah, that's what the Irish people and the Catholic people do.
What is with the Irish people, with the emotions?
You guys really don't like it, it's just share them or talk about them, what does that come
from?
Is that from when you ran out of the potatoes?
I think it's from the when we ran out of potatoes. Yeah
There's that line in the in the departed the the Irish are the only people that are impervious to therapy
And I feel like that might be true as well, you know, no, they're just a really closed -off
Group of people I don't know why it is but a lovable bunch
I was in I was in Dublin for the vote of phone comedy festival a few weeks back. I
Made dear friends with some with some lovely Irish people
out there. Yeah they're wonderful. I'm going to Galway for Halloween weekend to do the
Vodafone festival up there. Okay. I can't wait. I can't wait to see these people. And
I feel like as I I feel like John Candy and Plains Trains and automobiles. These are people
like, but I'm ever trapped in Galway. I'll be like, I know a guy. He owes me a favor. And
and I will have a place to sleep. You know, did you make love to any fiery red haired
glasses. Does last mean male or female? Dealers' choice. Then yes. All right. We're here
today to talk about Don't Breathe. Don't Breathe. I know. Just what? You're breathing.
Keep doing that. The whole time was in the theater in my head. Yeah, I can't help it. I mean
this movie couldn't have come with higher recommendations it's being very well reviewed you mean
very well reviewed but also everybody I knew aside from you that it's seen it was like
thumbs up man well I give it a thumbs up as well I just mean that I didn't talk to you about it right
you know especially for for a stroll and into some horror movie off the street not knowing
anything I thought a the twist was kind of admirably crazy and it got nuts at
the end which I respected and loved and at the first half I thought was very
tense and for me it all pretty much worked before we get to the end and the
middle and all that stuff this is just donning on me now this is probably a good
thing to do maybe we just give us an opsis sure we've never been doing that
Yeah, I guess we will when we do discuss the end we're gonna I guess we'll have to give you some sort of spoiler alert
Well, this whole thing's a spoiler alert probably so you're pretty much but for those of you that don't know
I'm sure all of you do but if anybody doesn't don't breathe as a story about a a down -and -out single mom
Who's got to gotta make ends meet so she gets a job in a diner with a sassy
cook that doesn't take no for an answer in a group of waitresses that all like to
shoot from the hip and the main one's name is Alice and it's a real fun
romp. Do you think that our listeners know the show Alice? I kept being like, is Joe
really describing the plot of the sitcom Alice? Which came first, Alice? Alice was
a sitcom based on the extremely depressing Scorsese film, Alice doesn't live here anymore.
Yeah, it's a real dark movie and then they turned it into this sort of saucy, it's a great
one. Kiss my grits comes from you. Kiss my grits with flow and then you had that guy that
the only other thing I've ever seen him in was was an episode of Teos on the Dark Side and the movie
Lover Boy with Patrick Dempsey or the guy that's like you got a married Asian woman. Yeah, yeah,
Yeah, that guy he he's the he's the no nonsense cook. Okay. No, I don't know if I've ever seen the show
But the movie is great if you want to see a different kind of Scorsese movie from early on in his career
They say kiss my grits in the movie. They do not that's
Harvey Kitelle plays like an abusive
Like asshole Pimp type character in it. Yeah, it's very different and this is what they turned into the sitcom
Yeah, exactly that's like what they did when a
when Ed Asner was on Mary Taylor Moore and then he had the spin -off but it was like the
gritty newsroom drama. I was like, what are you doing? It's very strange. I don't like when
that happens and I don't tell you another thing I don't like. I don't care for those wicked books.
Oh the wicked books. I don't know that anybody can finish those things but did you like the musical?
I didn't see the musical and I heard the musical is a disgraceful interpretation of the book but
I'll tell you something the book it had me sick to my stomach. They got the witch fucking dudes and it's there's
Extremely graphic to put the descriptive sex sequences in there. Oh, yeah, none of that is in the hell is this
That is in the musical I assure you
But that guy must have been so thrilled that he writes this smut and then it makes him
Hundreds and hundreds of millions of dollars as a musical
Yeah, the music was for like little girls. Yeah, like 12 year old. Yeah
Don't breathe in synopsis form is about it. Let me do it. All right. You go ahead. Let me do it. It'll
help sharpen my memory skills as well. So it's a woman and a kind of nerdy guy who kind of pines for
her and then her actual boyfriend who's your standard movie scumbag drug dealer type and
the three of them break into homes for a living.
She has a daughter, she lives with her seemingly abusive, checked out parents and she wants
to get out from under their thumb and provide a better life for her daughter.
Well, her mom and her mom's deadbeat boyfriend.
And the moment one point makes it a joke that her girlfriend earns her money by sucking cock
Yeah, she tells her daughter how are you making money and then does the universal cock sucking and does it does it does it
So essentially and so well
So yeah, they decide hey, and this was all this all happened very quickly. I liked how economical it was it was a short
Movie kind of blasted through the plot points, but they're like
We found this guy. There were some plot holes here to be honest with you, but they wanted to rob a blind guy
Who's like 60 years old?
He just came into a large settlement because his daughter was hit by a car and killed
They said they know he's got at least three hundred thousand dollars in the house and at that point
I was kind of like why isn't this money in the bank did I miss that?
How do they how do they know it's in the house and why was it in the house are my two question?
They had a series of hunches as to why it could be in the house.
If I remember correctly, one of which was the fact that he lived in this uninhabited
part of town.
Detroit.
It's kind of like based around this idea of this guy is an angry veteran whose daughter
has been killed, doesn't trust the system, feels fucked over because the killer walked so they're
just assuming he'll have his money and it's probably the kind of guy that keeps his money under the
bed and not in a bank or whatever. But then when they get into the house, they still say they don't
know for sure when they get into the house, there's all those locks at the front door when they get to
the house and they go, why are there four locks? And he says, because this guy doesn't trust anybody,
because he's got all his money in here. I'm telling you. And then, surely enough, he does have his
money in there. He does. They decide they're going to rob him and then it goes
horribly wrong. Yeah. The main obstacle being that this guy has has like
military training. And of course the standard as an all -blind movies, the heightened
sense thing. And he also has a giant killer dog. He's got a giant killer dog. And
really in the end, by the end, the movie becomes Kujo. It's there's a 20 -minute
sequence where it's just dog on woman. Not dog on woman folks, but you know what I mean.
That was the original title for the woman. Yeah. Don of justice. Yeah. Now, here's the
thing. That's that's that's your basic plot point. There's some heavy twists. Yeah. Oh,
heavy twists. I like the movie. I thought it was well executed. I thought it was pretty airtight.
Well shot certainly very well shot cool shots, you know, it was it was airtight
There was there were they they really didn't miss a beat or anything. Yeah, I
Enjoyed the fact that they threw a few twists into it and it wasn't just a sort of hunt kill kind of thing
That all being said I didn't leave
the film feeling
extraordinarily excited or same here or that I needed really did watch it ever again but I did
like it and I like that Sam Raimi produced it I liked the guy that did the evil dad remake which
I really loved I like that a lot directed it and I thought he'd have bang up job but yeah I guess
it is kind of taking you back to that especially with Daredevil being on the so popular right now in
Netflix. It's kind of hard to get excited about a blind guy that could do like all this stuff because
the sentences were so heightened, you know. Yeah, I mean, it is one of those like there's a
always like one comedy a year and one horror movie a year where you hear the premise and you're like
awkward and I think about. But like you know how these movies are always a deaf woman in the house
and people are trying to kill her. What if it was the other way around? Like it's a cool twist on that
premise is good and I thought everybody in it was fine yeah it's
luckily it cost almost no money it's doing very well I always like that kind
of a story I agree I felt the same I wasn't energized I wasn't pumping my fist
it's not the kind of movie where you are necessarily cheering or jazzed about
what's happening well it's all kind of they are breaking into a blind man's home
One problem that I certainly recognize and I've heard other people point out about the film is
Everybody in the film sucks. Is it pieces shit? Yeah, even the blind guy who you initially feel bad for turns out to be
Fucking lunatic. Yeah, I was actually kind of wondering okay, these three are kind of self -absorbed and kind of annoying and okay
The girl has a daughter, but I'm not really rooting for her right because she's robbing a blind man
I was kind of like how are they going to
put us on the side of these three sneaking into the house because they're doing something
that's very wrong. Right. And then sure enough, they show you exactly how when the first twist hits
and you realize that this blind guy is degenerate. Well, he's had some struggles. We already
said spoilers through the whole thing. I mean, so they assume that this bolted up basement
is the place where the money is being kept because of the amount of security
locks on the door, then they get into the basement and they realize, no, in fact,
what's being kept there is a woman, the woman that killed his daughter and
walked free. She's tied up in a very kind of disturbing way in a room with
like a bunch of cushions on the walls to muffle her screams. It's a scene, it's a
Uh, and then you later find out that the reason she is there is because he is artificially
inseminating her, yeah, to give him another baby since she took his baby from him, right.
Uh, now, this is where my suspension of disbelief started to teeter a bit.
Okay, sure.
I mean, this woman's in a sophisticated harness, yeah, uh, inside this guy's house, not just
in his house in his basement, which they make pretty clearly, they show blatantly that
the only way down into this basement from the inside is a ladder, yeah, not a staircase.
And the only way from the outside is, you know, a traditional storm door, but there's
like a sort of like a maze to get to where he keeps her.
My point is, is I'm all for going into this idea of heightened senses and a guy being able
to kick some ass. I was sitting there going, how the fuck did he get her down there?
Yeah. How did he find her? How did he get her down?
He has no ability to drive. Then she's also, when they find her, she's clutching a newspaper
article about what happened. I was kind of like, why does he have this lying around down
here? Right. It's an issue. I can misery when she's got that book of all the clippings
of like crime she's been involved in. It somehow doesn't really strain credibility because
she's kind of like you know a bit of a famed seeker and it's just her own private album sitting
in her house. This article like lying there to explain what she was the second they find her I was
kind of like really did that happen. Yeah I didn't I didn't quite yeah that's a great that's a great
point it was a little too convenient it was like how how did he get her down there yeah he and they
they say they say flat out he lost his sight in the war he didn't he didn't
lose his sight afterwards yeah he's see I don't think would be able to get
it out there and tie her up and you know he's also well how did he he's
get her period how did he find he's injecting his seamen into these women and
you're kind of like he's not even fumbling around the vagina like to find
where it goes it can be hard to find out how to get into a vagina when you're fully
sighted and I'm sober. I suspect that's where the sense of smell kicked in.
Jesus Christ, yeah. She has been down there on that basement for an easy bit.
Yeah, there was there was a lot of it where you're kind of like okay I thought
the twist was going to be that he's not blind or something at that point.
That's what I thought and that that brings me to another point I had about the
movie there was a there was a part of me that thought does he really need to be
blind you know I think him being blind as far as the marketing goes why that
movie is a hit sure sure but probably not but you're dealing with two
different movies at this point yeah dealing with a guy that's blind who can
defend himself you there is a dividing line halfway through when they go to
that basement and find her where it is a different movie.
I was like, okay, now I'm watching a different movie.
Not enough from Dust Tildon kind of way,
but I liked that aspect of it.
It felt, I never got bored.
Certainly it was short, quick,
and the twists when they came,
really kind of set you on a new path.
And I was on board.
What about to the thing, you know,
the kid, the boyfriend character?
He releases that gas,
Yeah, the guy's bedroom and he's like, yeah, he's lights out. He's knocked out. Don't worry about it
And then the guy's not and they don't explain that so I was like did he and he also acts
Stardold when he realizes people are there, but startled not startled like to the benefit of him tricking them
Startled like genuinely fucking startled and reacting to it. Yeah shooting at the cell phone and all like that
because when that went off I was like were am I to believe that a it was a
faulty smoke bomb or be that due to his military training he developed
sensitivity to gases I and they don't explain it but when he first alluded
it because I was like obviously he's not gonna fall prey to this trap or
whatever right my assumption was he's faking like he doesn't know they're there
But he does, but then when he doesn't counter them, again, it's not like he acts, well, maybe he doesn't, I'm not remembering correctly, but I don't think he acts, he doesn't act frightened.
No, and then tricks them and then beats the shit out of them. He like is like, oh shit, somebody's here and goes in action pretty quickly after that.
Yeah, um
And I think like what they were doing through the whole movie is they should have built this guy have to be the super human
Killer like in the way you would have freddy or a Jason like he just keeps coming or whatever
You know, which is why I didn't like the ending like that that scene at the end where they you know
The guy gets beat in the face multiple times of the fucking lead pipe
or a crowbar or something and then he falls backwards on flat on to his fucking tailbone
basically.
The nerdic kid.
No, no, the guy.
Oh, the guy.
Because the nerdic kid also fell on his back.
I mean, yeah.
At the very end, I'm talking about everyone in the movie takes savage, savage beatings
and are shot multiple times.
And everyone's fine.
I guess till they're not.
But if she, they stretch credibility there, she beats him repeatedly with the pipe.
Yeah.
The bad guy and then he falls blind guy and then he falls backwards onto his back, which would break your back
So okay fine then he's she sees the news real in the train station when she's about to get away
And she sees that oh no, he's alive
So like he's alive. Okay, fine. And then it's like he sustained some injuries
But he's doing okay, and I'm like that's absurd
Yeah, you'd have literally of brain damage and then on top of it
She's got this look on her face like where she's like, oh my god. He's still alive. He could find me
I'm sure you're going. What are you worried about because if I can blind you lose the middle you're home free
You're gone. You he's never gonna find you, but then but they're a million percent gonna do a sequel
Well, I would say there's no chance. They're not so
They're gonna have him I
I guess I bet they'll amp it up even more him having some sort of super powers almost not not Freddie style
Because I think they'll keep it grounded enough that he's just a man
But I think they'll try to play up the sense stuff. He's gonna be traveling the globe to find her
Or they're gonna and he will find her or there's no second movie or they're gonna say this guy was black ops
Right he yeah, okay, so fine, but here's the thing too
So then I, again, I saw this movie with my friend James Pinkstone, who I often reference.
And we left the theater and I said, I'm just a little confused.
Why did she look scared at the end?
She's home free.
She's going to California for Christ's sake.
Right.
He said, no, that's not what it was.
It's not that she's scared.
It's that she realizes he's still alive and that the money she has is dirty because he's going
to do this now to another woman.
And I said, he's not going to do it to another woman.
He did it to the woman who killed his daughter for justice, and they tried to do it to her because she
It inadvertently made him kill the woman
Right. He's not a lunatic in that sense. He doesn't want to do this to women
He wanted justice for his daughter
Yeah, it didn't even occur to me that he wanted to knock up another woman
No, and then I read a I read the original ending uh -huh when we got home and I was like dude
I
Hate to say it. I was right the original ending of the movie was him walking through the train station
yeah with this kind of like this is a bad you wouldn't buy it all this is absurd
yeah this is absurd yeah he can't you just can't do that like how would he how
the hell would he even know what train she was on he would not he would not part
to he's tracking her to California though guaranteed um and i you know what if
i'm sitting down right now and they gave me a week to write don't breathe to
keep not breathing then I would start it still don't breathe still don't
breathe I would start it with him kind of asking around town finding out where
where she lived finding those that dead be couple that you hate anyway the mom
and the boyfriend and they'd give her up immediately they know where she went in
California to go in if he kills those two you don't care their deadbeats and
there it is I mean he can track her that way pretty easily it's a good point
It's a good point if you remember that that's the thing you know when don't breathe two comes out two years from now
And he goes to that couple's house. I'll be like what the fuck like people have a real good memory for that kind of stuff
With a movie like this the details go away in a couple weeks from it
Well, it's like in a sequel like if they don't take the time to tell you what's going on
I'm like, what are we doing here? I remember I'd like to cite the episode where Pat thought the movie vacation was a straight -up remake
Yeah, the original vacation not that long and Chevy chase just happened to be in the movie playing a guy named Clark
Griswold. Yeah, because a year had passed and I don't need to remember details of that of a comedy. I'm just saying. That's how I feel.
I do remember don't breathe. I remember everything about it. And I think that's probably how they'll kick things off.
Uh, that's a great, that's a great, uh, theory. I wouldn't be surprised. And that would help.
So, you know, I'm sure we're gonna get people who say, like, blind doesn't mean you can't
do anything.
You can do a lot of things with blind.
Well, of course it doesn't mean that.
But he doesn't know this girl's name.
He doesn't know anything about them.
That's what I'm saying.
How does he even find out where she lives?
Yeah.
How does he find the parents?
That's true.
I mean, you can only sniff so much.
He sniffs a lot in the movie.
But like, you can't sniff your way to somebody's house.
It could be, I mean, if you want to get real stupid with it, I've seen stupor things
in movies he's out walking his dog and the dogs like starts going going wild
because it smells the girl and brings her up to the door you know maybe
that's it it'd be stupid pretty damn lucky yeah no I know it's the dog alive
it was left in that car I think the dog was alive does he get the dog that's
shit too I mean that that's straight up Kujo that's you know the dog in the
car that went on and on and on. I was surprised by how much time was devoted to the dog because now
it's not really a movie anymore about this blind guy coming after them. It's just a dog attack.
Well, also, too. This is your eye dog. Yeah, the dog that's good liable to murder somebody in any second.
Anyone, apparently, who speaks around the dog, it tries to kill.
Yeah, so all right just try because it's try it it tries to attack them before
They even descend on the property. Yeah, it's like they're they're just in the neighborhood and the dog
It tried like tries to attack them and it is kujo style to jump up on the window. Yeah
Yeah, and then what did you think was the benefit of of dragging?
Showing the climax of the movie him dragging the girl by her hair down the middle of the street
Why do they show you that in the beginning? I never understand that in movies
Why show me the ending at the beginning that didn't bother me I thought that that was I thought that was a nice
misdirection of you think she's dead and then she's not and it it goes past there
I don't mind when a movie does that what I did mind was a blind guy
dragging a dead or the lifeless supposedly body behind him down a street with no cane or dog or anything and
Just walking perfectly to his front door. I mean come on. I don't even know where his house is. Maybe he counts the steps
I don't know. I got a lot of questions about just blindness in general
Because I don't know how they do stuff. I am very curious. Well, you it's you count steps. Yeah, I know that
But I honestly it's feeling it's feeling whether it's with a cane or your hands. It sounds and things like that
But my point is, is you can count steps all you want.
I guess that's the military thing,
but I just don't believe that this guy,
how does he find where their car is parked?
Well, he goes to where the dog's parking.
But there's no fucking way in hell.
This guy has gone from the exact place
their car was parked and counted those steps.
Why would he ever have a need to do that?
He doesn't even know where that is.
Exactly.
It's not like he's like, oh, my dog's in the place,
my dog is always in he's like yeah I'm going to the sound of my dog and now
where the fuck am I have to get home right I think to its credit it moves so
fast to not allow you to really think about those things but yeah when it ends
I think the reason you don't feel like you've seen some great movie is that you
leave kind of going but wait a minute and as soon as you start picking at it it
does kind of fall apart well yeah I didn't pick that until now and now I'm getting
upset. Now I'm upset it didn't go in the direction also that I wanted to go in
which I thought it was gonna be a man that had like a booby -trap house.
Homelone stuff. Yeah like all kinds of contraptions and then I thought at the
end of the movie he would call her into his office and he'd give her the house
like at the end of Willy Willy Wonka and all of her dreams will come true. He'd be
like it's all yours. The money's all yours. You passed the test. Yeah you know. I
Didn't mind I wouldn't more out of that from you. I thought that was a very funny. No, I think that would have been a great film. I
Didn't mind
The the twist in it though because to me I was like boy. I bet nobody
Expected this twist and it wasn't like a fun twist. You're like oh god, and then it just kind of keeps getting worse
I mean you you see at one point a giant vile full of jizz
It's a turkey -based or yeah, and then she shoved it into his mouth and he gags on it and caught you see his own
Giz come out of his mouth. I didn't need to see that and I'll tell you though
To me anytime you get a whole audience to go like ah
Then you've you've really done your job and the audience reacted to that in a very big one right well
Look, it's one of the reasons I have such immense admiration for the end of pink flamingos. I mean, it's sure
Yeah, I yes, I do want to see you make somebody eat a piece of dog shit on camera. Yeah, that's pretty amazing
Yeah, somehow that doesn't offend me the giz turkey bass. You're upset me a little bit. Oh, I shouldn't upset me at all
That's what here's the thing giz that's like when people saw some don't marry and people go out of their fucking heads
Mike
That scene, you know, I was an usher when that movie came out and I used to like basically watch the entire movie
But I'd go in for the big scenes the dog attack the gizz in the hair because you'd watch these crowds just lose their fucking mind
But I wonder why jizz is kind of such a last frontier for movies when
50 % of your audience jerks off every day
The other 50 % has been in contact with jizz or pissed it out of them or spatted out or wash it off their hands
a million times. Why is Jiz this last frontier? And also all these people watch porn, right?
What is it? You know? And when people get all the norms about anything in a movie,
especially sex, you'll all watch porn. Well, Pat, I had to disgusting fluid. I mean,
I don't know what do you want to tell you. It's like, it's like why hasn't the territory of period
blood been tackled yet. It's gross. Well, it wasn't caring. Well, it was pig's blood.
Well, in the beginning, she gets her period in the shower. I don't think they show the period
blood. They do. And everyone else plug it up and starts throwing tampons at her. Where do you
see the blood, though? Is it going the drain down her legs and down the drain? Yeah. All right,
well, I mean, there's one movie that did period blood and one other movie did come. Yeah, I mean,
happiness had come, whatever. But I think it's a revolting movie. I detest the film happiness.
I resent that it exists. I resent that it exists. I love tapping us so much. But you know,
that's a movie where having it in my collection honestly worries me that that someone will see it
and arrest me. Well, I had little children in my collection for a while. That's gone. That's long
gone yeah a girlfriend gave it to me years ago and Julia McCullough said have
you seen it and I said no and he said you need to examine your relationship
that your girlfriend just gave you that move yeah I agree I agree I
happy that we I've said it to you before I got as far as the Gige hitting the
wall and then him putting the postcard on it and I was like this is fucking
disgusting but see let me let me press you on that for one second that's
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
You've watched in your life 10 ,000 hours of pornography?
Yeah, why does that bother you?
When you know it, this is actually fake
and not being shot out of a penis.
Because it's not a scene of two people fucking
consensually and enjoying it.
It's a scene of a fucking...
Well, he's not fucking anyone.
He's just masturbating.
Yeah, he's an immensely perverted shut -in
who calls people and jerks off to their voices and then yells is your pussy
wet is your pussy wet as he comes on it's just it's just so depraved it's
disgusting it's disgusting it's so gross and it's like it's not enough that okay
there's this weird wrong number scenario and then oh that's weird and then you
realize wait this guy's crazy and then it's like well no wait that's not enough no
wait hold on now he's gonna say is your pussy wet wait that's not enough he's
jerking off. You know, okay, okay, okay. No, no, wait, wait, wait, we're going to show
the come hit the wall. We're going to cross cut that with Philip Seymour Hoppins scrunched
red face of ecstasy, just, you know, and then if that's not enough, the cherry on top is
he puts the fucking postcard on over it. And then, and then goes and talks to his neighbor
like he was fucking bacon cookie it's just gross man and I know that's the point
this is what goes on by and close doors in the suburbs you know I mean it is
meant obviously to provoke reaction out of you but I I was certainly shocked by
it when I saw it in high school I hadn't seen a lot of movies like that but at the
same time people will really get upset about fluids and watch porn I've never
understood personally you know that's it I understand that you know I'm not
said about fluids, almost said about the scenario. Yeah, porn is not somebody jamming a turkey
baster filled with cum porn. That's meant to rape and pregnant somebody. Yeah. Well,
now he said, Joe, that he's never been around. Yeah. And then he, and then the guy is choking
on his come. It's a different story. I also don't like the porn. I also don't like the porn
where they, where they like, they take the girl's head. And she's like, oh, yeah, of course
not. You know, well, I mean, the girls doing those scenes a lot of time like that. Like,
I don't like it. I don't care if she's into it or not. I don't like it. There is so much
of that that there must be lots of people that like that. And that worries me and troubles
me. Yeah. Well, you know, it's it's there's a lot of things that trouble. Look, frankly,
if you like it, you like it. Sure. But all of the scenarios I'm describing that I don't
like. Yeah. Well, I don't like that kind of porn even to the girls. Some of the girls
But the things I'm saying for these movies that I don't like are things that are involving other people in depravity
That and the people that don't want to be in those situations and it makes it gross
Well what you might not have gotten to if you stopped it after that is that
At the end of happiness
The boy, the young boy who's his father molested his friend
Yeah
He
master bans and then excitedly he goes I came and he's all excited because he
finally got his chance to come and then the dog comes in and eats the
come and isn't this the same kid that asked his dad why won't you
bless me right which they kind of didn't always Sunday as well years later I
mean it's just gross man it's horrible yeah no happiness is and by the way like
fucked up movie you can you can't and and this is my thing with a lot of those
Todd Solens, Todd Solens, whatever, I can do whatever he wants. I don't care. It's not for me.
But you know, the defense for a lot of these types of gritty, gritty or cinema is,
hey man, these things happen and this is like, he goes into the, to the, to the minority of things
that are, of terrible things that are happening out there and then goes into the minority of the
minority where even the molester would be like this is fucking gross dude why is this
kid asking him that you know what I mean he goes into such a small percentile that it's
like dude I don't understand like how man anyway supposed to relate to this like I who
was this for um well me apparently I mean I I really did love happiness and I think I
loved walking to the dollhouse uh walking to the dolls for me is one of the only movies where
where the bullying feels realistic to me.
Whenever I see bullying in movies
and it's not like the worst thing I've ever seen,
I'm like, I don't know like to that.
I had it worse.
Right.
The kids in the documentary bully,
I'm like, no, I had it worse than all these kids.
Right.
I thought, well, the dollhouse was good.
Storytelling is half a good movie.
I was, I watched half a Wiener dog last night
before I fell asleep, which is his latest.
I enjoyed it.
Why isn't the same girl the girl?
That bugs me.
Why is Greta Gerwig sent suddenly the girl from welcome to the dog house? Well, I
Had just gotten to Greta Gerwig, but weinered weiner dog
It's essentially about a weiner dog. It's about actual dog
But Greta Gerwig's character is the girl from welcome to the dog. That's true
So it's like why isn't it just the other girl?
He's done that a bunch. He did life during wartime, which was all the happiness characters played by completely different people
Okay
So you know, you know, that's tough on a guy like myself
But uh, I did my best with it. You know, I'm doing slides. This guy couldn't follow the latest Chevy Chase vehicle. I think Paul Rubens played the
Thelpsimo Hoppen role, although I'm probably wrong with that. We, by the way, we give a lot of wrong information on this
podcast. I was, I was listening to an older one and you talk so much about your love of Justin Lynn and his direction of the
Conjuring and the Conjuring 2 and Dead Silence and you're speaking about James Wann
Oh, yeah, Justin Lynn is the other Asian director who did fast and furious and Star Trek and all that. No, but no
Wait, James. Wait a second. James Wann is horror Justin Lynn is fast and I thought I thought the guy that did the Conjuring also did fast and furious
No, wait a minute
No
Are you sure I am sure I'm just saying folks sometimes we say the wrong thing in here
We don't have a fact checker listening
Don't be mad at us. He meant James Wong who was a great director as is Justin Lynn
I'm just hold on. I think that James Wong directed Star Trek though Justin Lynn director
But yeah, we in a dog, you know, I'm watching it. I honestly felt sort of like a family comedy almost which is very weird
James one directed the new one. No, he said it. Yes, he did
just in the lead directed fast and furious six. Hold on. That's what I meant. James
Wan directed Dead Silence the Conjuring and the Conjuring 2. Hold on. Director MacGyver
TV. Yeah, Furious 7 was what was who? James Wan. He didn't direct Star Trek. That's
I got confused who the hell directed Star Trek the new Star Trek was directed by Justin Lynn
Well James one directed Furious 7. That's crazy. I got it on IMDB right here. You don't believe me. No, I do
I were mixing them both up which doesn't look good for us
Franklin
I
Had no idea James one had ever gone out of the horror world. Yeah, he directed and that's why I thought he directed Star Trek 3 as well
But he didn't that was Justin Lynn. I got confused. I'm sorry. Okay, so Justin Lynn also directed two of us is a true detective
Which I also got confused and thought that was James one James wanted saw dead silence death sentence and
Sidious
Conjuring and then randomly furious seven the only action movie he'd done. So that's that's confusing
for right
Because Justin Lynn also did a fast and the furious movie he did fast six. Yeah
Yeah, I believe he did Tokyo drift.
He did fast and furious, and I think he did fast and furious six.
Okay.
Why do you think he did Tokyo drift, racist?
I thought he did do Tokyo.
I'm saying, why did you...
I'm making a joke.
Justin Lin did Better Luck Tomorrow, which was like a pretty cool Asian Heist movie.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm glad we got that cleared up.
Well.
You know, we seem more confused when we start.
Wrong information, constantly.
But what can you do?
You know it's like very tame. Yeah, it's like a cute, it's like a Greta Gerwig movie,
right? Yeah, it's like there's the fun. I'm watching it not seeing any signs of Todd
shouldn't and the thief dog has so much diarrhea that I honestly was starting to get a
little sick and I fell asleep shortly thereafter, but there's a but that's even supposed to
be funny, right?
Yeah.
But there's a Monty Python level of diarrhea.
And Danny DeVito's in it.
Danny DeVito has not been in it yet, so I still have more to go.
He is in it.
Yeah.
Well, you think even Todd Collins has got to hit a wall eventually because I'm tired of
the N -bombs, and they come shots.
Yeah.
And by the way, Justin Lennon did direct Fast and the Furious,
Tokyo Drip.
I didn't say it in.
OK.
I was just making a joke that you were
seeing an Asian guy directed Tokyo Drip.
And to episode the True Detective, bring your back full circle.
All right.
Let's go to some questions about, I was said, noises off.
I can answer any question he had, but it was off,
Because I love it
About don't breathe
My my friend John Kensel sent me a video for some reason. I don't
Let's go back to that because I don't know if that's actually a question
The video is settled my dad found out where Irish and not Italian. Yeah, obviously that has nothing to do with this podcast
Yeah, well, he responded to the tweet
you know yeah all right uh Lucifer Bruce writes I wish John DeGuignio the JFK
researcher I don't know how to say the name would become famous Joe you sound
just like him okay I sound like a JFK okay finally I sound like a smart
person all right where are the don't breathe questions okay here we go hi from
Hello, Cole, this comes from Cole Rothecker at C -O -L -E -R -O -T -H -A -C -K -E -R.
I liked, don't breathe, wanted to know what you guys thought of the same director's evil dead remake.
I loved it. I loved it. We mentioned it very, very briefly earlier, but I loved it.
And one of the things that keeps me loving it is the fact that I know many people that
have said it was too brutal for them.
They couldn't handle it.
You know, my friend Jared Logan, who's a very funny comic and a writer, loved Jared,
just in his podcast, by the way, should be out soon.
Jared's a great guy.
Jared had said to me, and Jared has, you know, sits through some pretty brutal stuff and
has made fun of me for thinking a movie like Annie Christ was extreme.
But he said that after the scene where the woman is sawing her own face off, if it got
any worse, he was going to have to leave the theater because it was too much for him to
handle.
But I loved it.
I thought it was great.
And anybody, I finally got a chance to say this in a form where it matters, really bothered
me that reviews of that film, the biggest criticism it was getting was, misses all the humor
the original and it's like the first evil that doesn't have any humor in it right the first one
is a straight horror movie evil did two which is a loose sort of remake of evil dead one has
humor in it yeah but it's not a fucking slapstick comedy yeah and also they are
clearly going in a different direction with the remake it's like they they're not trying to be
funny in any way so what do you want I thought honestly the kind of over -the -top nature of the evil
dead remake was in its way funny. Sometimes something can be so intense that I sort of just laugh
out of panic and I was doing that in the evil dead remake. There was some crazy shit in it.
I much preferred washing it in a theater than I would have at home by myself. I had a good time
with it. Well, the girl sawing her face off with the piece of broken glass was rough. I also saw
that movie with my friend Jim Pinkstone and I remember the way the scene goes it's black and you just
here. So you know what she's doing before you see it. Remember him turning to me and going,
Jesus. Yes. And I was honestly scared to see like what we were going to see when the light
went on. Yes, that was rough, certainly. It was fantastic, though. Okay, here's another one
from Lucifer Bruce. He sent a bunch today. Discuss a remake you would like to see, not one that's
succeeded, but one that almost got it right or disappointed you.
So that's, you know, sort of on the topic because the evil dead guy did this.
One that almost got it right or just, but, you know, I, I'll go ahead.
You go first, a remake that got it right or almost got it right.
He's saying don't talk about a remake that got it right.
But what's a remake you wish would have got it right, but it kind of missed the point
or kind of with the mind you were disappointed in it.
I mean every everyone I'm disappointed in it seems like to some degree we talked at length on here about the poltergeist roommate which is about as bad as it gets
where you take away all the heart all the soul you get the story wrong you get the laughs wrong you get everything wrong yeah that was and that's a Sam Raimi joint too you know like.
Yeah he produced that that was a real let down that one and I mean there's no bigger Sam Rockwell fan on earth and I just was so disappointed at how bad that was.
you know there's there's so many horror remakes the stepfather remake was
pretty weak the amity bill horror remake was I like the amity bill right yeah I
enjoyed the amity bill remake and I also enjoyed the omen remake yes I like the
omen remake yes yeah I mean I think horror is one where more often than not it's
it's easy if you're remaking kind of a a lower level horror film which I think
all the ones we just discussed are but you can't do poltergeist nobody's
attempted the exorcist. You're not going to do it better. The shining remake you watched recently.
I did not. It's got its moments. It's not. And it's, you know, Stephen King would probably
slit our throats if he heard us call it a remake. Yeah. You know, to him, it was no, the proper adaptation.
Right, right. I found I've been pretty pleased with most of the horror remakes I've seen. You know,
not terribly, terribly disappointed. The two I'd like to discuss is one that
people hated and got panned so much that they're going to reboot it again with
different people and a different crew. But I liked the nightmare in Elm Street
remake. I thought it was fun. I thought they made Freddy scary again. I thought
Jackie Earl Haley was a great Freddy. I thought he looked scary. I like the dream
sequences. I thought they played good homage to the first one. I liked it. I liked the twist
where you kind of thought he might be innocent for a minute and then it turns out that he wasn't.
I liked all that stuff. I thought they did as good a job as you probably could have with that
daunting of a task. You know, like the Halloween remake. I hate the Halloween remake. Again,
It made me feel terrible, but I didn't hate it.
But again, it's Rob Zombie doing this thing
where it's like, yeah.
It's so in your face depraved.
Yeah.
It's not enough that they're struggling family
and the stepdad's kind of an asshole
and the daughter's fucked up, but then also he hits on her
and says he wants to fuck her at breakfast or would,
and it's like, jeez, for Christ's sakes, man.
And was that you I discussed that like even the janitor
that took care of him when he was a kid, he kills that guy.
Yeah, and then like later and like, God.
That was discussed somewhere.
Give me one moment of hope or feeling or.
Yeah, that was discussed somewhere where Rob Zombie,
I think, said like he had to do that.
So you knew Michael Myers was crazy or whatever.
Yeah, I got it.
I got it.
But I'll tell you my, my B y 'all end all like the,
I mean, no remake made me more, I threw it away.
I threw it in the trash go on. It's one of the only horror movies. It's one of the only movies period
I've ever thrown directly in the trash. Yeah, uh, was uh, Texas chainsaw
Not oh yeah, not the Texas chainsaw massacre remake with Jessica Beale. I like that a lot. I thought that was really good
Oh, I hated it. I like the BL one and the beginning which is the prequel to that. I thought was was was passable
Texas chainsaw I'm talking about the one that came out two years ago
Didn't see it or three years ago was in 3d
What a fucking pile of shit. Yeah, what a pile of shit the only Texas chainsaw movie to ever use CG effects and terrible
CG effects at that
laughably like sci -fi channel bad
CG effects of blood of blood. Why are you why are you computer generating blood right now?
That for three days they can make it splash. I guess so. I don't fucking know. It was so dumb
But there's this thing at the beginning where it picks up right where the original movie
ended and this vigilante group from the town comes and they fire bomb leather faces house.
Okay.
And then I was watching the, I was watching the, and then like leather face sort of becomes
this like anti hero through the movie, which fuck off, I don't want to see that.
And that was watching the behind the scenes, vignettes, or whatever, and one of the producers
goes, is what Leatherface's family did in the first movie?
Horrific?
Absolutely.
But what those vigilantes did was worse, because whether you're criminal or not, everybody
deserves due process, and that's how we got to do on Leatherface's side.
It's like, what the fuck are you talking about?
You loot it. This is what happens to people that somebody should talk to that guy, you know, behind bars for a minute
Make sure we're okay letting him out
But this is what happens to people that live in this fucking land. This fucking Hollywood for too long
Yeah, this son eats away their goddamn brains. Yeah, they think everybody is redeemable in some way and they go
Well, how do we make this guy likeable? Actually, when they made that Godzilla shit remake with Matthew Broderick
Yeah, and then the other shit remake was yeah, and broadwicks was shittier. Yeah. Oh, yeah
They actually and the and the monster look nothing like Godzilla right and everybody's very mad justifiably so
The lady who designed the monster goes. We wanted a sleeker sexy or Godzilla. She said that so that exact quote
So what the fuck is wrong with these people sexy Godzilla?
so
So that's my that's my one that I really hated, but what I want to do before we wrap this
up is I used to go through and talk about the movies I'd seen throughout the week. I haven't
done that yet. I'm going to blast them out real quick. You tell me if you've seen them or not.
The weener documentary fantastic. I heard it's amazing. I want to see it. It's funny. It's
crazy. What he puts his wife through is do it now. No, no, no.
and anti hero by the end of the game.
I wanted a sexy wiener, that's why I watched it, and I got it.
I saw the shallows, I think I talked about on here, pretty, pretty good little thriller
with Blake Lively, Worth or Rent.
It's not bad, folks.
Sure.
Not great.
It's not bad.
Not interesting.
Don't think twice the improv movie that Mike Breglia did.
How was it?
I liked it.
I have friends in it so I want to see Chris get there's a good friend and I want to see it to see there were things in it that really kind of made me cringe and I don't know if it was because I was relating to them or because
you know as with all movies about comedy the improv scenes themselves are kind of extremely not funny you can tell they're scripted
Uh, so it was hard to view these guys as geniuses when you're not laughing at their stuff, but all the stuff in it about
professional jealousy and and your friends
Taking off and stuff like that. It was all very relatable, and I thought it was a good movie about a subject I hadn't really seen before
Southside with you the Barack Obama Michelle Obama first date movie
movie was fucking adorable yeah I don't normally call something cute it was
really cute and like like they it was you really felt almost like you were
watching Barack Obama the actors they got for these two were incredible it's
like 80 minutes long I thought it was a very sweet movie and I liked it okay now
do you think it would have been distracting had they had Jordan Peele playing Obama I
think I would like that too okay they guys they got man they must have been
casting this thing forever because they really knocked out of the park.
Um, sausage party, I hated, uh, you saw all these movies this week.
No, over the past couple of months.
Okay.
I, I didn't laugh at all.
I don't know what the reviews are about.
The audience I saw it with was silent as well.
And the group people I saw it with didn't like it.
Um, I root for comedy though, so I, I, I hate that I didn't like it, but there we go.
War dogs I thought was fun.
Right.
Jonah Hill is shockingly obese in it.
Was that for the role, do you think?
I think he probably got super fat and then decided to say it was for the role.
Okay, but it's a good fellow's rip off.
I think what's his name?
That old school.
Why can't Todd Phillips?
I think he really knows how to direct a movie and make it look cool.
You know, it's nothing amazing, but it's a good time passer.
It was fun.
I wanted to see it and the last minute I bailed because I watched it.
I rewatched the trailer with my mom we were thinking about seeing it and as soon as I saw the
The overhead camera shot of Jonah Hill doing coke and throwing his head back. Yeah, no, it's HBO's vinyl style
I was like yeah
There's a scene at the end where
The narrations like and you know what the one thing that brought us down was it's almost the exact same line as good fellow
Isn't it you know he dresses the camera? Yeah, it's it's fun enough
I would say it's a fun okay movie I
Saw
Bad moms
Which was really bad folks as you can imagine. I mean
Although I think me lacunus is delightful, and I wish you got better material
I'll get I'll say one positive people in that movie are delightful just like a movie. Yeah, no, it wasn't good and
I'll end on a on a real great one which was heller high water. I'm gonna see that this week with Jeff Bridges
Who has either gotten older and weirder or he's doing a character, but his voice in this thing
He's insane. He's like, I'll tell you you're shuffing me. I'll steer. He's like doing a almost like a Walter Brennan voice
But it's him Ben Foster, Chris Pine everybody in the movie is fucking great
Titus shit. It's exciting cool dialogue. It felt like a kind of like a no -country -for -old men junior
You know, it's not that good, but it's it's great. I'm gonna see that this week
Uh, when I am on the road, and well, look, when I, when did I watch it all month?
Because I was away.
What'd you say?
Scotland.
I saw suicide squad, which we discussed the last show.
But I spent most of my free time when I had time to watch things watching every single
Alan Partridge thing I could find.
Oh, I fucking love Alan Partridge and I always have all that was streaming in Netflix on Netflix
in the UK.
And it's not streaming here and I immediately went on to Amazon to buy everything.
I own it.
You can get a box set of everything he's done. Yeah, partridge
Saxon Dale all that grid shit, and it's about 60 bucks. I got it on order. I got it on order
I'm getting that and I'm getting the knowing me knowing you box it awesome. It's in there too and alpha pop and alpha
Papa
Alpha Papa is surprisingly very funny. I love it. I saw that one. That's all I'd ever seen when he's crawling out the wind
I think I recommended it to you actually when he's crawling out the window and his pants fall off and he's hanging there
bottomless I mean it's it's look it's it's not the most advanced comedy but I
laugh my ass out I think he Steve Cougan is one of the funniest men in the
world and a guy who outside of like the trip where he's playing himself and
stuff he's generated himself they never get him right he's never had a part
worthy of his skills except like 24 -hour party people are something more like a
drama I love I love I love everything I've seen the guy do I look forward to
seeing more. Yeah. And I also started watching baskets, which I really enjoyed.
baskets is great. The Easter brunch episode is maybe the best TV episode of the
year. Almost may be emotional. I think Louis Anderson steals the God damn show.
He's fantastic in it. Yeah. The the gag at the drive -through of which is such a
writers room gag, which made me really love it. With a bunch of guys, you can see
the writers room sitting around being like, sure. What if he just ordered every
wrong soda. Yeah, yeah. Like every wrong soda. And then by the time it gets to
Shwebs. And he's just screaming. Shwebs. Yeah. Yeah, it's it was a very
strange unusual funny show. And I like to quite a bit. Folks, that's our show
today. I have a lot to plug. Forgive me. I will be. God, when is this coming out?
this will be out next week. Look, if it hasn't passed the 15th of the month yet, I'll be an old
Scottsdale, Arizona, it stayed up Scottsdale. But I have a feeling this is probably coming out
the week after that just happened. So, if it is, please, October 13th, come and see my special,
the taping of my one hour Comedy Central Special. It is happening in Los Angeles at the Masonic Temple.
at the Hollywood Forever Cemetery, Thursday, October 13th.
I believe we're gonna do two shows,
go online to get tickets for that.
Check that out, Paddy Wash will be there,
and check out the new short fiction column,
some severe situations, I guess, two or three stories
are out by now, and that's on fangoria .com as well.
I am on Twitter by an Instagram at D Patrick Walsh.
Last of my told you I was gonna be
on the high and mighty podcast. This time I'll tell you I'm going to be on the secret
masters with Jared Logan every week you discuss a different topic and entertainment. This
time we did mob movies. It was a lot of fun. That's all I really got. Thank you for your five
star reviews. You're great comments. We love getting your feedback on Twitter. Thanks, gang.
You've been listening to we'll see you on how a presentation of the Fangoria podcast network
work produced by Thomas DeFaio, executive produced by Ken Hanley, a Fenguri entertainment,
for present opportunities, advertising, and increase, and information about what we'll
see in health contact, Ken at KennetFinguri .com.