I'll see you in hell.
When the sun air your spring is big,
comes a thing on the drink and you know I say,
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'll see you in hell.
You know I'm a real woman.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell,
the podcast that discusses
your favorite genre films,
sci -fi horror and all that,
that there may be included
under that white umbrella.
You know what we do here.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be paying this
seven bucks a month to get this shit.
Would you bitch?
Oh my god.
Well, thank you for paying the money.
I'm sorry, the joke called you bitch.
At least in my case,
we've been watching a lot of night bar on Elm Street.
That'll be the next episode.
So we heard the word bitch
literally millions of times
just in the air.
But this is sort of a special episode
for Joe and myself because
we're reviewing the Exorcist III
which is actually the very first film
that Joe and I watched together.
As friends.
As anything.
Yeah. Well, that's actually not true, Pat.
The first movie we ever watched together
was the Ace Ventura when Nature calls.
Okay.
And we didn't finish the picture.
We didn't.
But because the people we were with watching it
were saying this isn't funny at all.
And Pat and I were saying it's a masterpiece.
Yeah.
In American comedy.
And that was where the friendship kicked off.
But then our first solo hang together
when we went out on Elm and said let's try this
and see how it goes.
And you and I were supposed to go to some sort
of a swanky comedy central type party, I believe.
But we wound up just hanging out.
I fell asleep, I believe,
which shows the level of comfort with you.
I don't usually have with people.
On my show.
Yes.
But like a newborn kid.
And the first hang for two men
to take it a movie on another man's couch.
It was, it was the first of Joe's
48 Los Angeles apartments that he lived in in the span of
four years.
How long are we out here?
Four years.
Six years.
One, two, three, four, five apartments in six years.
Okay.
No, six apartments in six years.
Grace.
It seems like more.
And then I wonder why I can't seem to have
have any savings to close through the pandemic.
Yeah, they were like, well, you know, hang on Mr.
DeRose.
So we'd like to just give you your deposit back.
And like they just start around and you're out the door.
Didn't even wait for the deposit.
I am sitting in shadow, which is good.
It wasn't really intentional.
But I thought I was going to get
it razzed so bad this morning because
I guess due to I have been
exercising outside in my neighborhood is all hills.
So it's a lot of like straight uphill wearing the mask.
And I believe that at some point
a poor or something in my nose
got infected or something went amok.
You can't tell right now.
I mean, you could probably tell by squinting.
But my nose is glowing red.
Like Frank driven when he gets the
whatever that is.
A scorpion attached to his nose and the naked.
Yeah, fighting the Japanese fighting field.
The Japanese fighting fish.
A gift from the emperor.
He'll be too.
Now the honest pad.
Is this an elaborate cover up for
the immense booze consumption?
Did you go WC fields full of
gin blossom?
And what better name for it then?
The gin blossoms.
But no, I so basically last night
I noticed that and I never
get zits.
You know, I haven't had a zit in a couple of years probably.
But I had that extreme pressure at the tip of my nose.
And I was like, oh god, this is very, very painful.
And then I tried to
drain the zit pop, if you will.
Sorry.
And realized it kind of wasn't.
It was just some sort of
impacted heat problem.
And my nose.
I guess it's better now than it was.
But I looked like fucking Rudolf.
For god's sake.
One of the grossest stories I've ever heard.
I'm sorry. It's very painful.
But you know.
So anyway, now when I go to the store,
I'm the guy who says.
I have a health condition.
I'm not wearing a mask.
And then if anyone questions me,
I lean over and cough into their face.
Right. Right. Right.
You're a Karen. Sounds like you're a Karen.
A Karen. Yes.
Did they just come up with a male Karen name?
No. I think that's just white guys.
Okay. Is it Karen?
Because there's.
I mean, there's Karen to care if she's not a Karen.
No, Karen is the insulting white woman label.
Okay.
Like one of white women's being awful.
Right.
Which I know is sort of a redundant sentence.
Folks.
Also, uh, speaking of current events,
why did you tell, uh,
Kristalia, Jeffrey Ross,
et cetera, to do what they did?
I have talked about this ad nauseam on my other podcast without a country.
I probably don't even want to hear what was said.
I, we don't need to discuss it.
I bring no comments over here.
Uh, there are no.
I, uh, I'm up in Mont out in Montalk.
Uh, uh, the Hamptons, if you will.
What are you doing there?
Well, Pat, it's, uh,
the short of it is,
I just need it to get away to clear my head over this Dixie Chicks name change.
Yeah.
I'm still really took out Dixie somehow made the name more offensive.
And that's the Jix.
Well, I was really alarmed to hear that they,
as a stutter staff, they wanted to change it to the fat chicks.
And then, of course, that was a big issue with the,
the overweight community.
Yeah, they were kicking a bunch in the porky pigs.
I heard they, they, they toyed with for a little while.
Right.
For Christ's sakes.
The, the word Dixie benefits.
Is it, I feel bad for Dixie Carter.
What she's supposed to do now?
Sure. Or Dixie land jazz.
You know, what are we going to call that?
Chick land jazz now.
You know, we're going to talk about Dixie land jazz.
I, um,
I also, uh, lady Antebellum just became lady.
Now that one, I was like, your name was lady Antebellum.
Antebellum is slavery.
I mean, essentially, it's like plantation life, isn't it?
Is that what that is?
I never knew what that, what that word meant.
If somebody's saying the word Antebellum.
Yeah. I mean, they, they've got slaves.
Uh, one of my favorite tweets in recent history, uh,
Carmen Lynch, who's very funny tweeted.
My last name just got canceled.
And I thought that was a great tweet.
That's good. Yes.
But I mean, it's what, you know, is, look, I'm sure there's,
please don't tweet at me.
I'm sure there are horrors affiliated with the term Dixie.
Dixie, but is anybody taking issue with the Dixie chicks?
They've proven their weight.
You know, they stepped out against George W.
There, we know what side the Dixie chicks are on.
Well, yes, we do.
I think what is happening now is that people are
scared and wanting to get to it ahead of time.
Because if it's a gotcha,
then it looks worse.
So they come forward.
But the problem is people are still not allowing that.
They're like, hey, you know, why did you have the name to begin with?
And it's like guys, they're doing, they're trying.
Um, we've just got from our, our fabulous producer.
And thank you, Mike.
We received that antebellum means occurring or existing before a particular war,
especially the American civil war.
So, so does that mean it just is a time period?
Right?
For me, when I hear the antebellum south, you know,
I feel like I'm watching the credit scroll before I'm on the film
glory or something.
You know, um, so I do think it's a,
it's a word that is problematic for you.
You can't, you, you can't get around the shaming anymore or the canceling.
I read a story today.
There, there was that director who was working on the Greg
Almond biopic.
Correct. Yes.
I don't know.
And the female AD was tragically killed.
They didn't, you know, it was a safety regulation.
Not taken or precautions.
One of those deals on the movie set.
And that's right.
But not as egregious as say John Landis, you know,
right. So it's horrible.
This woman was killed because they were shooting on train tracks.
She got hit by a train.
It's horrible. I feel terrible that that happened.
I feel terrible for her family.
Family was awarded.
I think $1 .7 million or something like that.
That doesn't make up for it, obviously.
But, uh, you know, it's a tragedy all around.
This guy's back directing again.
And I read this article today.
And it's like, it's like.
I just can't believe the audacity of this man to direct a film again.
A mere six years.
How long are you supposed to wait?
Yeah.
He's like, I go around promoting safety precautions now.
Every chance I get, I publicly admit the horror of the mistake.
And he's just the director, guys.
Like, I'm sorry.
To me, that falls way, way, way more on the shoulders of the studio than it does on the shoulders of the director.
Now, maybe I don't know some of the details of this.
Maybe he disobeyed a direct order.
I don't know.
But we don't know specifics.
But I mean, if he was found liable by a court of law, then he did something because they didn't find lambous guilty.
I just don't understand, like, like, at what point are you allowed to re -emerge after any,
that people make mistakes and sometimes those mistakes are tragically horrific.
But we used to be a people that would say,
hey, man, you turned it around and look at the redemption story.
That was a big thing.
The rise and fall and rise.
Like, we love that story in the United States.
And it's just gone.
It's just not.
You fucked up.
Doesn't matter.
It is true.
And of course, some people absolutely deserve it.
You know, the phrase cancel culture indicates in my opinion, people getting canceled for doing nothing.
And some people have done very serious things.
Kevin Spacey deserved to be canceled, you know, many others do.
But it does seem nuts.
And what's been crazy to me is like how many shows had more than one blackface episode?
How did scrubs have several blackface episodes?
Scrubs is a medical.
It's like, gray is an enemy.
It's really blackface.
Now, 30 Rock is a heavily satirical look at the entertainment industry.
Did I remember then having four episodes of blackface in it?
No, I did not.
But it makes a little more sense, I guess, than scrubs.
But these shows that are like, hey, obviously it's a different climate.
30 Rock was on the air five years ago.
So like, it's a little not always studies blackface episode was two or three years ago.
And they, you know, I think in all these cases they were using it to make some sort of satirical point, hopefully, but not all.
And the cartoon characters is the same thing.
You know, every cartoon this week came forward and was like, yeah, we have a white person playing a black role or a mixed racial role.
We're going to realize now that's wrong.
We made you realize that central park show premiered six weeks ago.
I know.
And just else playing a multiracial character.
The cartoon one, I think, at times goes a little too far for me.
I didn't understand Jenny's late step down when she goes, the character's only half white.
And it's like, okay.
So.
So why would it be any different if a full black person played a half white person or a full white person played a half black person?
I mean, it just starts to get into the splitting hairs.
Right.
It's absurd.
And then I look, I think we all need to do the right thing.
I will never, ever, ever in a million years support censoring art in any way, shape, or form.
I will go as far as putting a green to warning labels or whatever on things as I always have.
Sure.
Look, sure.
You're going to put a warning label on a movie and give it a rating with a warning up top that says contains graphic violence and this and that.
Fine.
I can understand that warning label just as much as it says contains potentially harmful depictions of racial character, whatever.
I get it.
I'm not against that.
I'm not against the warning label.
I'm not against people saying, well, on this show, we're trying to do better.
Or set an example, even if that's what you want to do, then great.
And I'm also not against the progress of, okay, guys, maybe if we're doing a cartoon and there's black people, we shouldn't hire white people to voice the, I get all that 110%.
But it does get to a point for me where I start to go, how much of this is a publicity stunt, how much of this is meaningful, how much of this is actually being helpful.
You know, when we're, when we're getting down to talking about the, you know, Amazon Prime, not streaming the dukes of hazard anymore.
As if Amazon gives a fucking rats ass.
Not anybody.
Just the most soulless corporation on earth.
So I mean, it's just, it's like, guys, is anybody watching the dukes of hazard getting the wrong idea?
Yeah.
Is anybody watching the dukes of hazard period?
Period.
Yeah, it's like, but I mean, it's weird.
We watched last night here in the house.
MTV 2, I think it was, was doing like, like a flashback Friday thing.
And they showed, they were showing a bunch of old shows and they showed the 2000 MTV music awards, video awards, whatever.
And it was crazy.
How much shit on it?
We were like, you could never do this right now.
And we're not talking about another world.
We're talking about 20 years.
It's not that long ago.
Especially the way time transpires now.
There's a big difference between 2020 and 2000 and 2019, 80.
You know what I mean?
Like, those gaps get smaller as, as we progress.
Yes.
I would say even movies that obviously with this TV show stuff, even as recently as five years ago, almost everything in them.
You're just like, no, no.
Like, you know, imagine going back and watching porcus now, you know?
I watched MASH.
I've been watching the Robert Altman movies kind of in order.
And MASH.
That's seen where they have, they, they tear down the shower tent around hot lips and she's standing there naked.
And there's 50 people pointing and laughing at a naked woman showering.
Right.
And then she runs into her superior and she's sobbing and like clearly shaking up.
All played for laughs.
It's one of the set pieces.
It's in the trailer for the movie that this naked woman, you know, being kind of exposed and mocked.
The times change.
But I don't, I don't know, you know, I guess we'll see where comedy goes.
Well, I mean, I believe, I believe the times change too.
And I think that's how progress works.
And I think.
I'm all for as we move forward saying, well, in this day and age, we don't do that anymore.
And go, okay, well, that's, that's fine.
That's, that's, that's okay thing to recognize.
But when I'm absolutely 100 % not for is going back and altering things from the past.
I think that that's insane.
I think it's right.
I think it's a very slippery slope to, to censoring and, you know, look, I'm all, I'm all for tearing down a statue of Hitler.
I would heavily protest if you, if they ever wanted to tear down Auschwitz.
Certain things, you know what I mean?
Like certain things are there to teach us and to learn from, you know what I mean?
And other things are just there to be provocative and, and, and predatory and, and, and indicative of hate.
I think then there's two very different things.
I'm going to tell you right now, Jeff.
If I see you on the news protesting that you want Auschwitz to be left standing, the, the friendship's going to be strained for a little while.
Why?
It's such an insane thing to be protesting about.
It's, I'm not going to protest it, but I mean, it's, it's, it's, it's there to learn from.
It's like, agree, agree.
It's, you know, it's, if we tear down every painful thing, here's the thing.
Like if you talk about, you know, for instance, the statues, you know, these Confederate statues that are up most of those were put up during civil rights as a fuck you to the civil rights movement.
Right.
They're the fucking things down.
Of course, it's horrible.
What, what people won't admit is that the, the, the reason that they want these things up so passionately, these statues are fucking dumb anyway.
But I feel like it is a racist thing.
They want their kids to know about racism because they're teaching their kids racism, which is why we will never lose racism in this country.
The only way you get it is, is being taught by your parents.
And I think a good portion of the country is just teaching it to their kids.
Sure.
So, so, so you want to tear one of those statues down?
I don't, yeah, I'm all for it. I don't give a shit.
But you want to tell me this movie about that same general can't exist.
That's when I started to go, come on, man.
This is, we're going to just pretend the man never existed.
We, we need to learn about this.
This is history.
It's how history works.
That's how progress works.
You can't be better if you have no example of worse.
You have to be able to go, oh, we were worse.
That's, that's bad.
And you can't make up for it.
Nine out of ten people are going to let you down.
That's just the sad reality of it, guys.
Stop trying on.
High nons.
Maybe ten.
Yeah.
Stop trying to fix and change and evolve everybody.
Cut and run.
Move on.
That's it.
What HBO Max did with this guy with the wind was put up this big, I think like a four minute statement.
And right, I think that the, the point is parents are going to teach their kids so maybe we can.
And I don't think it's going to help those families are doomed regardless.
But one good thing that came from it is that HBO Max announces they're pulling gum with the wind.
I run to my blu -ray shelf.
I got a copy of gum with the wind never opened because why would I open it that I bought for five dollars.
I'm not sitting down to watch a four dollar or four hour antivellum drama.
And I have seen gum with the wind.
Don't give it wrong.
But I immediately threw it up on Amazon.
And it sold for a hundred and fifty dollars in seconds to the point that it made me pissed.
I didn't charge more.
Uh -huh.
Now they have it right back up on HBO Max.
I hope the person that bought it for me feels stupid.
Why?
They wanted it as much as you wanted it.
You you both bought it.
You don't want it.
They wanted it more than I wanted it if they're paying a hundred and fifty dollars for it.
I never even want to bought it.
I'm better than both here.
That's true.
But I do like that you are a up a crisis profiteer.
I do like that you know happy to profit off of these people.
I just I want to I want to see a picture and ask a few questions of somebody who runs to their laptop
when they hear that gone with the wind is being pulled from a network that premiered four weeks ago.
And they think it'll never be around again.
I'm buying I'm buying split a movie I didn't even like that much.
Because there is yet a third or fourth round now of petitions that this movie needs to be banned and pulled from Netflix
because it depicts people with mental issues in a negative light.
Right.
I mean, so where does the people we all used to make fun of this overly conservative concept of where does the buck stop?
It's PC culture gone mad.
You know, it's it's brain police and all this stuff.
It's at a point now though where you're going well where does the buck stop?
I mean you know my friend pointed out the other side she was like well so what's next?
What are they going to we're going to ban horror movies because they promote murder?
It's not that crazy of an idea that that's what people are going to move towards.
Sure.
And if you all want to live in this fucking squeaky clean demolition man society
where the second one person goes against the grain things fall to pieces and you get a fall out of fucking
42 -year -olds to loan.
You know, when you're going to cry in a chamber to fix thing.
I mean God bless if that's what you want but make some sense to me.
I'll be fine because I've been wiping my ass with seashells for years.
That's a very strange scene of that movie.
Yeah, seashells bit.
Let's speak of Blu -ray's pad.
I got a nice news psycho for you.
Sure.
And it's not really a news story but it's something I read on movieweb .com and I know you'll be excited about it.
I'm almost hoping you haven't heard the news yet.
Red getting a 4k Blu -ray release.
So it will finally be back in circulation for all the fans of red.
It's funny you should say that because the very first movie that I profited hugely off of was red.
I know.
The pad was a VHS when I was at blockbuster video and I was working there.
And I used to show it to my friends all the time because I could not believe how insane and hilarious it was.
The slumb ocean scene at the high school dance with Lori Loughlin.
But you know, a stunt double who was probably 220 pounds with a black wig doing bike stunts as Lori Loughlin.
I'm like a little pink sweater.
We were blown away by this movie.
It was like the early days of so bad.
It's good for me anyway.
And then I looked it up online and red was out of print.
So I sold a tattered VHS of red for like 500 bucks when I really needed the money.
But this movie in 4k, if the stunt doubles look that bad in VHS, I can't even imagine what we're going to see.
But I'm ordering a copy for sure.
Red is a classic of these so bad it's good.
I've never seen it and I want to see it because of what you've regaled about it.
I've never seen the film.
Yeah, we're doing a double feature of that and I think gleaming the cube and a couple of BMX movies.
And I was so excited to go see Rad a couple of years back and something fell through there.
They didn't, the copy of the film didn't show up or whatever.
It's been very hard to find.
So I'm glad I made my money off it.
I'll be buying the new copy.
That's very exciting.
Yeah, yeah.
Nice little piece of news.
I'm more excited for the news psycho on the next episode.
Okay.
Obviously I'm going to save it for the next episode.
But why don't you, if you will, take us on down to pass movie corner.
I'm happy to.
Yeah, I have watched an outrageous amount.
You can listen to the runoff.
I've been doing at least an additional hour podcast or so a month talking about the movies I'm watching.
But a couple I haven't discussed on there.
I watched House Party one and two.
I'd only seen the original house party.
Not the sequel.
But I got one of those.
The only house party.
Yeah.
I got one of those four movies.
You know, it's like two on each disc.
Little mini box set that shows up.
House party one is a classic.
Yeah.
House party two.
We're already talking a pretty sizable slip in quality.
And I've heard three and four are about missions.
Three at least has Bernie Mac.
Three has some redeeming qualities.
It's way better than two.
But that's not saying much.
It's not good.
Yeah.
I mean, two, the amount of like three stages sound effects and shit they're using is just unbelievable.
I mean, it's like a boners like.
Yeah.
You know, they're doing it all there.
But it ain't great.
I was intrigued to learn that Rusty Cundiff co -wrote it because he's a great writer director who did, you know, fear of a black hat.
What else is Rusty Cundiff, too?
No idea.
But I know the name and I think he's great.
Yes, he is.
But anyway, the original house party is great.
It's a movie I wish I had been old enough to see in the theater because it's such a great party movie.
But just like what we're discussing, and I texted you about this, you know, it is a, in a really wonderful way.
It is a great celebration of black life.
A lot of people have been talking on Twitter and et cetera about why does every black story need to be trauma porn or about, you know, slavery or about oppression or whatever else.
House party is young, intelligent, black people having fun, having a great time.
And a really a precursor in that way to Friday.
It was the same studio.
Newland doesn't get the credit it deserves.
There were a lot more progressive than most.
And house party is just another side of black life that I love.
It's not as great as Friday, but it's kind of a test run.
And in watching it again, okay, this very progressive cool movie, when there's like 20 minutes to go in the thing,
there is a musical number where play the guy with the eraser head is in the drunk tank.
And they put him in the jail cell.
And within 30 seconds, everyone in this jail cell is trying to rape him.
Well, he's sweet booty.
I mean, that's a nice special little present booty right there.
He does a lengthy musical number about, please stay away from my ass.
Don't rape my ass.
It is so out of place.
And I do think that as the standards get stricter and stricter, almost any movie will be watching.
And they'll be that moment where you're like, holy shit.
You know, 16 candles is, of course, the main example of races of run -a -muck in a classic movie.
But boy, this came out of nowhere in House Party, this homophobia.
However, the movie is a blast.
I wouldn't call it fear of rape homophobia.
I wouldn't say.
It's a homophobic portrayal to show that everyone in the jail cell is dying for this guy's ass.
I know.
When it's not even a maximum security prison, it's like where you go when you steal a candy bar.
I don't think that's homophobic.
I think that's like I'd be afraid to be seen again.
All right.
I'll revisit.
I love a nice don't rape me rap.
And I've been looking for one for this week.
So I'll go back and see if I can download it.
Also full force.
You know, I know you're an old hip -hop guru.
I never heard of full force outside of the house part.
I don't know.
I assume they weren't amazing rappers.
Full for it.
It's funny because they play such assholes and bullies in that movie.
But their music is very like love -oriented.
So it's very funny that they play such assholes in that movie.
Yeah.
They got a lot of gay slurs and stuff throughout as well.
So, you know, it's sort of mixed back in that regard.
But the little guy from full force is tremendous in that movie.
Yes.
They are funny.
Can they're back?
Yeah.
It's like a cartoon car.
It's absurd.
I feel like a big drive with that movie was they said,
like, well, what if the Cosby kids was a real thing?
Yeah.
I feel like that was a huge inspiration for that movie, you know?
I agree.
And House Party One, what they want.
I mean, no.
I'll Fedover.
Yeah, that's the thing.
House Party One, you know, stealing the show to an absurd degree is the dual,
amazing supporting performances.
One from John Witherspoon, who would go on to be used even better in Friday.
In my opinion, one of the best supporting roles of all time is John Witherspoon and Friday.
But Witherspoon is like the nosy neighbor at the House Party is hilarious.
And even Funier is Robin Harris, who was an amazing stand -up.
He died very, very young, but he is the funniest part of House Party.
And you feel it immediately in House Party Two.
They devoted to like, they always have play looking at a picture of his dad.
Just because you know that everyone there just misses his presence so much.
Yeah, no.
It's in the second movie, is he dead?
Or is it just like he's not there?
He's dead.
He died right after House Party was released.
No, no, no.
I mean the character though.
They have him dead, but they use old footage of him like when he looks at a picture of him,
the picture talks and they use old footage of Robin Harris.
Sort of an Arthur II move.
Oh, well, did, did I talk about Arthur two last time?
You did, yes.
That's why I didn't write that out.
I do want to mention before I move on though that Rusty Cundiff wrote and directed tales from the hood.
I didn't want to say it if I was wrong, but you know, that's a move we've discussed in this show.
Cundiff is amazing.
And I think he wrote House Party Two and was very young.
And of course started doing much better work right away.
But I watched an abortion of a film called The Good Lire.
I thought you were going to say Juno.
Juno's about abortion.
God almighty.
This is a film starring Ian McKellen and Aaron Mirin.
Ian McKellen plays a con man.
Helen Mirin plays a rich woman.
He's in for the take.
It's the classic.
I'm going to pretend I'm in love with her, get her money and then skip town.
It's a start.
Pictures called Joe.
The Good Lire.
I said it already.
I saw it in theaters.
Yeah, I said it already.
Anyway, so it starts so fun.
And I love movies that star old people.
I'm a big fan of anything.
You know, you know, me know my love of the golden girls.
I love anything with old people in it.
Mine is the cocoon films.
Sure.
But it's exciting.
It's fun.
It's fun watching a man in his seventies.
Play a con man.
And it's fun watching these two fall in love, even though it's a con.
And Helen Mirin is wonderful and charming in it.
It's just a great movie for the first like hour.
And it's exciting.
And you're waiting for it to turn on its ear.
And you're like, is she going to outsmart him?
Is she conning him?
What's going on?
Very fun.
Capery kind of thing.
I would call it delicious.
Sure.
For that first hour.
And then this fucking thing, man.
I don't know what.
I don't know who wrote it.
I didn't look.
Sorry.
I'm not as good at doing that as Pat is.
But this writer clearly.
This, this to me wreaked of agenda.
It was like this was a fun movie that now suddenly there's eight hundred twists
that are commentaries on.
And he was a Nazi, but he wasn't a Nazi.
He was a Nazi that helped the English.
And then he actually knew her when they were kids.
And he raped her.
And this is all she's been tracking him for 50 years.
So she could get revenge for the rate.
It gets so fucking complicated.
And so polluted with plot lines that don't need to be in there.
When that are there to very quumsily showcase the strength of a woman
and the strategy of a woman, which at the end of the day,
it just comes off like bad writing.
It could have been a simple.
She knows what he's up to.
She's two steps ahead of him.
She takes him for all his money.
And it would have been a beautiful showcase for a female actor in her seventies
that that that that conveyed and displayed and celebrated the strength of a woman,
especially a woman at that age that we get written off by society,
even by society people that are hurried.
And instead, it's just jamming every fucking theme of war, abuse, assault.
And by the end of it, you're like, what the fuck is going on right now?
This doesn't make a lot of sense.
This is unfolding like some kind of Scooby -Doo Kaper.
He goes through two or three identities by the end of the movie.
It's ridiculous by the end.
It's ridiculous.
When I saw it, it was getting laughs near the end.
But then again, my mom loved it.
I mean, there's something about it that's kind of just like silly fun.
But and it's always good to have movies about the elderly because you never shoot her.
But yeah, it's ludicrous.
And you know, without spoiling anything, Helen Mirren did a movie that was the exact same thing called the debt with Jessica Chastain.
That was a thriller about kind of exposing an old Nazi war criminal.
Pretty good movie, pretty solid.
But so clearly, you know, that's all they want to see older people as like the last link to the Holocaust.
And Ian McKellin has done this kind of role, the exact same role, and have people.
Mike sent us a note.
I'm sorry, I just stepped on your hypothesis.
Mike sent us a note, the writer.
The writer of the good liar wrote for Colombo.
That's perfect.
My joke whenever I make fun of an older writer is that they wrote for Quincy,
which was the same era as Colombo.
So very funny.
The scripts have definitely been sitting around since probably the 70s.
But it's on HBO, I think.
And it looked.
I thought it was kind of trashy fun, but but a bad movie.
Don't get me wrong.
Yeah.
You're right.
You know, you're talking about Colombo.
I would be remiss if I didn't tell you, Joe, that over the last week I have watched every John Casabetti's film.
And I believe he's a favorite of yours, isn't it?
I love John Casabetti's, but that's a heavy week, babe.
I mean, that's not a, that's not a skip through the park.
Extremely heavy.
The only one that I had seen I think was the most fun of them all, which is Gloria,
which is like completely unlike his other movies.
Right.
But I watched them all.
Have you seen them all?
I haven't seen them all.
I've seen most of the ones in that box set.
Okay.
Yeah.
But, you know, eventually, you can't take any more.
And you say, I need a break.
Sure.
It's, again, I love John Casabetti's.
He's not a director and writer that you're, that you've, you rush back to.
Because you got to be in a real specific mindset to watch those flicks.
Yeah.
My new thing is kind of trying to track a director's career and watch them.
They're movies in order.
And he was perfect because he's only really got six or seven, you know, movies that you
would consider John Casabetti moved.
He did a few gunfire type things.
But, um, for me, the find of them all was the, uh, the movie Husbands.
Have you seen the Husbands?
Uh, not in the box set.
That's not in my, that's not in the box set, right?
It's not.
The material unjust did release it.
Okay.
And it looks incredible.
See that.
It looks great.
Well, I thought, especially for you and me, uh, this was the one I was looking forward to the
most.
And I looked it up.
Ebert hated it.
Some people loved it.
But Ebert loved John Casabetti's hated Husbands.
Husbands is three guys, Peter Flock, Ben Gazzara, and John Casabetti's himself.
Who was also, uh, me, a pharaoh's husband and Rosemary's baby, of course.
Yeah, three dozen.
He's an erotic.
A lot of classics.
He, you know, acted basically to fund his film career.
But Husbands is those three guys, their best friend dies unexpectedly.
They go on a week -long drunk.
They are drunk for an entire week.
Uh, the drunkenness leads them through New York City.
It leads them to their job's drunk.
And then eventually they all go to London drunk.
They're drunk on the plane.
They get to London.
They go to a casino.
They gamble at the casino drunk.
They pick up women drunk.
These men all are married with children.
Um, and they pick up, you know, some, some strange women to have fun with in their hotel room.
It's like two, two, 20, like all Casabetti's movies are very long.
But it seems to be for a purpose.
He wants you to have every scene drag out to the point where it feels like real life.
He doesn't like traditional editing and like cutting to the juice of a story.
So Casabetti's is a difficult, a difficult filmmaker to get into.
But I really did.
And my favorite of them was Husbands.
But when you look online, everyone says his most difficult, his hardest to get into.
Maybe it's the fact that I spent a lot of time with my male friends drinking and having fun.
That I just related to it.
But it's rough.
They're all turning 40.
You know, I'm about to turn 40.
They, they, they lead much darker lives than I do.
I'll tell you that.
But there was a scene early on where we listened to Peter Falk vomit and tried a vomit for like eight minutes.
And then finally when he's vomiting, he's like, ah, it feels good.
You know, you get the blood out.
Three guys in a bathroom stall, like trying to puke, gagging, watching each other puke.
And when I watch the documentary, all these sets have amazing documentaries about Casabetti's.
But their producer is like, I told him, Johnny, that's enough.
That's enough of this scene.
And he looked me in the eye and said, it's never enough.
That producer tells that story a hundred times over the course of the box set.
And it was enough.
Frankly, I mean, when you're listening to Peter Falk gag for eight, nine minutes, it is tough.
And the scene that precedes it is even worse.
They torture this old woman because everyone's singing a song of remembrance about their dead friend.
And they get in this woman's face and are screaming at her because her performance doesn't have any passion in it.
So there, there knows, knows this old woman like, again, sing it again screaming at her and kissing her over and over.
And it is rough.
It ends with Peter Falk getting completely nude inches from this woman's face to try to get her to feel something.
Husbands is a very rough movie.
It's new to criteria.
I recommend, but you're here in for a ruffle.
All right.
I watched a little picture called Bringing Out the Dead.
Loved it.
Don't have much to say other than I really enjoyed it.
And I'm grateful for my friend Pat Walsh because I texted you.
I was about 30 minutes in and I said, man, I'm watching Bringing Out the Dead.
I've never seen it.
It's losing me, man.
I'm about to turn it off because they were, they went in the beginning of the movie.
So the movie is about Nicholas Cage.
He plays an EMT who is extremely sleep deprived.
Probably an alcoholic, right?
Like he's, you know, like they're, they're, you know, it's basically taxi driver in an ambulance.
It's a guy coming unraveled because of the job, because of the sites of the job.
And the hours of the job and the demand of the job.
And like taxi driver directed by Scorsese written by Paul Shredding.
Yes.
Exactly.
Adapted.
And it's one of these movies.
It was adapted.
The book came out.
It was, I think it was optioned and adapted before the book was even published or do it.
You know, it was kind of like a casino in that sense.
But anyway, Cage is at the end of his rope.
He desperately tries to get fired from this job because he doesn't have the strength to quit.
He shows up late all the time and his boss won't fire him from some very funny scenes between him and the, the supervisor about, you know, he needs that he needs cage on the job so he can't fire him.
And they have some funny exchanges were cage.
You swore you'd fire me if I showed up lying again.
Yeah, I was in the trailer.
Yeah.
And he keeps seeing dead people everywhere.
And it gets very surreal.
Ving Rames really in a really stellar performance.
John Goodman is great.
Everybody's great in it.
But the movie Anthony, the Latin pop singer is fantastic and never acted again.
Literally Oscar worthy.
Yeah.
Mark Anthony.
You see his name in the opening credits.
You're rolling your eyes like what the hell is Mark Anthony doing in this?
Because you're like, why wouldn't it be John Link, Wasambo or whoever?
And then Mark Anthony comes in and you're like, this guy is killing it.
It's incredible.
But anyway, I, there's a, there's a, I wouldn't call it a love story, but there's a certain, you know, they, they, they sort of toy with a potential love story between Patricia Arquette and Nicholas cage.
That I found terribly boring and I didn't care.
But they kind of go to that well a lot in the first 30 or 40 minutes of the film.
So I texted Pat and said, you know, I'm watching this movie for the first time.
But it's losing me, man.
I'm bored.
And he said, no, no, it's a great movie.
Once you get past the Arquette stuff, it's, you know, that's, that stuff's boring.
And I said, well, that's what's boring me right now.
He said, no, just hang in there.
And then sure enough, it becomes less about the two of them in their potential attraction and far more about the, the themes of the movie, death, life and, you know, and that all culminates in the climactic scene.
I won't give away.
But pretty great from a weird period of Scorsese.
You know, I think that's, it's from a period where I think a lot of people were starting to write Scorsese off.
Yeah.
He was in this sort of interim position in his career.
He had kind of stopped working with De Niro at that point.
And he had yet to start working with DiCaprio.
And there's this sort of weird little in -between phase where it was like, as he tried to recapture his old stuff.
And these are strange movies and what's going on here.
And then of course, Scorsese came back swinging like, you know, like no other.
But, but it's a great little flick that I don't think a lot of people have seen because of, because of the period it came out.
But I enjoyed it.
And it's not available.
It's, you know, I had the DVD of it, but it's not on Blu -ray.
So I'm hoping Criterion does it.
Criterion did Age of Innocence.
So they must have a relationship with Scorsese.
I hope bring out that is the next one.
Because I've seen it in ages.
I remember loving it.
I wouldn't watch Age of Innocence with a gun to my head.
I'm going to watch it again. I was too young when I saw it.
So yeah, check out bring out, I think it's streaming on Amazon Prime right now for free.
Very good, I'll narrate a film.
And a great soundtrack.
I had always heard that when Scorsese was directing Taxi Driver, he used to lock himself in a small room, drink a pot of coffee, and listen to the clashes first album.
And I was like, boy, I wonder why that early punk reason doesn't make his way, make its way into his films.
And bringing out the dead is a lot of that clash burst album.
It's a lot of that.
It's a lot of that like 1970 style of filmmaking where like, you know, there's like a, they'll do a scene where there's like a spotlight on somebody for no apparent reason.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The lighting is all crazy and extreme and super defined.
And visually crazy. It's a good, it's a visual ride. I would say that, but it's, it's fun.
And you know, my, my third pick, a quick one is, is very few people can turn me on to a movie I haven't seen just because I've seen so much, but Joe, you really introduced me next just three.
And I've also been telling me for years to watch the remake of the blob, which I finally did.
Directed by Chuck Russell, who did Dream Wars, which we'll discuss when we get to the nightmare on Elm Street franchise.
Next time, but I really like the blob. It was fun. I would compare it tonally to a movie I know you don't like, but tremors.
Yeah, that's definitely in the vein of it. Yeah, or like even like a slither or something like that. It's not funny, but yeah, exactly.
And the effects in it, especially on a low bone, it's incredible. This blob. I mean, I, you think how scary can a blob be, but they do such cool shit, especially from 1988.
When we get to the nightmare on Elm Street, I was blown away by how much better effects look in 1985 compared to 1990, you know, like there are pockets of special effects where they just haven't figured it out.
And they look absolutely terrible. But the blob is really, it seemed mostly practical effects. And I just thought it was incredible in that regard. Very fun movie.
Performance by Kevin Dylan, who of course, you know, played the brother and entourage.
Drama, Johnny, Johnny, drama, Kevin Dylan, he's everything he's in. He plays such a great prick. He does. So he's great in heaven help us. He's great in the blob.
He's just platoon. I just, uh, Ru was rewired. I was started rewatching all the tales from the crypt start to finish. Yeah, he's in one called, I think it's called House of Horrors, where he plays a frack guy that doesn't want to leave college.
He's like 28, but he's still there just because he wants to keep hazing the kids. No, that's a scary story. Yeah, he's great in everything. I love when he plays those types of roles. Anyway, sorry.
Yeah, drama, he, they didn't realize he was playing a creep, but my God, he was to any normal person watching that show. That was kind of the whole point of entourage is that the people making it thought these were the heroes, then you watch that's a show.
I mean, that show was nominated for Emmys best, you know, best comedy series. They won Emmys. I would imagine you watched that now and your job would just be on the floor. I mean, it was, it was crazy sex is back in the day. Yeah, not to mention Ari, the hero is constantly screaming slurs, gays, slurs and racial slurs and his assistant Lloyd.
See, it's a scene. Yeah, I've never seen entourage.
I, you know, I watched it a few times when it was new. It infuriated me the, the indulgence and privilege of the entire thing made me furious.
It's, it's an infuriating show, but I remember liking it for a couple years. And I also remember watching it to learn how I should dress for Hollywood meetings, because I was like, I don't know what's cool.
And that's not a good, not a good, uh, barometer.
Orometer. Yes, exactly. I auditioned for entourage. I auditioned to play the manager. What's it? No, no, no, no, yeah. Yeah. That would have been a very different show.
I didn't get it. I know. I wrote it a very different life. Yeah. He also directed gotty. By the way, you could have been directed gotty. Yeah, I think I would have done a better job. I'm just gonna say that.
I'll close it out with a movie. I'd wanted to see for a very, very long time.
And I finally got to see it because I have HBO Max.
By dinner with her way. Okay. The biopic about the final interview with her, they villages.
The writer and I believe director of my dinner with her way is the guy that actually wrote the original article that the movie is or interview that the movie is based on.
He said years after it transpired that he realized that the interview was basically her village has a suicide note to him.
I was just always fascinated by the story. I really wanted to see the movie Peter Dinklage plays her reveal at the jazz, of course, Grand Slam as always.
It was just a great Andy Garcia plays Ricardo Montabon, which is the love fund. It's my kind of movie. I love movies like that. I love these two character, you know, like, you know, very simple, straight stories that are you're just going to get to know these two.
People over the course of 90 minutes. It moves because the dialogue is snappy and the scenery keeps changing, but it's really just these two guys carrying the entire film.
Garcia only appears in the flashbacks when he tells stories about fantasy island to the reporter.
And apparently her village has was fucking wild, like just wild, like, yeah, nuts.
So it's fun to watch for that reason, just watching the guy be, you know, he was just a wild personality, but it's heartbreaking at times.
It's very funny at times. It's very intriguing. I really enjoyed it. I don't know that it's a movie I would purchase for the collection, but, you know, it also harkens back to for me to that classic era of HBO when HBO was a little bit more in the business of doing made for HBO movies.
You know, they kind of once they kind of got into TV and became the place for great television. I felt like that wasn't a special thing anymore.
And it was way more TV focused at HBO than it was on movies, but, you know, when I was growing up, there was a thing called a made for HBO movie and it was a special event.
And they were kind of considered like sort of B movies until HBO became more prestigious. And this just reminded me of all that.
This reminded like when I first saw, I fell in love with Stanley Tucci because I saw the movie Winchell, which was an HBO made for HBO movie with him in Giamatti was one of my first Giamatti sightings.
Was the origin story for Winchell's donuts, correct?
Yes, yeah, yeah. Giamatti plays the donut.
Yeah, but I really enjoyed the film. It's worth definitely worth a watch and it's fast. You're in it out in 90 minutes or so.
I'll check it out. I know nothing about him, but I know Dinklage has a big company at HBO. So it must have been an important project because I have a meeting there coming up.
And I think clearly that was his dream thing. I mean, when you're Peter Dinklage, the roles are, you know, you don't have to acknowledge the height, but it helps certainly.
Sure, sure, yeah.
And that's a perfect role. So, now, he's in Irving Village is obviously Hispanic, right?
No, French.
Yeah, French. Now I don't know if he was also Hispanic, but it grew up in France. I always thought he was Hispanic, but the movie focuses really on he grew, he was French.
And I, if I'm remembering correctly, grew up in like Nazi occupied France, basically.
And his dad loved him so much and his mother was sort of a not physically abusive, but like emotionally abusive to him.
I think because of his condition, but the dad, it's heartbreaking. The dad loves him so much and the dad does so much when he's a little kid to try to rectify
his condition and like get him to grow to a normal height or whatever. Like it's very sad. It's very heartbreaking at times.
I'll check it on. Yeah. All right. Let's get on to our picture.
The, the exercise three, I, of course, saw it first with Joe rewatched it on Joe Bob on shutter, Joe Bob's drive in.
And Joe Bob had just tons of great information and stories about it. I highly recommend watching it that way.
But it is a movie that for all its huge pluses, it, it does have some minuses that really seem to smack of studio interference.
It seems like what we got was a very highly compromised version of what William Peter Blattie wanted to do.
Initially, this was going to be a return of Freak and William Freak and who directed the first exercise to the franchise.
But they weren't seeing eye to eye on the project. Then John Carpenter came on board.
John Carpenter wanted to do it, but realized pretty early on that Blattie just really wanted to direct.
And he said, this is your baby. You should do it. They remained friends. So, Blattie did it.
The only other movie, Blattie, as directed is the ninth configuration, which I talked about on this show.
And that was probably 15 years before this. And he never directed again.
It was based on his book, Legion. It does not take into account the events of the actresses too, which is probably very smart.
If you see an actresses too, ISO.
I've seen them all. And one in three are the only good ones.
That's right.
Two had some trippy sequences that are kind of fun, but it's not a good movie by any stretch.
It's a cool visuals, but yes.
Three leads is excellent movie. It's not up to the first one, but it's a really interesting movie.
And Legion, the book, is a direct sequel obviously to his book, The Exorcist.
So, this is the true sequel. The film was supposed to be called Legion in order to just get everybody away from the idea that this was some big exorcist sequel.
And also I think to ignore the second one.
Right.
Because I think if he had his brothers, he would have called this The Exorcist too, if he had to.
But the studio, as you said, interfered heavily.
They forced him to call it Exorcist three.
And then we're pissed that it didn't have an exorcism in it.
They're like, you can't call it extra three, but it doesn't have an exorcism in it.
And he's like, I didn't want to call it the exorcist three.
Yeah.
You did it.
It's it's classic studio fuckery.
And it's the same reason why I always defend Godfather three, because Coppola has said in several interviews that he and Mario Puzzo wrote a treatment.
And a script for something called the death of Michael Corleone.
He said it was never supposed to be Godfather three.
We didn't want to call it that because people were going to then compare it to the first.
This was supposed to just be an epilogue so people could see who were the character ended up.
And he goes, they forced us to call it Godfather three.
And then of course everybody goes, this isn't as good as the, and he's like, but it wasn't supposed to be the third, you know what I mean?
That's not what we were trying to do.
So Friedkin definitely, or sorry, Vlad, he definitely ran into some of that with this movie.
If you get the screen factory version of the Blu -ray, which I own, it does have the original cut of the movie in it.
Vlad, he reassembled the original cut from footage that he thought was lost completely forever.
Which is really incredible to that he, that this happened because this was a thing of myth to the fans for years and years and years.
They found the footage finally.
He was able to reassemble the movie.
Obviously it's uneven visually because you can tell like this is, you know, this is un, what the hell do you call it?
You know, the, it's not mad, you know, it's film that's not mastered or whatever the fucking term is, you know, whatever the final phase of film production is.
But it's not like the alien three Blu -ray where they have like drawings and stuff.
It is actually, it's actual footage.
It's very much worth a watch.
You should 100 % watch it. It's a different movie.
Yeah.
And it's not so different that it's insane.
But it's a different one of the big things that the original cut does is there is no Jason.
What's his face?
The place.
Yeah.
Jason Miller.
Jason Miller is not in the original cut.
Oh, God.
In the original cut.
That, uh, father carous is only Brad Dorif.
Uh, and they show pictures of him at the beginning on the wall.
So you know like when they start talking about father carous, it's this other actor.
Right.
Which makes it make way more sense when the murderer in the cell who's possessed by the demon that went into carous at the end of the first movie looks like Brad Dorif.
Yeah.
And it's suddenly in the in the studio cut.
It's hopping back and forth between Jason Miller and Brad Dorif.
And Brad Dorif's Jason Miller's performance is great.
Brad Dorif's performance is stellar.
So clearly, Vladie fought to keep.
Dorif in there.
Uh, which makes it even more confusing because like I said, it's jumping back between two different people.
Um, yeah.
And Joe Bob goes into that apparently Jason Miller showed up ravaged by alcoholism.
Uh, you know, didn't look good.
Couldn't remember three words in a row.
His brain was just gone due to alcoholism.
And he couldn't do those big speeches.
Um, so they had Dorif do it.
Um, Joe Bob goes into all that.
Apparently it was a big process where Brad Dorif had to film all those scenes twice.
They had to get a new set.
You know, uh, they flew him back out and like sorry, but you know, a very troubled production.
Um, because of all that.
Yeah.
And of course the original black, uh, Vladie cut does not have an extra system at the end.
Right.
That will.
I mean, for me, you watch the extra three and I'm riveted for.
You know, 75 minutes.
And then the ending.
I can't even pay attention to it.
They have, they bring in that, uh, that crazy old actor to do the extra system.
And you just are like, this isn't even the story we're telling.
It feels so crazy and dumb to me.
It's not scary.
It's not interesting.
But I can give us a quick synopsis, Joe.
Uh, what transpires in this film is it takes place exit, uh, you know, X number of years after the original film ends.
I think it's 20 years.
If I'm not mistaken.
The plot basically is that this demon that, uh, Pazuzu that was inside of Reagan.
Uh, in the original movie was also, uh, inside the body of a serial killer at that time called the Gemini Killer.
And I guess he jumped from the Gemini killer into Reagan, whatever.
But this killer's been dead for X amount of years and blah, blah, blah.
And the police never were able to really bring full closure to the case.
Um, this film picks up where all of a sudden these murders are occurring.
They're mere, they're mimicking the Gemini killer's murders.
George C. Scott plays the Lee J. Cobb role from the original film.
He's on the case.
He realizes these can't be mimics.
They have to be done by the same person because he's leaving a trademark that only the, uh, police department knew about the public didn't know every mimic always did a different trademark because that's what the police told to the papers so they could weed out the copycats.
Um, so he knows something's up.
Uh, eventually it leads him to a cell inside of a hospital, uh, padded cell, uh, occupied by none other than Damien Harris.
Lee, Jake, I'm sorry, George C. Scott says, I know that man, that man is, uh, Damien Harris.
He's been dead for 20 years just like this killer.
This doesn't make any sense.
And then he realizes what happened was when the spirit jumped from Reagan into father carus,
the spirit was somehow able to regenerate father carus's body and escape from the morgue and live.
It's a little convoluted.
It makes a little more sense than the bloody cut.
Um, but that's basically the plot.
That's basically what the plot is.
And this spirit is leaving carus's body every night from this cell going into people around the city and committing these murders,
which is basically I guess what it was doing in the 70s too.
So, um, that's it.
Stellar performances by George, she's got just just grand slam.
George, she's got, uh, feels like, you know, around that time he was playing like the grandfather and Angus.
You know, so like he really likes, you can tell getting his, uh, his mitts on some really good material at his age,
because he is great in it.
And the movie is strange and has a big sense of humor in its dialogue.
Strangely comedic, right?
Yeah, as was the ninth configuration.
I think bloody, um, especially for a guy, you know, as heavy as the original exercises,
he's a guy who clearly is very funny and likes the quirkiness of, of his characters.
Um, the Dorif, George, he's got seen.
Joe Bob said, George, he's got was very angry that he did not have more to do in it.
And it just seemed like this tour to force for Dorif.
You do feel that when you watch it, but Dorif is amazing.
I mean, to blow, George, he's got off the screen.
You got to be, uh, Brad Dorif is so fucking great in this movie.
His, you know, the big 10 -minute showdown between the two of them in the jail cell is, of course, a highlight.
The other highlight is arguably the best jump scare in horror history.
I won't even tell you where to look for that, but you will know it when you see it.
Yeah, there's some real good scares in this one.
So well done.
And mixed in with that is to me, some horseshit.
They, they seem where like Fabio is in heaven or whatever.
They have all these bizarre cameos in it.
You know, there are some touches in it that don't really work.
But by and large, it had an eccentricity that I liked a lot.
George C. Scott talks about how he's got a fish in his bathtub.
You know, and it's this long monologue that comes out of nowhere.
And Joe Bob's like, that should have been cut.
That should have been cut.
I disagree.
I think it gives the movie a lot of spark, you know.
Yeah, it feels real like real people talk.
The carp speech is very funny.
I have nothing against the fish.
Yeah, but it's swimming up and down in my bathroom.
Fabio was not Fabio yet in this.
So he's just in it.
The, the weirder cameo is Dominique Wilkins, the basketball player.
There's a couple basketball players, which I thought was an interesting touch.
Because I was like, no, that's how a dream is.
You're like, and for some reason, there were basketball players there.
Right.
I don't like.
So I actually thought that was kind of cool, but.
But all in all, my hog is up for this film.
And especially if you're comparing it, first of all, to make a sequel that is in any way worthy
to the predecessor of the exorcist is an impossible feat.
So the fact that they land this in any way is impeccable.
And then also if you compare this to the other.
What is it, one, two, three, other exorcist film?
I mean, my god almighty, this thing is.
Yeah.
Virion in comparison.
So it's my hog's up.
My hog is absolutely up.
I've seen it like three times now.
It is.
It's definitely more fun watching the original exorcist.
Nothing can hold a candle to that.
That's, you know, easily one of the top three horror movies of all time.
But I'm a big fan of troubled productions.
I, you know, I, I love read a book about Bonfire the Manides.
I read a couple books about Heaven's Gate.
You know, I just love movies that go off the rails in some way.
Okay.
This one does the job of it really is like taking a class on the exorcist three.
He talks a lot more than he even normally does.
Seems to have a lot of information about it.
So again, very recommended if you want to know about the troubled production of the film and what might have been.
But what is there is, I think, pretty fucking great.
And I was glad he would write him direct more.
He's dead, isn't he?
Well, that's probably why he's not doing so much.
Yeah, it's a great movie.
I urge you to check it out if you haven't seen it.
We oddly didn't spoil much of it if you haven't.
But check out the plot is the plot.
I mean, everything is in the details in this one.
So a lot of great, really creepy things happening in this picture.
I did die a couple years ago at age eight and nine.
RIP bloody.
That's that's our app.
Stay tuned for the next one.
We're going to tackle the entire Nightmare and Elm Street franchise.
That one, I don't want to speak too soon.
But I don't know, we might even skip the segments on that one.
We got a lot of pictures to get through soon.
We got a lot to get through, yeah.
Jodoros Accomedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Jodoros Accomedy on TikTok and Facebook.
And check out without a country over at the gas digital network.
And if you want a full 30 day free trial, use that promo code WAC.
I am V Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
They're less and less of course.
And I've guessed it on some friends podcast you can look up if you like.
That's it for me and Joe.
We will see you next time and we'll see.
Oh, by the way, check out the bonus episodes on Patreon.
I do a bonus solo movie quarter.
That's an hour of me going through the movies I've seen.
And it's fun to do.
I hope it's fun for you to listen to.
Tell your friends.
We are we are loving the Patreon.
There's been discussions lately of of doing other things with the Patreon and we shall see.
But thank you to those who support us.
Thank you.
We appreciate it greatly.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.