Welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the movie pod with your movie boys my name is
Joe DeRosa and my name is Patrick Walsh Joe and I were just having a fun conversation about
stranger things and I said hey we need to monetize this shit I don't talk to you for free
if I'm talking to Joe I need to be compensated as I arranged with my manager and with Joe's
manager the only time I am to speak to Joe or Joe speak to me is if I am being compensated for it
yes and we do do if we do speak off air the managers are present and it's it's a lot of would
you please tell mr. Walsh saying it in front of him and then the right has to say it for me
right to your manager and then your manager says it to you and various gurus in the room as well
that advise us a lot of me leaning over to some guy like in a hoodie that nobody can see he looks
like orco from you man and he's like whispering the advice and I'm nodding and kind of laughing too
and you take it like I'm laughing at you and of course I am with my orco friend if only it wasn't
so true that that not not with us but with people yeah in Hollywood it's so true the bigger you get
there's always a guru or something like I won't I'm not gonna name names because the guy is awesome
but he an actor we know great guy perfectly normal as down to earth as you can get out here
and he had a guru he had a shaman that like followed him place to place and then you know met with
the other people in his life to make connections and stuff and you're like and folks that man was
Andy Dick and that guru has it work since bad advice gurus filing me to charge
yeah yeah I know a couple people that are big on the spiritual advisement thing
it's so it's getting harder and harder to speak freely because that circle of people you don't
know get smaller and smaller somehow you know oh no by the day and also okay no it's what I was
talking about on on the other pocket just yesterday or two days ago I recorded the solo movie corner
and I very briefly told people that I'm getting a divorce so you know it's uh where was I going with
this it's completely derailed I don't know let me point out though that I was aware and I'm not
just silently cold uh you know like when that was it just complete lack of empathy no Joe Joe knew
that this was half but um why are we talking about this why did I see the circles getting smaller of
people oh right no so what I was saying is that I'm at a place in my life where people tell me about
this shit that two year one year ago would have sounded like madness to me and I'm just like what's
the name of your crystal dealer you know uh so where did where did you do ayahuasca
who uh reached down your throat and made you throw up your childhood off a bridge yeah you know yeah
and it's uh there's a part of me that has just flipped over into a new level of like I'll try it
what do you got you know because sometimes people go you know it's the craziest thing but you know
it worked for me uh hypnotism and I'm like maybe I'll one day find the thing so I keep trying yeah
but I mean you do get people out there that'll be like so have you heard of string release
your tension is in strings it's an energy strings and this guy pulls the strings from you
yeah you're like okay get away from me as you're drinking by the way at a bar
right please I've found my guy get away from me please yeah well and then uh rakey is another big
one here where they it's a massage where they don't touch you they're holding their their hands never
come in contact with your body instead they're moving the energy around and it's like just get the
fucking massage I can't wait by the way for that to become a me too that will happen where somebody
says they were rakey me too like they they moved the energy in an inappropriate way oh my god
moved a good deal of energy into my butt I'm gonna to not approve but I'm gonna talk
strangers negative energy I went home and my butt was filled filled with negative energy for day
I'm gonna talk stranger things for in the movie corner but I'm also gonna do it in the new
psycho we're not gonna review it for the show's pet got rid of Netflix so he can't watch it but
which means I'm also I'm going to get it back once once the normal Donald special drops if it has
an already I saw it already so I believe it is drafts but I saw it at a viewing party so maybe I don't
know but um but I'll do that in the corner today yeah drop something well I didn't say a name I didn't
say who was hosting the party I think it was the propped up corpse of normal Donald you see that
video of the rapper who got propped up at his it wasn't it was more of a wake but it was a wrap
concert they propped his dead body up on stage which I guess was probably his final request yes I've
seen that it's disturbing oh my god it's disturbing deeply deeply disturbing and then you know that's
what they do in some countries it's like it's why is it disturbing it's like in movies when somebody's
talking to a live person and then one second later it's dead and they're like I'm like what why does
it scare you that much and I mean I get it if you're stumbling upon a corpse or something but
and don't get why you're scared of a skeleton yeah that's not gonna be a threat even if it comes to life
army of darkness style you can knock over a skeleton with ease I define anyone who says I do
if I did funny when a skeleton slowly creeps through a room and scares the fat man
and what I enjoy that it's scaring him of what he can never be you know yeah sort of a double meaning
he's eating himself further and further away from the skeleton
I well speaking of what we were just talking about like appropriate and all that
this is news psycho I so I so stranger things was in the news because the new season had a warning
added to it disclaimer added to it after the horrible school shooting that happened
um so I forgot that had happened and I turned the TV on to watch the new season and I forgot
that they had announced this disclaimer and this disclaimer comes up and I I'm rolling my eyes
not out of indifference to the tragedy the tragedy is absolutely devastating and heartbreaking
I'm rolling my eyes because I'm going what the hell could stranger things have to do with this you
know what I mean it's not a violent show it's not so I'm just like why why what is this right now
and spoiler alert thing opens with a mass occurrence the facility where the kids were
and it's dead bodies of children everywhere and I'm sitting there going they didn't want to delay
the release a week was this thing already out I don't know but I know I think it was it doesn't
thing yeah but I was like Jesus Christ and I was like this might be the first time ever I've
agreed with a disclaimer on something where I'm like right okay I get it I get it why it's on this
but then I heard that they were going to put one on Obi -Wan and I was like I guess that's because
it deals with order 66 which is when all the younglings and the Jedi temple got killed so maybe that's
why I guess but like okay um but yeah this was the first time ever I was like good job on the
disclaimer guys that was smart you should have done that um oh what a time what a time yeah it's a
horrible terrible we live in a heart well it's I feel like it's always been a horrible time and it's
just keeps getting more horrible I guess but you know anyway it's just everything let's keep it light
and let's keep it tight yes by which I mean a dead ass folks
so you are I'm the proud now as a divorcee they call them man a divorcee or is that just a woman
divorcee is just a woman and I think you have to be sort of like Jack Hay to really fully get the
title fully earn the title um yes you got to be a bit saucy to be a divorcee right so what would I
be a dev oh boy they're all depressing as hell whatever I think just a divorced guy which is a vibe
I've had for many years anyway you know and you've got it too frankly I do I have on my fifth marriage
it's on the rocks kind of right but you know the one really positive thing from your total lack of
commitment that you've committed your entire life too yeah and my uh finally saying yes I will commit
only to have it blow up in my face is that we don't have kids yes you know we're not talking
of anybody else's lives and you're not talking of anyone's life no no you make your choices are
your own yeah so but you know it's just like no nobody looks at the harmful portrayal in movies and film
and TV of the divorced guy where are eight -part Hulu documentary I mean they'll mix I would maybe
I'm just noticing it in the in the month or two I've been getting divorced but it's like they
really paint divorce guys it's just the saddest sacks on earth yeah you had Baldwin for a minute
there he really botched it up though he was a good spokesperson for a minute for divorced men and
then he went on a string of slurred outbursts and then that ended up shooting of a camera woman
uh now have you seen him on twitter like he's like uh actually some actors are really committed
to safety on sets like he's been responding from the point of view as like this never happened sort
of thing really wild that is hilarious like just act act like nothing happened
Alex just pretend and it'll go away I'm gonna eat more kids
fine what what do you need Alec Dan kids I'll do it there'll be nothing left of me down there Alec
oh boy please Alec more kids oh boy slipping in and out of a cage and accent yeah yeah
you're not even supposed to be Cajun he's doing a full British accent that he's in his whole career
what I'm gonna do is have more kids that's my Cajun um you used to pretend to be Hispanic now it's
some sort of weed Creole I do well why do you sound like Kelsey Graham do you think you're from the Bronx
but do you think the breathiest men in Hollywood are Baldwin well the the the floor only opened up
the day Gandalfini died he he had it right that was more though like I eat too much cheese breathy
yeah and they would force him while he was really struggling with his weight they would force him
to eat these giant plates of pasta and every scene so he was just breathing a lot and stirring
it a lot to avoid having to keep shoveling in his mouth like the fat guy from seven so oh god
yeah like like like Baldwin breathy Harrison Ford has become quite breathy
it's very like I'm here to present the award for best actress
um I met Baldwin's daughter the other night doesn't what's gonna tell you
uh the one married to Bieber now Ireland is her name
isn't she married to Bieber died no okay I don't think so
I don't know maybe she was at one point and she seemed young she seemed like she was like 21
well where did they held the jumea were you grooming her at a comedy show no she was at a show I did
but Joe answered the question I was grooming her even have to be aware of it I was grooming her in
the traditional sense I was doing her hair oh she was the one that referred to as a rude thoughtless
little pig oh she was not by the way I wasn't trying to trivialize I wasn't trying to trivialize
we know you weren't it's a serious issue we know you weren't I didn't realize that was her
yeah she is the daughter of Alec Baldwin and Kim basinger pretty good jeans
um but she was the one referred to as quote a thoughtless little pig she is not
dating Justin Bieber Justin Bieber's wife now I need to know that to soothe my savage OCD
he is dated no he's married right
it Haley Bieber Haley all right who's that Haley Baldwin is that she's the daughter she's the daughter
of Stephen Baldwin oh that's right married into the wrong dynasty hey well she'll be fine she's got
I think Bieber's got his Bieber doesn't need to do it yeah yeah once his mega church collapses around
him I didn't even know he's a mega I'm so not about I have nothing I'm not up on any news I didn't
even know he had a mega church he's very big in the same mega church that Chris Pratt was involved
in that is that is allegedly very homophobic and like has a 12 -part discovery channel documentary
about them which is usually not a good sign well yeah there you go uh somebody did a 12 -part
documentary on discovery about my colon I think hey I'd probably better go get that checked out
you know what I'm saying bad uh I uh I that used to be stand -up comedy yeah it was better
quite frankly it was better actually that was a pretty good bet I'm gonna stick with that one
yeah stick with it there you go that's when you make your return yeah I like to do stand -up for six
months once every 35 years well I'm starving I've been on a diet and I can't do this no
bread shit anymore I'm going crazy here I need a sandwich at lunchtime or something I you know
yeah well what can I do here well you know I did no carbs for the whole time I was in Atlanta
and then I come back I get pizza one night with friends and it's like I feel like again the 20 pounds
I lost back it's brutal it's brutal it's brutal as you get older it's just maddening I think I might
just let it go become a fat fuck who cares I just wish I gained weight the right way I gain it in certain
areas and it looks so disproportionate and odd you mean it goes to your bedonka dog I get a
little bedonka dog the taint gets plump forehead it sizzles for some reason yeah earlobe like a sausage on
the grill yeah I get it I get gut neck and tits and it's like it like but nothing I don't get wider
I don't get any weight in the legs or the arm it just looks absurd it looks so bad
yeah I mean me riding this bike helps but when I'm in Atlanta I don't do that it's all just
it's so depressing to know that like okay I I did weights for three months really hardcore over
the pandemic you notice a difference but then when you stop doing them for a week you're back to
square one yeah so what's the point it's like what's the point what's the point of anything and then
you start spiraling out and asking yourself what's the point of life at all it's rough man
well scientifically you should have that bit but it was so true where he's like the only point
of the workout is to be able to do the workout right that's the whole goal like and it's like yeah
you're kind of like who cares you know like I don't know I find if you eat decently
meaning naturally right the problem with bread isn't that it's bread I don't think I think the
problem with bread is is that it's a concoction you know what I mean it's not normal and yeah if you
kind of just eat naturally you know meaning you eat stuff that you can make from scratch one way or
the other and that doesn't contain any sort of processed junk and you and you and you move around
and walk and don't drink constantly right you've got to shot it being presentable sure yeah you know
but lunch time's a tough one for I got to get back and eat and salads at lunch that's the thing
that's what I got to do yeah I I got no problem on the work schedule at work because they eat lunch
at like three o 'clock all week when they're shooting which is all the time and I can just not eat till
three that's the quickest and easiest way to lose weight right don't eat till three then you eat a big
meal maybe eat a little something at seven o 'clock and you're done but you just commit you're eating
into a small window that's helpful as well and don't eat late at night it's helpful as you get older
because it has nowhere to go it used to be like when and it's metabolism and everything else that changes
as you get older but used to be you could eat like a giant bowl of ice cream and then go to bed and
your insides would work at it and be like beating it up throughout the night now you eat ice cream
and it just sits there inside of you and just starts bonding to your fat and never goes anywhere
just sets up camp because your body is old and it's sad and it's weak and it's tired
glad we kept it light yeah well I guess that that is why you work out you know so that if you get
the you know I'm taking it even down darker roads well let's get off this let's get off this
I'm just looking at a picture as you talk on a movie website of Tom Hanks
uh as jepetto oh I saw it looks idiotic they how many they do three panocchios a year
they did one with Roberto Benini like last year this this twin peak style Elvis movie coming out
I'm real curious about this hangs in that fat suit he's not like what is that accident he's doing it
sounds crazy it's his lady killer's voice which was his Colonel Sanders voice
he's got what looks like the skins of a hundred nut sex attached to his chin yeah fat suits are
allegedly not cool anymore unless Tom Hanks does it but this thing they even and he was a shady figure
in Elvis's life the Colonel he kept him from doing great work because he just wanted
schlock that brought in big bucks and it's a great story but that role always legally has to go to
Paul Giamatti that's he's played that role in 50 movies he's messed with the careers of many of our
greatest musicians hangs is just wrong for it he looks ridiculous and every time I've seen it he's
he gets a bigger laugh now than Nicole Kibman walking it's doing her shit it's ridiculous look
and man it looks tear and then they got bads whatever's name is running around in like
fucking full eyeliner it makes no sense what is this I don't know uh yeah that movie looks bad
also do we need another god damn Elvis movie how many times they're gonna tell this fucking story
well John Carpenter of all people did an Elvis movie starring Kurt Russell as Elvis that I love
I remember and then they did the mini series in the 80s they still have yet to do a proper
synatra storytelling they did that one mini series which wasn't very good the rat pack was good
but it wasn't a story about synatra really they've never told synatra story they never told Dean
Martin story they never told Sammy Davis junior story they never told the fucking Beatles story
even though I have no interest you know like like uh there hasn't been an appropriate
doors storytelling you know they did a doors they got that's don't get on the doors well stone did
his thing and it's an enjoyable film but you know you taught you listen but it they've used the spirit
of the doors in a way that that maybe no other movie could because he was there and lived it and
were getting further away from directors that would have been able to have that experience but you
know it's just like there's there's so many I mean Chuck Barry for Christ sakes like it's yeah
well probably because they don't want to have to deal with everybody going but did you know that he
ended his career videotaping women peeing in the bathroom in his restaurant
the mighty have fallen yes that's a bit we just said then to the career stuff under the rug
if you want to sit under a glass table and pay a woman to shit on it that's your thing
yeah while drilling the holes is their thing and he shouldn't have been doing that
who was that Danny K that did that oh Chuck Barry wasn't it well Chuck Barry was the under the table
under the table yeah that he hurt nobody no that's true that's true I think it was Danny K anyway Danny K
let's not kink shame no I always say the only kink shaming I do is when I'm trying to reel in my
garden hose I say shame on you kinks or if I'm scolding the 60s British invasion banned the kinks
for having too many hits I might hey guys I might kink kinks shame them I mean hits are there I
thought there's only two kinks have so many hits well they I don't know it's lola's huge but so
you just know the the 70s I mean the kinks had you really got me and all of a night yeah I really
got man out at all that punk rock early stuff yeah you really got me and lola that's what about every
song in every Wes Anderson movie that's all kinks songs there's a bunch of them I mean they're
they're those those hits though they had hits I know I'm just you know let's go to the movie corner
because I want to talk about stranger things that's not the kinks no that's a stranger thing song
that I remember are I'm I doing Halloween you're doing Halloween okay whoa yeah no stranger things
as bro do do do do do do do you know yeah synth synth the synths I'm like what's the name of the
synth instrument oh it's good called synth have they decided to advance the plot at all this season
they did and they yeah uh this season's been it is good I haven't seen the last episode but
I've seen enough that I feel like I can give a take on the season um there's a new supernatural villain
who's 20 ,000 times more interesting than the monsters from previous seasons because he actually talks
and has a personality and is really sinister and evil he's like this dark wizard from from the upside
down so that's a welcome change definitely some more mature themes in the show like I said it's it's
got some pretty violent moments but then also too there's some drug use and and stuff like that in
there uh you know um and the kids are the kids are you know they're they're still playing too young for how
old they are they're playing freshman and college in this in high school in this season you know when
they should be like juniors by now but like still whatever um but story wise you know every year I think
I'm done with stranger things and then I go add let me check out the first episode and immediately
I'm like all right this season is way better than last season as far as giving a shit about the
characters and where they're at it's way better than last season as far as the story is concerned
it's way better than last season as far as horror is concerned uh there's a lot of very cool
nods this this season takes place in 87 and there are a lot of nods to
part of that period you know Hellraiser which came out that year um uh Nightmare on Almond Street which
was you know kind of rolling along at that point um Robert England has a great little part in it um
it's it's a it's a it's a really solid season I like it you know um and I'm growing to like the
secondary characters more than the original four like I really like I can't remember anybody's name but
I really like the kid who used to go out with Mike's sister in the first season and started out as a
prick and now is really good friends with them he's become my favorite character uh there's some new
characters in this that are like metalheads that are great that really nail like what metalheads of
that time period were like um you know what known as awesome as usual harbor is awesome as usual
Brett Gellman his part has been expanded and he's very entertaining in it very funny
um and and uh Millie Bobby Brown steals the show she's tremendous in it you know she's tremendous
I know I've made fun of her in the past and said she's kind of annoying but she's this is her show
she's fantastic Paul risers back which I was happy to see um huge spoiler Modine is back
which we all thought he was kind of dead it was just just been an enjoyable season they do a good job
and what saddens me and wall she'll forgive me can I just do two in a row because these connection
correctly sure what saddens me is I'm watching this and I'm saying why is Obi -Wan Kenobi not this good
Obi -Wan Kenobi is part of the Star Wars franchise the greatest fantasy franchise of all time
next to Lord of the Rings and some would say it supersedes Lord of the Rings
or we can in the airbud films as well airbud yeah well there's a third but I'm going top two here
and look man Obi -Wan has its moments but it just looks like a TV show it feels like a TV show
once again Disney shoe horning in the woke shit like so obvious there's this again spoilers the whole
plot line in the first two episodes is about how Obi -Wan is pulled out of his rec loose whatever
where he secretly is watching over Luke Skywalker to go on a mission to save a kidnapped young princess
Leia who's like five or no she's ten and she's like this sassy little ten -year -old it is painfully
fucking annoying there's a line where Jimmy smits who plays bail organic whose lay his dad
pressures Obi -Wan to leave his mission of watching over Luke to help Leia and he goes she is just as
important as the boy and it's like guys Jesus fucking Christ like it's just so forced
uh Moses ingram who plays one of the inquisitors I feel really bad for her um because she's getting a ton
of really racist stuff thrown at her which sucks and obviously is disgusting and gross
and it makes it hard to talk about her character because I do think she's miscast in the role I
didn't really enjoy her performance but again I think that was just miscasting I just don't think
she was right for the role uh and now that's all over shadowed by the the disgusting shit that racist
people are saying so I won't even get into it but but at the same time it's not even a big deal that
I think she's miscast in the role because I thought he had Christians who was miscast in the role too
and here I am 20 years later excited to see him back I've gotten over it and licked my wounds
maybe 20 years from now I'll be excited to see Moses ingram back in this role I don't know
and well had Christians someone's fantastic and shattered glass he was he was so uh you know
look the one thing that counts to me more than anything else is uh I've watched interviews with
with um uh you and Moses and Hayden all three of them seem to be incredibly excited to be doing this
and even like Moses ingram said she wasn't like very familiar with Star Wars until this but she
seems to really love it now and Hayden Christians and you and McGregor obviously have a long history
here but they're all excited which that is important to me like I think that's really important with
something like this um they seem to be teasing that Liam Neeson is coming back um cool uh I hope
that happens my biggest gripe with the show is the young princess laya thing I just think it's
corny I think it's stupid I think nobody wanted to see and experience a 10 year old princess laya
in this for the same reasons nobody wanted to experience a 10 year old Anakin Skywalker none of us
like that either uh and none of us wanted to see a 10 year old Han Solo which is why they cut that
character from Revenge of the Sith so I'm confused as to why they chose to do that it just feels
forcibly like kind of woki to me like we need to stress how important she is we know how important she
is you don't need to condescend us but whatever um the reviews of this thing are through the roof
um which who knows anymore with Disney it's such a goddamn machine uh those could be real those could
be pale who fucking knows at this point but at the end of the biggest distance I've ever felt in my
life from from reviews you know like I used to kind of align usually and now I very very often don't
yeah it sucks um and that's the thing like you know I was saying earlier about her getting the racist
messages it's like there's this small percentage of every group of major fans now including Bernie
Bros that do horribly disgusting um things to to to to to convey why they don't like
the choices that that these producers and writers and creators are making and it really bothers me
because now we're unable in a lot of cases to just talk about from a quality standpoint it's very like
even as I said the princess lay a thing I feel like there are people out there that are gonna say you're
that's just sexist and it's like no I don't mean it in a sexist way I mean that I don't want to see a
sassy kid in Star Wars I don't enjoy it I don't give a fuck what character it's supposed to be
I don't want to see it and I it's just you know it's it bums me out that that's what this has all become
you know like I was reading I was reading the response articles to what was happening to to Moses
Ingram and it was just making me sick to my stomach man it was really gross and and this is the like
she even said she's like there's nothing anybody can do about this like this is what it is I just
want to I'm here to say thank you to the people that showed me love you know like what a horrible all right
sorry we say we're gonna give it anyway those are two therefore yeah I wish Obi -Wan was as good as
stranger things but it's not and hopefully gets better surprise here you say that but I know you're
very hot and cold with Star Wars TV outings I saw three movies on a plane each of them designed in
the lab to be watched on a plane I saw a draft day starring Kevin Costner which is just a movie that
I missed like 10 years ago Jesus yeah recently voted like the most rewatch movie on TNT like it's a
big dad movie and guys like it I think a lot of fantasy football dudes like it that's never really been
my scene but it was one of the last movies of Ivan rightman of course a legendary director of ghost
busters and twins and many other things and it was a very solid competently made movie about a topic I
could not have cared less about which was the football draft there was almost I would say 1 % of the
action was on the football field the rest was like people organizing trades I'm very surprised it even
got made but it's always great to see Costner Costner in a sports world is always fun pretty stacked
supporting cast you got who I mean who who who is the gentleman who passed away of cancer
who passed away of cancer yes I don't know
why can I think of the gentleman's name the blind Panther oh Chadwick Boseman Chadwick Boseman
yes Jesus Christ you know something I just forgot I forgot that he died well that I just shocked
that was like as I said it I was kind of like because in the movie he's so young and it was horrible
not that long ago actually a buddy of mine always talked about how he lived across the hall from
this actor Chadwick Boseman and that's how I think of him like he he lived across the hall and he was
like I always hear him like he's really intense and works on his scenes real loud and everything
it's crazy I didn't ever that did that wonderful he becomes famous
but yeah and and Chadwick Boseman is in a very small part in it I assume it's one of his first
movies but it's good I've never even knows how to deliver kind of an old -fashioned it is a
dad movie good one to watch with your dad on a Sunday or something like that and then I'll do my
second to catch up to Joe I watched oh yeah we discussed Rex Reed's review of it the lost city
I do want to point out that you said we a text perfectly fine piece of entertainment before you
saw it mm -hmm I love up to that because because I was like it's a comedy just like I wouldn't have
ordinarily seen the Jumanji pictures but I root for comedy and I found laughs to be had especially
in the first Jumanji Jack Black is amazing in the first Jumanji the lost city is a rung below Jumanji
but it's a rung above most comedies Sandra Bullock I call her Sandy she's always very charming she's
always delightful and especially in a role like this she makes it look effortless probably because she's
not having to try that hard she's been playing this kind of character now for 30 years
um and I know I don't ever like her in a drama so you know she she's great at what she does she's
great at being the light funny romantic interest and it's kind of cool that she's like
significantly older than Channing Tatum or at least I think she is just because she's been around
much longer in my life um because that's how it should be it should go both ways young hunks young
babes if some young babes got to make out with Clint Eastwood and his 92 year old ass then it should go
both ways um but no uh Sandra Bullock I don't know she's uh it's like she's been frozen in amber she
she's just a delight and since she's not in much anymore at least not the last thing I started
was bird box it's just fun to see her do what she does best and Channing Tatum is good at playing an
idiot which is what he's doing here Brad Pitt has a fun little cameo there's always these little flashes
like it's gonna start being funnier and better than it is but it never quite goes the distance
for me however not a terrible movie Rex Reed was really being unnecessarily harsh I would say
by the way side note side note lightning fast news psycho did you know that Margot Robbie and Jay
Roach have teamed up for an oceans 11 prequel I saw so you're gonna have none of the same characters
and it's in a different location and also nothing nothing nothing nothing it's just a prequel that's
somehow it's supposed to relate to the other movies well at the end I bet like she'll have a baby
and it'll be Danny Ocean or something like that there's some like very tangential connection
who cares does anybody care enough about oceans 11 that we need a prequel
and all right what's your third my third is yet another airplane feature ambience and I say it
that way because the LA is capitalized an ambulance and this is the latest from Mr. Michael Bay
the man who briefly the criteria in collection was releasing Michael Bay films and then
they increasingly got more and more stupid when he got into the Transformers realm in my opinion and
I think a lot of people spend they were always stupid but I think you know there's been a
re -appreciation of Bay especially the Rock bad boys bad boys two you know the man made some great action
pictures for sure I didn't know Bay did the rock you must have told me that before and I just didn't
remember the rock is early on he had something to prove I think Armageddon is awesome it's Corny's
tell but you know the guy knows how to make a picture but they have a criterion under his belt
that's impressive he does the rock and Armageddon actually aren't wait a minute Armageddon is in the
criterion collab with all due respect now come on and it's got the video for I don't want to miss
thing why would that be in the criterion collection I don't actually never made it to Blu -ray
it only was on DVD but yeah it was I think it was probably when they were trying to stay afloat
because they started doing action movies around the same time okay um and you know Michael Bay earned
it because he is the greatest of his of that kind of like him and John Wu and those kind of people
are the best at theirs genre you know I didn't see his latest with Ryan Reynolds it just looked too
stupid maybe underground 600 ground or whatever but I used to keep up with them uh this is fun you got
Jake Gyllenhaal and kind of a villainous role you got yeah yeah I built Matin the second
who is great he's the guy from us and he was in all kinds of other shit candy man etc you got Garrett
Dilla Hunt a lot of people you know a lot of people given in good performances and Michael Bay is
good with the jokes you know he keeps them coming and they're usually pretty good except in this one
two of the characters know about they argue about bad boys and the rock two characters in a Michael Bay
movie discussing two Michael Bay movies that almost made me shut it down the rest of the movie is a
pretty fun action movie about half of it is shot on a drone but it all looks very cool
it's worth your time that's that argument I promise you was one of two things it's either the two
characters saying wouldn't it be funny if we were arguing about your movies and Michael Bay went
oh okay sure or it's Michael Bay trying to be Banksy where he's like I'm gonna be so self -referential
you know like tell me it was his idea yeah well that's like in in the fan or not the fan the
fanatic whatever that Travolta Stalker movie was that Fred Durst directed where he's the main
character is playing Limp Biscuit for his kid right you like this is awesome this is what your father
used to listen yeah Chris at least Bayes earned it they're out on a tour right now Limp Biscuit called
the We Still Suck tour yeah and he's like older now and doing a mellower delivery on the vocals and
it's like buddy the music yeah the music sucks either way but all it had going for it was you screaming
you know what I mean like now that's gone all right break your fucking face tonight
my last is oh yeah nor Mcdonald yeah nothing special I watch this the other night
with some dear friends and you know I was a little nervous going in because I was like man it's
just him and his computer like how funny could this be I gotta tell you man I watched it with a room
full of people thing killed yeah I was laughing my balls off like some of it I was like this is
start the funniest shit I've ever seen him do and then I realized like oh wait a minute I listen
to his audio book and laugh my balls off there was no audience there for that right um just some great
jokes um is he talking about death I'm not really like there's it's not a morbid special you know
okay I gotta be honest I we were we had a few beforehand so I don't remember
joke after joke but but also with all the celebrities and the credits do they all just like talk about
them and they're like there's like a there's like a 35 -minute roundtable discussion afterwards
oh okay with Molly Shannon David Spade Chappelle Letterman and Sandler
gosh and they tell funny stories and you know blah blah blah so um but yeah the uh the one uh
he talks he talks he opens with a lot of stuff about casinos and gambling
and uh one the one one joke then really maybe laugh what's he said he he thought he breaks down
roulette and he's doing that normal Donald thing where he's like you know roulette is a game where you
can bet on either black and he's like way over explaining it so anyways I uh what I would do is I'd
go to the table and I'd put chips on black and then the dealer would go and the winner is red and I'd
go son of a bitch I was gonna choose that one is it funny shot one unbroken take one unbroken take
and he's got two cameras like two angles okay clearly did it like because it was the pandemic and he
would just like I got to get this down I don't think he did it as like a rehearsal right I think he
was like which is also why it's great that he's having fun in it like he's being fun and silly like
he's not you don't watch it and go oh this is a sad sick man or anything like that he doesn't it
looks sick either he looks pretty good like you know because there was a while where he was bloated
and I think he was probably on steroids or something yeah some sort of treatment yeah yeah and um
he done he just looks you know he looks older but he you know it's it was it was really cool to see like
and it was really enjoyable and it was a nice nice thing to get from him in the end so yeah
I'm very excited to watch it but not to immediately go back on my Netflix promise
actually usually when I stay at these Airbnb's out in Atlanta they have Netflix and I just
will I'll watch it on their account yeah and feel better in my soul yeah so anyway I thought it was
much better than Hitler's dog yeah um I thought it was not as good as me doing stand up okay
was right sort of in the middle there anyway I'm very pumped to watch uh and
I was very pumped to watch our latest which just a quick mention that Amazon the day of
the launch of the new kids in the hall show I'm up at midnight trying to watch this thing
all excited they got it nowhere to be found now to be fair and Netflix did the same thing with the
pen tavern it didn't show up till like eight hours late but shouldn't the point of these fucking services
be servicing the fans in a way that they can't get elsewhere if you're saying it's going to drop at
midnight drop the fucking thing at midnight but not only that I'm watching this we watch this we watch
this admit you text this we watched at midnight yes this one showed up on Amazon I'm talking
I went off and talked about the pen tavern as well oh that's I'm sorry I got confused I
sure what you mean yes they don't take care of their problems you couldn't find an advertisement
I to I text Joe I text my buddy Tim who's a big fan I text several friends oh my god the new kids
in the halls up not a single one of them had any clue so they all put put it on every one of them said
except Joe who I guess is a little more computer savvy did the same thing I did where they started
watching season one because it was almost impossible to find the new season of the show on Amazon
as it premiered well let me let me jump in with something yes the problem with the midnight premiere is
this it if then if you're on the west coast you get it at nine p .m. can't they just set an algorithm
I don't think so how could you do that how could you tell who was larger does it no shutter does it
I guess at the same time yeah yeah I don't think you can I think you can do it by country or
something like regions but but you know like like Obi -Wan I ended up getting at midnight here yeah and
they considered it early because that meant the west coast got it at nine p .m. gosh okay so I do it's too
different but you know it's totally yes yeah the other one of the midnight drop and the other is
where the ads and then a week later there was a documentary about them the one that Joe saw at the
film festival comedy punks that I also had to search for the old fashioned way by typing it in
and bringing it up and then I see the poor kids in the hall retweeting every compliment on Twitter
and they're like we find out this weekend this was the second weekend it was on Amazon we find out
this weekend if we're getting picked up for another season please watch this weekend it's like that's how
quick we're deciding on this unanimously beloved return from these comedy legends that
probably doesn't cost shit that's how we're treating these guys it made me sick yeah because they
probably won't get renewed it's still going to be a niche audience and that's how look how they
treated it if they wanted it to be a big hit they'd promote it on Amazon well look it's it's partially
Amazon's fault and it's partially our fault as a as the public because don't include me in the public
I'm including you uh no but it is because we want our stuff when we want it we all abandoned cable
for for these streaming services which fucked up and by the way before that we abandoned watching
things in real time for the DVR and we abandoned the DVR for the TVO and the you know what I mean
they haven't been able to accurately rate at we abandoned television as a whole for the internet
it's like they haven't been able to accurately rate anything in so long which is why there's this
whole weird shadiness with Netflix and how they don't release their numbers and everything so I can only
partially blame the corporate giant for doing what the corporate giant does when we handed the reins
over to them we allowed them to do it like so here we are you know it's like it's like when everybody
complained about what Spotify was doing to comedians and not paying them properly now do I think
that sucks and is gross absolutely but do I also think we myself included are it fought for demanding
convenience at all costs and using something like Spotify yes that's part of it when our hands aren't
clean either so it's unfortunate and unfortunately as much as it can benefit something like the kids in
the hall which at this point is quite niche you know yeah it also can really hurt it so you can turn
to your streaming services and say well thank god because shutter for instance has allowed a world in
which creep show comes back as shitty as it is it wouldn't have happened without shutter on the other
hand you know don't expect a lot of special treatment because they're they're juggling 2 ,000 other
creep shows yeah so you know that's the problem and it sucks you know that said this this was this was
this was kids in the hall was focused very much on the fans which was great I would go as far as to say
there was some real inside baseball here with some of the jokes some of this if you didn't know the
history of the show and you didn't know brain candy and ever that you wouldn't have understood some of it
but I mean they never care they kick they kick it off with an extended brain candy riff it's like they
they've always just not been welcoming to their to outsiders and that's why people love them so much
which I loved I thought was great you know but that said it's like let's say this did get rebooted
on HBO which is just a streaming service now right yeah basically but let's say it got rebooted on
proper TV would they have let them do that stuff would they have let them hang down within the first
three minutes of the fucking thing you know would they have let them get away with what they got away with
who knows but very critical of Amazon too they and they said like on the show many times they were
like they basically leaves us with puns like what they didn't want them to do basically leaves them
with puns so I don't know if that's true how how little freedom they had but it doesn't seem like
they got along great and maybe that led to the lack of promotion but they're always prickly guys for
sure I watched I watched some I watched some in an interview with them from the set
funny it was the day they were shooting that weird rock DJ thing with Dave Foley like in the
apocalypse yeah weirdly that's getting a lot of traction it was very haunting I didn't understand it
but so they were all dressed normal and Dave Foley was in that ridiculous wig the whole time like
which looked really funny but they when they were talking they said that among within the group
they were getting along better than ever before and they were all kind of split on this whole like
censorship thing like they all sort of immediately seemed to not really care and say like you know
it feels fun to be like dangerous again like we have an edge again because people
because of PC culture basically was what to take away from me was but then as the conversation went
along Bruce McCullough said I'm happy to be told what's not appropriate and how I need to evolve or whatever
and Dave Foley sort of agreed with that McKinney was very quiet and Scott Thompson clearly did not
agree with that because the interviewer went back to Scott Thompson and said I'd expect to hear way
more out of you right now about this subject matter and Scott Thompson kept going I'm just here to look
pretty and it was like it seemed to me like he had been told like do not say anything right you know
or don't make a big deal out of blah blah blah or whatever but um but you know it's it's interesting
because they are still I mean look even with playing by uh uh stricter rules right with the content
yeah they're still really fucking edgy like I mean it's still like
for it didn't still yeah it didn't feel like they were playing by stricter rules to me
maybe there was a few things they couldn't do but yeah it was really funny really edgy there was always
sketches that didn't click for me just like there were always sketches back in the old episodes that
didn't work for me I think it's part of their charm there were a few real duds I would say that also
felt like in most cases the longer and more expensive pieces which I would also say about the original
show um but the ones that hit really hit and you don't mind the misses because it's so good to have
them back it's also like comedy's a young man's game and there's very few comedians who remain funny
and edgy and successful throughout their career so when you first see them of course it's jarring
that they don't look baby face anymore they look like man who have lived hard lives but they
make it work for them and it's just very very funny throughout to me it didn't miss a beat from
the original show I agree did you find it weird at first that it was all uh you know on tape no live
audience no because eventually if memory served the show started doing that too but I could be wrong
no they only did it had like they had sketches that had no audience but they always kept the life sketches
yeah um it seemed like a natural progression yeah the only thing that felt shoehorned in and I'm
sure amazon asked him to do was the celebrities that chimed in with one quick show but the bits were
all very quick I thought Samantha bees was not good I thought a few of them were kind of funny but
on the whole I didn't need them you know it was weird though because I started to wonder did net flip
did amazon make them do this because some of the people were not you know like huge gets in that
and then I noticed a pattern I was like every person in this is part of a modern day like sketch
conglomerate you know it was all s and l it was uh more and more than michael's producer their
shirts they probably just set up a quick camera yeah it was um there was uh i think key right
it was in there i think from key and peel right i think there's another sketch i can't
remember who else was in there it was it was s and l um i don't know it doesn't so i wondered if
that's a no hair i see tv yeah so i wondered mark camel from star wars
that was the one where my theory fell apart i don't understand but i was like i wonder if this was
just like their way of giving nods to like the fan you know the sketch comedy family or you know
or something but it didn't make any sense but um but uh yeah it was uh i yeah
brief and harmless overall i really like the show quite a bit there's some real banger sketches in
this um some of them are slight variations of things i saw them do on the tour of duty uh they brought
some back even from when i saw um uh at the comedy the tenacious d comedy festival out here i saw them
do a bunch of sketches and it was on there some of them yeah but uh for the most part it was mostly new
right mostly i well i read some interview and i don't i don't remember exactly what they said but i
was a mix and some of them that they just made more cinematic than theatrical but it's still very
much worked they're all still super funny i think kevin mcdonald walks away the mvp his funny sketch
to me is the black and white one in the last episode and i also love when they're all just playing
themselves and clearly venting their own personal frustration in that last sketch of the whole season
yes where they're just like giving each other very subtle shit yes made me laugh really hard
and i just hope we get more you know like it couldn't have been that expensive compared to
the fucking wheel of time or the lord of the rings or whatever else amazon's doing
yeah to me to me it seems like amazon is spending five hundred million dollars on every show and nobody
i know watch anything on amazon yeah now i hope these guys get another shot um i was going to
mention a highlight sketch and now i blanked on the one i mean the baby drop was great with the with
the delivery doctor i thought was awesome uh i'm glad mccullod did a song in one of the episodes
that made me very happy um you know mccinny definitely did the weirdest stuff this season
Thompson's buddy sketch was great with the last koolori hole being retired uh
uh although i did wish i kind of wished he had just did a buddy monologue but again i guess with no
audience that's kind of weird but um but i really did enjoy the that we got to see that character again
well and i saw him do a night of monologues two minutes from my house and it was so great and he had all
updated monologues new subjects so it is weird to me that none of them made the cut because you think
they would have filmed one at least well he did them when they toured live i just feel like there's
something weird about a monologue with no audience true but um but yeah i i i i agree that mccdonald
probably gave me my hardest laughs uh followed by Thompson there's a couple great sketches oh that's
the sketch Thompson anytime he plays the business man with the mustache it just kills me uh yeah
the thing where he appropriates the clown shoes and he's like uh -huh talking to the boss how he's
getting fired and he goes couldn't i just issue one of them apologies and uh day full he goes it's not
the 90s yeah yeah they were they were as sharp as ever and you know i'm an admirer of the comedian
Julie Klausner and i know that she played a big part in writing and i've never met her but just
lover work proud to see happy to see um it's it was a really special very funny comedy return i read so
many people on twitter talking about how they got emotional when they heard the song oh yeah kind of
seeing them being old and going through the motions and everything might have gotten them but
it's all just like expertly performed you don't lose this shit like and i may probably a lot of
it's that they kept touring but uh yeah to me this is about as good as a return can be especially in
a world where like arrests of development came back and flop so hard and so many so many comedy shows
in particular when they try to come back it doesn't work so this was a big thrill for me uh
yeah when when Paul Belini turns to Cameron goes you ask for it and the song starts i was
year to year smile i was so happy yeah it really just it just got me man it really just got me it was awesome
um i hope we get another season my hog is way up for kids in the hall my hog is way up too my hog is
also way up for comedy punks which jodas dust but is like a great perfect four -hour documentary about
them check it out on amazon i also recommend Paul Myers book about the kids in the hall that came out
year to ago covers a lot of the same ground as the documentary but more in depth we will be back with
our review of what is it called the saddening no that's next time we're doing the top five uh yes
we're doing special episode yeah we're gonna do our we'll be back with our top five comedy episodes
of all time so pat and i'll each pick five episodes of comedy tv shows that make up our what we think
are the five funniest things that we ever saw on television so we'll be back with that uh sadden
is probably coming later in the month yeah jodaro's uh yeah the hard zombie movie that neither of us
want to tackle given our current state of mind uh uh jodaro's a comedy in instagram and twitter
folks i'm coming i got dates popping up all over starting in july with san francisco i'll also be coming
out to l a in july well so maybe i'll see you all right we're back to town that week um i might
have a show in l a i don't know yet uh uh fairfield canedicate in july at lannick city in august
sandiego in september um north carolina in october lost vegas in october so lots of dates folks go to
them and then also i'll be uh you know joey roses as always joey roses and yc dot com for our info and
info uh about days and hours and all that come see us have a drink and a sandwich thank you
the patrick wash twitter and instagram this pat show coming to be et plus season two's coming in
august i think something like that i would definitely watch it there repair mount plus unedited
it's a lot of the appeal of the show it's really funny because it's unedited um that's what i got
love y 'all see you next time and we'll see you in hell