I'll see you in hell.
When the sound of your scream is big comes up.
Hang on my dreams.
You know I'll say hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, back with the intro, the same old intro, but new
energy after I didn't give it the energy it needed last time. This is the picture show,
the show about pictures, folks. We review. We skewer and we commentate and discuss. I'm Joe
Derosa and I'm Patrick Walsh and today we're stuffing your face with Thanksgiving, the new Eli
Roth slasher picture. It really feels like a classic slasher in a great way. Kind of crazy that we've
had holiday themed horror movies, but very few Thanksgiving. Almost every other one has been covered.
Have you ever seen one, Joe? I know there's one from the 80s Thanksgiving horror, but I never saw it.
No, in fact, when they did Grindhouse and this was one of the fake trailers, I remember thinking,
oh, well, yeah, they never did a Thanksgiving. That's a good idea.
But no, this is this is the only one I've ever seen.
Yeah, everything it is showing here on this list, pilgrim, boogie man, flesh and blood, blood for
recomb, sweet home, black Friday, Christie. I haven't seen or even heard of these movies. Blood
rage I have. That's a Thanksgiving horror that they did on Joe Bob, but it's also not a good movie by any
stretch, the imagination. So this is the first. Is it good? Does it live up to the promise of that classic
trailer? We will let you know. Yeah, I think it's well, it'll be a good talk. Now, Joe, you talked
about your kiss show. Have I discussed going to the new sphere in Las Vegas? No, tell me about it.
Very cool. I mean, much as you were not a huge fan of kiss, I am not a huge fan of you too.
What's interesting is that people 10 years younger than us and younger despise you too.
They couldn't fathom anyone listening to you too. And I think it's because of that big iPod trick
where they put their album on everybody's iPod and everyone made fun of them for like 12 years.
Still, it seems weird to me that people that got that upset about being given a free album, but
I loved you too when I was a kid. I used to go to bed to the Joshua tree. I liked
Octoong baby a lot. And then like most people, I kind of trailed off after that. But they were the ones
who were playing. Fish is playing there now. I hate fish a lot more than I hate you too. So
I went. They played Octoong baby and it's entirety with a lot of big hits sprinkled in. Bono can
no longer sing a lot of those songs as well as he's drops them all quite a bit, octave -wise. And
it's not great. He can hit all the notes on the recent U2 songs from the last 20 years, but you don't
want to hear any of those songs. So it's a little annoying. Sometimes people just age out of their
voices. I don't know if you've seen clips of like Enrique trying to sing on his latest tour or
Shania Twain trying to sing on her latest tour or Bon Jovi trying to sing, but these guys are going
out there and still charging the same old stadium ticket prices and they can't sing anymore. And people
are getting pissed. Bono's not that bad. He has always had a great voice. He can hang in there.
The real attraction is the sphere. So if you're in Vegas, no matter who's playing, you're going to
want to go experience it. I got pretty good tickets at a great rate from the comedian Will Saso,
who's an old acquaintance of mine, a great guy. There's no bad seats. It's a three -level place,
but think of it as like the world's largest iMacs. You're surrounded on all sides. It's like
your inside Epcot center and the entire interior of this giant ball is screen. So sometimes you're
just watching, you know how if you go to like a concert at the Hollywood Bowl or at a stadium,
there's two big screens on each side and they're showing the band play. This at whenever they're doing
a band thing, there'll be four different views. So you're close on each member of the band playing.
All the, it's a very small theater. So you're always pretty close to the band as is. There's just
always somewhere to be looking. And then the main appeal is that they put up crazy light designs,
crazy like, you know, not not like the old mx thing where you're on a roller coaster and kind of
following along stuff like that. But just beautiful scenery. There's a play two songs and it's like
you fully believe that you're standing outside in broad daylight on the Vegas strip even though
you're inside a ball at night. It's really, really cool. I really want to see the movie Darren
Erinowski made to kind of showcase the format. But it's by the same guys that did Madison Square
Garden. They're already making huge bank off it. I would go, I would go. If you can get tickets below
like a couple hundred bucks for it, it's a once in a lifetime thing and it's really, really cool.
It's probably the coolest thing to do in Vegas right now. Although I'm not going back for a long time
because now they're doing formula one racing on the strip and the entire place is falling to shit in
my opinion. But I don't get to go to Vegas as much as I do anyway. Everywhere is falling to shit.
It's all over everywhere. Nothing is good anymore. I know. Me and my buddy Ian went to the sphere and
we were like, let's just walk down there because one of the joys of life is walking the strip and seeing
all these freaks and being able to enjoy a beer while you walk down the sidewalk. It's all great.
But the entire strip now is big, clumsy, awkward, metal, bleachers set up
for formula one racing. So the people who are there for vacation can't get anywhere on the
Las Vegas strip, one of the biggest tourist attractions on earth. But is that permanent or is that
just, you know, they're doing that for this month or whatever? According to the residents,
like they're pretending it's not permanent, but the scaffolding has been up now for months and
months. So it's okay. Yeah. Well, even down, even in the old school, old, I guess, whatever it's called.
What is it? Fremont Street? Yeah, downtown or old town? Yeah, it's like, you know, I like it down
there. There's, it's fun. But like, you know, you walk down that Fremont Street now and it's like,
first of all, the music, they start the music at like 10 a .m., but it's not Fremont Street. It's like,
it's like shitty, like EDM remixes of songs that sucked the first time around. And it's like,
it's like, guys, this is like club shit. Why this is not free, Fremont Street should be 80s, throwback,
fun. And it always was. Yeah. Classic Rob down there. It always was classic rock. It always was,
you give love a bad name and all that at night. And then by day, they understood that the whole client
tell of downtown Vegas is people that like the older quieter, more classy style of Vegas. Now,
granted, it's a shit show down there. But people just, they don't come for club life to old town
Vegas. There's 10 giant clubs on the strip. That's where you go. Yeah. You're absolutely right,
Joe. They do so many things completely wrong there in Vegas. And it's getting worse by the time.
It's got every, you know, this is the hackiest thing to ever say in all of all time. What I'm
about to say, but everything has just become so homogenized. It's very upsetting. It's very upsetting.
It's all just being universalized like like, and you know, everything has to be variations of
the same. Yeah. It's a shame, man. It's like, no, that like the old Vegas is supposed to be the
dive bar. It's supposed to be where the old folks go. And you hang out and the characters and all
that stuff, a little weird. And it's just hot, man. It's a, it's a, it's a bummer. It's kind of a bummer.
But, you know, it's happening in New York. It's, oh, God. All right. I'm depressed now.
No need to be depressed. Things will come back. No, of course, there's ever a reason to be depressed.
I realized this week that how crucial working is to my mental health. I woke up this morning
and I was like, I don't think I had a single negative thought all week because I was working hard.
And a man needs to work. A man needs to work. A man is his job. It's true. It's like there's some
about being without for a while that makes you realize like, yeah, I know everybody kind of
hates their job and complains and it's a grind and whatever, but try sitting without one for a while.
It's, uh, you'll appreciate it. It's, I'm trying to be better about gratitude, you know,
which is classic LA bullshit, but just to be better about saying I get to go to work today
on a television show, which was always my dream as opposed to I have to go to work today.
And maybe I only got seven hours of sleep or something like I always find something to complain about.
And I think that's what was obviously keeping me unhappy. So, anyway, yeah. And you're in this house
with that beautiful piece of art behind you. What is not to, you like that one? Check this one out.
A wall size giant spoon and fork. That is the subplot of an entire episode of everybody loves Raymond.
The giant spoon and fork? Yeah. Yeah. At the parents house. I never saw that one. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, that's
a good one. Um, yeah. No, I hear you. The gratitude thing is tough. Um, you got to do it. You got
to do it. Otherwise you're, you're gonna fucking put a news around your neck. You have to. I mean,
it's just. Yeah. It's one of those things, man. It's one of those things. It's like drinking water.
You might not want to do it. You just have to do it. And you will feel better. If you do it,
just do it, you know, yeah. Same as exercise and, you know, cutting off drinking and all the other
things you don't want to do. They all have their perks. There's a reason to do it. Yeah. I'm cutting off
drinking. I don't know if you can see the cut on my head here. That's that's from when I walked into
a door the other night and split my head open. So. Oh, wow. Was it bleeding? Oh, yeah. Oh,
yeah. Uh, I mean, it was a like a closed door. No, the door was open. And I, I just gauged it wrong
and I hit the door frame with my head. Yeah. Uh, you know, was it because I was too drunk?
Was it because I'm clumsy? Was it a little bit of both? Who knows, Pat? I'm not gonna ask those
questions. Yeah. I'm not drinking while I'm down here because that would just be drinking alone
for the most part. I work so much that I would just I don't know. I'm trying to strongly trying to
avoid coming home and drinking. So I have nothing in the house. And that's been great. Um, my, my house
that I'm renting is like a smart house or something. So what's most annoying about this place? First off,
the first night, uh, the smoke alarm in each room went off about an hour apart, like that beep. Oh,
it sucks. So I'm up on a, you know, a chair at three in the morning, trying to unscrew and get the
battery out and everything. Then every morning, whenever there's a slight breeze, and of course it's
gusty winter down here in Atlanta, house wide. And I have to call them today and figure out how to
hopefully I can shut this the fuck off. House wide. Anytime there's a rustle outside, it goes
the whole house does this. Motion detected at the front door. Motion detected at the front door.
So that's annoying when I'm sitting here at 10 a .m. But at 4 a .m., I'm like, you know, fumbling for a
gun as I wake up, you know, like I'm gonna die. It's the worst way to wake up. So, uh, I got to figure
out some of those works in this house. That's the problem with Airbnb. A, it's that people want you
to do all their chores now. Take the trash out, flip the linens and all that. No, that's not why I'm
here. You can't charge the same as a hotel and make me do everything for you. Um, yeah. And then the other
thing that I dislike is just that you, you're not really comfortable because I always feel like there's
cameras in there and Airbnb always. I don't like the idea of an Airbnb. I've never been for it.
I've never done it. I don't want to. I'm staying for three months in a hotel down here. I had no
choice, but sure. Yeah. That's that is true. You're in a different situation. But uh, I just, I don't
know. I feel like that these people are so anal about their fucking houses. Like this house
locked the, the access to the laundry. And I said, look, I'm staying here for two months. I took
your place because it has laundry. Why would you have laundry if I can't use it? And to their credit,
they gave it up. But it's like everything's a fucking negotiation. Well, wait, then you bring,
why did they advertise that there was laundry? If they didn't, well, they said we had to lock it because
we had a problem with people like doing too much and like not cleaning out whatever else. I'm like,
then take it off the ad, baby. Yeah. No, exactly. Fuck off. Let me in. Yeah. It's annoying.
It's just for you fright fans out there. Uh, I just got an email. I came through. I popped up.
I'm not looking at my email. I just got the notification arrows, you're tied, whatever,
their arrow UK is still doing a sale. Which I can do. Well, I would, I would highly recommend
if you have not checked out arrow in their sales, you should. They have a lot of very cool stuff.
Despite my hiccup with the psycho box set, I still will shop arrow frequently.
Matt McCarthy, let me know last night that Kino currently has a sale going, which is interesting.
Yes. Uh, and then also he sent me another sale. What was this other one? Hold on. I got that as well,
but I was asleep. Uh, uh, uh, synapses. Synapses having a sale. I mean, it never ends as I
texted to Matt. Goddamn it. It never ends. Uh, cause it doesn't. And one day, I'll buy them,
the, I'll finally buy the movie that makes me feel fulfilled as an adult emotionally. Yeah. Until then,
I'm going to keep it in these sales. Uh, Kino realized what it is for me. That, you know, it is
the feeling, the whole with buying things. And I'm always like, Pat, buying a couple blu -rays a month
is not the, not the worst way you could fill a hole in your soul. You know, I try not to beat myself
up about my hobby. But, um, as of late, I've definitely been like, I have too many great movies sitting
here unwatched. And I have not even been looking at Amazon or any of the sales. I feel like I'm,
I'm in ketchup mode. Matt and just hit sales two weeks ago. What are you talking about? But I'm
done. There'll be no purchases while I'm in Atlanta. There'll be no purchases while I'm in Atlanta.
And I realize what it is is that when they show up for me, it's the only time of the year,
I'm not looking for sympathy, but it's the only time of the year I get to sit down and open
something that's for me. Now it does come from me. But like my mom texted me last night, she's like,
I assume because you're traveling home for Christmas, you just want money.
So for the last 15 years, my mom and my dad have each given me a $100 bill for Christmas. That's
the extent of my presence. There's nothing else. I don't get birthday gifts. No, I do when I had a
wife. But like grown male friends don't give each other gifts. You know, that doesn't really have.
No, no, we do. The ones when I have done it, the ones willing to open up to one another do get out of
LA, leave that horrible city and move to where people with feelings live. Yeah, you might be right.
I'm right. Yeah. Working in Atlanta at six months a year, move to Atlanta and go back to LA for
the off months. You could be right. I mean, when this house that I'm staying in for like crazy
cheap and the show pays for it, this is a four bedroom house, even though I was complaining about it
earlier, there's no need for me to have this much space, but it's so cheap. It's five minutes from
set. And when I looked up how much the house cost, it was 200 grand. Yeah. There you go. There you go.
It is a huge, great house with everything you could want at a basement. I'm slowly sliding out
of New York, unless I have some major windfall of money, you know, that allows me to live here without
even, you know, live here part time without batting an eye. I'm slowly cutting the ties. I'm like,
I'm not doing this anymore. I'm not, I'm 46. I'm not spending obnoxious amounts of money
to keep one foot in a city and just go, I just, I'm just not doing it. There's no need anymore.
There's no need. When I want to work, I will come here and I will work. That's what the last two
decades have been about in my life, getting myself to that point. I'm not going to continue to live
in the concerned area of, well, if I leave, what if this and what if fuck that, man? You know,
as in recent months, so basically how it works when you write a movie is they send it out to like
six people. And then sometimes they'll be like, ah, sorry, that's it. And then you have to like
keep making them send it out. I have friends who they inspired me so much. I read this script
there's nine years ago. I said, it's really funny. Their agent was like, sorry, there's nothing we
can do. Very recently, they get a new agent manager. They started sending their scripts out within a
week. They sold a nine year old script and a seven year old script for like, you know, that's big
money selling a movie script. They have two little kids. They were like, fucking rejoicing. And I
was like, well, look, these two movie scripts I wrote are great. They were sent out to a tiny pool
of people. And in a world where every time you get on these streamers, every time you go see a movie,
there's 20 production companies before it. I'm like, let's start reaching out. Like, let's just
start sending it. And I swapped my feature agent. She sent it out suddenly. We got big, big action,
big leads on like two of these scripts that I written. So I'm pumped about that. If these two scripts
were to be made, then I become a go to movie writer or a movie rewriter or whatever. I'd be out of
LA in a heartbeat. I'd sell my house. I would buy a mansion anywhere other than LA in New York.
And send my scripts and go, you know, do do notes meetings over zooms. Send my script in. That's
the dream, really. Yeah, it's this this this idea of like, I got to I got to stay in LA because
because Jason Blum lives seven minutes from me. You're in the scene. They got to see you, you know,
that that ship that he says in, I can't remember if he says it in the actual movie.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, or if it's just in the book. But de caprio's character says like
they see that address man that you that you live in Los Angeles. That means you are part of it.
You know, like that whole thing. It's like, yeah, that was true at one time. That's true about New
York at one time. It's not true anymore. It's not true anymore. Nobody gives a fuck.
Especially when the younger, tragically, that movie was set 70 years ago,
you know, like the movie was set in the 50s. Right. Especially too, but that's not right. The 70s,
right? The 70s. So, you know, I'll continue to operate and work and do things in New York.
You know, I've got a fucking bar and sandwich shop here. But I'm not going to, you know, this this
you know, for the last week, I've been, I've been waking up every night at 5 a .m. sweating profusely
because it is so hot. I'm like, I'm not doing this. This is, you know, I'm tired of the like,
well, it's not perfect, but it's a good spot in New York. Fuck off already with it. It's nonsense.
I'm living in an airport for Christ's sakes. Yeah. The, the perks of it always were culture, you know,
like, like, when I lived in New York out right out of college, oh my god, I was like every concert
comes to New York, every movie comes to New York. Or, you know, people forget that, you know, if I
asked my mom, hey, have you seen May, December, my mom doesn't have Netflix. She has no idea what that
is because independent movies do not come to where my mom lives. You'd have to go almost an hour away,
like what I used to do in college, drive to go see an independent movie.
Yeah, I mean, it's, we don't really need to be in these big hubs anymore because there are pros
to streaming. The pro to streaming is every movie ever made is there for you. You know, I'm at an
age now where I'm kind of phasing out of wanting to go to every concert that comes, you know, I don't want
to become a homebody, but the cultural advantages of LA are starting to not appeal to me in the way
they used to. I just don't care as much anymore, especially because these great cities are crumbling.
LA is not what LA was 10 years ago. And New York certainly isn't.
Well, that's the thing too. Like I, I saw Thanksgiving last night.
Yes, in New York. Now, the beauty of New York is I had to do, I had to do the podcast. We might be
drunk Mark Norman and Sam Arrell's podcast yesterday at 2 p .m. Yeah. So I knew I had to see some,
I had to see a showing that worked somehow around that two hours that was going to be there in
the travel time getting there and all that stuff. The beauty of New York is I looked up six theaters
until I found the one that was equidistant from the studio as all the other ones that had the
viewing time that worked where I was able to go see it. That's great. New York, New York, 2 a .m.
I want some, I got a hand cream for cheesecake and I need some dental floss.
Great. I'll have both delivered to me right now within the hour. That's the beauty of New York that
those things are great. That said, I don't think, you know, that the, it's not an even trade,
meaning when I, when I got to the theater, yeah, it was one of your AMCs that you love so much.
I mean, my God, man. That means New York, it wasn't AMCs fault, but it's like, it's gross.
Like the theater's gross. I'm like, you know, and I'm sitting in it and then like it's,
it's the same old shit. Like people are coming in halfway through the movie. There's kids in there
being too loud. Like you're like, if I saw this where I bought my house, I would have watched it in
peace in a theater that I didn't think I might be getting bed bugs from. You know, I can use this movie
as a, as a perfect example of like the movie going experience nowadays. When I went to that
grand reopening of the Vista, Tarantino's new theater, five seconds from my house, two feet from
where Joe lived in LA. I walk up, I'm with two buddies. The show was sold out. Eli Roth introduces the
movie with the cast there. And that, that big black Friday sequence that opens up the movie,
people were screaming, clapping. Ah, gross. And I was like, Pat, you have to start going to horror
movies on opening night again. This is so much fun. You guys start going to comedies on opening night.
Theater was going batshit, but then the sound fucked up and we all left. So I'd only seen half the
movie. Now, when I went back to see it again, I had an AMC with a couple of buddies of mine on a Thursday
night. The projection sucked. It was like dim. The sound really sucked. You were straining to hear
every word. The audience was talking. They were on phones. They were not interested. Somebody was
like, wait a minute. I thought he was the killer. Like 10 minutes into the movie. And you're just kind
of like, oh, no, I'm wrong. I'd rather just be at home. It's a, it's a problem. But when you get a
great experience, and usually these days, I think that great experience is only on opening night
or opening weekend of a big movie, you can still get that magic back. You just can't go beyond that
opening weekend because the audiences are just over it by that point. Yeah. So anyway, folks,
we hope that you're living in listening in a city that's not crumbling. And if you are, it will
be. But try to enjoy it before it does. And look at look positive. Say I get to live in a city
that's crumbling. Let's go to that movie. Corn. I would like to kick things off with a movie called
Mr. Oregon. I was extremely excited to see this. It's not about it. It's not a point. Oh, no. Mr.
Oregon is a movie by David Farrier who makes very specific and weird documentaries,
including tickled, which is one of the great uncomfortable disturbing documentaries. It's up
there with the original catfish documentary, which I remember a friend slipped to me on a CD
rom. And I was like, God, this movie is so good. But tickled is a movie about a guy who's kind of
lightly investigating something and undercover this world of tickle freaks, people who get off
sexually on tickling. The movie is very disturbing and I highly recommend it. This is his follow -up,
Mr. Oregon, very strange movie. I wish I liked it more. It definitely held my interest. But
when you're doing these documentaries like he does where he just kind of decides to follow somebody
in hopes that they have an interesting story to tell, sometimes that's not going to pay off big
dividends. You don't know what you're getting into. I often wonder about how many documentaries we never
see just because they decided they were going to film something and nothing interesting happened.
You know, that's always my fear when I think about maybe I'd like to do a documentary is what if you
just get no good footage and you waste your time. This is somewhere in between. We do have a fascinating
character that we're studying here, but not much happens in the movie. He's so basically
they're in New Zealand. There is a guy, this very very narcissistic blowhard who's like a master of
legal loopholes and basically a master of getting under people's skin and pissing them off.
He has befriended this older kind of homely woman and he is doing this thing where anyone who
parks on her property, he has the cars clamped and finds them a huge amount of money which he then
pockets and he's been making a lot of money off it. So this is a news story. They're going to arrest the
guy. It's like a local news story, but our guy David Ferrier starts to become fascinated with this man
because everyone who has lived in close proximity with this guy has either committed suicide or had
some major scandals or some and he's like what is this guy doing and little by little you realize
that this is just a dark fucked up narcissistic manipulative scumbag and our guy is trying to kind of
expose him and just basically be a character study of this real life sociopath. But over the course
of the movie, David Ferrier the filmmaker becomes deeply fucked up and disturbed and annoyed by this
man because that's what he does. So even though he's trying to expose him, he can't help but fall
prey to him as well. So it's spending 90 minutes with just a deeply sick and annoying person.
It doesn't really go anywhere, but it's certainly a fascinating portrayal of like somebody on the
fringes of society like a con man worth a watch, but I would watch tickled first. That's the superior
documentary for sure. I'm going with three disappointments this week. Okay. Unfortunately, I bought
Malone the Bert Reynolds. This was finally the first purchase in my Bert Reynolds mustache 80s action
purchases. I liked it. I didn't dislike it. It was just re -released actually by Kino. It's a nice
transfer. Movies enjoyable. Malone. Malone. It's enjoyable enough, but it doesn't play much
heavier or much deeper than like a roadhouse does. And roadhouse when you kind of get the nostalgia
and catch out of it is not really a great movie despite what people say. And Malone is remake with
the sort of fun quality. Like it is fun to watch Reynolds take down like a bunch of red neck
bullies and five of them in one shot or whatever which does happen. Yeah. And there's some fun action,
but it's overall it's okay. If you can watch it cheaply or for free, I don't think you're going to
have a bad time, but it did not bring me the joy that Sharky's machine did which was batshit.
So I was hoping for a little more of that. It does contain a trailer for Rentacop, which Pad
has been pushing for us to do, which is more of a comedy, which I didn't know. Or at least the trailer
makes it look that way, but I want to go down the list and acquire all of these Bert Reynolds films.
So Malone was the first one little disappointing, not terrible. I want to rewatch it to see if I like
it more. And that's that. I have not seen Malone, but one of my favorites of that genre of like
late 80s sleaze. I got two of them. I love 52 pick up with Roy Scheider and Margaret, which is like
a Elmore Leonard thriller in the Pornow world real sleazy. And then I think I recommended to you James
Woods in cop. Yes. That's one I would I would seek out. But man, that was a period of time where
just the most sleaze and hate was coming out of those low budget movies. Well, that's the thing.
This one never gets that sleazy. So you're like, you want it? You want it? You want it? It's way more
like he he's he's trying to find a new assume a new identity in a small town. It's like the equalizer
except it just doesn't hit the heights that equalizer three hits. So anyway, it was it was okay.
What do you got last night for whatever reason I rewatched ghost. I remember ghost came out when I was
nine. It was the biggest hit of its year, massive phenomenon nominated for best picture spoofed by
all kinds of movies naked gun two and a half does a hilarious spoof of it.
Um, and I was just like, you know, I remember enjoying the hell out of it. I wonder if she holds up.
It's on HBO max. What a strange movie. It's definitely not great. The biggest issue with it nowadays
is that the special effects are just shit. They're terrible special effects. It's a lot of like
Patrick Swayze's head floating in like a beam of light. It's just not convincing at all.
Directed by Jerry Zucker, who is one of the Zuckers who did airplane and the naked guns.
Like everything about this movie is weird. This was his dream book. He broke away. Exactly.
I'm going to start doing serious movies now. Exactly. Um, Swayze is just the guy who would never
be a romantic leader in a movie nowadays. He plays too feminine, you know, he just wouldn't be.
I love him, but he just plays too feminine. Uh, Demi Moore is of course lovely. I never
think much of her as an actress, but she's great. And we'll be Goldberg steals the show.
She very deservedly won the actress, but won the best sporting actress Oscar. Um, but the movie,
there was so much in it I forgot. I thought it was just a love story and the guy dies and he's trying
to get back and like say goodbye and I love you to his girl one last time. And that's basically what it is.
But Swayze goes to this psychic who is who'll be Goldberg and she's a sham psychic, but she actually
sees him. He's dead and she actually sees him and helps. So she starts. It's a great
problem helping him. Yeah. Helping him communicate with Demi Moore. And it's lovely. There's a scene
where I read Ebert's review and he was like, whoopie Goldberg lets Swayze come into her body so that
he can embrace his ex -wife one last time. And it's this opportunity to see whoopie Goldberg and Demi
Moore like embrace and you'd know it wasn't like a lesbian scene, which you couldn't have in a big
mainstream movie back then. But it would have made that such a more interesting and compelling sequence.
Instead it just cuts to Patrick Swayze and Demi Moore making out. So in your mind, you're like, oh I
guess Demi Moore and whoopie Goldberg are kissing and so it doesn't it doesn't quite go where you want
it to with its premise or it doesn't go far enough. But the real crazy thing about this movie to me
is that Swayze's best friend at work played by classic 90s sleaze Tony Goldwyn.
Is trying to smuggle $4 million from like, there's like a reference to like, I need the discs.
Yeah. There was always some discs subplot in the 80s and 90s like midnight run has a discs subplot.
But that subplot is so ridiculous like this movie did not need a villain and a heist plot in the
middle of it. What you're left with is like a thriller horror romance comedy. And just just that that
they managed to kind of hit all those bases pretty well. And the fact that this was as big a hit as
it was, I found myself admiring it. Although I didn't love it. I didn't like missed up at the end
like I might have when I was a kid. But if you've never seen it, it's a wild ride. And whoopie Goldberg's
really funny in it. All right. All right. I expect these next two disappointments to spark a little
controversy between me and old Walsh over here. I rewatched Dr. Sleep. Okay. On the scene.
I was the director's cut. The three -hour cut are the old ones.
Whatever fucking one I watched was two hours and 34 minutes. If there's a longer one,
God help us all. I think that's the director's cut. Yeah.
I saw Dr. Sleep in the theater. I thought it had some tremendous moments. I did fall asleep
in the middle of it, but I enjoyed it. I was excited. It was one of those Amazon purchases for me.
It was like the Blu -ray came out. It was like $10. And it also, you did not watch the director's
cut. You watched the OG cut. Well, that's crazy. So I, so I read, so I buy it on Amazon. It's got the
director's cut on. I'm like, sure. Good enough. I rewatched it. I was excited to rewatch it. I wanted
to see the director's cut, but all my movies are at the home. I, my other home, not at my apartment in
New York. So I'm on, sit on the New York couch the other night and I see it's on like two B
or something and I'm like, you know what? I'm going to watch Dr. Sleep. I am in the mood to see this
again. Great start to the movie. Sort of, they don't do that which scene justice. But it's still
as a good opening. When you first meet, grown Danny, played by you and McGregor. It's intriguing.
It's very good. And then even, yeah, I was even, I was even tickled and charmed by the most cliché
Stephen King characters ever in a Stephen King movie. You know, he meets the guy Mike or whatever's
name is that's working on the train in the park and that guy, you know, that guy being like,
you got the look friend. I know the look when they see the look. You know, there's that character
there's, you know, he goes to rent a room. He needs to get a room. By the way, he's doing this because
he's an alcoholic, grown Danny is an alcoholic and he has to, as he puts it, he's running away from
himself. So he relocates to this new town to start a new life and potentially eventually gets
sober. And he rents a room and the lady that rents them the room. It's so funny. It was
years before this movie came out. When I worked on, when I worked on
Mount, uh, wet hot American summer, uh, Michael Show Walter, we wrote a scene in, in one of the,
it was, it was, there was an episode where David Hyde Pierce's character was coming to the camp
that he needed a room. And there was a landlord showing him the room. And Michael Show Walter was
like, we're going to do every, every, uh, Stephen King landlord that you've ever seen in Stephen
King movie. Uh, and he would do it. It would make me laugh so hard and I would, I would make him do
it. Like, please just do that for me right now. Even though we're not reading the script. And it was like,
yeah, oh, listen to me going on, you know, Johnson's lived down the street. Nice people shame what
happened with that dog. Listen to me going, you know, well, that's a story for another time. Yeah,
yeah. Down this way. Yeah. And they do that. Yeah. And they do that in this movie. I'm like,
guys, come on. Come on. But whatever. Yeah. I'm, well, I let all of that go. Fine. Blah, blah, blah.
It's got some very alarming scenes. But ultimately this movie suffers from what I think. And I like,
what's his name? Mike Hanigan. Flanagan. Flanagan. I like Mike Flanagan. I think he's got a good head
on his shoulders. I think he makes a quality product. I think he gives a shit. Uh, I really admire the guy.
But I think this movie suffers from what all of his projects suffer from, which is there are some
amazing tent poles going on throughout the project. But God damn, man, it just gets so bogged down in the
fucking minutia of the characters and with just scene after scene of people driving and then talking
and then parking and then walking and you're like, dude, pace, come on, man, get this thing moving here.
Like it's a, it's a movie that's literally about a race against time and it's dreaded. So, um,
I got to give another shot. I remember loving it, particularly the tremble scene, but um,
I got to give it another shot. I got to say, maybe I'm getting soft in my old age, the tremble
scene really disturbed me. Like I had to turn the volume down. I was like, I, that's what I'm saying.
I think it's one of the more disturbing scenes of recent horror. I was, well, like, but when I saw it in
the theater, I was like, like, wide eyed. Like, wow, they went for it. That was crazy. Now I'm like,
I don't want to hear this fucking kid screaming. This is bothering me, you know, like whatever. So, um,
I don't know the, the trembling must, uh, tremble, it must have aged bad. I haven't seen him in five
years and some, you know, he had that even in laws, but he's not even in the wonder sequel.
Yeah. Exactly. Hick in the wonder sequel over to the side character. So, um, yeah, I don't know,
man. I'm just like the end of it too. It's all sort of just, it's an interesting story, but it's all
sort of, it's, it's a Stephen King story that also, in my opinion, it's, it's not bad. It's just
Stephen King is so fucking hung up right now on this idea of
characters that have to go on this journey and a mission in order to outwit the sinister force
and when it, and it becomes so much more about the, the chase and the race that it does about to me
an intriguing spooky fun story, uh, where I could even focus on, on, on the main characters because
there's so many characters involved now. I know you and I disagree on this, but, um, it's, um,
um, oh, damn it. There was a, there was a, wait, uh, there was a Stephen King thing that you
really liked that I was just going to say I thought, oh, damn it. I can't remember. Anyway, uh,
it's, it's, it's, it's, it's just, it's just not something that that, you know, and, and it gets
again, it gets a bit convoluted with like, it's a cool idea that there's this pack of these,
these, these immortals that eat the shining out of people that have it and that's how they continue
to stay young and live. That's really interesting. Uh, and that's kind of enough like, but then there's
this whole other thing where like, Danny is now able to see when people are going to die.
And that's his purpose he serves at this hospice. And then there's this other thing where he's still
being haunted by the ghosts of the overbroke hotel. But he's able to now entrap them in his mind
because he pictures these boxes. Like, it just starts to get like insane. And then I'm like, I don't,
how the fuck are the ghosts that Danny is trapping attacking another human being that's never encountered
the ghosts. That's how Rose the Hat dies at the end. I'm like, I don't know. It just doesn't
really make a lot of sense to me ultimately. And it gets a little quarry. And I was disappointed.
I'm not going to sell my blue ray, but I was disappointed. All right. It was weird. I think that might
have been the same year that we got Dr. Sleep and Ready Player One, but it was like two movies playing
with the legend of the shining and like on the set of the shining. Really strange. Yeah.
I from my last one will be a brief. I saw what is it? What is it? The Five Heartbeats.
I had never seen this movie. It was written by Robert Townsend and Ken and I every Wains. Townsend
I'm working every day in a 90 % black writers room. And a lot of times the touchstone movies for
black kids are not the same. Obviously as those for white kids. So I, here I am thinking I've seen
every movie. And like when they want to talk about juice, boys in the hood, stuff from when I was like
older, I know it. But Five Heartbeats, I had just missed and I watched it. And then I was able to go like,
oh, okay. So this is your version of that thing you do. So I got to recommend that thing you do to them.
But that's been a blast. I watched what's the other one? Jack the Jackson's an American dream.
Because I had never seen that. The mini series about the history of the Jackson family. I'm halfway
through it now. It's like 12 hours long. But The Five Heartbeats is a movie about a fictional band.
Think the temptations are the four tops. They are coming up during that period. The 60s. And it's your
classic, you know, walk hard. Pretty much ended this genre by spoofing it to death. But it's your classic
five best friends come together to form a singing group. Drugs and women and the times changing and all
that. Caused them all sorts of problems. Then at the end, they're old men and they managed to put it
behind them and be friends again. But there's some great music in it. It's two by the numbers.
It's every music, biopic, rags to riches. It's also the same story as that thing you do.
But this was one of the first, you know, certainly one of the first black ones that traced it.
Townsend just showed up again on the bear as Iowa to Barry's father. And I was so excited. I said,
Robert Townsend out loud alone in my house because he is kind of been unheralded pioneer of certainly
black independent movies. And criteria and his started throwing him some love. They put out a new
addition of Hollywood shuffle and so forth. But Five Heartbeats great movie. It's on HBO Max right
now. It was it's impossible to buy on as far as I know, Blu -ray 4K anything. So check it out. If you
paint by numbers, but they do that because those stories work really well. And it's very likeable movie.
Have you seen the Five Heartbeats jump? I have not seen it, but it's funny you pick that because my
final pick in disappointing movies is that thing you do. I had never seen it. Oh, disappointing.
I knew I knew it. I did. I did not say this would cause some controversy. The movie stinks.
And did you watch the director's cut of that thing you do? No, I'm serious. There's an excellent
like 30 -minute longer director's cut of Tom Hanks made. Well, I'm going to go on the version that
was released that everybody gave a 95 percentile rating too. This in my opinion, this film,
and maybe I'm being a little convergingly, but this movie was made when Tom Hanks could do no wrong.
Nobody would say a bad thing about Tom Hanks. It's such a basic, it's brainless. There's zero conflict,
there's zero drama. Every time there's an opportunity for there to be some conflict, they don't
explore it. For instance, perfect example. The manager that represents them, it lives in his RV,
and you're waiting for this guy to, so when they meet up with this guy, because I knew
enough about the movie to know, well, eventually Tom Hanks is staring the ship of this band.
When they meet up with this guy, I was like, okay, here's the guy where Tom Hanks is going to come to
them and go, you know how you think your manager's great? He's an idiot. If you want to make it,
you got to dump him and come with me, and they're going to have to dump this guy and it's going to be
this big blow up, and he's going to threaten to sue that whatever. They don't even do that.
They have the guy that you think is going to screw them, bring them to Tom Hanks,
and then amicably say, you've got to go with him now as the band argues to not ditch this guy.
Yeah. Zero conflict, nothing. The one confrontation that happens in the entire movie is when
live Tyler, they're playing on a TV show at the end of the movie. The guy in the band that she
dates, they put on, when they cut to him during the broadcast, they write on the screen, careful
ladies, he's engaged, and his girlfriend has lived Tyler, played a little and they're not engaged.
Right. So in the laziest, laziest devices, how does he find out the screen said that?
Because he sees it as their playing. Folks, I've been on TV. You would never see that as you were
on live television. You would never see the key of what was being written in front of you on live
television, as it was, it's, it's just not how technology worked. You're certainly not focusing
enough on your drummery, if you're noticing that. Let's say that he's the singer. It's not even the
drummer. He's the singer. He's got a, he's got me even more to worry about. So, so, so, so, whatever,
so, so, but whatever suspension is really fine. He flips out at her without giving her any benefit
of the doubt for suddenly he's a complete asshole. You're like, he hasn't been an asshole for the
entire movie. Why is he an asshole now? He's been a little self -absorbed, if memory serves in
the most mild, this is how he self -absorbed. When do we get to record a new record? That's his
self -absorbed. Yeah. I want to record a new record. Right. And then live Tyler dumps him in front
of everybody with the sappiest, most maudlenstery. I've wasted thousands of kisses on you. Oh, I want
a fucking puke. Maybe if I watched it now, I would turn on it. I watched it before my hard died. So,
you never know. Tell me, Steve's on still funny in it. Steve's on still very funny in it.
The cast is great. Everybody in the movie is fine. It's good. Tom Hanks does not do a poor job of
directing. But the script is paper fucking. I'll tell you who steals, in my opinion, you still read
a Wilson, it's fucking great. She comes in as that bar waitress at the jazz club. And she plays it
so well. And you're like, this she is nailing the energy of an older woman who still got sex appeal,
but is working in this place. It maybe didn't pan out the way she thought it was going to. She's not
mad about it. But she just kind of knows what the score is. She's great. Everybody's very good in it.
And the movie looks nice. But at the end of the day, it is a paper thin script. And Jesus Christ,
do you hear that fucking song? I mean, and I guess that's sort of one of the points, but you hear it
like 11 times in the movie. It's ridiculous after a while. Well, that's what I was about to say,
is that the five heartbeat really struggles because their music is not on point. So like granted,
they didn't become the four jobs. They were a second tier band, but it's lacking that catchy song. So
you're kind of don't buy them on this big sky rocket. However, the song that thing you do,
I think is probably the catch you a song ever written for a movie. I mean, it's it's so perfect.
And I was a big founds away in fan. Anyway, I love that band. So I was thrilled to see them getting
that getting that gig. I love the song. I can never tire of that song, to be honest. 11 times in a row,
I played for you, you're not going to be like, all right, guys, I'd be okay. I'd be okay. What are
the other side? I don't remember the other ones being that bad either. There aren't any other one.
The other was another couple. Like two times they play like 10 seconds of a different song. But
dude, there's so many scenes that start with them performing. And yeah, boom, boom, boom, boom. And
you're like, guys, I get it. Like, it's about a one hit wonder. Like, I understand that this,
but like, Christ, guys, it's it's the the there's what I'm saying. The script is too condensed and too
thin for this song to be that prevalent. You have to space it out with other things.
So, so it's not insane after a while. But, um, yeah. But I'm a big fan of, uh, who's the kid? Uh,
I always want to call this kid an Emory. Oh, it is Ethan Emory. No. Well, Ethan Emory used to be Ethan
Randall. He changed his name. That's the kid from Dutch. I was confused. But that's when I was a kid,
too. He was the kid in Dutch with that O 'Neal. And then he grew up to be and that thing you do. And
you know, he's he just changed his name. He's in, uh, the high school movie too. He's in
Vegas vacation. Hi, he's in can hardly wait. Can hardly wait. Well, I love that movie. He plays rusty
in Vegas, vacation. Can hardly wait is great. But wait, I said Ethan Emory. No, who did I say was
in the ranch? Ethan Emory. It's not Ethan Emory. I meant the kid that was Ethan Supply, right?
The big fat guy. That's what I meant. Yeah. Okay. Um, so Ethan Emory's, I find that kid incredibly
endearing. I really like the guy that's that was in American Werewolf in Paris, who plays the drummer.
Tom Everett Scott. He was pegged to be the next Tom Hanks. And it never happened for him. They were
like, this guy is Tom Hanks. It's a bummer. Uh, I, I'm a fan of Steve Zahn. The, the lead singer guy
was the guy wasn't that familiar with, but he's still out there doing a thing and and got a check.
Used to be married to Applegate. Uh, lived Tyler always, uh, delight. Uh, and Tom Hanks,
of course, most of the time Tom Hanks nails it. And he's great in this. I like that he's kind of
barky and, you know, throwing Peter's scolaria bone. Nice. Yeah. He's, yeah. I enjoyed the
glory. He's excellent on girls. But, uh, he doesn't act much. He's excellent on girls. He's dead.
Did he die? Hey, died a few years back here. Shit. I didn't even know. Yeah, it's sad. Very sad.
I don't know. I like Peter's score. Joe, Joe, Joe, is he on the policy cats? No.
Now I've heard it's actually funny because it's like a sad tire. It's funny. But it, uh, may
have my friends were so obsessed with this movie when we were teenagers. It is the meanest movie to
its target audience. It is, it hates teenage girls so much. And it is so funny. They have killer fucking
songs on that movie too. I have to soundtrack to Josie on the pussy cats. I'm not ashamed to admit it.
But, uh, I recommend that to everybody. It's hilarious. And you got two all -time great comedy villains
in Parker Posey. And, uh, who's the great gay dude, Joe, that, uh, did cabaret.
He's British. He now hosts a peacock reality show. Why can I think of his name?
The guy that was in the, uh, the cabaret that from the 70s, he got nominated.
No, that's Joel Gray. Parker Posey. And who's the guy, Joe?
Oh, Alan coming. Thank you. Alan coming. Yes, they play, uh, this, this like, fucked up brother
sister villain duo. And they are fucking awesome. Check out Josie on the pussy cats.
Um, and we are talking this week. If, if we're, are we clear from the movie?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was okay. That was the end.
We're talking this week about Eli Ross Thanksgiving, the full length adaptation of the, um,
two -minute fake trailer that was in Grindhouse between films. This movie recreates a lot of that
trailer's most memorable kind of shock moments. But this, Eli Roth has always talked about how much
he loves just slasher movies. And this is a true, pure slasher. Like, I don't think there's a formula
per se, but it feels like every 10 minutes we get a kill. It's cleverly staged, cleverly done on
theme on, you know, has something to do with the Thanksgiving holiday. Um, and it's just a blast.
I texted Joe when I, when, when I said the audio ran out of that first viewing of Thanksgiving,
I texted Joe. If this continues at this pace, I think this is one of the best slasher movies
ever made. I don't think there are a lot of A plus slasers. I think you're down to Halloween and a
couple of others, but I was like, this movie is killing. A lot of that was the audience. I realized
the second time, but you do have, I think certainly the best Thanksgiving horror movie. Um, and I think
you have a holiday slasher that can rank with the grates. It's a classic who done it. Um, I won't say
it's like a beautifully constructed mystery, but I didn't guess the killer. Did you, Joe?
I, well, sort of, sort of, let's, can we come back to that question? Can we describe the movie
first because I don't want to get ahead of who I, why I thought what I thought, but I agree with every open
zone. You just said, I was just going to say I agree with everything you just said. This is absolutely
in the vein of the more outrageous, but well executed slasers. So, so sometimes you say slasher,
you think Halloween, this is not a Halloween. This is a Jason lives. This is a scream. This is, um,
uh, and I know what you did last summer. No, you did. I'm sorry. The gem to be honest. My bloody
Valentine, the original, uh, comes to mind. I, this is a really wild slasher that manages to land
the plane at the end, uh, which is, which is hard to come by. And I, I had a blast. I, I usually don't,
I'm usually nitpicking from moment one with a movie, but I try not to. Like, when a movie nails
what it's trying to do correctly, and it works, it works. And this is one of those things. Like,
this is a thing like, like hostile part one, where it was crazy and insane, but he just nails what
he's trying to do. And he makes it very clear to you right away. The stuff, yeah, right off the bat
with the, with the Black Friday sale, mob, you hate everybody immediately. You're, you can't
wait to see some of these people get this come up and it's perfect. They couldn't, there's no
world in which they could have sustained it. It wouldn't have been a good movie. But if they had
sustained the pace of this opening Black Friday thing, I was like, holy shit, because the opening
20 minute, 10 minute, 15 minute Black Friday sequence, probably 20. You realize what a younger,
more immature Eli Roth would have done. They got Tim Dylan, who's hilarious, you know, being like,
shut the fuck up, yelling at everybody and stuff. And those get laughs, but he's not making jokes on
top of that. Right. He's simply doing what his character would do in that moment. And you look at
like cabin fever where they're doing like almost broad sitcom comedy mixed with the horror and it just
doesn't work. Right. This, this movie was getting really nice big laughs, but not because of
jokes. Eli Roth was just kind of presenting it. Even when the carnage starts at Black Friday,
it's all within the bounds of what we've actually seen happen online. There's so many great little
gags in the Black Friday bit in terms of gags and in terms of everybody goes that's gross,
but also in terms of funny bits like that like zombie grabbing the last waffle maker, you know,
with his dying breath. Yeah. Our heroes, you know, the teenagers that were supposed to be following,
they pull up to this store in the opening scene and park their giant gas guzzling truck in the
handicap spot. So what you're saying about us hating them is absolutely right, Joe. Even our heroes,
we can't stand. And that's what you need for a slasher. You want a few people you care about that
you're rooting for, but really you like seeing these people get killed. That's the beauty of it.
They do a, they do a good job. The daughter of them, the character of the father who owns the
price mark, whatever the hell it's called, where the Black Friday thing happens,
often from hostile. Yeah, he's great. But his daughter, they make them, they're going to the movies
on Thanksgiving night and they make her obnoxious friends make them pull off at the store.
Because they know she can get them in past the crowd because they want to get a phone before they,
before the crowd gets in. And she's the only one saying, I don't want to do this right now. So they
let you have a little sympathy for her. And they let you have a little sympathy for her boyfriend,
who also doesn't want to do it. And blah, blah, blah. Everybody else basically from there on out
is obnoxious. In fact, the only person that gets, and these are spoilers, the only person that gets killed
where you're like, by the killer, I mean, where you're like, he didn't deserve it, is Tim Dylan.
Because you're like, this guy didn't do anything wrong. He's the security guard put in this ridiculous
situation and he goes, fuck this. And he leaves. Yeah. And I'm like, that's what I was. That was a,
that was a beautifully executed, so simplistic kill. Like, that's just a guy in his apartment with
his cat. And they, I love what they did with that. That one, you know, they're, they're, there are
insane violent kills in this movie, but they're all memorable and they stand on their own. The
Tim Dylan one, you know, again, you're talking about a moment that like gets a laugh, but isn't a gag
per se is the killer turns and looks at the cat. I used to not give a shit when the audience is
would freak out about dead pets and movies because I never had one. But once I had a cat, I get it. And
I looked at that cat and I was like, fuck me. Eli Roth, you know, I saw his cannibal movie. And he's
a guy who doesn't pull punches. And I'm like, now we're going to watch this dead cat. And you see
the killer walk over and he's filled the cat's bowl and pass it on the head before he heads out. Like,
he's not a monster. And I love that. There's just so many like perfect little moments like that. And
I love this, this side of Eli Roth, you know, he, it's like, it's almost like how puritanical the
world has become helped him because he's not trying just to gross you out. Like he's got
restraint now. And he's a master of tone and and of staging shit. You know, he wasn't the best
director early on. And I think he really knows how to stage a stabbing sequence really, really well.
The movie itself is basically a who done it about who, who was putting on a Pilgrim mask and killing
people in town. And is it payback for this violent massacre that took place on Black Friday
the year before? And he's basically it. Yeah, he's posting, he's posting things online and he's tagging
all the kids that the daughter and her friends. And you start to realize pretty quickly, like, this
is clearly payback for the people that died in this in this in this riot that happened at the Black
Friday sale. But why? And it kind of goes from there. And Eli does a really good job of peppering
the movie with a lot of red herrings, uh, maybe the ones. Yeah, yes. Like this girl, it's not going
to win an Oscar. But the screen in terms of these who done it, they do a really good job of giving you
a lot of possible suspects. And they're all they all have believable motives. That's the key for
something like this. Yeah, there's the guy whose wife played by Gina Gershon gets killed. You know,
you're like, you know, the only result basically. Yeah, the only reason you know, it's not him is because
he's too large. But, but still, he's got a motive. Then her boyfriend, he gets his wrist in, he's
he's going to be a baseball star. And his wrist gets broken in the riot. And it ends his opportunity
for a career. And then he disappears from town. So nobody knows where he went and then resurfaces
suddenly the next hot Thanksgiving. So it could be him. She's dating a new guy who's a complete douchebag
who they really make you think is the killer for a while. Like, um, that is, uh, Cameron Mannheim's son,
by the way. Oh, he's great. He's my little man. Yeah. He plays it. Fucking God. He's, he nails it.
Yeah. Then there's the guy that owns the store that has been, you know, he thinks the riots weren't
his fault. He's under all these lawsuits. The town is turning against him. He's trying to fix it.
Maybe it's him. Maybe it's his wife who thinks that they did nothing wrong. And, and that,
that this, you know, that, that, that business, the business show must go on at all. They,
they just do a good job of making you guess who, and as people die, obviously the suspects get fewer
and fewer. Um, but every kill, every single kill is inventive. It's something I don't think I've ever
seen. Uh, you get your gore. Uh, it's, it's, it's, it's, and, and the killer in the mask. John,
what was it? John Carthamus. Yeah. Some, some, like, the killer in the mask is like,
it looks fucking scary, man. It's a freaky looking mask. It's, it's scary. Like it, it almost looks
like an old Jesus statue because of the beard and everything. Like, that's what I thought it was at first.
Yeah. It's freaky looking. So it, it gives you that the famous trampoline scene from Thanksgiving. But
to show you, you've got an older normal chair, Eli Roth, the knife does not actually enter her sexually
in this version. But, um, there's that scene where she's kind of showing off her ass and bouncing
around on the trampoline and then get stabbed up. But they're all trailer or something. That's
in the original trailer. Yeah. She likes, it winds up sitting on the knife. I thought that was
going to happen in this and I didn't split some lands on it. Oh, okay. Okay. I didn't remember that.
Yeah. I didn't remember that. Um, yeah. He just, I, I admired it. I admired the, the craft of it
in both the writing and the directing. And they just announced Thanksgiving too. I think that
I'm happy about that. You know, I, I hope they get a couple more good movies out of it. I don't
think it's going to be go the Halloween distance. But, uh, I would definitely go see the other two
parts of a Thanksgiving trilogy, for sure. I would too. Leading the charge of the entire film outside of
the main character, thought the main character of the daughter is, uh, Patrick Dempsey. Very welcome
back. Patrick Dempsey. I haven't seen him in a minute. He's as charged as an anime. I don't, is he
still on it? I think he wasn't on it for like the last. No, he's not on it. But I, I only watched the
first couple of seasons, which were right. I just lost interest. But, um, he was on it for at least
15 years. I think I know he was on that. But since that even, that's been 10 years since he's been
off of it or whatever. So I, I, I, I look fantastic. He's good in the movie. And I tell you, I don't
know if you've seen him interviewed, but he's genuinely funny in charge. It's annoying. How much
the man has? And he does great. Well, I think he lost his wife to breast cancer. And he does
like all this work for breast cancer or fundraising or whatever. He seems like a really wonderful man. And
he plays such an endearing character in this, which is why, to answer your question, I did suspect him
from the jump. And I kept through the entire movie going, please don't let it be Patrick Dempsey.
Please don't let it be. I love this character. Please don't let it be Patrick Dempsey. Yeah. Of course,
it is Patrick Dempsey is the killer who dies. Heavy quotes around dies in a blaze of glory.
In a, in a literal explosion at the end of the movie, but then they can't find the body. Now,
this is what I like about this. Clearly he's going to come back and be the killer in the second one.
Yeah. I was like, the second, the second reason I didn't want to be Patrick Dempsey was, I was like,
I'm not scared of Patrick Dempsey. Right. Not scary to me. He's always going to be lovable in my head.
But put Patrick's Dempsey through an explosion and make him all fucking charred up and crazy looking.
Then like, all right, now you got to, you got a scary killer on your hand. So, so I look forward
to seeing what they do with that. They do the classic. There's nobody was nobody could have died.
That survived that explosion. Right. No, we didn't find a body. Right. Eli Roth really knows how to
steer into the, into the tropes when it's right. And he knows how to avoid them when it's not. And he
does that throughout this entire thing. I thought he did a great job, man. I thought he did a great,
he must have, by the way, though, he must have been like, fuck, when that last screen came out and
the cop turned out to be ghost. Right. Right. Right. Right. Yeah. Like, so, no, it's great. What's weird
is that, you know, an actor at his level, sorry, director at his level, who has now gone on to like
big budget Hollywood movies. And he did the death wish remake and the house with a clock in its walls
and all that, whatever, like, usually your 10th movie would not be a low budget slasher.
But that's what it, that's where his passions are. Like, anytime they do any network does anything
about horror, there's Eli Roth talking about it. Anytime I go to a horror movie in LA, Eli Roth is
in the audience. And it really just seems like a guy who was trying to stretch a little bit out of his
capabilities for about a decade. And then finally was like, fuck it. Why don't I do what I'm passionate
about? And he does some of the best work of his career. You know, I hope he realizes like stick
with horror. You're great at it. You know, I liked his knock knock with Keanu. That was a good thriller.
But I just don't want to see him doing kids movies. That's not, that's not where his strengths are.
And it doesn't seem to be what he's interested in either. So I hope you get more of this. I agree,
I agree. Hogs up for Thanksgiving. Thankful for Thanksgiving, as they say. We'll be back next time
with we will probably do this director's episode that we keep teasing sometime this month. And then
I'm sure we'll do a Christmas movie of some kind also. We don't know what it is yet. I think that's
giving to has to be like back for seconds. Who wants seconds? Second helping. Second helping.
Something was already called second helping. I can't remember what it was. But anyway, leftovers.
No, there will be no leftovers. They said that that's right. That's right. Yeah.
All right. Thank you very much, everybody. See you in hell pot on Instagram. We've got the
Etsy page. Thank you to Emily for all your help. And thank you to all of you who have done
the beautiful art and the support and come out to the live shows. And we love you. And thank you so
much and happy holidays.