Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff.
The slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured
game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -Terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see you, I'll see
is all we, uh, the only umbrella we have for the show, uh, in TV. So even that doesn't count.
TV is in there too. Basically every week we'll talk about something. That's what this specificity
is. How a podcast makes it in today's crowded market. And this podcast is all about things.
And while we're on the topic of things, just a reminder to the fans, our live show is coming up
October 20th, it will be at Oh, my ribs in show my ribs. Right? There you go. In Los
Angeles, tickets are on sale now. The ticket link is live. You can go to the, we'll see
you in hell. Instagram page to or feed or whatever you want to call it to find that link.
It's a see you in hell pod. Yes. And there's two shows that night, 20 bucks for one, 30 for
both, limited tickets for both though. So if you want to, if you want to try to swing
through both of these things, they will be two different shows. You should do that sooner
than later and a drink and party after. Yeah. Free drink, not free drinks, but a free to
hang out and drink with us. I want to be very clear. You'll be paying for the drinks.
We'll pay for our own. I mean, we're not trying to get anything out of you.
No, and I believe March will be for sale and all that all that crap
Pat how are you?
Terrible Joe me too. Just a
stressful
Time and Joe and I were talking right before we started recording about how miserable we are
And I was like, hey, why don't we set up the the recorder so we don't lose this magic
Just before we hit record pat and I both
shared that independently of one another, we were both so depressed that we both cancel therapy
tomorrow. That's a level of depression. I don't know if you're experienced. We go,
what's the fucking point? What's the point? Wouldn't do anything for me. Pat, you're down
about what? Because I know what I'm down about. I mean, all, all matter of things, I just can't
It seemed to find any happiness anymore, but, you know, just every situation, every one
I meet, every place I go, I just see hate.
I hate people, I hate my life right now to be honest with you.
And there we are.
I watched a man, I went up, Joe stood me up for dinner last night, I didn't stand
I made a plan that I said I can't make it and for some reason you were there 45 minutes
before we were supposed to meet. So I dined alone. I walk out. There's a guy in the street
who has clearly died. His car has died. So he's going through like a green light on Los
almost monster trucks sized truck behind him who has a full lane to go around
right but instead starts honking like get out of the way honking and we're
like all right well here comes the realization that he's honking on a guy who's
cars breaking down and they'll be able to apology wave or something he honks for
five full minutes at this car slows and slows and then stops and then he stays
is behind the car in traffic.
No one in his lane to the right.
He could go around at any point.
He just keeps honking and honking and honking
at a car that has died
because he can't open his brain a little to realize
maybe this guy isn't fucking with him.
Right.
I hated the man so much
and yet I also feel like in a couple weeks' time
I could be him, honking and honking at a dead car.
It's where I'm at.
That's the problem now,
you go, what an asshole, you're honking at a dead card.
Then the other path, he goes, oh no,
this guy's just been behind enough people
that are that entitled, that they'll come to a complete stop.
Yeah.
Yeah, that he's losing his fucking mind.
It's that you can't win.
I'm at a party last night for a buddy of mine's birthday
and the cops show up because everybody's outside, OK?
So clearly a neighbor complained about the outside noise.
So you know, we go and tell me, hey, there's cops outside.
Cops are very nice.
They're like, look, you just get everybody inside.
It's too late to have all these people out here.
He's very kind.
This thing's been going on since 2 p .m. by the way.
This is an all day party.
Right.
He goes up to everybody.
He's very kind.
He's like, look guys, just so I don't get a ticket or something.
Why don't we just all go inside, shut the doors and the windows.
We go inside.
As soon as we're inside, people are trying to open the windows.
I'm literally shit -faced.
I'm telling people, keep the windows shut.
The whole thing is there's noise.
Within five minutes of this happening, everybody's back outside again.
I'm losing my fucking mind, talking about this to a buddy of mine and I go, it just sickens
me.
It's sickens me.
The people in this fucking town, they act like they're so open -minded, and they're so progressive,
and they're so open to everybody's problems, and they're struggling, and all this bullshit.
And these fucking people can't even have the courtesy to stay inside at one o 'clock in the morning
when the cops were just here for the sake of this guy not getting a noise ordinance.
Or noise violation, excuse me. And my buddy just kept going, well, people are like that everywhere.
And I'm like, I know they're like that everywhere,
but it's more annoying here because here they act like they get it.
Right.
And here they go out of their way to show you how open -minded they are
and how they care about other people.
Yeah.
Do it in New York, fine.
People in New York tell you to go fuck yourself.
It's a lot more palatable there to me.
And you just kept going, well, it's like this everywhere.
This is what, you just kept saying it.
I will say though, if I was hosting a house party in Missouri,
which I did on a few occasions,
people start blurring out into the porch and let's, you know, we're 21 and everybody's drunk
and stupid.
As soon as the cops come up, everybody's inside and shuts the fuck up and then nobody
goes outside.
Yeah.
Generally, there'd be somebody at the door like, Hey, we had cops, or so unless you're leaving
staying here.
There's, there is more respect for certain things in, in the Midwest.
Oh, I agree.
There are also trash in many other ways.
Don't get me wrong.
I agree.
No, I think people are better.
I'm gonna go out and say this, it's not even on a limb.
I believe it's a fact, and I'm speaking about LA
and the Hollywood sense, because that's what we're in,
both geographically and in the abstract of the business.
Everybody, everywhere else is better.
These are the worst people on planet Earth.
They're the most selfish fucking pigs.
I just moved into this new apartment building.
We're here now.
Pat, it's a nice building, am I wrong?
Beautiful.
It's a nice building.
You know, it's not cheap to live in here.
I mean, it's not ridiculous, but it's, you know,
it's like, you're living here, you're investing
in your lifestyle a little bit.
Sure.
They'd send a fucking email out today
to tell the residents of this building
to stop leaving trash in the hallway.
In the hallway.
Wow.
What the fuck is wrong with everybody?
We talking like a trash bag or like littering or like both are bad.
They're like guys.
We love that you're the residents here.
We thank you for being here.
Please don't leave your empty, broken down moving boxes in the hallway.
Please don't leave them in the floor.
Who are the anticipated is going to get that?
That's just somebody who's had things done for them their whole life.
It's ridiculous.
It is ridiculous.
these are these are privileged, pampered, fake fucks in this city. They fucking think
and they'll man, they'll make you think they're on your fucking team. And they love everybody.
And oh, what a tragedy over there. And my heart goes out to these people over here. Meanwhile,
you have to deal with one of these cock suckers in a fucking store. They'll cut right in front of you.
They'll do whatever they need to do to get out there for their mother fuckers. I hate them.
Oh god, damn it. I'm angry. I hear you. But I did get I think a good son from above this morning
when a 75 pound crow, crow fell from the Los Angeles skies dead and landed in a heap in my front
yard. I watched it go down. And I had to go out with a shovel to start my morning. Tony
soprano style and like boxers and a robe. And I jammed this shovel under the 75 pound
hawk and threw it in the dumpster. So I started my day. And it was downhill from there, frankly,
so until this moment, that's how the stand begins. I believe that's a real goochier man.
I believe so.
I can't be good.
Joe, you mentioned the stand and that sets me up for a real juicy segue to tell you.
We're talking about the first four to five episodes of Castle Rock today.
I say four to five because I watched four and a half.
There's five available.
But you know, it's the new Stephen King, J .J., Stephen King influenced J .J. Abrams produced
show on Hulu.
That's what we're talking about.
That is the subject today and look we plug the live show we've bitched yeah
Why don't we why don't we go to a happy place now you talk about that's what I'm talking about well then let's
Go ahead and get on with the show
And at the same time
Get on
With a hand out and now
I don't think of these till they're coming out of my mouth.
It's hard to shoehorn a Joe in.
There's not a lot of songs that start with the O sound.
I'm going to have to start getting creative with it.
But when I listen to that collection of all of the all with the Joe's, I was like, I can't
deprive people of this.
I was making myself laugh.
I was probably because I don't remember doing some of them.
But I'm looking up who made that right now so we can give it's great.
It's a collection of it's from the very first time I did a little on with the Joe.
To like, you know, now the operatic performances that you hear each week.
Benjamin Medi. Thank you.
Benjamin Medi took literally every single on with the Joe and added it together into a super
cut and it sounds it's basically all pat like you because it's all him saying on with
the Joe it sounds like a man descending in the madness yeah like it's just what it is
it absolutely is so thank you sir for putting that together Benjamin
So what do we got at the movie corner this week?
I got a few things.
In the movie corner.
And I'm saving MI6,
because that's what we're talking about for next week's show.
Yes.
But I saw, can I just tell you real quick,
before we start, before we came over here,
I went over and had a midday pint at the Tamo Shanta.
Kitchen wasn't open, infuriating.
Why was it an open 4 p .m. No kitchen open. Why was it not open Joe? I don't know that it's just
another thing was the carving man. I was like boy. I'd really love some of that corn
beef today. I had eaten and I'd love a nice like pint of Guinness. It's on the way to
Joe's. I have an hour to kill. I go in. Yeah. Kitchen's not open. You know and no carving
man either. No carving man. That's the carving. But let me tell you she said the carving
stations open, but the carving station man never appeared. That guy's always off
doing something and blow probably. Carbon up, carbon up lines with his master card.
That's what he's carving. I saw, well, I gotta go back. I have a long list because we haven't done this
in a while, but I'm gonna start with tag.
Yes, my friend Jeff Thompson directed the film.
Okay.
But I mean, if you didn't like it, cut loose,
I'm not gonna...
No, I mean, I really root for comedies
because I don't think people even really notice this,
but we are at a time where we're getting
like two theatrically released comedies a month.
Yeah, two.
And generally, they're both bad.
Yeah, so it's dark and tag is not like, you know, a fucking diamond in the rough, but it had a certain charm to it
It reminded me a bit of game night and that they did a lot of things stylistically and with little special effects and action sequences
That really helped it rise above the pack a little bit. It's not as good as game night. The premise is just too stupid that these guys have been playing tag for years
and the depths they go to.
But I will say, in the final third of the movie,
there is an elaborate, is this real
or is this part of the tag fake out?
Because they also do a lot of fake outs, right?
With the woman's miscarriage.
She's been pregnant throughout the film
and they start saying,
do you think it's a real miscarriage
or part of the tag game or whatever?
and they do 800 jokes about miscarriages.
It's really the whole last third of the movie
is just about miscarriages
and are these people sick enough to fake a miscarriage
whatever.
And I've never heard the air go out of a theater
so fast in my entire life.
And I've got a real difficult to offend meter myself.
And from the minute the bit started,
I was like if this isn't one joke
about how sick these fucks are and then get off it.
They've made a huge mistake.
And when they tripled down on it to the extent
that they did, I just was blown away
that nobody stepped in and said, guys,
people don't think miscarriages are super hilarious.
Right, right.
Because it was not funny.
And, you know, there's also like moms there.
My mom said she saw tag and she was like,
we're kind of enjoying it.
I almost had to walk out.
Really?
It's that it's that level of kind of weird. I thought all right a real something you don't see with with the amount of notes all these things go through
Was that somebody should have given them this note? Change it to something else. Is there a part of you that it feels a sense of hope that
Something that edgy and crash got through without the notes. No, cuz it's tag at the end of the day
It's not like it's something really subversive or something. Okay. Okay, I don't know. It didn't it rub me the wrong way
movie the first two -thirds of the movie are kind of fun. I'm going to hit you with a double shot.
I watched both LBJ starring Woody Harrelson. Long blow, John. Yes. It was along the adult
story of Lyndon B. Johnson. Yeah. Lyndon B. Johnson. And then I also watched all the way with Brian
in Cranston playing Linda B. Johnston.
One was about, one was focused more on his reelection after he became president after
Kennedy died.
Yes.
Well, hold on, I'm getting to the good part.
Sorry.
I dozed off.
That was the Cranston one.
The Woody Harrelson one was more about him becoming president when Kennedy died.
Right.
Both versions of LBJ in the films were, it was like watching where the Buffalo Roman fear
and loathing.
It was like they were identical, characterizations of this guy.
Both movies contained one to two scenes of LBJ shitting with the door open in the Oval
Office, instructing his team on stuff or whatever.
The similarities were striking, but at the end of the day I found the story very riveting
to see a southern racist Democrat get put with a very liberal, northern Democrat because
of, in the interest of strategy and gaining votes, and then watching the southern racist
Democrat slowly progress and adapt and fight for the right reasons.
I thought it was a very interesting story.
Okay, and you like both movies where they're generally a film critic would compare the two or draw any parallels at all between them or
I did he had the door open shitting
All right, it was the same move and you know in both movies he's like he's like I ain't got no tits on my head
But I ain't no dumb fucking asshole either like you know, so they were just very similar moves
They were almost identical, like a bug's life and ants.
Yes.
The cramston one ends with him getting re -elected and somebody goes, LB, like, come on in,
it's your party, you know, come celebrate, and it's this slow motion shot of cramston
walking with this voice over as he's scanning all the people around him cheering for him.
And he goes, that's right, it is my fucking party.
And you mother fuckers, I'll cut my throat the first chance you get like it gets real fucking into like how dark Washington is
Yeah, the bullshit of politics, right. I just I just enjoyed both films
You know, I always love seeing Woody Harrelson playing like a sort of pecker wood guy. Sure. That's walking around
Which is rare for him is dick. Yeah
Yeah, there were usually playing kind of the smartest guy in the room
are you joking?
Yeah.
Okay.
There were identical passages of dialogue, identical monologue, it was, it was, they were
the same biography.
One was made for HBO, and the Woody Harrelson one was, I think Rob Reiner.
Rob Reiner.
My, my friend Alan Mandelbaum produced it, so I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I did not see it.
I did very much.
All right.
I mean, I'm, I hate biopics, and if they're political, I hate them even more.
but maybe I'll, maybe I'll check them out. How about that?
Pat, I don't give a shit what you do, to be honest.
I saw a little picture called first reformed,
written and directed by Paul Schrader who did, you know, the scripts for taxi driver.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that movie looks good. The UN McGregor.
Nope. Ethan Hawke. Ethan Hawke, I mean, as the priest.
It was Ethan Hawke, Amanda C. Freed, and Cedric, the entertainer, going by his actual name,
which is like Cedric, Cedric, the negotiator.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
All right.
There's a very interesting movie about religion, faith, hypocrisy, et cetera, Ethan Hawke
playing a priest who may or may not be dealing with people who are, you know, doing environmental
mental crimes, but it's just, I know that sounds insane, but it's a movie about like the
hypocrisy of religious people basically at the end of the day.
Environmental.
And how they act like they're, you know, doing the right thing, but also supporting companies
that destroy the environment is where it starts to go to.
It starts to feel a little like a conspiracy nut wrote it because I think Paul Schrader
is conspires on it. But it's a very interesting movie and like pretty crazy which I really
enjoyed about it. There's a lot of like really weird shit in it and I liked it quite a bit.
I recommend it. I watched it all the HBO made for HBO film called conspiracy
see. Starring Stanley Tuchy. Tuch. What's his face? The King's speech. You know, the guy
from the King's speech. Well, tell me who it is. I don't remember his name. Colin Firth. Colin
Firth. Say his name. I couldn't remember his name. He couldn't say his name either in that
film. And then a can of murdering.
He was a brown problem. Kenneth Brown. All right. As not to hide. Oh, I remember seeing
the box for this movie at the video store. Well, it's called conspiracy and it's about
this secret meeting that a bunch of Nazis had in this house somewhere in wherever the fuck
it was. You shouldn't get to use the title conspiracy on a Nazi movie. Well, conspiracy is
too general and it should have something to do with Nazis. I thought because it was
There's a bunch of Nazis, the beginning, there's a text scroll that says, there's one record
of this meeting.
Everything else was destroyed.
It's a fabled meeting, but it did happen in this film is based on the one record or whatever.
So I'm like, oh, this is going to be about how like there's some like spy got in and infiltrated
the Nazis.
Like Val Carie.
Yeah.
Tommy Cruz.
Good picture.
But it wasn't.
They were just all Nazis having a meeting.
And the meeting was about, and I never knew this, which is, which is what I found interesting
about the film.
It was a piece of information I didn't know about history.
It was them Kenneth Brano plays the guy that proposes the plan to exterminate Jewish people.
They're kind of already doing it secretly, but he's the guy that comes in and says, we're
going to do this gas chamber thing, and they, they, you know, it's the debate in the meeting.
I never knew it happened like that.
I always thought it was like Hitler just said, we're doing this and everything's just like
like, okay, but at the end of the day, they did it.
That's usually the kind of guy Hitler was.
Yeah, yeah.
So there's really no hope in the film.
It's bad guys talking to bad guys.
The bad guys do what they say they're going to do because you know, and the craziest part
is one of the guys in that meeting ended up almost everybody they do the little blurb
at the end, like two years, two months later he died, he was shot or whatever. This guy
died in jail. This guy was convicted of war crimes. Justice has pretty much served everybody
except there's one guy where they're like, he later contribute to the American University
of Quebec. He just came over here and worked at a college. And I tried looking up like more
more info on that. And there's very little out there. Like this fucking guy. How the
fuck does that work out? You're in the goddamn, the, the, the most, uh, uh, infamous
Nazi meeting of all time. And you're part of the crew. And you get to go teach it a fucking
college or something. I thought that was crazy. And same fair to me. Anyway, it's a good
film, uh, good actors, but it's not a pick me up. What now, as I always ask, what brought
inspired you to watch conspiracy.
I had finished all the way,
which was my second LBJ movie of that day.
And they said you might also enjoy this.
No, I was just flipping through the HBO movies.
I saw the touches face.
It said conspiracy.
This was a three movie day for you.
Yeah, I said, I've never seen this.
I'm going to watch it.
So I watched it.
All right.
Real slow burn that one.
Yeah.
Anyway, I'm not going to watch that.
I watched on Netflix, although it was made for theaters and eventually not released.
Conspiracy, excuse me, not conspiracy, is it legend of a white tail deer hunter?
You just said conspiracy.
That's what made me say that.
Did you talk about this or any?
Huh?
Didn't we talk about this in one of the other episodes?
not on the show. Okay. Sorry. Legacy of a white tail deer hunter directed by Jody Hill
starring Josh Brolin and Danny McBride. It was very excited to watch it. Jody Hill, you
know, was a big force behind Eastbound and down. As is Danny McBride. Just a movie that
just didn't work. You can totally see how even with a town involved, it wasn't released.
There's nothing getting you from A to B. You just kind of don't care.
And it's just kind of one of those guys trying to connect with his son movies.
They pitched it as like a new bad news bears or paper moon like one of those 70s character studies.
Right.
When I read up on it, but it doesn't feel like that at all.
And then at some point somebody must have said you got to insert a little edgy humor in here.
There's nothing happening in this movie so at some point Danny McBride starts showing the little boy that he is
On this journey with
photographs of his
Girlfriend being gang banged
Okay, Polaroids and a movie that's been like a light PG to this point
So I'm just I'm sounded like a prude this week, but I'm just there's just like wild tonal shifts in
in these movies that do not work.
And I'm a guy who likes tonal shifts.
You are.
I've always said that about you.
I have that t -shirt.
I'm a guy who likes tonal shifts.
But yeah, just kind of a lackluster picture.
And I do wanna say that I saw Josh Brolin
at the Weezer and Pixie's show the other day.
Okay.
And that was kind of cool.
That's cool.
That's it.
It's a great story.
And the Weezer and Pixie show was fantastic.
Good. I'm glad to hear it.
Yeah, I'm glad to hear it. Did Weezer pull out some of the old stuff?
They played all their hits which were awesome.
And then enough time has passed from like some of their shitty albums that
you remember that the hits from those albums are actually pretty awesome too.
Like if you're wondering if I want you to I want you to from the Red Album or whatever it was that a
Ratitude I think that's from which is their worst right, but that song's great. It sounds like cheap trick
Then they have they played Africa
That's a great cover they do with weird. Oh, yeah, I can pick on backup vocals and our my accordion really that was awesome. That's pretty cool
but
They got some good songs pork and beans from the Red Album is a very catchy song
there's a few songs from Malibu, 10 minutes long or whatever, that's burnt jam, I think.
I mean, they're fun. They're, they're not what they once were, but they put on a great,
almost a kid -friendly kind of show. Would they open with Buddy Holly in the outfits, in the,
real, in the video, basically, they had the same set. And they're, and they're doing set changes and
out for changes. Yeah, it's like a pop show. Wow. But they're, I mean, they were
right. I can't, his voice sounds awesome. He's still one of the best rock voices there
is. Great. And I had a good time. And the pixies are maybe my favorite live band. I just,
I mean, part of it that I love those albums so much. But they're so good. And the songs
they pick from their new ones are very carefully chosen to like showcase songs that you forget
about. Like, both times, the one they played that Magdalena song, when you and I saw them,
that I know is your favorite. And I got super into it right after. This one I had another song
where I was like, yeah, I forget they're still making good music. You just don't listen to them a
thousand times like their other four. Okay. They're good. Slaybells opened it up and they're good.
It was a fun night of fun. And then Pixies. Yeah. How were the Pixies?
So I just talked to you about the Pixies for upwards of 90 seconds.
No, then I was just now while you were on your phone, I was talking about the Pixies.
I was tuned out. I'm sorry, not out of offense to you.
I just trying to see what movie I needed to go to next.
Ice go ahead. I'll save my concert for the next episode.
Oh, all right. I went to a concert too.
Okay.
But I'm going to save it. I'll close this out with I'll give you the same laser focus when you talk about that concert that you just gave me I'm sorry
I needed to see what movie you go rub one out in the bathroom while you're telling that story. I'll close treat you with the same level of respect. I love you
And I respect you. I just don't always respect. I love you.
six. Uh, I'll close the segment out with Borg versus Macon row. Oh, boy, starring
Shyla Buff on Hula right now. Yeah. Yeah. What do you say? Oh, boy, you didn't think
that looked good. No. Why? Was it good? It's a typical biopic. It's a little paint by
numbers, but Shyla Buff delivers a powerhouse performance. He's awesome in it. All right.
He captures Macon row. He's great. The do you see battle of the sexes? No.
Now, they just look at the exact same movie and I was very bored, but battle of the sex.
Well, it is except this is about two men, right.
And one of them screams, why don't you shut the fuck up at the audience and referee the
entire right?
So it's fun to watch.
Okay.
You know, he's got, you know, you got, you got opponents coming over to Mac and Rob being
like, why don't you calm down, man, just relax and he's like, why don't you shut the fuck
up.
You know, I'm like, I'm, he goes, nobody's talking to you and the guy's like, I'm talking to you. He's like, I'm not talking to you. So shut the fuck up.
But it's just, he's fun to watch. Go off like that. All right.
But the movie's more about Borg than it is, Mack and Rowe.
But it was an enjoyable film. The performances were all great. Your, your boy, Stellen Scars guard is in there.
My boy, which connects us to today's show because his son is in this castle rock TV show.
So I can't remember the guy who played Borg, I've never heard of him.
And I was an enjoyable piece of work, anyway.
How about some deadlines from the screaming end?
Do you have any?
I have one.
All right.
Susperia, the remake.
Trailer looks awesome.
Great trailer.
Love the trailer.
Got the runtime on this thing.
it was released. Two hours, 30 minutes. I'm on board. You're on board? The original is 96 minutes.
Yeah, I think it's going to be a different movie. You always bitch about how long movies are.
But something like that, I'm going to get high, I'm going to have a beautiful time.
All right. Neon Demon was long. When it's that kind of movie, I'm with you. I'll ride with it.
All right, what I hated is when it's superheroes punching each other for two and a half hours doesn't need to be all right
Tarantino cried when he saw the news a spirit and I don't know why I know that but I saw it online somewhere
I read that too online and that's to be taken with a grain of salt
Tarantino also swears psycho two was better than psycho one. That's right
So, you know, that could mean it's great. That could also mean it's Tarantino being Tarantino. Yeah
Yeah, I think the run time is a little absurd.
I think adding an hour to a film is a questionable move.
Sure.
It's a questionable move.
And it doesn't seem like they're just doing their own thing
with it, like it's not a slavish remake of Susperia.
I mean, then why the fuck remakes Susperia?
Why don't you just make a different movie?
Because the only thing they make is remakes.
Yes, it's the call me by your name, dude, yes, it is.
And tell the Swins, I don't know his name, no, it's till the Swinton.
It's till the Swinton, yeah, directed this, no, isn't told the Swinton in it.
Yes, tell the Swins, this is crazy, tell the Swins stars in it and tell the Swinton
directly.
We on blow or something.
No, what did you say?
The guy's name was, I think you were making a joke about his name.
No, his name's like 18 syllables.
And I couldn't tell you like Luca Guadalupe or something.
I think his name is Luca Guadalupe.
I thought you were saying his name was till their
twins. No, I think till the twins.
And then you said, tell the sweat.
I think you mean it until the swim is in the movie.
Tell the sweat is in it.
Once again, playing some weird ghostly, weird bird lady.
Yeah, I can't tell people are good or whatever.
Yeah, I don't know. Look, here's my fear that it's going to be another Blade Runner 20 49
and another one of the and and Neon demon and drive and another one of these music video music video
directors where I'm going to masturbate with imagery. Why can't that be a movie? It can be. It
doesn't mean that's going to be a good movie means it's a movie you're not going to like.
I think, look, I'm not crazy about the original Suspiria, and I know that's probably sacrilegial
to a lot of people, but those are Argento movies.
They're fun to watch, I guess, but they have all the qualities of these other movies I'm
talking about, where it's a lot of pretty images, but it doesn't make a whole hell of a lot
of sense.
So now this guy's saying, I'm remaking that movie, and I'm adding another hour to it, which
to me sounds like, oh, I'm going to go stroke my artistic dick all over this thing.
Hey.
Maybe I'll join them on that stroke.
All right, well, we'll see.
We'll see.
Where's it come out?
Halloween?
I don't know.
Halloween night?
All Hallows Eve?
Is that Halloween night?
All Hallows Eve Eve?
Or is that the night before?
All Hallows Eve, I believe, is Halloween.
Okay.
The Eve of the New Hollow.
And then all Saints day is the next day.
Yes.
And the Catholic Church, that's what it's called.
I used to play soccer for the all -sense spirits, as you...
I used to sell all...
May well, no.
I used to sell all -state insurance.
Really?
I used to sell state farm insurance.
I worked on a farm in the state of Pennsylvania.
Folks.
It all comes together.
Let's take another trip over to a little town in Maine.
I'm gonna get a beer.
Why don't you set us up?
that I call Castle Rock lightning crash, lightning crash.
Crow. Crow falls dead into my lap.
Castle Rock is the new show on Hulu. There's been five episodes.
it's Stars, Scott Glenn, Sissy Spasek. It's Stars and one of the guys from
Moonlight, I should know his name, Melanie Linsky, and Bill Scarsgard, Pennywise
the Clown. It is set in a world of Stephen King in the same way the Fargo series
is set in a world of the Cohen brothers and it is basically a drama. You know, it was marketed
to me as horror, but thus far it appears to be a glacial -paced drama. I'm curious to hear what
you have to say, Joe, but I've seen almost as much as you. We're going to talk about the first five,
so spoilers beware. What do you think? The show opens with the head of Shawshank prison
committing suicide played by Terry O 'Quinn, the stepfather. Yes. So it's it's on lock.
There are definitely horror elements. There's some weird shit going on. He's got this boy
locked in a cage in the basement of Shawshank. He says that the boy is the devil. It's
Certainly not Stephen Kingharrer in the sense of,
it's, you know, I put it up,
I'd say it's the same type of horror
as like the shining or something.
There's an eerie sort of psychological burn
that's happening.
I like the Easter eggs.
You had said that you didn't see any Easter eggs.
Nothing, and the first couple,
I mean, the few obvious ones I caught,
and then more and more I was catching them.
But they don't add anything to it. I think at some point, scars guard will be revealed
to be Pennywise's brother or something. They'll do some big reveal where it shows you
they're actually related to someone in the Stephen King of Earth. I think he's going to
be the man in black. Well, that would be a big swing that would miss me because I hadn't
read those books. Well, but the man in black is the bad guy in the stand. Oh, the stand,
Yes, but isn't they also in the dark tower and stuff? It's the dark tower. Yeah, those I haven't read Stephen King stories
Yeah, essentially in the stand he is the devil basically. Okay, but he's also in the story the man the black suit
Yeah, which is very scary Stephen King story right then
Um, I like the show. I thought it was a little cheeky having Bill Skars guard in there
Um, especially when he's playing pen because not especially because he's playing Pennywise and it
Yeah, that's a little distracting, but he's very good.
Did you feel the same with space I can carry or not?
No, because carry isn't, carry is 40 years ago.
Right.
It is about to have a sequel in the theater.
Yeah, in 12 months or whatever.
Yeah.
I just thought it was a little too immediately on the nose.
Sure.
It was kind of like how it put the kid from stranger things in it.
Right.
And it's a two, it just shapes too close.
But he is very good and at the cast is great.
They all do a stellar job.
I think the show is, I would say,
expertly written and or edited or both.
But I have never seen a show get so much information across,
so efficiently.
Oh, it's, they waste no time with,
they show so much through action and they cut to something
and then you realize, oh, this is the outcome
of what that conversation must have been.
But you don't see the conversation. I think that's great. You know, I think it's great. Like there's not a really a lot of
Exposition in the show. It is a slow burner, but I like it. A lot of Stephen King is a slow burner.
Sure, I just the guy, by the way, Henry Deaver, the lead guy, is
Andre Holland. I felt bad not knowing all these great. I
Thought all of the actors across the board are fairly dull
I thought the storytelling was fairly dull.
I thought the story was fairly dull.
I thought the way it was shot was fairly dull.
I found the whole thing fairly dull, frankly.
I was bored by it.
There'd be something now and then the end of episode four,
where the guard at the prison there
is shooting everyone up on security cam
and they should be getting all those angles.
It was a very effective sequence, I think,
only because they use the Roy Orbs song crying, which is a fantastic song. But that's the only time
I ever really was like, oh, something's happening here. The rest of the time I thought,
can we get to it? Well, you know, like, I didn't really give a shit about anyone in it.
It's not holding my interest. I don't know why it needed to be tied into the Stephen King
Iverse. Maybe that'll be revealed. But it doesn't even feel like Stephen King to me. It didn't even
feel like a good mimicry. It just didn't have the same vibe to me at all, which I was surprised by.
Because I thought the Fargo TV showed it's such a great job of capturing the Columbus vibe,
but doing their own thing and also telling you store a great story that existed on its own,
even if you didn't know the rest of the stuff. This feels like I don't care enough about the Easter
eggs and the Stephen King thing, and I'm a big Stephen King fan, but I also don't care enough about
the story. You don't care to figure out why the little girl kills his dad. You don't
care to figure out why the town thinks he murdered his father, why he doesn't seem
particularly sad that his father died, why he's so mad at the step, not step -dead, but
the mom's boyfriend now and that's the guy that literally saved him when he goes to the
house that he was kept at. You didn't find any of that shit interesting?
You're just watching these five episodes knowing that I guess in 10 these these questions will be answered, but there's no sense of laying out the clues or the storytelling of that like I don't feel like I'm on the journey with them trying to piece this together
I feel like I'm just watching what's being thrown up in front of me.
All right, I'm not I'm not involved in it in any way, and I don't care. So like they'll they'll say this thing is unknown and then five episodes later
It's still unknown and you've made no progress answering the mystery. I just
I don't know it's not
absorbing me in the way that
These types of shows can and the way I thought the show would I had really high hopes for it and I've just been
bored
All right, then again, if they're planning on bringing in, you know, whether it's Penny
Wise or whoever from the Stephen King world into this show, I'm going to have to get
back into it.
Well, here's why I like it.
I like the one thing I will thank Marvel for in what they've done, even though it's been
overkill.
I like the door Marvel opened with entertainment.
I like the fact now that they are taking brands, very large brands that have a big universe
and telling different storylines within that universe.
I like now that there's a Stephen King TV show that isn't the same story as the stories
that happen in that town in the movies.
And it's the way comic books work, you know, you have Batman, and then you have Batman
and Robin, and then you have the detective comics and the dark night, and they're all different
storylines.
And I think that's very, very cool.
they're doing it with Star Wars. They're about to come out of the Star Wars live action show.
I think it's very, very interesting. I do think it feels like, I mean, look, it's hard to say
doesn't feel like Stephen King or not. Stephen King doesn't make his movies. He's occasionally written
some of them, right? But it's always a different story. They never let him after. Max, I'm overdrive.
Did he direct that one? It's the one time that I'm directing. He was coked out of his mind.
never offered a toe again.
So let me get this straight,
but you want to make a movie about trucks that come to life?
Yeah, trucks with psychic powers.
Yeah. All right.
Here's two million.
Yeah. The, uh, the, um, it's hard to say.
Does it feel like or not feel like Stephen King?
Cause it's, that's all a matter of opinion.
Everybody's going to interpret his books the way they interpret them as they read
them. Um, and his movies have always been made by different groups of people.
No, no one group of people have ever made this a few Stephen King movie. I think so
But there's something about like a misery or even a Dolores Clayborne, which I think is a very underrated movie
where they just get
The feeling of his books across so well like misery feels exactly like living in that book down to like the smallest detail
But this castle rock to me. There's just no
I don't know. I don't have that feeling. It's like when you see a Tim Burton movie, you know,
you're watching a Tim Burton movie. I'm watching this, and I'm not feeling that Stephen King
feeling. I feel it much more in a strange way, which is a homage, but I just don't see why this had
to be a Stephen King thing. It's weird to me. Well, I don't know. I have faith that it's sort of being
a slow build. I like the idea that Stephen King has written a million stories about this town,
from Castle Rock, where all these hard things have happened.
So we're gonna do a show that gets into the minutiae of all of it.
Like why are these things happening here?
I think that's a cool idea.
I think they're also, if they had come out of the,
I think it's gonna be like Gotham,
which you know I'm a huge fan of,
for the first season of Gotham,
it was like Penguin and Fish Mooney,
who was a character they made up,
that Jay to Pinkett Smith played.
And you could have said the same thing.
And you're like, why is this called Gotham?
Just so they could call this guy Penguin
and he'd hate's being called Penguin.
But then you realize, oh, they're dealing it out
little by little because it's eventually gonna become
the fully realized universe,
which is what the last season of Gotham was.
I think they'll do that with this.
I think they also realize though, too,
if we come right out of the gate where they're like,
you know, my name's Jack Torrance,
I work at Shawshank Prison.
I saw a clown last night, you know, it's too much all at once.
I did like the Jack Torrance Easter egg.
I thought that was very cool.
I thought...
You mean the character named Jackie Torrance?
Well, yeah, but later she says, I hate this town.
Nothing interesting ever happens.
She goes, I'll tell you a story.
My uncle was a normal guy and then one day he decided he was going to hack his wife and
his kid to pieces.
And then he killed himself and my parents won't even talk about it.
I thought that was interesting.
I thought, I like little stuff like that.
So I don't know.
I think it's going to go on the way Gotham went.
We shall see.
We shall.
Here's my question.
Why not throw $100 million at Stephen King and say we're going to do 10, 10 episodes seasons
where every episode is one of his short stories, different writer, different director?
Why not do that?
You mean you mean a logical thing? Yeah, no, that's why they don't do it. Like, you know, like it would be the new twilight zone
He's got a hundred perfect horror short stories. Yeah, you hire a different writer and director for each
Yep, that is a show that goes a hundred episodes no questions asked and makes on their money back time and time again. Yep
Yeah, they because it makes sense. That's why they're not doing these people are fucking idiots
Yeah, I hope I didn't just give somebody the idea and they get rich off it. Well, we copyrighted it here TM
I mean, it's it's just you know, it's it's why don't they you know why the fuck didn't they put
De Niro and Pacino in a movie together until righteous kill or I know they weren't heat together, but you know what I mean right you know
Why why did you know I prefer righteous kill and I know a lot of people don't agree, but for me
I felt heat was missing
50 cent in a key supporting role.
Yeah. Why is, uh, why is Creep Show just now finally coming back?
Thank you, Shutter, by the way, Shutter's bringing Creep Show back.
But what is a weekly thing?
Yeah, it's like a tale from the Creep Show show.
But it's like, why the fuck, you know, that's, that's, that's been talked
about for 10 years.
Right. Why did it take this long?
Why does everybody make all this so fucking hard?
I don't know. It's rich. Don't get me started. Anyway, Pat. Yeah.
Any plugs, buddy. Not really cool kids coming to Fox September 28th. It's going to be a
really funny show. Check it out. Martin Moll. Martin Moll, Vicki Lawrence, David Allen
Greer, Leslie Jordan, created and produced by the great Charlie Day. And I'm on Twitter
Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe DeRose a comedy on Instagram.
And, uh, when do I got coming up?
This will come up, uh, I mean, Washington, at the end of this month, DC.
No, I mean,
when this comes out, I will already have been to DC.
Um, um, let's see here.
What do we got here, folks?
No, I'm in Washington state.
at the end of the day.
It will be in Denzel Washington.
Recording.
I'm performing at the Campbell's Resort Lake.
Now, that's a lake made out of soup, correct?
It is.
It's a soup lake.
And the nice part is, it's different types of soups.
I don't know how they do it, but every three feet
the soup flavor changes.
As you go deeper, the flavor changes
or if you go out further into the lake.
Now, just as you walk along it,
you can say, let's go to the tomato part.
sounds great. Campbell's Resort Lake in Chilan, Washington,
Chelan, Washington, Kellen. I don't know how to say that, but
great plug. Anyway, I'll be there. So coming out and say,
hello, if you want. And again, I'll be the Red Clay Festival
in Atlanta. Now, that's a festival where you and the ghost of
Patrick Swayze sort of make a red clay pop together.
Exactly. Right. Exactly. And all interpretations of that
scene. Right. And at some point, it's pretty clear that the clay being molded is representative
of Swayze's dick. Yeah. It's 55 performers doing their take on that scene. Right. I'm doing
the naked gun style one hilarious where the clay flies all over the room. Right. You'll see. All right.
Anyway, Red Clay Flesival in Atlanta 28th to 30th, and that's our show, folks.
We'll see you next time, and we'll see you in hell!
No, no, no, no!