Welcome to We'll See You in Hell, the podcast you go to.
When you need to know what's going on in the world of genre
films, be it your sci -fi, your horror, your fantasy, sometimes
your drama, drama, comedy.
I'm Joe DeRosa as always here with Patrick Walsh.
Hello everybody.
How are you?
I'm in New York City, New York City.
Yes, but can't yourself where Joe now lives came out here
doing a little Valentine's weekend with the Mrs.
Joe and I are stockpiling.
I don't like when you call me the Mrs.
Joe and I are stockpiling some EPS.
I'm going to see David Byrne of the Talking Heads this evening
is Broadway show, which I'm excited about.
I hear the show is incredible.
I hear the same.
I hear it's like stop making sense too.
And I it's one of my favorite things ever.
So I can't wait to see it.
Speaking of Byrne, I'm going to light a cigarette.
You told me it gives you heartburn when I smoke.
The only thing that gives me heartburn is somebody else smoking.
I don't know what it is.
Are you getting it now?
I got it.
Yes.
I always forget it because I'm rarely around smokers.
I live in Los Angeles.
So this is going to bother you if you crack a window.
It's fine.
It's cracked.
No.
Well, go ahead if you need it.
Asking permission in my own house where my children
sleep.
Now, Joe, I see the Faith No More poster.
Are you I assume you're a fan of Mr.
Bungle.
Did you know they played like three four nights in LA?
Yeah, they played here too.
And I was offered a free ticket by my dear friend tall.
And I didn't accept because it was my first and it was my
first night back from Vegas.
And it was my only night off the whole week and I had a busy
week this week of shows and daytime radio and podcasts and
all this stuff.
And I had to get it two different rewrites finished.
And I said, buddy, I really appreciate it, but I just can't
do it now had it been bungle doing like a set from the
consistent of stuff from their albums.
I would have probably gone.
What was the set?
They were doing their very first EP that was never really
released.
Any piece for songs?
Well, they did a bunch of cover songs, too.
Okay, so it was mainly them doing like a thrash metal show
was Patton there.
Yeah.
And Scott Ian.
Scott Ian was filling in like Lombardo and Scott Ian were
not in the band, but it was Patton, Trevor Dunn, the
original bass player and Trey Spruance, the original guitar
player.
Okay.
But I was just like, you know, at this point, it's like I
don't I would like to see this, but I'm not dying to see
Mr. Bungle play a bunch of thrash metal songs.
I'm not familiar with right on a night where I desperately
need to rest.
Yeah for the week and I'm glad that I did stay in.
I don't regret it, but but I love Mr. Bungle, but Faith
the more is very close to my heart.
They just announced they're doing a European tour, which
probably means they will I'm assuming will hit the States
after which hopefully also means that a new record is
coming.
Okay.
Even more and this constant.
Something in your apartment.
It's always something with your apartments.
Okay.
Yeah, I know right.
It's the radiator.
This this city makes a lot of noise.
It does.
You know what?
I say that by the way, I would never sleep with that.
I would have to I get a white noise machine.
I have a white noise app on my computer here.
I play it.
You think that's bad.
You should hear the women screaming in the street at two
o 'clock in the morning.
Not in not in danger.
Just coming out of the bars and for some reason.
I don't mean this in a sexist way, but there's something
about women in their 20s when they're drunk.
The only way they can communicate is by screaming at
the top of their lungs.
Right.
I don't understand every night.
There's a girl just literally being like like it's the
opening of like a fucking skid Row concert.
I'm like, you know who you are.
Yeah.
So the white noise blocks it all out though.
Sure do.
And speaking of music and bands and things I said on
the other episode this month that I was going to talk
about something stones rolling stones related in the
movie corner.
It is movie movie related and when we get to it, I
promise I will do it today.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm excited to talk about it.
And speaking of great music.
I was asked by my friend Mielle who used to do this
podcast with.
Demi they both have names that are more that are
tricky his last name.
I'm not going to attempt because he's a friend of
mine and it would be rude walkie -kie his last name
is is African.
You know, it's a it's a it's a difficult to pronounce
name.
Okay, but the two of them are just absolute delights
extremely talented.
They're the only friends I made off of the vine app
because I was just like you guys are really smart
and funny and they were very young too, which is
crazy.
They're like 20.
Wait, I know though.
Oh, yeah, I know.
I'm sorry about okay.
Sorry blanked.
Anyway, they did a podcast together and much like
you and I they went their separate ways.
But when they went their separate ways meal took
the podcast over they didn't keep trying to keep
the charade alive like you and I are doing this
marriage is a farce at this point.
But we're kidding everybody before you go to the
Facebook group work and say we're sad because Pat
and Joe don't love each other.
We love each other by the way, I deleted my Facebook.
So you won't find me on there anymore.
You deleted your Facebook long time coming.
All right.
But anyway, me all now does it.
It's called punch up the jam and basically you
discuss and go through line by line sort of a guilty
pleasure type song that you love that maybe others
may not and then at the end she rewrites the song
and makes it better.
And these are incredible like recreations of songs.
You know, some are like weird L type parodies.
Some are a little deeper than that, you know, but
just a really cool podcast.
I recommend it highly.
Okay, I'm going to be on it soon.
And what am I doing?
Hey jealousy by the gin Blossoms.
Oh boy.
They showed me this bit.
The worst thing you can say to me is like pick a
song that you want to discuss because I'll spend
days like thinking about it.
But I opened up the Excel sheet.
I did a quick scroll through like 800 titles and
the page I landed on contained a jealousy and I
was like done.
I thought they sent me a sheet of song you pick.
Okay, I see.
I see.
But anyway, that should probably out in a couple
of months and it's it really is I have been
brushing up on it to get ready and it's it's a
great podcast.
Check it out.
That's punch up the jam.
That's great.
Yeah.
Check out.
Well, I'll plug a podcast.
Please do my buddy Adam.
For are a very funny comic great actor.
You may know him from nurse Jackie or rescue me.
A good buddy.
Yeah, I just did his podcast and it's called 30
minutes.
I'll never get back.
And we had a blast.
We had a blast.
We had a very deep conversation about both his
father and my mother going through cancer and we
laughed our balls off and but also had some really
nice emotional discussion too.
It was a really nice time.
So Adam's a great guy.
It's a new podcast.
Check it.
I sent some great guests on there too.
Jay Leno won like two weeks ago or so.
Wow.
So he's he's he's off to a good start.
I thought he said great guests.
Oh, come on folks.
Come on.
Fuck Jalen.
Oh, come on.
But don't fuck your friend who sounds great.
And I'm sure it's a great podcast and it's a good
guest.
Don't get me wrong.
I like Jay Leno.
All right.
I never had a sure right.
You know, we never touched the tonight show money.
So he says he just lives off of touring money.
I mean, he got criticized so much for that show
compared to what is on now shows a goddamn honestly
masterpiece.
I hate I hated.
I hate everything he's ever done, but and him
fucking over Cohen repeatedly.
But like you're absolutely right compared to
Gordon Fallon, whatever fine.
Oh boy.
Do what you got to do anyway.
Yeah, we know people on all those shows.
I actually look if I depict I shouldn't say
anything.
I need to probably do late night spots on all
these shows.
But yes, you do.
But I just mean the page around puts another
level up at least a protection because I feel
like James Corden's not paying that whatever a
month I at least feel like I could kick it with
Fallon.
Like I feel like we could hang and have fun.
Definitely on cocaine a lot of the time.
So you could party allegedly.
Well, not allegedly is as massive drinking.
But anyway, but I don't feel like I could hang
with Corden.
Right.
You know, I don't feel like I'd get much out of
that.
Right.
All right.
Anyway, that's you know, that's that I got it.
I got a quick scary stuff.
Ladies and gentlemen, I don't know if you've
seen this yet.
And if you haven't, I urge you to buy it because
the price on this thing is insane for what you're
getting.
There is a new okay.
So for years, I knew the Godzilla films, you
know, the original films.
Yes, you'd see them here and there.
And then you I'd say, you know what?
I bet these things would look awesome on Blu -ray
and you couldn't find it like you'd find, you
know, the original one was a criteria is a
criterion.
But it was really hard to find Godzilla movies
on Blu -ray.
And if you did find them, it was one of them or
maybe two of them together, whatever.
But there was never a set.
I was like, there should be a set.
They've released a set of the Toho or Zitojo
Toho, Toho, right?
I don't know, but I bought the set to the
criterion set.
This new set in the big pink.
Yeah, and yellow like what bought it.
I'll probably won't open it for years, but I
love it.
It looks great in my collection.
It's an amazing set.
And it's the it's like the first like 15
original Godzilla movies.
It's like a hundred bucks on Amazon.
It's crazy.
If you already own the Godzilla criteria and
do what I did make 30 bucks selling it, you're
almost halfway to the price.
So for scary stuff, I would say this is
something we both highly recommend.
Yes for your collection.
It's I just again, I can't get over the price
of this thing.
Yeah, sometimes you get these deals like, you
know that that criterion set of old what's his
face Berg Bergman.
Yeah, I got that thing for I think was $120
and it's Sam every Bergman movie ever on
Blu -ray on Blu -ray when I did the math.
It was like three bucks a piece.
It's crazy.
Yeah, and it makes you look smart even if you
never watch any of them.
Yeah.
It makes I have mine prominently displayed on
top of my DVD chest underneath the TV.
Yeah.
So when you know, preferably a feminine someone
of the feminine persuasion comes over she goes,
oh, you're into Bergman.
I only date women that were characters on
Happy Days.
I forget I never or Woody Allen movie.
I thought you were going to go with I was talking
with my analyst about the new Bergman.
Yeah, I had two encounters with my two least
favorite people in Los Angeles.
Number one, the old dude at the post office who
I finally wrote a complaint about.
I think I told you he was the one who's like,
oh, so you didn't see the sign and he's always
playing these power trips with people.
He'll make you go stand back in line if you
come over too soon.
Like he's just sick.
It's a lot.
It's soup Nazi ask is what it is and I saw him
make a girl cry this week and he wouldn't let
up and he was like basically she said one
sentence and he goes, well, you wouldn't have
a problem if you packaged what you wanted to
mail before you come to the counter.
He's screaming unhinged at her.
She goes, sir, I didn't know I was supposed to
do that and he goes, get out of line.
Get out of line.
Next one goes up and she goes, I'd actually
like to speak to someone else, please.
I totally got why she did it.
Sure.
And he goes, well, you got me.
So you get me or you or you leave the store.
Okay.
So he's clearly all amped up.
Here we go.
She goes, sir, I just like these.
What's it going to be?
And she goes, don't talk to me like that.
And before you know it, this post office is
jumping.
People are stepping in.
Hey, you can't talk to her like that.
Blah, blah, blah.
Finally, she leaves in a huff and he goes next,
is me.
So I really don't want to go up to this guy.
I hate him.
The last time we had an encounter.
I said, you know what?
I'm going to go over to the self checkout and
he goes, okay.
So I didn't think this was going to go.
Well, I go up there.
My hands are shaking.
That's how much I let this fucker get to me,
but I slide the thing over and he goes,
so, uh, flips it up.
He doesn't know what's in it.
Does a flip in the air like it's a pizza pie.
So it's on the back and I've round this thing
tight.
He's on everybody.
These past two girls.
He was mad because they hadn't put the thing in
the envelope before they got to him.
My thing is completely packaged and ready to go
and I hand it to him and he goes, so, uh,
I'm going to put this through.
I look at him like, uh -huh.
It's a package.
Yeah.
And he goes, but, uh, for future reference,
we don't like duct tape.
Okay.
So hard stance to take.
So I don't say anything because I'm like, he's
waiting for me to get in a fight with him.
I'm the third, fourth person in a row.
He's gotten in a fight with so I kind of nod my
head and he goes, you use this tape and he takes
out some kind of tape that no one has in their
home and wraps it covering up my duct tape and
he's taking so much time to wrap over my duct
tape with this stuff and I'm standing there
looking at him and he goes, so nothing to say
about that.
Oh, and I said, sir, what are you?
I go, sir, what is your problem?
Right.
And he goes, what do you mean?
And I said, I brought so many packages in here
wrapped in anything, right?
Whatever I have in the house.
Right.
And no one has ever said a word to me.
There's no way that you guys have a problem
with duct tape.
There's another guy there who's always very nice
and I look over at him and he chuckles as if
to say we don't.
Right.
So I knew I kind of had, you know, he kind of
had my back.
He goes, do you want me to go ahead and process
it then or what?
Because I'm trying to help you out.
I'm actually rewrapping it using tape that you
did not pay for to rewrap the box.
I go, you can do whatever you want to it, but
I'm just saying I don't believe you have some
big problem with duct tape, post office, or
you'd have a sign up or something.
Sure.
How would anyone know that?
He wraps it up.
He sends it, puts the stamp on it.
And I realized I told him media mail, which
would make the thing three dollars to send.
He did it for, you know, first priority or
whatever.
And it's like 17 bucks.
And I said, sir, I was very clear that I
wanted media mail.
I'm sorry.
I wanted media mail, huge eye roll.
He puts it through and I said, thank you.
And I start to leave and he goes, hold up,
hold up, hold up.
He goes, come back here.
Come back here.
Come back.
He circles a barcode on the receipt, slides it
over to me and he goes, that's a survey.
So you can go ahead and tell whoever you want
what you think about me.
Whoo.
Well, I like that move.
I said, I'm happy to do it, sir.
Thank you.
It's like, is this guy just, I mean, he's 55.
He must just be like, I don't want my pension.
Fuck all of you.
I want to get fired.
He's despicable.
I'll say this as a customer.
Yeah, with that guy.
Awful.
If I'm working in the post office, I want him
there, but that's the highlight.
I'm just saying no, no, no.
I get it.
I say that's the highlight of your day is you
get to sit there and watch this.
Cause your post office probably isn't a real
electrifying job.
True.
You get to sit there and watch this guy freak out
all day.
It's probably pretty entertaining.
I completely get him given a little guff to a girl
walking up.
And I mean, this girl had her items to ship in one
pile and a bunch of envelopes in the other.
She was kind of dumb, but like he made her cry.
And then the next girl he's like, I'm still mad.
So I'm going to treat everybody like shit.
It was, it's, it's appalling.
Like they're, they're government employees.
So then of course I hit a guy I know you're
familiar with a guy who actually looks a lot like
this guy, our friend over at amoeba.
Oh boy.
The guy who shook his head and discussed when you
brought in your big hall of purchases.
So I come in and I know I've got a lot of quality
stuff.
Cause I, I usually am just trying to peddle some
old DVDs or something.
And I know they're not going to take them, but I
had some really good stuff.
So I walk over and the main reason I went is they
had this criteria and blue ray.
And last time it was in a glass case upstairs and
it was $350 out of print blue ray.
And mine is new sealed and mint condition.
This was used 350 less circle Rouge.
Okay.
So I stroll in because they won't let you resell
criteria on Amazon.
One of their many quirks.
So I go in, I'm like, hi, how are you being overly
polite talking to him through it?
And I got all kinds of stuff.
He goes, all right, I'll call you up.
I am now planning to walk back to the rock section,
which as you know, is roughly a hundred yards
away before I've gotten there.
He calls me back up over the loudspeaker.
Not a good sign.
So I go up and he goes, look, man, I mean, I can
do 20.
He's got an addition to the thing that I know is
being sold upstairs for 350.
He's got 40 blue rays and DVDs, many new.
So I go, but this upstairs right now is selling
used for 350 because that doesn't mean and he
goes, and I say this all day every day.
So please remember it this time.
That doesn't mean we are going to sell it for
350.
Why I mean, my eyes are huge that that he's talking
to me this way right off the bat.
But I go, well, no, it might not sell for that
price, but it also might I go and you can pay me
less for a new version.
I go, you can pay me 200 if you want 100, but you
can't give me 20 for it and all this stuff.
Right.
And he goes, look garbage, garbage, garbage.
He starts throwing stuff off and I go, well,
that's got the price tag on it for $25.
It's brand new.
Right.
So it's not garbage.
And he goes, nobody wants physical media anymore.
I go, then why are you working here?
And another guy there laughed, which I again,
they must know these people are sociopaths.
Yeah, but we kind of get into a little heated
thing and I go, all right, let's start over.
I go, what would you just give me for this?
The thing that you're selling upstairs for 350
and he goes, oh, I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to break it off.
What I go, what do you mean?
I go, now I'm not giving you this stuff.
Just what can we, can we negotiate the price of
this one thing I want to sell?
Yeah.
He's nah.
I go, what do you mean?
He goes, the transaction is done, man.
The transaction is done.
And I go, so if I wanted the 20 now for this
pile, you wouldn't take it.
That's right.
So now this is what I always wondered at Amoeba.
Do you have the option?
I never tried it to go.
I want to talk to that guy and have him do my trade.
I got to start being more aggressive.
I mean, I always just wind up walking away.
Make you feel well, nobody makes you feel right.
All that bullshit.
But it's they they put you in this position in
that place sometimes where it's like you're afraid
to stand up for yourself.
Yes, because the fear is hold on.
There's the every 12 minute fire engine going by
the every 12 minute fire engine going by in New
York City, a city where not only have I never seen
anything on fire, I've never even seen a building
that was previously on fire.
I don't understand how many drills need to be run
in New York City with the fire trucks.
Anyway, this fear sets in an Amoeba of I am terrified.
I'm going to look like the cheap guy.
Nobody wants to be because we've as media
collectors, we've all seen the guy in the store.
Like I see it a lot with video games where a guy will
go into a video game shop with like, you know, 20
games and every one of them is like Madden 97, right?
You know, NHL 2002, these worthless games that
nobody wants.
Guitar Hero 2 or whatever.
Yeah, nobody wants because it's like, dude, no, they
make a version of this every year and then that
makes the old versions worthless.
Right.
The new one in six months will only be $10 in
Missouri.
And then you don't have slackers trying to sell
Bush come down machine for like 20 bucks.
They're like new.
It's eight.
Yeah.
So you never want to be the guy going, what do you
mean?
Because you don't want to look at the guy who
doesn't understand how this works.
Yes, where that you're some amateur collector guy.
But in that situation, and I've been there in it
at Amoeba, you know, sometimes you're not getting
what it's worth and you're the fear of looking
like the chump takes over.
Right.
And you let it go.
But that sucks.
That's why I thought I'd be clear.
I'm like a lowball would be I'm offering you 80,
you know, and I wouldn't have taken it.
But don't come in with 20 for the pile.
No, stop.
That's ridiculous.
You're slapping me in the face.
I got into it in the airport recently.
I booked I was on a run of shows and the last of
the shows was Lancaster, Pennsylvania, but we had
to drive from Ohio to Lancaster and the Saturday
the Sunday night show in Lancaster.
I'm sorry.
The show in Lancaster was on Monday night and the
show in Ohio was on Sunday night and Sunday
afternoon it started snowing and sleeting and
all this stuff.
Lancaster was a six hour drive and it was supposed
to carry on for over 24 hours into Western
Pennsylvania.
I had to cancel the show.
I was like, these are dangerous conditions.
We can't drive this drive.
Right tomorrow.
And I felt bad and folks of Lancaster.
I will make it up.
I know some of you are Hellions out there.
I'm going to make it up.
I promise.
That wasn't the issue.
The issue was now suddenly I have to find a
flight to get myself home from Ohio to New York
last minute and I called Delta.
I'm like guys the prices and I fly Delta all the
time.
I'd like to fly Delta for this prices are
very high.
Is there anything we can do guy the phone goes
no problem.
Got you a basic fare here 130 bucks.
Okay tomorrow morning.
I go.
Oh, that's great.
Thank you.
Yeah, book it next morning bright and early on
my way to the airport hoping nothing's going to
go wrong because of weather blah blah blah.
I'm trying to check in on my phone.
I can't check in.
It's not letting me check in.
I start getting aggravated.
I'm like what's going on here.
I look I realize it says 30 days till check in.
I'm like what guy on the phone booked it for
February the flight.
So I'm like Jesus.
All right.
I call back I go miss.
I'm going to really try to stay calm here, but
I'm really stressed.
This is so she loves any call that starts like
that.
Yeah, and I go I go I'm trying to keep my tone
in line, but please understand.
Here's what the situation is.
Look, I'm not going to call you bitch or anything.
I'm five minutes from the airport.
I'm trying to check in.
I booked it for a month out.
I don't know why he did that.
I was very specific about the date.
She goes I get it.
No problem.
It's all taken care of.
You're on the flight for today.
Don't worry about it.
Great.
Thank you.
Yeah, get to the airport.
Go to check in the flight by the way is now
boarding in far less than an hour.
Uh -huh.
Can't check in.
I'm like you got to be kidding me, man.
I go up to I wait in the line to go to the desk.
I pride myself on never having to go to the desk.
I have TSA pre -check.
I check in on my phone.
Yeah, you know, I usually don't have a bag to
drop.
Now I got to wait in the line.
I'm like this is I get up to the front.
I get the guy who's clearly the leader because
he's the only one in all red.
Everybody else is in blue.
Uh -huh.
I go listen, man.
I'm trying to check in over there.
It's not letting me check in.
He's like, huh?
Well, you're not on this flight.
And I go, no, I am on this flight.
I tell him the whole story.
He goes, well, why did the lady that you just spoke
to tell you she fixed it?
She didn't fix it.
I go, I don't know why she told me that.
Right.
That's what she told me.
I don't work for Delta.
Yeah.
He goes, yeah, you're not on this flight.
I go, sir, I have to get onto this flight.
I have to get home and he goes, okay, here's what
I'm going to do for you.
Uh -huh.
He goes, I'm going to go ahead and refund the
wrongly booked flight as if it's a favor.
I go, okay, I'm going to go ahead.
I always love okay.
He goes, but you're going to have to buy the ticket
for the flight today outright.
So at this point, it's like $600 one way.
Yeah.
And I go, no, no, no, no, I'm not doing that.
Do you understand that at this point yesterday?
Had you told me that that was my only option?
I could have rented a car, right?
And beaten the snow and driven home in this
amount of time.
Do you understand that?
Let me ask.
Are you making a scene at this point?
My voice is starting to get low.
Okay.
And I wouldn't have done that, but I was just
making, I was just trying to make a point to the
guy like this is like the position you've put me
in now, how much time, uh, and I go, or I could
have just booked with a cheaper airline.
I went with Delta because I'm a sky miles member.
Yeah.
He goes, well, why did you do any of those things?
Ooh.
And I go, because I didn't know that you were
going to screw me over like this.
Do you understand?
The guy goes, sir, I'm going to ask you to keep
your tone down and not make a scene.
And I go, not make a scene.
You're leaving me stranded in Ohio.
What do you mean not make a scene?
The plane boards in 20 minutes.
And he goes, sir, I'm going to ask you again.
Don't make a scene.
I slapped my hand on the desk.
I go, I'm fucking believable.
And he goes, okay.
Okay.
I'm going to ask you now not to use that kind of
language.
And I go, oh, I'm sorry.
Are you offended by the F word?
Right.
And the guy goes, yes, I am.
I go, you're 42.
Get over it.
Guy next to him goes, you want me to call the,
you know, CCPPD, whatever, solve all these
initials.
And I go, oh, who's that?
The airport police.
The guy goes, yeah, I go good.
Call.
Call him because I'm not.
Now there's going to be a scene.
Call him.
So he calls him.
The guy goes, I'm not doing anything for you.
I won't do the refund now.
You can't buy a ticket with me.
You want to buy a ticket?
You better go buy it on your phone.
Leave the desk.
I go, all right.
I walk over and sit there waiting.
Airport cops show up.
They're like.
Every time I tell the story, I make this point.
I'm sorry, but a real quick question.
Did they come up on a motorized?
Vehicle they came by chopper, which I thought was extreme.
I just mean, was it like the Zamboni?
Okay, they walked.
They just walked up three cops are like,
what's up, buddy?
And I go, you hear from me and they go, yeah, we think so.
What's going on?
I tell them the whole story.
All three of them are like, do we get it?
Yeah, this isn't your fault, right?
And then the one dude goes, listen, what has to happen here?
I go, what has to happen is I have to book a six hundred
dollar ticket on my phone right now.
And I need to get my refund, but I'm not allowed to go back
up to the desk.
And the guy goes, I got it.
Don't worry about it.
Walks up, comes back.
He's like, I got you the refund.
You're good.
Okay.
And they go, did you book your ticket?
And I go, yeah, I booked it.
I go, guys, I'm sorry that I'm looking at my phone as I'm
explaining all this to you, but I have to book the ticket.
Like we get it.
Do we get it?
Because they're clearly like these jagoffs behind the counter
call us when there's not a bomb.
Right.
Yeah.
And it's a waste of time.
Like who cares?
We're trying to smoke confiscated weed in the back.
So I end up getting on the plane.
I call Delta.
I complain.
And this is the capper.
I'm talking to a manager.
I call Delta.
I have to speak immediately to a manager like our supervisor.
I go, trust me.
I'm going to waste your time by go.
I need a supervisor that can approve something for me.
Okay.
No problem.
They put me through to a supervisor talking to this guy
for so long that I go from I miss that flight.
I have to get on the next one.
I'm talking from so long for so long that I am waiting to
get on the next flight boarding the next flight.
The phone call is ending as I'm saying, sir, we're about
to take off.
I have to go.
This is how long this is taking and the guys going I just
you know, I don't know what I could do.
We could put in a complaint.
I don't want to put in a complaint.
Listen to me.
You guys did everything wrong.
Help me out here.
We're just going over and over in circles on this thing.
And at the end of it, he goes, well look man, you know,
I mean I could give you a $300 voucher, but I'm just
saying if I do that, then you can't get a and I go give
me the $300 voucher.
That is why I'm calling you.
Yeah, I just want some compensation for this.
Right.
I want to pay $600 for the flight.
He goes.
Oh, okay.
Well, if you want a voucher, I'll do it.
I'm like this is I'm fucking real man.
Yeah, and it was that thing to where and a lot of companies
do this now.
You're not talking to a person in a call center.
You're literally talking to a guy at his house.
Really like like, how do you know because I can hear him
like dealing with his dog and shit like Amazon will do that.
I did not know that was going on.
You'll call Amazon and they'll they call you back.
That's how it works.
Yeah, and then you get on with a rap and I go listen, you
know, this is this thing is broken or whatever, you know,
can I talk to a supervisor about and they go there is no
supervisor.
I'm in my house.
Yeah, it just did an Amazon.
I just tell you right as it's like hey deal with it or don't
go right yourselves.
Yeah, we're worth thirty nine billion dollars or whatever
the hell it is.
It's way more than that.
But yeah, so but yeah, I'm just like this is this is insane.
Yeah, this is insane that attitude.
I even said to the red guy.
I go I go I go stop saying it like you're doing me a favor
right now.
Of course, you're going to refund the flight.
I didn't want.
It's so nuts.
They say that so that a you think they're a great guy, but
also they know they're going to have to fuck you over.
So they're like they something that they'd have to do.
They act like they're doing you a big favor and they think
you can't see through it.
I think most people don't because most people are quite
stupid.
I'm real close to a public arrest.
Yeah, I'm not.
It's going to happen.
Yeah, you ever have a phone service job?
Oh, yeah.
Which one?
Oh, I did telemarketing.
I did.
I mean, well, I guess that's not phone service.
But no, I never did like call center.
I let me help you with your problem, but I definitely had
phone sales jobs and that sort of thing.
And I had a million and one retail jobs.
So when a guy in the store is going I just can't it's like
I always say no you can you just don't want to.
I'm not trying to I turn into the dude where I'm like I'm
not trying to scam anybody here, man.
Like I'm just like just don't just do what's right right
now.
You guys made a mistake.
Help me out.
My one of my first jobs here in New York when I moved here
was student services in Kaplan test prep, you know,
like a CT MCAT LSAT all that.
So the parents would call if their kids didn't get the
grades they wanted after like six months of paying for
tutoring and what I always wanted to say and then finally
did say the night I quit.
I remember is a Monday night and I was done.
I was so thrilled to be done working there.
And this lady called I had heard from her before she's
going on and honestly the kind of thing where they're
already yelling like as you say hello, she's going on
and on and on about I paid this much money and my kids
still did not pass the you know, I don't know what to do.
Like I why do you guys promise things you can't deliver
on and I said ma 'am.
Did it ever occur to you that maybe your daughter is an
idiot?
It was the best feeling of my life.
She was like like it turned into like a pterodactyl howl
we immediately fired.
No, I was done.
I mean, I was like quitting it that night.
This is my last day of the job.
Okay, sorry, but you know, they kind of came over like,
okay, it's funny.
You know, it's your last day, but we'll have to play off
the phones.
If you do that again, I was like, yeah, I don't care.
But it was it was a great feeling Jesus.
Those guys are you know, like those are the guys who
kill people because they have no power.
They want power so badly.
Remember that guy that we saw at LAX who came up and
was screaming at that old Asian man because I was
taking to get a taxi how long it was taking to get a
taxi and he's like, I'm not a taxi wizard, you know,
like that guy.
Give me your badge number.
That's a new thing.
What's your what's your badge number?
What people are pathetic on both sides.
You sound like you were very much on the right here.
But Jesus Christ, no, it's just it's madness.
It's it's you know, everybody so it's just nothing
works.
Yeah, no, nothing works.
Nothing is the way it's supposed to be.
No, there are way too many people.
Yes, and everything is a nightmare.
Absolutely.
Let's get over to the movie corner because we're
already at thirty five minutes.
Excited to do it.
The movie corner.
Would you like to start us off, Joseph?
I want to hear this Rolling Stones thing for the
thing.
I've been teasing in my rolling by Rolling Stones
related.
I mean, it's another band from England that is wildly
famous, but I finally watched the Oasis documentary
supersonic.
Oh, great.
I saw with Vince.
Yeah, great.
It is a fucking masterpiece.
I agree.
I officially think Oasis might be the greatest
band that has ever lived.
Were you always a fan?
No, I mean, I liked him.
I liked him just fine.
But like now me and Vince saw one of them open for
the who and it was the the singer.
No, or Liam.
Sorry.
Yeah.
And my god, he sucked and he sang five songs.
He just canceled some shows and was like my voice
just isn't up to it.
Sorry guys.
Like, okay, good.
Like I like that.
He's kind of owning it.
It wasn't but I will say this.
I always thought that Liam was the dick and that
Noel was the cool one.
And after watching this, I'm like, no, Liam kind
of seems like the fun one.
That's always kind of pulling pranks and up to
something.
And he kind of comes off shitty on stage because
he does that like pouty face thing.
Right.
But like off stage, it's like he's laughing and
joking and like he just seems like he's having a
great time with it all.
Yeah, Noel is way more the guy that's like, you
know, the totalitarian like this is how it done.
This is the band.
Fuck you.
You're fired.
Right.
All being said, they are the two funniest men that
have ever walked the face of the earth.
Yeah, documentary is great.
I loved it.
It made me download morning glory and and definitely
maybe definitely maybe the two best.
I also downloaded BDI second album.
I think it's called she never heard any BDI.
The second one sounds like a good Oasis record to
me.
You know, so I didn't get too deep into the Oasis
catalog because I know after the third record, it
kind of spins out a little bit more.
But that's true.
But I just loved every minute of this thing.
It gave me a new respect for the band and like
what they did.
Yeah, the massive massive success they had and
just again, like the quotes through this entire
thing are so funny, man.
Jesus, it opens where you hear I think it's Noel
Gallagher saying it.
I think the opening line of the movie is him going
I want the fucking head of Phil Collins in my
refrigerator and if I don't have it by year's end,
I fucking failed.
Yeah, it's insane.
Imagine being like the bass player in that band
and you know that your ticket to receiving like
$10 million annually is for these two pricks to
just stop being assholes to each other, but they
won't do it.
That's a great part of the dock when the bass
player like is like guys, I'm leaving the band
because I'm going to have a nervous breakdown.
Yeah, because I can't take this anymore.
Yeah, you guys are throwing things at each other
in the studio.
It's too much.
I can't do this right and then they're in the jam
for their tour.
They go do Letterman without him.
Yes, I remember this and then they come back to
do this big string of shows to promote.
What's the story morning glory and they're like
we don't have a fucking bass player.
So they asked the guy to come back because they
can't find a bass player.
Right and then he comes back and then there's a
clip of Liam Neeson going, ah, Liam Gallagher.
Yeah, or Liam Gallagher.
Gallagher.
Sorry.
He goes, he goes, oh, do you have a nice rest?
You lazy fucking bastard.
Yeah, they could not have been fun to work for.
No, again, it's the post office guy.
Yeah, for sure.
You don't want to be in it, right?
But you do want to watch it.
Maybe a grip in the background not being yelled
at.
You want to watch it.
I finally saw I have a few gaps in my filmography,
but most of your classics of any genre I have seen
I had never seen THX 1138 George Lucas's film.
Flick dude.
I of course have been hearing about this forever.
George Lucas is actually not directed many movies.
So I was intrigued, but I was bored out of my mind.
It's it's it's it's a slow movie.
I wouldn't say it's necessarily riveting.
Yeah, but I find it to be a fascinating movie.
I think the commentary the social commentary that
it was presenting was great and the fact that they
did what they did on such a small budget.
I did think it was a very revolutionary
groundbreaking film.
Sure.
I mean, you definitely see why they'd given the
reins to something like Star Wars off of that.
But yeah, it did nothing for me.
Criterion channel, which you can subscribe to for
a very reasonable 99 a year.
Which is cheaper than your Netflix or anything else
to me is the best of the streaming services shutter
had a real nice little run.
But then to me then the offerings they're given
new and old have not been up to snuff.
I got to say I'm not excited with what they add
each month.
It's kind of slowing down.
They're adding.
Yeah, very slowly.
And I I'm hoping that means because they're about
like because Netflix did that at one point and
then all of a sudden they bum rushed with that
with a ton of stuff.
So I'm hoping that's the case with shutter.
Yeah, but it's been I agree.
I almost canceled my shutter.
I was like, I don't know that I need this anymore.
Man, but it's so cheap that I was just like, yeah,
it is.
And I got the year which made it even cheaper,
but it's always worth it for Joe Bob.
Yeah, but I've been let down.
But anyway, Criterion Channel did a month of
70s sci -fi and it had some of your your heavy
hitters, you know, like Mad Max and so forth.
But whole lot of movies I hadn't seen or hadn't
heard of.
And that's what I'll be focusing on today's movie
corner because it included THX Joe.
I watched Born Dead Still Weird documentary about
Gahan Wilson or gone Wilson who was a provocative
cartoonist that did a lot of really amazing work
over the years.
Gahan, maybe it is.
I don't have much to say about the documentary
other than I didn't really know who he was until
I watched it.
And in watching it, I found him to be a fascinating
guy.
I'm not a huge fan of cartoonists.
I don't dislike them.
It's just not my bag, right?
But he did some really, really cool provocative
interesting work and he's one of these like sort of
cult heroes in that community and the amount of
A -list celebrities in this thing that were singing
this guy's praises and talking about how much he
influenced them and their work was really
impressive.
And he was just a really, really fascinating guy
that lived his life according to his own rules,
but wasn't an asshole about it, you know, like he
and his wife of I mean, I think 30 or 40 years up
until his death.
She lived in England and he lived here and she was
just like, yeah, we got to a point like she goes
we were 20 years in and we were like we don't need
to see each other every day.
I like England.
You like the Midwest.
I'm going to move back to England and we'll visit
each other and we'll be married and it was just
little stuff like that where I was like this guy
was a really cool interesting guy and it
just overall inspired me in the sense of going.
Oh, you know what?
You can kind of live your life the way you want to
and it's not always about the award, you know, it
doesn't have to be about the award shows or the
spotlight or the money or the palatial estate.
Yeah, we put these prizes in front of us and think
that that's what success means and this guy was
successful but so much more of a lifestyle wise
traditional human being than I think you would
expect, you know, would take the bus like every
week, you know, to just go like like a four hour
bus ride every week up to a town he liked so he
could just go up there and create like read the
paper every day lived in a very normal like two
bedroom apartment or small house like it was just
as an artist.
It was a cool, cool, cool documentary to watch.
I really enjoyed it.
I'd suggest checking it out.
It's on like Amazon Prime.
You never even know it was there.
You know, what's the guy's name?
I think it's pronounced gone again.
Okay, Gann or gone Wilson.
It's G -A -H -A -N.
Okay.
All right.
I saw also from the 70s sci -fi collection the
Omega Man starring Charlton Heston fascinating
piece of work certainly was it is, you know, based
off the Richard Matheson story that also became
the Will Smith movie.
I am legend.
There are definite similarities, but it's
basically Charlton Heston living in a world that
he thinks is free of people.
And then at about the halfway point you learn
there are people and they got to kill some some
bad guys and so forth.
The Heston wonder is the most it strays furthest
from the path of the source material.
Okay, to me the first 30 minutes and same with I
am legend by the way first 30 minutes were
fantastic and then it started to lose me more
and more but when it's just Heston alone, you
know every day you watch is the same movie which
is Woodstock Scorsese's Woodstock because it's
the one playing in the movie theater and just
seeing a guy alone in a city.
There's something wonderful about that.
The road also did it a lot of Apocalypse stories
do it last man on earth, of course, but in the
end it completely fell apart for me like like
honestly like a lot of the I watched several of
these 70 sci -fi movies and a lot of them did this
very intriguing premise that they just did not
know how to land that happens a lot.
I like those movies.
I like that genre.
I like that time period for that genre.
But yeah, like Logan's run is another one that
starts Logan's run is fucking mind -blowing for
the first like 90 minutes.
Yeah, that's my next one is I why I'd never seen
that either the last 30 you're just like this is
kind of losing me guys.
Like where are we going with this?
Yeah, Logan's run how that has been are made.
I do not understand and they should have remade it.
I think it's been attempted to be remade.
Yeah, that's million times.
They should have remade it back when they allowed,
you know, nudity and stuff because it lends itself
to there's some sex in the movie and very weird
uncomfortable sex in it for a PG movie a lot of
nudity, but it's basically, you know, they live in
a society where you're killed at age 30.
So great premise and it just gets loonier and
loonier until they're talking to Peter Ustinov
in an underground bunker.
There's like a robot where you can see the guy's
face, you know behind the robot amazing sets and
special effects on this robot comes out and it's
like somebody painted a cardboard box blue, you
know, these movies all make a lot of very strange
choices.
All right, and Michael York should never have
been the lead of anything.
What's your third just that being said, I want to
because visually it's it's incredible.
My third was your Rolling Stones movie, the Oasis
movie.
Yeah, that's what I was saying.
It was just because it was a famous band from
England.
Okay, I'll stick with the documentary theme for my
third and I won't say much on this, but there's a
Frank Zappa documentary on Amazon Prime called
Frank Zappa calling freak jazz movie madness and
other and another mother's as a Frank Zappa fan as
Frank's have a non fan.
I don't know how much you would get out of this as
a Frank Zappa fan.
This is an absolute 100 % must see it takes you on
the journey of Zappa from him dissolving the
original lineup of the mothers of invention which
was the his original band and the band that
brought him into the you know that brought him out
into the spotlight and his forming a new lineup of
a band recording and then going into his jazz
fusion phase that followed right after the original
mothers of invention lineup.
So as a Zappa fan, if you are one, you know how
important the album Hot Rats is.
It gets into the whole recording of that it the
recording of the Grand Wazoo that whole period
they're interviewing session players from that
stuff.
They're telling stories about what happened in the
sessions how they did all of it.
It then gets into him doing the movie 200 motels
and what that was like behind the scenes.
It gets fully into the flow and Eddie years with
the new lineup and reintroduction of a new lineup
of the mothers of invention as a Zappa fan.
It is incredible.
I've never seen anything this thorough that got
into the specifics of what really went on during
this time period in Frank Zappa's career.
It's fascinating.
It's interesting.
The stories are fun.
They're crazy and it's it's not you know, it's not
look it certainly doesn't paint Frank Zappa in a
bad light, but it's also not a puff piece.
You know, they don't pull any punches about some of
the stuff he did with the band members.
You know, he was he had his tyrant like ways that
people didn't always love and there were tensions
in the band and that sort of thing and that sort
of thing and they don't stray away from it.
So I would say please check it out.
I don't know that it'll make you a new Zappa fan,
but if you are a fan check it out because it was
really really incredible the fucking things like
three hours long.
It was it was so so so thorough.
This sounds like something I would not want to
watch at all.
Well, as I said, if you're not like a big Zappa fan,
you're not going to you know what I mean?
But because it's not like oh God, you got to hear
about the time the girl ended up dead on the road
and they were on the run from the kid.
It's not like crazy stories like that, right?
It's just if you love those albums hearing what
went into those albums and how they were made.
Yeah is really fucking amazing.
It really mean lots of George Duke footage,
which for you Zappa heads, you know how cool that
is and just hearing George Duke went on to be his
own force of nature in the jazz community.
Talk about like how impressed he was with Frank
Zappa is it's it's it's a really really cool
documentary.
Anyway, check it out and then with that said,
let's get to what we're reviewing today a little
screaming and that you see that Indiana Jones 5
starts shooting in two months.
Yes, I'm very excited.
Okay, I'm very excited.
You'd think they better have something good to go
back to this.
Well, I don't know.
I think what they're going to do.
I think they realize that despite the financial
success of Crystal Skull, it left a bad taste in
a lot of people's mouths.
I think they want to end the series on a high
note.
Yes, I think they realized after Force Awakens that
they are able to do that and I especially with
Harrison Ford and I think the reason that this
has been postponed for so many times and that
they keep bringing in new writers is because
after seeing what Scorsese did with the Irishmen
and seeing that it could work.
I would bet my life that they're going to do some
sort of de -aging thing with Harrison Ford.
I would I can't imagine they're not going to dip
into that at least in fat flashback sequences or
something that just doesn't seem good to me.
I think look I think it would be awesome if they
were like it's an anthology Indiana Jones movie
and it's going to be old Harrison Ford telling a
story of who he was to a younger person and showing
three periods from the life of this guy and the
first one he's very young like like the Irishman.
Right.
I think that would be awesome.
Personally, I would really dig that but I don't
know that that's what they're going to do.
Obviously, but what is this week?
We're talking about knives out baby.
Ryan Johnson's knives out Ryan Johnson is a
filmmaker that I like almost everything he's done
and I have yet to be kind of Gaga over the moon.
I thought Brick was maybe his best.
I like Brick a lot, you know, very hyper -stylized
dialogue, which puts people off, but I thought
it was very well written and well done.
I thought Looper was fun.
I didn't love the Brothers Bloom.
You know, Last Jedi I thought was fun, but had
major problems.
What's Brothers Bloom again?
Brothers Bloom was boy about the unsung brothers
of the Judy Bloom family now other spelling of
bloom.
It was Rachel Weiss and the men were Adrian Brody
who I guess doesn't act anymore and Mark Ruffalo.
It was fine.
It was a kind of a sting type movie, but you know,
he's a very clever writer.
He's a very clever director, but sometimes they
feel a little soulless and sometimes they feel
almost like just exercises of a guy who's seen a
lot of movies as opposed to like its own thing.
Knives out to me was probably his most successful
and I still had issues with it.
I thought knives out was a whole lot of fun.
Tell the premise of the movie premise of the movie
basically is a the patriarch of this big feuding
family.
Christopher Plummer who's always great dies under
mysterious circumstances.
His pretty young nurse is seemingly involved and
the family comes sort of with their knives out if
you will to get revenge.
They bring or find out who did it.
They bring in Daniel Craig because the will that
he has left has been left to the girl.
Yeah, it's well and it's also it's a parent suicide.
Yes, and then the cops come in and they bring in
the last gentleman investigator played by Daniel
Craig and it's a very it's very much an homage to
Agatha Christie.
Of course murder in the Order and Express and all
and then when that guy starts questioning the
family along the lines of did you maybe kill your
father?
That's when things start to get tense and you you
get to see this really great commentary.
The family is very divided politically.
They're they're they're very right -wing members are
very left -wing members and they're all very sort of
passively condescending to this assistant right to
Christopher Plummer because she's of I guess Arab
descent.
I think it was I thought she was Hispanic or
Hispanics.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to miss remember miss remembering sorry
in the way that a person on the right or a person on
the left would be in very different ways, but it's
still condescending.
So when all of a sudden the fingers start pointing
at the family members the blood relatives about
where why this guy is dead and was it foul play and
where this money is going to go you start to see
them slowly turn on this assistant to their father
who they all praised right at the top of the film
right and that's and then it becomes about this
assistant solving the mystery of what happened
here and in fact she was involved with it.
Yeah, but why she was involved in what's actually
going on and what's afoot and all that stuff.
So is a great cast.
Yeah, Amelie Curtis great in it.
Don Johnson's great in it like John Johnson third
act like a motherfucker right now.
Yeah, God damn still looks great.
LaKeith Stanfield Daniel Craig gives an insane
performance but very fun and funny.
I have no idea how he got cast in that role, but he
was fun and then somehow pulls it off.
He was I was like, how's he going to pull off a
Southern man?
He great Southern man.
So he I had two issues a and this is a spoiler
briefly, but everyone I talked to had the same
complaint who's seen it.
You know that Chris Evans has to be involved in
some way because he's one of the biggest stars in
America and you get to the like hour and 30 minute
mark and he hasn't spoken or hour and 15.
No, that's not true.
He pops in and pops out of scenes.
He's like in and out.
He has no no real reason to be there.
So to me he stood out like a sore thumb as being
perhaps involved.
The biggest issue for me is okay.
Everything everything in the setup was very fun.
It's a very funny movie.
The political commentary is done extremely well
where I couldn't imagine either side being offended,
which is probably why the movie is so successful,
but they do a lot of great commentary under the
surface.
However, there's the fun of who done it who done it
who done it once, you know, who done it then
there's like a 30 to 40 minute period that to me
was extremely dull because I'm like, okay, we got
it then at the end they're trying to figure out how
it happened to details and then the fun comes back
into the movie.
But for me that middle portion where you know who
did it and they're just kind of going through the
motions really should have been trimmed way down
or taken out of the movie frankly because what's
interesting is who did it and why they did it and
that whole period is just kind of like kind of
grinding their wheels a little bit.
I would say yeah, I hear you.
I felt like there and you're talking about the
sequence where things start happening out of the
house, right?
And I was disappointed to see things leave the
house because the first thing I thought of when I
saw this trailer was clue.
Sure.
And I thought oh, this is fun.
This is going to be like one of these sort of
farcical murder mystery things right that all
takes place under one roof with a bunch of
characters and you're trying to figure out who's
guilty right and it is that for the most part but
there is this sequence that Pat's talking about
where you're pretty sure who's guilty here.
You don't know for certain just yet, but you're
you're pretty sure and now all of a sudden they're
doing all these things outside of the house and
it's the next day or two days later whatever and
you're going no, no, no, no, no, keep it all to
that one night.
That's great.
And then it starts to feel a little bit to me.
What it reminded me of is like in Wedding
Crashers when they go to Christopher Walken's
house and you go thousand percent agree.
Oh man, this should all should have just happened
at the wedding.
Like this is great, you know, so that that chunk
of Wedding Crashers where it's Owen Wilson and
Rachel McAdams who I like both of them, but when
they're like sitting on the beach talking and
you're like already an hour 30 in it's like, oh
no, I remember going to an advanced screening of
that movie here right before I left New York and
they asked for audience thoughts and I was like
this thing is going to be fucking huge.
It is so funny.
Premises so good and relatable.
I was like all you got to do trim that little
section with Owen Wilson and McAdams and
Walken's house.
Nobody's going to care about that and they were
like, yeah, we've been hearing that a lot movie
comes out.
If anything, they made it longer.
Yeah, and and by the way that then there's like
after that sequence.
There's like another 30 minutes of well, then they
go back to Farrell.
Luckily Farrell's in it.
So it can flow.
But yeah, I mean look writing is very difficult
and movies is about as hard as it gets to try to
keep something, you know, that's why I don't get
too upset when something sucks unless it's super
egregious, but it's hard, you know, and like it's
hard to keep balls in the air the whole time.
Ryan Johnson is an excellent writer.
This that section does get away from him.
Yeah, I will and I will agree with that.
I'm like as and I was not a huge last shadow fan,
but I will say as a writer director, Ryan Johnson
is very impressive.
I'm like, this is yeah, I mean the tall order and
he pulls it off, you know, when they start putting
the details together, like there's so many cool
little things that fit together.
The last shot of the movie is, you know, a little
bit of a cutesy joke, but it's also pretty awesome
when she brings the mug up to her mouth, you know
what the mug says and all that.
And then and then she's standing on the terrace
above everybody, right?
They're all down below, you know, yeah.
Yeah, he he definitely shoots in a way that is
he's married to a really great film critic as well.
You get the feeling they do a lot of analyzing of
movies and that shows there's it seems like the
kind of movie would be fun to revisit taking the
sometimes when you go to see something where like
it's a mystery when you go see it knowing who did
it. It makes the movie a lot more fun.
Like I like Gone Girl a lot more on a second viewing
because I knew it was happening.
You know, it helps you respect the craft a little
more. He's a great director.
I don't think he's hit his quote masterpiece, but
I think he will he will get there.
It's a great movie.
Very fun B plus for me.
Very fun cast is all great.
It was a lot of fun and I was intrigued.
I wanted to see what happened.
I mean part of why I was so.
Intrigued was I mixed up.
My reading a review of this movie with my reading
of a review of I think it was the new Black
Christmas, which I haven't seen yet.
Oh, I saw it.
We should do it on here.
I would like to do it on here.
You scream at me for a while.
Why?
Because you loved it.
No, I didn't.
But you're really not going to love it.
Oh, OK.
Not scream at me.
Oh, I got you screaming the same room as me.
I think it was the I read a review of something
or no, wait, no, no, no, I'm sorry.
It might have been ready or not, which I still
haven't seen either.
But very similar.
It's not as good as Knives Out, but very similar.
But but one of those two movies, the review was
like and then there's this crazy supernatural
twist and I was like, oh, makes me more interested.
And for some reason, I got it in my head that
that was Knives Out.
Oh, OK.
So the whole time I was watching Knives Out, I
was like, I bet it's going to be that Christopher
Plummer transported his spirit into Chris Evans.
Chris Evans is a great looking guy.
And this girl is going to get to end up with
Chris Evans and all the money.
Oh, everybody wins.
Right.
You know, like but maybe write that movie.
That sounds cool.
And and that's not what it was.
But but I still I still thoroughly enjoyed it.
But perhaps having that in my head prevented me
from guessing what the actual ending was going
to be or whatever.
But needless to say, regardless, I enjoyed it.
Basically front to back.
I mean, you know, I'll say this, despite the
portion of the film, I still sat there pretty
glued to it front to back, which is tough for me
to do.
Yeah.
And it's also a great, you know, family movie,
which I don't mean in the sense of like the Apple
dumpling gang.
I mean, it like parents would like it.
Kids would like it.
It's just a fun, good time.
I agree.
And I'm happy to see Jamie Lee Curtis back in
action, despite not liking that newest Halloween.
And I can only imagine the next two are going to
be even worse.
I am happy to see Lee Curtis in there swinging.
I'm happy to see Christopher Plummer still around.
Oh, Michael Shannon, as promised on the other
episode of this month.
I said I would get a little deeper into Michael
Shannon.
Yeah, I almost wish they'd amped him up a little
more.
I mean, he's great in it, but he's really let him
be unhinged.
He's fine in it.
I always like him.
I'm a little bored.
Okay, it's the same.
It's oh, you're a prick again.
Oh, this time you have a cane though.
Right.
It's just every movie.
He's that guy.
You mean to tell me that you don't like every
fucking movie ever.
You ever see Take Shelter?
No, I'm talking about an awesome.
I'm talking about in the last four years.
Yeah, for sure.
I agree.
I'm just getting a little tired of it.
Like it's just like he's always this, you know,
sort of prick weirdo right creep.
And even when like this was it was supposed to it
was veiled this this it was supposed to be like
the reveal was oh, no, he's actually a prick.
Yeah, and it's just wafting off of him from the
first you're like, oh, he's going to turn out to
be an asshole.
Right.
But it doesn't mean he's bad in it.
I shouldn't say, you know, but that's knives out
people and that's our episode.
How do they not play knives out radiohead song?
I don't know.
Now the thing they play.
This is a weird thing that annoys me.
I'm sure somebody else has it.
If a song is played in a movie, a notable movie,
especially if it's like a very notable use of that
song, then it's done.
There's a billion songs like to me, if I was going
to make a movie, the biggest thrill would be like
which songs can I share with people?
Which songs can I, you know, I always think in
terms of Tarantino's thing.
He said that about he's like he's adamant about
that, but he does it too occasionally.
Like why is he playing Mrs.
Robinson in Once Upon a Time in America?
That's the graduate obviously.
But that that's a little different though to me.
He's commenting on a time, but it was weird to me.
If you're taking something from an iconic movie,
then it's almost like you're making a commentary
in the movie by using that song.
And it is when he's looking at the young girl in
her jeans, you know, but but but he said like,
yeah, you can't like, you know, you can't.
And I mean, has the soundtrack speak for it if
yes, but but they play so Tarantino uses the song
sundown Gordon life sundown.
You better take care.
Use it in Django, which came out 10 years ago.
Max not even so when sundown popped up in this.
I'm like Brian Johnson and Tarantino know each other.
There's no reason for this song to be sundown.
Pick a different song.
I agree.
It just baffles me.
You can you can turn people on to cool new music
with movies.
Those kind of discoveries never happen anymore.
The last one was in a movie.
I know you hate lights out.
No, not lights out.
Sorry, you're next.
Which I thought was kind of fun.
But that Dwight Tilly band song looking for the
magic.
I was like, this is one of the best songs ever.
And I had never heard it.
That discovery never happens anymore.
What do they do?
Turn around and use that song a couple years later
in the movie Diary of a Teenage Girl.
Sure.
They heard it first.
And why were you watching Diary of a Teenage Girl?
It's not a teenage girl movie.
It's an adult and independent.
It's from the lady who did quite a misleading
title, I'd say.
I was reading the Diary of a Teenage Girl
at a restaurant.
Yes.
She was 14 in lululemon pants.
That's a callback, I think, to the other episode.
Yes, it is.
So air these in order or it's a call forward folks.
Yeah, I'm going to be on Punch of the Jam with
Mielle.
I haven't done it yet, but I assume it's going to
be great.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh Twitter and
Instagram.
There you go.
Jodorowsacomedy, Instagram, Twitter, Jodorowsacomedy
and Facebook, Jodorowsainfo for tour dates.
Go buy the new album.
I go to Atlanta all the time digitally, iTunes,
Amazon, wherever you buy digital hard copies
through Capsule Records on vinyl only and it is
not available for streaming.
So I hope you purchase.
Thank you everybody.
See you next time and we'll see you in hell.