Welcome to we'll see you in hell this is your one stop shop
for genre movie reviews discussions sometimes commentaries very rarely I'm the man
with the hog and I'm the hog with the man Joe DeRosa to my right my name is
Patrick Walsh we're talking today about Bong Joon Ho's parasite we'll get to
our tones a little off but it's not because of anything it almost sounds like we were fighting
or something before we started but there's we just didn't come in hot today you're well you're
the first person I've spoken to it's a Sunday around 1 p .m. Joe and I have big plans today maybe
a future episode but it is dismember the Alamo so finally Los Angeles got their Alamo theater draft
house and in true Los Angeles style it is the most sterile and lifeless of all the Alamo yeah
it's it's missing a pulse but we're hoping to bring it to them today and we're seeing four movies we
don't know what they will be till we get there starts at 3 p .m. and goes all night tricks and treats
and I was telling Joe here's what I got the biggest treat that we can't wait to share with you is
something of an urban legend a so bad it's good film and footage so cursed it dooms any who
dare to watch to share more would be a spoiler but needless to say we finally got our hands on some
footage and are excited to premiere it on the big screen for all of you what could that be maybe
they got that Jerry Lewis clown holocaust flick immediately my mind went to the day the clown cried but
it ain't horror it's hard enough isn't it I mean it's a holocaust but if that's what we're watching
this is worth every penny I've been dreaming of seeing it someday um that or maybe it sounds like
the ring but you know the rings obviously not hard to get the you the ring because they're saying
it's cursed but it's so cursed yeah uh no it's uh yeah I don't uh I'm trying to think of
I mean maybe it's one of those old like you know there are those like VHS like black devil voodoo doll
I think it's called uh huh it's like these movies that were so shitty and so but they're so rare
that like VHS collectors pay like seven hundred fifty dollars for a copy of it
maybe it's one of those kind of things I want sold a VHS copy of Gatorbait I got it as a gag gift
and I sold it for five hundred dollars uh and then Joe Bob Briggs when I saw his live one man show
as part of Beyond Fest it was called how the redneck saved Hollywood an amazing night like a two -and -a -half
hour Joe Bob talk for standing ovation and he discussed Gatorbait for a lot of it and I was like
that kind of wish I'd held on to it well it's a it's along the lines of like a Texas chainsaw but these
are deliverance these backwoods hicks rape a farmer's daughter type and gene cutoffs and then she
travels the uh buy you in a canoe executing all of them so everyone they've ever known
like I spit on your grave exactly exactly I got you by the way fun fact I for reasons I can't
explain I enjoy listening to celebrity autobiographies if they read them themselves and uh I did Parker
poses you know I'm doing to me more is now who's an actress I've never had any interest in but I'm
listening to her autobiography yeah why and uh I learned that she was the model the butt model for the
poster and cover box of I spit on your grave that's her buck her pose no to me more yeah it's a great
butt it's a great butt god to me more is so hot she's so hot she spends the entire book talking about
how she was insecure about her weight for her entire life it's just a it's a terrible life for
everyone you know what was she fat at one point never and she talks about these different points in
her life where she was fat and you like Google a picture and you're like what are you talking about
now that sounds like she's got that dysmorphia John well all actresses do dysmorphia John John
what's that mean John you know like that's like I don't like slang term never give me that John
right there like smoke that John no well it could be it's just saying like it's it means like
thing okay it's like a word for thing so she's got that dysmorphia thing or thing if you will I will
you know this morning I put on a face mask borrowed from my wife and uh I walked into your apartment
realize I still had it on that's why I was wiping it off as I walked in I didn't even notice it was
clear but you know I wasn't like I had cucumber slices over my eyes to look at your face you know
you get older you got to keep it moist a friend of mine in New York is constantly asking me my friend
Irene if I want to do face masks and every time I'm like disgustedly like no I don't want to do a
face mask why wouldn't you do it why would I do it keep your face moist healthy radiant I like you
just stepped out of us along this is how little you know about me bitch uh I spray my face with
rose water every morning okay that's why are you avoiding the face mask why are you above that I don't
need a I'm not putting a damn but you'll borrow my Nana's rose water and spritz it like what is it a
seashell with one of those big boobs on top yeah yeah I'm not doing that fucking American psycho peel off
thing I don't want to do it they're not all like that I mean this was just a cream I put on my face you
don't even know you're wearing it until you walk into a friend's home well that just sounds
like moisturizer to be honest well it's called a face mask and then so you put it on and then how do you
get it off this one you just wash off with water I do have like a charcoal one that looks a lot like
black face and then you peel it off in one big sheet you hope no one comes to the door while you're
wearing it is it fun peeling it off super fun really peel off your nose and et cetera all right gets
the black heads uh well that's no does it discriminate against the white heads I don't think I don't
think it does no okay uh the uh I well that that I mean the peeling off part seems fun it's very fun
but yeah I don't want to ever do a pure a strip I've seen a pure a strip it's always fun to
put on your nose and trees no I don't what is that what does that mean you tape it it's like a
band -aid looking thing you taped your nose you get it a little damp and then 10 minutes later
you peel it off your nose and it's covered in black heads it's disgusting but very satisfying
I don't think I get a lot of black heads I mean but I might be wrong you'd be surprised I haven't
looked closely at your nose but everybody gets them all right everybody hurts as they said who was
that R &M R &M okay you used to well I still do love R &M I'm getting it mixed up with round here
round here both just the most depressing fucking songs ever written R &M is a hell of a lot better than
kind of grows I overall is a band sure uh I would agree with that but I mean the two songs just
remind me of one another uh what did you you said last night when you walked in you saw Marisi
and Interpol last night I saw Interpol opening for Marisi I was even more excited about Interpol
who I've loved for years they used to be like getting ready to go out in New York jams I never
listen to Interpol what's it sound like how are things on the west coast they sound like uh joy
division new order mixed with the strokes okay it's how I would describe their first two albums are
perfect the rest their albums are fine they're a band that always puts out a good single but you've
kind of learned to not keep buying the new stuff okay um but they came up with strokes block party all
those kind of bands I think block party's one of those bands too where I feel like every time I hear
the whole record I'm like yeah yeah give me these two tracks I'm good but Interpol knows to largely
play their first two albums which are phenomenal those are the classics the classics yeah I remember when
those were out my buddy wouldn't shut up about Interpol but I never for some reason took an interest to
find out what they sounded like always loved them Marisi came out uh you know as I was telling you
he was wearing a shirt that said fuck the guardian he was talking about how we need to challenge our
society and etc um but he's it was in great voice he looked good he still takes his shirt off even
though he's kind of paunchy uh at the end like very seductively takes a shirt off which always just
makes me laugh uh now were there any does is he at all in good spirits during the show does he ever
make a joke or anything um yeah yeah he said does anybody want to come up here it's like there's one
hitch you have to announce my band does anybody know all my band members names it's just like his
traveling bands that everyone's like uh not really he's like well this is a problem because I don't
either which was kind of a funny joke that's good that's that's like a real like Jerry Lewis style yeah
and he never introduced his band which made me think maybe he doesn't know them but all right uh I'm
trying to think if I can do a on with the Joe in honor of Marisi you definitely can well of course I
could you know what he did was how soon is now in my opinion the best Smith song of all time
and Smith fans will you like yell at me when I say that well I think you know it's the classic thing
if you pick the band's best known song they're like you're not a true fan it's the best Smith song
it's a great song that song is incredible and then I go I want to get the Smith sound with that song on
and of course it's not on any of the albums and I'm like oh none of the albums sound like this song
of course it's on one of the album it is not it is from a soundtrack
no that's not true they have they have two odds and sod's uh compilations that full of hollow
which is then maybe it's on a best stuff but I mean it's not on there's not an album you know
that this isn't they don't do best of this like when British bands would release like all their singles
like the who did and stuff right but it's not a greatest hits they have that too I'm saying it's not
on a true album but where like the band did this sound on this out that's what I would have liked
I don't want the other songs on the damn best of either I like that song you get had full of hollow
that's what's got it it's got a lot of other shit and it's on meat full meat is murder which is one
of their true albums it is not on meat is murder I'm looking at it as it on the deluxe like
bullshit we added oh really yes well then I got to get meat is murder I have looked for ever
meat is murder you you prefer had full of hollow it's a way better album than meat is murder
wait hold on this is the single and it's saying the B side oh the B side I'm sorry from the
album meat meat is murder okay hold on made a minute hold on I swear I've looked no it's not see
it's not it's it's on some reissue for meat is murder it's not on the original album because the
original doesn't sound like that god damn song all right I mean do you want a whole album to
sound the same I want this that is it space you know what I'm saying it's like it was added to the
US edition so I mean yeah in 92 and 92 they've been broken up for 15 years already no but 10 years
they broke up they broke up in what like 83 or 84 I feel like 84 probably 85 but you know it's like
it's like a band like queen where you say I like bohemian rhapsody I'm gonna get the album that's
on because that album reflects that sound of queen you don't want to get you don't want to go and get
fucking uh uh this I can't think in you and though it sounds nothing like you don't they broke
up in 87 all right but I'm telling you half the lojolo is about as good a compilation as you can do
and it's got that song I feel like all their other songs are like just them being like
meat is matter meat is matter and the queen is a bitch and they never do what we want and there's
like no real melody to it like it's uh you know uh completely disagree that was a funny little
parody but it's wrong all right how about girlfriend in a coma I know I know it's serious now what
you're doing now does not sound like notes to me it might not they all at marcy it always sounds
like in between the notes to me oh yeah it never sounds like that's probably true just right ever
you know yeah I do but I but I respect the hell out of the guy like and his legacy so it's like
it's weird he's one of those musicians where it's like I respect him but I don't like to listen to him
fair enough absolutely fair enough uh and he is the I will tell you man he is the guiltiest of pleasure
for some of these staunchest liberals I know like he is there their Kanye if you will you know
I'm I got to eat veal I'm sorry yeah I mean like he didn't do any of the shit like if I smell
something cooking out there it better be human usually does stuff like that
well the Hollywood bulls not really known for their barbecue oh they're definitely not
yeah how a bowl is not known for much except eighteen dollar cans of beer yeah all you're
gonna smell that Hollywood bowl is the is the cheese brick and wine some lady brought yeah next to
I do love going to a show there I mean it's it's a beautiful venue and the sound is good
which uh what do you think is the best album title of all time because I'm looking at one across
the room right now and it this just popped in my head I think it might be the greatest album title
I've ever heard one of my favorites and it's not you know it's not because this band is so great
or anything even though you know I like them but uh one that always makes me laugh is a gin blossom second
album and it's called congratulations I'm sorry right that's a great title and you know how I feel
about the gin blossoms and I'll give it up for that that's a good title yes uh well one of the great
ones I've heard and it's very recent is your boy Liam Gallagher's new or no which one is it
yeah who's got the new record out Liam why me why not is a very funny title but I'm looking
across right now at a a rapper named Big Shug yeah who was from the Gangstar camp triple oh Jesus
it's a fucking great title it's good and he did it way before Kanye did Zezus or whatever the
fuck you called that thing Jesus I tried listening to that new one the other night I can't can't
I can't people are despising it I haven't seen one positive word about it it's like a crazy gospel
mashup like yeah it's not I'm not saying it's bad I just I'm just saying it's in for me man yeah his
last two were unlistenable I thought so we're the last two they barely were released I mean it
almost called yay and one was called like ghosts love trees or something I thought which one is
the one where it's like I hate bipolar it's so awesome yeah whatever yeah uh yeah look the man's
not known for his consistency let's put it that way I saw with our boy Vince Abel the who the
other night who were spectacular better than when I saw they're possible look I don't know they're
better than when I saw him five years ago on their greatest hits tour because it had a lot more
personality there are planes this some of their favorites they played with the ball orchestra which
was cool but opening was Liam Gallagher we rushed up there to see him Vince loves Liam yeah sorry my
phone I thought it was on silent Jesus Christ was that Salisbury Hill what do you what do you what do
you got as your ringtone I got this because I left my iPhone in a cab and I have this
galaxy phone as a standard until I can get the phone back okay and that's a ring that's the
default ringtone on it I've never even bothered to change it I didn't want this phone to get too
comfortable there enough uh Liam Gallagher came out he sang five songs he sounded horrible three kind
of boring new songs one oasis song that sounded like he couldn't come anywhere near hitting the notes
anymore what was the oasis song rock tonight I'm a rock a roast okay but he did it like four
octaves lower no like you weren't getting any wonder wall he closed with wonder wall which he made the
audience sing almost an entirety okay it was awful frankly that's a shame it was that's a shame
he said that's it five tracks five tracks I've never seen such a short opening act
and then the who comes out Pete Pete Townsend does the guitar yes full swing throws his shoulder
out immediately somehow he still does the windmills not as much yeah windmill that's the word for it
yeah I couldn't think of what you would call that so let's get on with the show and an honor of Liam
because I couldn't think of any for Morris he somehow get on with the Joe Sally can wait
she knows it's too late as she's walking on by right that's great and I've got a
Morris you want for you and I can't believe you missed it you ready yeah I was trying to talk
while thinking that's fine but you did it let's get on with the Joe friend in a joma right there
I like it to actually rhyme with the schema girlfriend in a joma yeah but say just start with Joe
friend that still makes sense Joe friend in a joma yeah all right yeah all right it's a good one all
right for whatever well I don't like to do that though I don't like to start with like the fourth
word it's got to come organically it's got to it's got to come original it's got to start with a rhyme you
mean yeah okay it's got to start with the Joe oh I'm trying to break you out of your you know I
could have done Joe Vemberspawn to monster what's that no Vemberspawn to monster he didn't do that's a
mercy song yeah or Smith song he more say he didn't do the more you ignore me the closer I get
maybe because it sucks that song is awesome I know I'm just kidding no that's you know what
I thought it sucked when I was younger and now I like it I also thought Friday I'm in love sucked
when I was younger now I really like that song great song great joke by the way that I just thought
of because you said you're calling your own great joke I don't know no not my joke asshole no
as a golden girls joke man this this I don't know why I just thought of this but it had something
something you said reminded me but man this this lit me up yesterday they're at an art gallery
or an exhibit and there's a mime with white paint on his face doing all the dumb mime shit and
Sophia walks up and she goes why are you wearing a mask so your mother won't be embarrassed
that's good that's good yeah it was very funny anyway let's uh mosey on over sure to the movie corner
start us off Joe I've only got two for this week because we just recorded like yesterday or something
then I should start it off right um I can start and then you can do two yeah yeah you start it I'll do
the yeah yeah all right yes that makes more sense I feel it does well then started off I sore well Joe
you said you're not gonna see zombie land two right I can if you think it's I just if you're saying
it's not that hot like I don't really feel like seeing it I'm not that interested I'm just gonna do
it zombie land double tap no idea why it is called double tap I guess appealing to the millennials uh it
made a lot of money I sat there stone faced um I I would say I hated it I almost walked out early
it was getting laughs I mean to me these just felt like the most funnily obvious jokes old jokes
nothing fresh about it I really enjoyed the original I might revisit it and not feel the same
way no the original it's holds up the film Murray stuff was awesome you know but uh this really
just kind of plots along the highlight I would say is uh the girl who plays the dumb blonde who is
zoeach she's the highlight she's the highlight literally the trailer I was like I can't
set through 90 minutes of this character this is this is that is such a bad unbelievable sit -com like
multi -cam character I was like this is so broad it's stupid and I am telling you she's the only
thing with a pulse in the movie it's also a bad sign to me when the only person in the major cast
I'm not tired of seeing is the girl from Little Miss Sunshine like Gal Breslin yeah like I'm a huge
Woody Harrelson fan I he's doing too much he's doing too much Emma Stone I think she's fantastic I'm
getting tired of her Eisenberg is teetering on it like it's like yeah Breslin's the only one where I'm
not like kind of rolling my eyes like okay well you want to talk about people I'm done with they brought
in Thomas middle ditch forget it I'm out you read his playboy interview where he talked about his three
sums right after he got married he decided he wanted to have an open relationship yeah he's saying
it like he's a hero why is nobody calling him a scumbag they are I mean that's all Twitter was for a
week okay they meet up with it's exactly Bizarro Seinfeld they meet up with Luke Wilson who's exactly
like Woody Harrelson Thomas middle ditch exactly like Eisenberg yeah that's it I'm out I'm not
middle ditch it I mean like every joke you've seen a million times the review the positive reviews and
the big box office I don't get it I would say definitely skip zombie land double tap and then Bill
Murray you know obviously the clear highlight of the first one you're waiting for it and then
it ends and I'm like of course they couldn't get Bill Murray back I mean that makes sense and then
they do this post credits thing where they flash back to a press junket for Garfield three and they
have Bill Murray it's got to be two because two was actually made it's a it's a joke though oh because
the joke in well the joke in the first one is he they say any regrets he says maybe Garfield two
so why wouldn't they just make that I don't joke they probably weren't trying to stick to the
continuity of the zombie land averse but the entire credits is Bill Murray being subjected to like
beating the shit out of Al Roker who's interviewing him Al Roker is a weatherman and turns into a zombie
no this he turns into a zombie and then the last one he's just beating the shit out of
people Roker I mean turns into a zombie yeah exactly yeah okay and Murray really doesn't even have
funny dialogue he's just kind of beating people up like he's an action star I don't know it wasn't
for me I say pass I saw most of and I do intend on finishing it but I got most of the way through it
but I've seen enough that I feel like I can give it a fair rating at this point for what the movie
is I bought I went to Best Buy the other day I was in a shopping center where they're just
happened to be a Best Buy and I thought let me go in and see if they have any deals on Blue Race for
Halloween sure sure enough they did one of them I'm gonna actually save to talk about for scary
stuff today but they had leprechaun returns on Blue Race for eight bucks I'm like I'm curious enough
to see this I I trashed the trailer I thought it looked terrible right but I was like God damn it I
really want to see what this is like and that's as cheap as you're gonna see it bought it I'm about
three -fourths of the way through it I'm having a great time it's absurd it's actually they actually
do a really good job of explaining how the leprechaun comes back all right why the leprechaun comes back
they set it up fairly suspensfully they give him his dumb little jokes that he's gonna make but the
Gore is a lot of fun the kills are a lot of fun okay and I would say that I'm enjoying it more than
any other leprechaun movie I've ever seen and most of the leprechaun films within 25 minutes I'm
just like Jesus Christ man right this is fun the only my only criticism right I mean you know what
you're getting the sci -fi is actually kind of doing some cool stuff it's a sci -fi movie it was released
on Blu -ray and stuff and so it's R rated but you know they just also did the new critters sequel with
D Wallace yeah and that actually looks pretty good too and I want to see that I don't want to pay
$20 for the Blu -ray but I do want to see it like I think sci -fi is on to some cool stuff with
like snatching up these legendary franchises that aren't crazy expensive right or the most revered
and doing these like sort of reboot sequels to do them justice after they've had several bad sequels
my only criticism of the film really is or it's not even criticism I wish Warwick Davis would have
done it his absence is noticeable but the guy that's filling in form does a fine job in a little
person yeah and I'm I'm it's an enjoyable film I say for seven bucks you know six bucks eight bucks
whatever it's worth the price of admission is it party bill party no he's dead hologram it's a
hologram bill party but they dress the hologram in a costume which is confusing because it keeps falling
down okay the hologram can't hold the clothing on there enough yeah I saw honey boy honey bully but
what movie did you see honey boy is an interesting concept really I mean the movie was written by shy
a buff it's an actor I've always liked especially you know his recent kind of indie stuff when
Hollywood edged him out I love the buff man I think that guy is doing everything that everybody made
fun of him for I'm like no that's him doing it right yeah it's him saying why don't you go fuck yourselves
yeah yeah I've always liked him American honey is a great movie that he was great in this is honey boy
the man likes honey clearly he's the Winnie the Pooh of indie cinema folks but he basically wrote his
own life story and he had like a stage father who in an effort to keep him off drugs and alcohol
became like his manager so his son at age 10 was like his boss and the dad resented that because he
had always wanted to be an actor and the mom is estranged so the buff plays his own father
in the movie an absolutely phenomenal child actor named Noah Joupe plays 10 -year -old ish Shaya and
Lucas hedges from you know Manchester by the sea and many other movies plays him at age you know
20 okay so we keep going back and forth between like Transformers era LaBuff and child actor on
Disney shows LaBuff and is it actually is it like based on these two people or is it actually
is it Shaya LaBuff in the movie they never call him by name but it is very clearly Shaya LaBuff so
they don't ever say we got to get to the Transformers set they just know that he's doing some big robot
thing exactly right got it um Shaya LaBuff playing his father is one of the best most interesting
performances certainly of the year I would be amazed if he's not nominated he was incredible like
I would imagine I wanted to see footage of his dad because I bet it's so accurate in the way like
you can only impersonate your own parents you know right he was incredible in it he played him as just
a despicable hateful man um I related to a great deal the movie and it was very very well done LaBuff
wisely did not direct it it doesn't quite tell like a satisfying story it's just kind of a slice
of life but as like an artsy type movie I thought it was super good super entertaining and LaBuff I think
should be nominated for an Oscar all right uh I saw Dolomite is my name oh what do you think
oh it was it listen it was it was a Eddie Murphy is excellent in it it is a well executed but paint by
numbers biopic story and it's an enjoyable film my disappointment was only in I mean but that's not
it's not the movies fault that this is what people do for the last two weeks everybody that's been
to a screening of this thing has been saying like this is the funniest fucking movie ever Eddie Murphy
is back and it's like then you watch you go this is just this is a dramatic story about a man that has
some funny scenes this is not they're making it sound like it's nutty professor three or something
yeah I wouldn't think of it even as a comedy really I mean in the same way Ed Wood is a comedy yeah
exactly there are some very funny parts um Wesley sniper is very funny in it for sure um the large
girl I don't know her name but she's great in it yeah queen bee queen bee let me get her name I
hate when I don't know somebody's name it always makes me feel like it should have she's great everybody is
great like it's well done um I just was sad that it wasn't I went in like expecting to be like cracking
up yeah I was like now this is like a real story about this guy I was always a Rudy Ray Moore fan
I was really respected him sure um I love like learning this stuff about him that you learned
the movie that he was the guy that basically invented party albums I didn't know that right um
but I was familiar with the records they were talking about in the movie I was familiar with the movies
because I saw them in the way that Eddie Murphy talks about seeing them for the first time
you know my friends and I in college saw them the same way you the you would rent these things
and get super high and watch them and laugh because you'd be like this is so crazily bad like what is
happening um but I also like towards the end of Rudy Ray Moore's life or career he was in on the
joke he got it you know yeah um and the movie is very endearing it's you know it makes you really
appreciate him very much but it's you know it's paint by numbers stuff which is fine so it was the
queen movie and I love that um I was just sad that it wasn't as cackly funny as I thought it was
gonna be just from what people were saying um and then also too I felt that they stepped on too many
jokes because they would put them into montages with music playing behind them there was far too many
montages in this where you're missing these great moments because they're being buried in these
on in these music beds right and whatever and I thought the movie suffered a little bit because of
that some of the experience of watching it that being said it's it's it's a great little movie you know
and I thought my little that's not the meaning I didn't mean it to it but it's it is a little film
it's I mean considering the star power this is a pretty small movie yeah it's you know so um there
was something fun about seeing in the theater and kind of infectious the laughter and the cheering
and everything I will say yeah I can imagine that divine is great my buddy Craig Robinson awesome he
was fucking great in it um Chris rock great in a little cameo yeah Chris snipes does steal the show
snipes isn't great I mean he's got that cocaine pinky finger right he's really really funny yeah
divine joy Randolph is the woman who the who also kind of steals her scenes uh my only grievance
because I thought it was enjoyable throughout was the amount of endings it almost had a fellowship
of the king type pile up of endings till you're like guys come on but I I loved it I loved it uh my
favorite joke or the one that made me laugh hardest and it's one that people will I'm sure get angry at
and consider it appropriate but it made me laugh when his gay friend when they're at the
barbecue yeah and he says the thing about he's like I need a best boy and he's like I'd like a best
boy and he goes come on now we had a nice barbecue don't know what I want to hear that shit
yeah I mean it was great the way they treated that character was probably not how he was treated
in 19 whatever but uh yeah I I just thought it had a good vibe yeah there's the line in the
diner where he's like what else are you gonna do in jail you could fuck yeah we know you could
fuck that's the guy Titus Burgess from uh uh unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt who steals the shit out
of that show he said he had some huge laughs he's great in this movie too everybody is really good man
like it's it's again my disappointment only came from and it's no fault of the films it was just
people were talking about this like it was gonna be like watching trading places right and it's not
that kind of movie it's it's you know it's it's a pretty straightforward film that has funny moments
in it but uh he everybody's really great particularly Eddie Murphy like the guy is just like god almighty
and like I know those I know don't like like I'm familiar with all that like I've seen the movies I
I knew the standup and away before this when this movie was announced I was excited because I was like
holy shit they're gonna do a movie about Rudy remote um he fucking nails it dude yeah like
he was awesome he just this spot on the way he captures people is it's just fucking quick he said in
Jimmy in the Jimmy Kimmel interview he has a puppet of Paul Mooney um that he pulls out only when
Paul Mooney is at his house okay and he talks to Paul Mooney as Paul Mooney through the puppet okay
and he starts and then Jimmy Kimmel goes what does Paul Mooney say and then he does an impression
of Paul Mooney reacting to the puppet and it's the most exact Paul Mooney impression I've ever heard
my the it's the only Paul Mooney it's it's instantly identical to his it's it's insane how good he is
Eddie Murphy is one of the top 10 most talented people on the planet unquestionably uh I found this
a little upsetting but also it made sense to me the sequel to coming to America is called coming to
America with a two yeah that's it it's called no column number two America that's the same director
as Dolomite Craig Brewer who did uh you know hustlin flow I think he's a good director I'm gonna see
it I can't wait to see it too I'm a little bum that land is isn't back to do it again yeah but uh but
but you know look you'd be head two people with a helicopter that didn't stop from getting
do the first one now it sure didn't uh yeah that was right after that incident actually uh and my
third is a picture called motherless Brooklyn which I hate the title so much uh it's Edward Norton
he's got Tourette syndrome it's clearly they you know they talk about how he wanted to make this movie
for 20 years and it's so obviously because he wants to get an Oscar off of it he has Tourette syndrome
and for two and a half hours he's in every single scene and in every single scene every single line
he's gone it can't shit piss it is so annoying so annoying and he's trying to solve a mystery
so it's like distracting to say the least there are some sort of interesting scenes of where he's
like trying to connect with a woman or trying to interrogate somebody and he has to keep explaining
to them what his affliction is but ultimately I sat and watched this thing I was talking with my
buddy I saw it with I was like how the fuck can you not have his illness factor in ailments sorry
factor into the plot right at no point is he hiding from someone and right he gives up his location
through the Tourette at no point even the jerky boys knew to do that in the movie you have to get out
sticky situations by doing crazy voices yes it has to factor in in some way or else you're just doing
this I guess because the character in the book did but because you want to win an Oscar and it is so
distracting Edward Norton it's just annoying Bruce Willis's second build Bruce Willis is in this
movie for two minutes it's one of those old like they did with the thin red line where it's like
George Clooney right walks past the camera and doesn't say anything right walks it at the very
end it wasn't just a line yeah it was a thin red line I wish they'd given him some more thin
red lines because they pitched him as the star Alex Baldwin is in it playing brothers with Willem
Defoe if you want to see two brothers who look very dissimilar from each other right Defoe is good
as always Baldwin is kind of fine they they lean so heavily on him being a Trumpian character that
of course the very knowledgeable Hollywood screening room was like did you catch that it was about
Trump and it's like yeah we all got it the movie annoyed the fuck out of me it's going for like a
Chinatown thing and that's sort of the interesting element about it it's a it's Norton looking for who
killed his best friend right yeah sorry he's looking for who killed his best friend but the bigger
story is what they're doing to like what they considered slums which basically they just mean
black neighborhoods and neighborhoods with minorities they were trying to wipe them out that years
this take place it takes place in 1955 I didn't know that even though the book takes place in 1999
so that historic that New York history aspect of it and the same way that Chinatown has a lot of
fascinating LA history shit that stuff works everything else is just a miserable slog it did not
need to be two and a half hours it looks good it's not a complete waste of time but it's an annoying
movie you know what I do have one more oh good I got a few episodes into the new season excuse me
of channels zero which is the sci -fi anthology series each season is based on a different creepy
pasta from the internet creepypast as if you don't know our urban legends that are on the internet
you know like these internet spread slender mommy yeah slender yeah slender man slender man
that kind of stuff I got to say people and I put the feelers out to the listeners tell me of what
I'm missing here when I'm wrong I heard great reviews about this latest season I heard that it
was riveting and whatever it's well done but my god almighty I cannot get into this fucking thing
to save my life I don't give a shit I really am trying to find some spark of interest in this thing
it's yet another a season of channel zero that revolves around a weird door existing they love
their doors in this series this is the second season literally that it was season two and now
this one where a huge plot device immediately is a weird door that appears for no reason okay
and it's not related as far as I can tell to season two I don't know guys I mean look I like channel zero
way way way I hate American horror story because it plays as I believe I've said before on this show
like a 13 year old trying to show you he's allowed to curse and say tits right you know it's so
desperately fucking edgy uh that it's just I think it's stupid and I think it's a lot of stunt casting
on that show too which I also think it's stupid channel zero they they they bring in casts of people
that are not well known in the mainstream that are immensely talented like you know it's it's great
it's a great great show I'm just not it's this is not grabbing me man so in fact season three was
the door one the other door so two seasons are on about a door um I was so disturbed by the man
covered in teeth just that picture that I never watched the show I love that first season it was
about a kid show creepy kid show that was hitting all my notes yeah anyway I'm not saying it's bad
this season I'm just saying I'm I'm missing something and if anybody out there knows what I'm
missing let me know because I feel like I feel like something's going over my head here uh with that said
little scary stuff for you uh I said I'd gone into Best Buy to purchase some Halloween
priced DVDs and Blu -ray uh there's a phantasm set out that you can get I got it at Best Buy for
$12 .99 Walmart carries it for $14 .99 Amazon carries it for $12 .99 once the Halloween cells are over
you can still at least get it on Amazon for cheap um this is it's a DVD set it is every phantasm movie
starting with phantasm remastered ending with phantasm ravager $13 bucks I went out of my way to look
up review and and then all the special features from the Blu -ray set right I went out of my way to look
up reviews of the DVD set specifically on the internet to make sure what's the catch what's the
catch and I kept seeing these are amazing quality I don't understand why anybody is paying $200 for the
Blu -ray set you can just get this one yeah and it's great so I bought it and uh you know if you're a
phantasm fan I think that's a pretty good goddamn deal agreed uh and it was also saying repeatedly
which is true they were like every review was like does the cover art suck yes is it terribly packaged
yes yeah don't let that be the thing that throws you off and that was my thought I would look at it
and I'd be like this can't be good and then I read the Blu -ray as though no it's the DVDs but according
to the reviews I read they're saying this is a negligible right uh difference in quality
indesernables the better word I guess um and that this is the way to go but you're getting all five
movies and you're getting all the fucking special features that's great I I went back to Best Buy
for the first time in ages the other day and and uh it's just fun to walk through the aisles again
you're gonna see down at the Alamo they got that video store which I fucking love I was gonna buy
Annabelle comes home just came out on Blu -ray which I do want to own it was 14 bucks for the Blu -ray
which is a hell of a deal yeah the only reason I didn't buy it was I'm like in a month they're
gonna come out with some fucking triple box set of all three right and then all as a completionist
I want to have those even though I didn't even like the first two yeah I'm sick yeah something wrong
with me and you're moving so you don't need to be buying things anyway I don't shake it don't forget
that that's true uh did you watch the new joe bob speaking of phantasm because he did it kind of bum me
out of christmas there's so many great christmas horror movies and he did phantasm one three and four
skipping to yeah I just was it seemed like a missed opportunity this year for the Halloween one he did
Halloween one Halloween two and then Halloween five which I don't know it's not even that it's
Halloween one four and five one four and five I was I didn't watch this one because never
when I've seen those movies a million times sure number two four and five uh hey if they're
on fine I'm not going out of my way to watch them yeah number three I felt like that was a real
fucking mail it in he's a shudder's part like I was like come on guys this is all about these weird
crazy exploitation driving movies phantasm I'll go with you on Halloween he spends the first five
minutes kind of suddenly shitting on shutter he's like they you know where else could you watch
john carpenters Halloween you know like he's kind of shitting on it and it's it's insane because
he basically put shutter on the fucking map I mean he shut down their servers he's the first
he's the reason a lot of people signed up for it and now they're just giving him Halloween four
and five well outside of this too man you're doing Halloween for Halloween fine which every you know
that that's something like that blockbuster video would have come up right exactly so there's
nothing that unique about it but then also let me get this straight you're doing three of them
and two of them are the worst two yeah or next to six I mean it's the same issue with phantasm show
them all in order or don't do it like you have people who are like oh cool I'm sure there's like 16
year olds who are like I'm gonna watch all the Halloween movies with joe bob and then it's like oh we're
skipping to well here's the thing with phantasm you could get away with it because two is recapped at
the beginning of three anyway yeah and two is the only one that didn't have the same actor playing Michael
in it right so that I was like I can live with that I love two it's my favorite one but I could live
with that this to me is like there's there's continuity issues here yeah there's you're two of the
three movies or two of the the the the possible fucking Halloween movies H2O is better uh two is better
three is better uh eat fuck man I wasn't a huge fan of that new one but I'd take that over the god damn
yeah over four five apparently he just shat on four and five two I mean show Halloween one and then
show three great Halloween movies you know it's not far exactly yeah uh the Christmas one coming up
I think because people are so annoyed by the phantasm thing will hopefully be something along the lines
of black christmas uh silent night deli night whatever I look forward to it well I get it too by the way
I also get that shutter's got rights to what they have rights to they gotta work with what that's fine
so I just hope they have some stuff on on the shelf that they can use I gotta tell you to man
here's a quick news cycle before we move the movie this fucking uh blum house remake of black christmas
can kiss my ass yeah I saw the trailer first of all black christmas has already been remade second of
all it's not a movie that ever needed to be remade because the first one is a fucking masterpiece third
of all it's just so painfully desperate enough let's do it where the girls become badass and fight the
kill and it's like okay then don't call it black christmas anymore right that's not what that movie
is about right just make another movie and give it a different fucking title the title means nothing
to anyone who's gonna want to see the remake of black christmas it's so stupid I can't they're doing
this with everything we were talking about this at lunch the other day like that house of haunted
hill series on Netflix is so fucking far away from the source material and guys nobody in this day
and age is going ooh house on haunted hill my fate nobody's doing that yeah no kid that wants to see
a blum house harm movie is gonna go black christmas right half of the people that remember black christmas
are dead or in their 70s by now yeah I mean even horror aficionados don't always know that movie so
I don't know what they I don't know what they're getting by paying a hundred thousand dollars for
the rights or whatever they paid it's just it's just fucking stupid anyway I am hearing good things about
doctor sleep well and after several lackluster trailers the latest one I was kind of like this looks
pretty fucking cool I'm excited about doctor sleep here's by the way you're probably here in this in
January and doctor sleep has already come and gone we're kind of recording these out of order a little bit
uh steven king gave it a good review yeah well it's just how contrary but this is how
contrary steven king is to fucking to the original sure is that really you like the sequel to the movie
that you hated about your book right right uh then by the way this movie went out of its way to make
it a sequel to the movie and not to your book um but also to yeah dude he just came out and talked
about the new child's play uh I was like I just love that movie so fucking much I'm like is this guy
I mean I feel like he's in a wheelchair with like pea soup dripping out of the
I mean I like the new child's play too but uh but I would just love this movie so fucking much yeah
it's crazy uh yeah he also said the new pet cemetery was great but that's embarrassing yeah
all right let's talk about a movie that in my opinion at least and I got a little taste of from Joe
midway through but I haven't talked to him since he finished the movie uh for me the best movie
of the year and for me my favorite movie the last several years I would say there's really no
way to overrate it because it's a masterpiece that movie is called parasite Joe did you love it as
well uh let me say first uh this is going to be very spoiler heavy are we gonna do that I think we
need to at this point it's been out you've seen it so yeah parasite is a movie talk because here's
why though too in case they haven't seen it I wouldn't explain yeah I need to be able to talk about
the twist and turns in this to give my review sure and it's gonna be too vague otherwise that's why
I think we need to so fair warning ahead of time parasite is a movie more than almost any other I can
think of where you should go in completely cold I went in knowing nothing and I've told everyone
they have to do the same the trailer does a pretty damn good job about not spoiling anything and just
showing you kind of vague moments but um it's really important to go in cold so if you haven't seen
it turn it off well listen once you've watched it and here we go uh this movie like a lot of Korean
film uh in the that falls under the horror or thriller genre uh has a lot of different moods to it
it takes you in a lot of different directions it starts as a sort of family kind of drama thing
and then it starts to get kind of quirky and funny yeah and then it starts to get a little bit darker
and then it gets extremely dark yeah and I would say this this movie I was I was very intrigued at the
top of it I was really into this story when you get into the middle of this thing okay so basically
here's what it's about it's about a very poor family in South Korea uh their son gets a job tutoring
a daughter in a very rich family the way he gets the job is his friend lies for him and says that
this guy is a college student and he's not he's just a kid that lives in the slums uh but he's like
this guy's a college student he's he'll be the best tutor for the daughter and the kid will be a great
tutor for the daughter but he needs he needs the lie to get his way in so he does and immediately the
what the mom uh in this family who's a stay -at -home mom like a very like you know the husband's always
out working making shit loads of money and she's like sort of one of these trophy wives that's left
alone in the house all day with the kids she mentions that she needs an art teacher for the daughter
the kid that's already lied to get into be or for the son excuse me the kid that's already lied to
get into be able to tutor the daughter immediately lies and says that his sister is an art teacher it's
bullshit right they bring the sister in then they start to plot to get the driver fired for the
family driver fired so they can get their dad in as the driver and then the family's really
destitute they need money they're they're folding pizza boxes for cash yeah and then eventually they
get the mother in as the housekeeper while pretending to not know one another yeah they're not at no
point do they say well this is my sister this is my mom this is they pretend like they're just they
just happen to know people that they could be good recommendations for these jobs and right there
you know this the first hour really plays like a screwball comedy there's not much thriller aspect to it
but what it is doing is showing you how much money corrupts people because at first it's like we'll
tell a little white lie to get this job a little white lie that lots of people tell to get jobs by the
end they're causing the or by the end of this first hour they're causing the housekeeper to have a
allergic attack putting her life in danger so they can push the mom in because as they get closer and
closer to this rich lifestyle they become more and more ruthless and your heroes become kind of
monstrous which I thought was a brilliant way of showing how money corrupts which is a lot about
what the movies about yes and then our first major twist comes into play where the family when the rich
family goes away the poor family who was working for them all hang out and start partying in the house
together and really showing how flippantly they feel about this these rich people and right but now they're
risking everything that they've worked so hard to manipulate and get into so then you start to
dislike them and you're like and they have been even when they're drinking at first they've been so
lovable and such a great family and such great characters that it sucks you know like it sucks how much
they start to change yeah long story short they get caught in the house they find out well we don't
go in every detail they get caught in the house and it becomes this sort of they're trapped in the
house and it's very tense because the family comes home unexpectedly these people are now trapped in
the house the previous house keeper that they got fired had come back before the family came home from
camping she's dead supposedly in the cellar because they knock her down the stairs to shut her up
they've got a dead body on their hands they're stuck in the fucking house the families there they're
hiding under the couch it's very tense this is the point in the movie where I started to lose a bit
of interest and I was like man if this is just going to turn into one of these they're trapped in the
house and have to figure out how to get out like I don't care and this is like that's nowhere near
what this movie is it keeps evolving from there from this point and as it evolved past that situation
because they do end up getting out of the house safely right and becomes fully what the movie really is
in that last 45 minutes or whatever that's when I was like this is one of the greatest movies
I've ever seen in my life like I can't this is happening here you said I was waiting for the other
shoe to drop there Joe no I was it is it is it is and I agree it is one of the best movies I have ever
seen and yeah it is revealed that the housekeeper's husband the original housekeeper's husband is
living in the back of the or in the back of a shelving unit in the basement he's got his own kind of
home down there which they explain was back in the day South Korean homes would have bunkers
built into the bottom right into the basement area in case North Korea ever attacked and they say
that rich people were embarrassed about having these bunkers right so when the people that
currently own and live in the house bought the house they had no idea the bunker was even down there
right so the original housekeeper has been keeping her husband down there so he can live for free because
they couldn't afford to live right meanwhile these people have millions of millions of dollars it is
the family the family that owns the house it is such I mean forget timely all anyone is talking
about right now is the disappearance of the middle class and how there is only the rich and the poor
and this movie not American made somehow is the best thing I've seen on explaining what is wrong
with America and what is wrong with the economy right now and what is wrong with people in general
and there's a scene near the end that that's also a running joke in the movie yeah they repeatedly say
like they'll talk about a product will go it's got to be good it's from America right right yeah yeah and
that detail by the way that okay there's a bunker and it's it was to hide from North Korea and families
didn't know about it is so it the whole movie is full of that kind of shit and you think about when you
watch an American movie the half -assed pathetic way they'll try to explain a plot twist and this movie
has twist after twist after twist every five minutes there's another big juicy twist that any other
movie would be thrilled to have as its main turn of events but they're doing it every five minutes and
they're all based in reality in fact and they make sense and even as the movie gets crazier and
crazier you're never like fuck this because everything is so beautifully explained and and links
up so when you know the kid had this nightmare of seeing someone emerge from the basement and when you
see that scene of that guy's head popping out which is a amazing scene that all adds up you're like
that was the guy from the basement coming up once and he saw him that was real all there's all these
moments where you're like this is gonna get away from them there's too many balls in the air and they
land every ball the uh and speaking of twists the the emotional shifts in this thing that the scene
where they're hiding after the rich people come home surprisingly two minutes before that the dad
who the dad of the poor family is being a complete pig in this house trashing things he's being he's
just being a drunk and it's when you start to dislike him and then cut to 10 minutes later
he's hiding under the couch under the coffee table now because he's trying not to get caught
and you're mad at him that he's put himself in such a careless position and the husband unbeknownst to the
guy staying under the table starts talking about how that guy smells yeah and the the immediate
emotional shift on the guy where he is so hurt by this and he smells his own shirt realizing I smell
right you feel so fucking sorry for him immediately and it's like how am I feeling sorry for this guy
hated him four minutes ago I was mad at him and I feel sorry for him and that's also just such a seed
they plant where you're like this fucker's gonna snap yeah he's gonna snap that pays off in such a
massive way at the end at the kid's birthday party which is like a scene where people I saw it with
Heather and people were standing up in the theater like the tension got so great people were standing
up I was laughing yeah I was it was like a lot to kind of release tension it was almost like the it
was almost like the end of the toy where they crashed the like Ku Klux Klan yeah yeah watching the like
it's like everything from the whole movie comes together in a perfect storm to ruin something right
I was like this is almost funny because the whole thing with that kid's nightmare is
four birthdays ago whatever he snuck downstairs to get cake out of the fridge and he sees this ghost
come out of the seller yeah and it was a horrifying experience for him a traumatic experience and
then you realize oh it was the guy that lives in the basement sneaking out to get food right but he's
a little kid so he thinks it's a ghost and then as they're bringing the cake out for the first birthday
in four years they've had in the house for this kid because this kid was too traumatized by his last
birthday they had in the house as they're bringing the cake out the guy from the seller comes running out
with like a hatch it yeah that was hilarious and you're just like you're like this this is the
first thing the kids gonna see again yeah kid sees him faint yeah I was like this is this is like almost
comical this was great it was genius and when they introduced the supernatural element before you know
what's going on I was like they're gonna go for some cheap supernatural shit some bad explanation
and everything is real by the end of it you're like not only is it real but everything makes sense
and that was the beauty of it what a scene that I really loved it so at the beginning there's this
drunk guy who keeps pissing in their alley outside their house and a neighbor comes out to kind of
defend the neighborhood and they both throw buckets of water on the guy and it's like stop pissing and
being an animal then at the end when the neighborhood is being flooded they try to return to their home
and people are begging them for help their old friends their old neighborhood right and they go
right by our heroes because they've had a taste of this rich life are now not a part of that
community anymore right because when you're rich you're not a part of a community you're out for
yourself and those little details and that willingness to paint the heroes who you've loved this entire
movie in this shitty light the a it's it's truth to characters and truth to the theme of the movie no
matter how it makes people look because the themes in this movie are what elevates it I think to you
know it could have just been an amazing thriller and it is that but like what puts it above even an
old boy or other classics of this genre is the thematic stuff to me is amazing it really is and then
the final the final blow of the movie is the husband the dad of the poor family snaps at the birthday
party for the way the rich dad has been treating him right he sees the rich dad cover his nose at the
cent of the man who's been living in the basement who just murdered his wife yeah he's so offended by
this that the fact that this guy's dead wife is on the ground yet the his first thought is to cover
his nose from the cent that the dad runs at him murders this guy he's been working for
and then to hide from the cops descends into this basement chamber that nobody knows is there
but now has become the guy living under the house again yeah for the new guy who he scoffed at at one
point and uh and it ends with this soliloquy of the son writing a letter to the dad finding out the
dad is living down there secretly and knowing the dad can't leave because he's wanted by the police
and it ends with that soliloquy of the son writing the letter to the dad saying I will
my goal will be to make so much money I can buy that house right and then we can finally be a family
again so even in the end the endearing moment between it still does revolve around money yeah
and it seems like it revolves around money in the right way but they're back to where they were at
the top right which was if we could just have some money we could be a family we could live better
and then the end it's they're right back there again if I could just afford this we would be fine
right and at the beginning when the four you know the mother father son daughter are sitting penniless
they're very funny seeing from the trailer where they're saying open the windows so we can get some
of the fumigation to kill the bugs in our apartment yeah and they're folding these pizza boxes for money
the family is poor but they are clearly so happy and so loving it actually it may be so jealous
that this family had such a wonderful caring loving relationship with each other and that's when
they're poor and as money enters the picture it drives them apart it leads to violence it leads to
their entire lives being destroyed and their final revelation from this as Joe was saying is
I got to make more money it's it's an amazing fucking movie and generally when Heather my wife and
I go see a movie we go on the car what did you think yeah yeah I didn't like the ending yeah
it was so stupid right and then we talked about something else we talked about parasite for three days
she would like come home from work and we were like just picked up the conversation where we left off
and it's that kind of movie it's the kind of movie where I would I would respect somebody
less who didn't like it I really do mean that it is incredible and it makes every other movie
look so fucking lazy when you think about a movie that'll has one twist to pull off and they
botch it and whatever out this movie is constantly evolving and becoming something else and everything
works and everything makes sense I don't know how they wrote this script but it is something to be
in awe of and I know they don't like giving or awards to other countries but this movie deserves
absolutely best screenplay I would say best picture it won't get it but the acting is great there's
nothing you could have a problem with in this movie I was talking to my friend Crystal about the
interesting duality that characters have in Korean films yeah we're saying like in other Asian
countries like Japan China it's a little more black and white you know what I mean right Japan
if you go back to like sort of classic cinema Japan you'll get a lot of the samurai stuff where
it's very like it's very it's Star Wars it's what Star Wars is based on it's very black and white it's
very good versus evil China if you go back to the old China you know karate flicks and all that stuff
just for an example it's a lot of you killed my master I will avenge him that is what honor is blah blah blah
right Korean movies and I haven't seen tons of Korean movies over the years but at least some of
the modern ones that I've seen you know it's audition it's stuff like that where it's right because
audition was Korea right audition is Japanese oh that's Japanese all right never mind then anyway
then this could be completely wrong then I thought audition was free but I was just saying like a movie
like this it's interesting that it's a product of a country torn in half yeah because to us it's
very clear North Korea is bad South Korea is good if you live there there are probably people
that have family in North Korea right live in South Korea say I love my mother and I love my father
but they're over there yeah and they're not here or whatever it is and I think that that gives you a
very interesting perspective when it comes to art and and people and the how complicated it can all get
right especially in a country that is such an alley middle class you know as we're headed for here
it suddenly it's there's there's a much clearer perception of like what desperation really is
what struggle really is yeah and even in this you know this rich family who were supposed to we're
supposed to eventually love at the end of the movie when the when the poor dad is living in the
chamber underneath and he's he has that moment of remorse about the rich dad that he murdered right
I think his name is mr. Kim or something yeah but he he takes starts crying and he goes I'm sorry
mr. Kim I'm sure yeah and you realize like yeah that guy wasn't really a bad dude no you just came from
a life where he didn't understand certain things and and he had flaws but he took good care of this guy
you know right you understand both sides and that's what makes the movie so complex and so beautiful
really is that like we've all been the guy who's like oh that homeless guy smelled like piss as you
walk by you know like but there's no there's no clear villains there's no clear heroes in this movie
which is what makes it amazing and I don't think any movie understands America better and that's crazy
that a foreigner did this bong june ho he did memories of murder which is a fantastic movie the host
great monster movie mother a really good movie snowpiercer which I was kind of split on which mother
did he do the it's not the yeah not the other one not the American one but he's well worth going
back and looking through his filmography but he's been a guy who I've always thought yeah he's a really
good filmmaker but nothing ever like punch me in the stomach this is his best movie by far
go check it out Joe and I are off now to see our horror movie marathon uh but if you didn't see
parasite go see it I'm sure now with uh you know if you listen to this in January hopefully it got
a bunch of nominations because it's well deserving two hogs hard and strong upright like uh as
if I ate a blue chew that's our show people I think this episode comes out in January if that is the
case I am on tour this month go to joderosa info for details Pittsburgh Lancaster PA amongst other
cities I also have other uh another tour coming up in February uh go to joderosa dot joderosa info
dot com for information on that tour that'll be more of the Chicago area and then finally uh
uh skankfest in houston texas in march at the secret group uh go to their website the secret group
website and uh to get details on that joderosa comedy on twitter and instagram joderosa comedian on
facebook the patrick wall should twitter and instagram uh check the feed of our patreon because I'll be
bringing you more of these special episodes including one I'm working on where I'll be going
through each film of Oliver stone because I recently rewatched all of them uh that's it
we're on etsy at the hog house if you want merch check with our facebook page and our glorious
leader Emily Florence uh if anyone out there has questions about I still get where is the podcast
still going on whatever communicate with each other let people know we're patreon only thank you so
much for making that transfer with us that's all we got we uh we will be doing the creep show the
shutter series creep show coming up so catch up on that we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell