I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, the inaugural February episode.
I am here with my dear friend Patrick Walsh, my name is Joe DeRosa, and we are back to
discuss a film called Leave the World Behind, which the title was stolen by the producers
from both Pat and my own private diaries.
They know how we feel, and they're trying to speak to us.
Would you like to leave the world behind, Pat?
I think about it every day, I think about it every day.
Not offing myself, but I think about going into some other galaxy, like the end of the
Northmen, like flying off on a majestic horse up into the galaxy, if that makes sense.
I understand, I get it, I get it.
Go big or go home, I say.
Or at least leave the life behind, I often think about like buying a ranch, a cool ranch,
I would call it the cool ranch, and there would be bowls of the cool ranch Doritos out
for everyone to enjoy.
And then what you should do is, Sam Elliott style, when people come to the ranch, you
should greet them by going, welcome to the cool ranch Mojito, and it almost sounds like...
He calls people Mojito?
It sounds like he would, he doesn't.
But it rhymes with Dorito, and it would make sense, it sounds way more like a thing you'd
call somebody, and then you get the full...
Did you watch the entirety of the ranch?
No, no, no, no, I watched the first season, and I enjoyed it, but it was starting already
to get, I was like, this is going to keep getting more and more like dramatic, which
I didn't want to deal with.
And that's where they want all comedy to go, including Multicam.
And then also...
We get it all the time, we're doing an episode of Miss Pat next week, and the notes from
like the network, and then the younger writers is like, there's just, it's just, there's
not anything really meaty behind it, or like the B story, there's not a meaty emotional
thing behind it, and I'm like, yeah, it's a Multicam sitcom B story, you know, some
of them are going to be dumb, and some of them are going to be important issue episodes,
but we're not all going to be important issue episodes, because nobody wants that.
That's drama.
It's my biggest pet peeve with the Golden Girls, is in every episode there, and I feel
like it's a network note, always, but in every single episode, there's like, even amidst
a really wonderfully funny, silly plotline, there's a horribly awkward moment where it
has to get like too real, and it does that sting where it goes, you know, to let you
know something's wrong.
And I remember that on The Simpsons, where it was like, you know, it had been revealed
that there was a mandate from networks with different shows, and The Simpsons was one,
that every episode had to include a lesson of some kind.
And then I remember The Simpsons producers, like, sort of celebrating when that was lifted,
and they were like, now we can just make a fucking show that we want to make.
Right.
But, yeah, Cool Kids was always that, could somebody have dementia?
No, this show's on Friday nights at 9 p .m., people get off work, there's six beers deep,
and that's the show we're making, like, leave me alone.
This is along the lines, we started recording earlier and had to restart because of tech
issues, but this is along the lines, interestingly enough, of what we were talking about, which
is comedy movies that do have a little depth, and that does add something to them.
So it's a little contradictory on both our parts, but for some reason with a comedy movie,
it works, and in a sitcom it doesn't.
I don't know why, you know, Fatso's a great example, Fatso's got a lot of, it's one of
my favorite movies, it's got a lot of really emotional parts, and it makes it, it's what
makes the movie great, trains, planes, trains, and automobiles, you know, but then, you know,
and then you, and then, you know, we were saying it's why you think a movie like Tommy
Boy is actually a good movie, and a movie like Stripes is just a movie that has funny
parts versus being a good movie, you know?
Well, you know, Wet Hot American Summer is like a sketch movie with zero heart to it,
and that's one I would consider a great movie, you know, it's, I don't have hard and fast
rules on this kind of stuff, I feel like I know it when I see it, if, you know, Anchorman
is a great movie without plot or heart, you know, and the me from 10 years ago would have
demanded that comedies be just comedy, that's what I wanted, but, you know, I do, there
difficult about shaping a narrative and a story and emotions and et cetera, then again,
what do I return to most often when I want to laugh, something like, I think you should
leave something like that with nothing like that, so, I'm wishy washy on this opinion.
I think it's, I think it's like any, it's like anything in film and television, it just
either works or doesn't work.
Yeah.
The reason we were talking about this on the previous shell, and that was an issue we didn't
get in a fight, folks, but we were talking about Groundhog Day because we are recording
on Groundhog Day, and Joe's not as much of a fan as I am, and I speculated that it might
be because it's a PG Bill Murray.
It's a cranky, angry Bill Murray that we love, and yet, it's a little sanded down.
And I wish Groundhog Day had just simply bumped up to a PG -13 even because he's a dick, but
he's never like, you know, R -rated tends to lead to comedy.
PG is very rarely a belly laugh to me.
I don't disagree.
I think, I think I didn't, I was saying earlier, I think I didn't initially like Groundhog
Day because, and then I missed the boat because the window closed, but I just think I initially
didn't like it because I want it like smart -ass, fun Bill Murray.
See, it's weird.
Now that I'm older, I'd love a movie where they're like, Bill Murray's going to play
a prick and it's a comedy.
I'd be like, oh, sweet.
Back then, I was like, no, I want like Venkman, which actually, wait, ooh, which brings us
to a new psycho, the new Ghostbusters trailer.
I was very, very happy with what I saw.
They released two, they released an international and then the United States one and they have
entirely different footage, but I think that the American one was better because that's
the one that starts with the voiceover about, I hate these guys, the Ghostbusters are done
and then the reveal is it's Walter Peck and you're like, oh man, this is great, like awesome.
You know, it looks really good and I, you know, the first one for all its negative press
and bullshit, it really laid the ground for like what could be a really fun new franchise,
you know, I'm excited about it.
I think it looks great.
I think adding Kumail and Patton Oswalt is a perfect addition.
Guys kind of known for like their nerd obsessions and the first laugh I've had at a comedy trailer
in well over a year is Paul Rudd saying, look, I'm sorry, but busting, it just makes me feel good.
You know, it makes me feel good.
I laughed out loud.
That has not happened in ages.
I'm ready.
I'm pumped.
I'm excited about it.
I was happy to see Murray pop up in the trailer, which is a good sign that he's in the trailer.
Also was happy to see him smiling.
I don't remember the last time I've seen the man smile on camera.
It's been a while.
And it was just a simple, stupid line, but like him just, Annie Potts' character,
Jeannie, is it like Meltzer or whatever?
Jeannie Metzler, I think.
Metzler.
Just like him coming in like, Metzler's suiting up.
All right.
You know, you're like, and then the tall, dark and horny 12 o 'clock.
You're like, yeah, man, this like feels like Ghostbusters.
Like it just, you know.
I'm pumped.
She was in the last one, right, Annie Potts?
She's in it at the very beginning.
Yeah.
And it makes perfect sense that she steps in because like she and Egon always had that
weird flirtation and it makes perfect sense that she like, you know, like that's awesome.
All right.
There's a female Ghostbuster now and it's Jeannie and she's got Egon quality.
It just makes perfect sense to me.
I think she suited up on the cartoon too, but that's why, that's I think one of the
reasons they're saying there's so, this plays so much like an episode of the cartoon.
I really hope it's good, man.
God, I'm nervous that it's going to be like, nah, we showed you all the fan service in
the trailer.
And other than that, I'm a little, I think the, the, the, the harder, more awkward thing
to do is to launch a new franchise.
And the fact that they did it so successfully to me means two should be a blast personally.
They did all the groundwork of bringing us up to the modern era and filling us in on
what happened.
Now we can just have fun.
Hopefully there's a, in the international trailer, there was something that I was a
little, I was like, I don't know how I feel about that, but it's Winston explaining like
that the ghosts basically there's like ghosts that live in the firehouse now.
And he's basically like, so we can study them.
Like now we can, and I was like, okay, that's kind of interesting.
It seems more like just a device so they can live with Slimer like they do in the cartoon,
but whatever, you know, but I'm excited and man, it's soon.
It's like comes out in March.
It's like right around the corner.
I think so.
I mean, it's, it's things are about to pick up.
I just noticed that Curb is coming back Sunday and got all excited.
You know, it's I'm really enjoying the new True Detective season, which I did read for
the next news psycho.
Joe was telling me that Nick Pizzolato, the guy who did the first season of True Detective
is now shitting in the comments on his Instagram on the new season.
He's like, Hey, I had nothing to do with this and don't blame me.
And I know it's stupid that they're trying to tie it back into the original.
And it's like, why wouldn't you be flattered?
They're trying to tie it into the original.
I've only seen the first episode of the new True Detective with Jodie Foster.
It's only six EPS.
I thought it was fucking great.
It looks great.
The mystery is great.
Foster's great.
We should, when it's done, we should review it because once all six are out,
I'm going to binge it in a day.
We should because it's, it's also it's a Lopez who did tigers are afraid,
which is a on shutter or in a really interesting horror movie.
And it's supposed to have horror elements as well.
Going back to that original, which I forgot.
I rewatched the original True Detective recently and I forgot the kind of supernatural
elements that come into play in it.
But what a dumb thing to do when you have done two other seasons of the show
that were like fine at best.
That's why he's now you got, huh?
That's why he's doing this.
He's he's like, but her like somebody else took the thing.
I mean, I told you last night, there's, there was like all.
It's worse that it's, it's a Hispanic woman.
It's like, come on, dude, like, like read the fucking room.
Like she's done a brilliant job.
Here he, he, I was telling you last night when the first one came out.
Hold on true.
I'm going to actually Google this true detective season one stolen.
There was plagiarism controversy of true detective season one explained.
This is from Vox or Vokes, whatever it is.
There are allegations that Pizzolato heavily borrowed lines from Cole's hand in hand line
from the work of the horror writer, Thomas Legati.
John Padgett, the founder of Thomas Legati online and Mike Davis, the editor and founder
of the Lovecraft easing website, looked into a few of his a lot of famous lines and compared
them to Legato, Legati's work conspiracy against the human race.
Here's an example, true detective.
Here's the line.
We became too self -aware.
Nature created an aspect of nature separate from itself.
We are creatures that should not exist by natural law.
Here's the legati line.
We know that nature has veered into the supernatural by fabricating a creature that
cannot and should not exist by natural law.
Pretty close and that's just, that's just dumb on a Pizzolato's part because people
rip off shit all the time.
You have Matthew McConaughey, who is an extremely literate, borderline genius, alcoholic,
and true detective.
It's a fascinating character, but he's barely, he's not killing himself just out of like,
I'll see what happens.
You know, like he's a miserable, depressed guy.
And all you got to say is like, you know, it's like, what's this guy's name?
Legrand or whatever.
Legato or something.
You can go, you know, you ever read legate to Woody Harrelson?
Then he looks at him and he goes, what do you think?
You know, you get a laugh there and he goes, no, he says blah, blah, blah.
And then you just say what he says and give him credit in the episode.
By the way, he does in other parts of dialogue, like McConaughey literally says at one point,
he goes, it's like Nietzsche says.
Yeah, exactly.
Aiken McGuy.
And that's what that character would do is spouting shit that he's read and seen online
and everything.
Harrelson, by the way, is so funny in that at calling McConaughey out for just being
a weird freak who's his partner.
There are so many laugh out loud moments where he just, he's given him the B Arthur look
half the time.
Like why am I partner with his nutcase?
You could add a laugh track to true detective season one and it would play like a sitcom.
Yeah, for sure.
It's great.
It really is great.
You know, I was happy I watched it again.
The reason I remember the Nietzsche line is because I was writing on Pete Holmes's show
at the time and this was the big Monday morning discussion was true detective.
Every writer's room has that thing that everybody's doing.
And I remember Pete came in one day, I hadn't seen the latest episode and he goes,
this show is incredible.
I mean, they're quoting Nietzsche.
And I remember being so impressed.
Like, wow, Pete's a well -read guy.
He knows that they were quoting Nietzsche.
And then I watched the episode and he goes, it's like Nietzsche says.
And I was like, all right, Pete, let's not walk around as if.
I could pretty much guarantee Pete doesn't know anything about Nietzsche,
which is no insult to Pete.
I don't know anything about Nietzsche either.
But yeah, this piece a lot.
If I was Trump, I'd go, Nick, he's a shit.
Can run his mouth.
So am I reading that right?
Yeah, we are.
We, again, don't want to get into politics again, but like just.
He's allowed to run.
He's just had to pay a woman $83 million for sexual assault.
This is one of our two choices.
It's wild.
I don't know what is going on right now.
It is wild.
I've tuned out.
I can't, I can't stress me out bad, but, but anyway, Nick P.
Nicky P.
Yeah.
You know, he's being a fucking little turd, man.
He, you know, he, his two.
So anyway, he's got all these plagiarism accusations in the first season.
Right.
Also, I believe if I'm not mistaken, some of the team he worked with on the first season
split and he kind of went solo on the second and third seasons.
You know, the classic, I can handle this.
Yeah.
And, and he couldn't.
Season two, despite my major, major fandom of Colin Farrell, of Rachel McAdams, of Vince Vaughn.
It was like a dream cast.
Yeah.
It's terrible.
And, and by the way, I knew there was trouble in Paradise when they announced season two
and it was like a bigger cast.
I was like, oh, we got problems here.
That's never good.
Yeah.
And then the third season, everybody was like, it's much better.
It's much more like the original, but it's like, well, it's sort of, as far as I understood,
like almost a retread of season one, except with different characters.
Well, unfortunately it was boring.
I mean, I, I, I don't know that I ever finished it.
I was too bored.
It was not a compelling story or mystery at all.
So.
So now this woman comes along.
She, look, Nick's off the, he's just an executive producer, which in television means
nothing, right?
You know, it's like.
Well, I'm an executive producer, so that's not true, Joe.
There are, there are writing producers and non -writing producers.
Usually your non -writing producers do nothing.
That's what I mean.
You're, you're a show running.
Yeah.
Writing produce that, you know what I'm saying.
I'm saying if you're just, let's put it this, let me rephrase what I just said.
They are making it clear in these articles about his gas or shade throwing that he is
just an executive producer.
Well, he said it himself.
He said, I had nothing to do with this.
Yeah.
So my point is this.
And why would you try to, I'm sorry, and I'm interrupting you, but why would you try to
distance yourself from something that currently has like a hundred percent?
Well, I'm, this is what I'm getting at is, is either HBO said, take a walk.
Right.
Or he got fed up and said, I don't want to do this anymore.
But.
Definitely the prior.
Yeah, cause I was going to say if it's the latter.
Yeah.
And you want to be Ricky Gervais and Stephen Merchant.
You want to go.
Guys, we're over here watching you from England.
Great work on that American office.
Keep the checks coming in.
We support you a hundred.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
This guy's now throwing shade, which again, makes it seem the prior happened, which is
get the fuck out of here.
We don't, we don't think you can handle this anymore.
And now she comes along, hits it out of the park, has the highest rating critically since
the first season.
And with a coincidence, he doesn't approve.
It's like, you're, you're a dildo, dude.
Well, I think you and fans of this podcast will really enjoy, at least from what I saw
the first one, because it's got major, uh, the thing vibes.
It's at like a station in the snow, you know, and it's there.
Something goes wrong.
It's, it's really cool.
Um, but yeah, it's so dumb.
I worked on outsourced, uh, you know, which was a one season wonder kind of, it was like
the office set in India.
Really a pretty interesting show.
I thought I liked working for it, but, um, there are these things like
the producers of the movie outsourced, which the show was based on, which people don't
even know there was a movie.
No idea.
They were getting sizable checks each week and they, we never saw them.
They weren't even in America.
I don't think, but like that scenario, if that happens to you in Hollywood, shut
your goddamn mouth and enjoy the ride.
You're getting money for nothing and chicks for free, you know?
I, um, I, uh, I think that, uh, it's, um, oh God darn it.
I was going to say, uh, I can't remember now.
Oh well.
New True Detective, the thing we were talking.
Yeah.
Uh, and you were saying that it's got these horror elements and guess what?
And I'll say something that might be controversial, but might not be regarding
season one of True Detective.
Nikki didn't stick the landing.
No, completely agree.
That finale was a disappointment.
Everybody was like, wait a minute, but what about all the supernatural stuff?
Like what, wait, what, wait, what was it?
And why is this -
It's one of the only shows where when it, when I realized it was eight episodes instead
of 10 on the rewatch, I was like, no, I wanted two more.
Like we didn't end this, right?
Yeah.
Totally.
And then there's that weird sort of surreal, but not well executed surreal scene, the
final scene of them at the hospital where it's like clearly the CGI, uh, sky behind
them and you're like, wait, are they dead?
What is going on?
What is this?
Or is that just bad production?
Like it just doesn't work.
So I hope that she sticks the landing in this new season.
Well, this is only six, so hopefully it's a tighter story.
But yeah, it's there's McConaughey like in the cave trying to find the creeper.
And he's, he like, at one point, you know, you're like, is he getting pulled up by
aliens or something?
There's like this special effect thing that doesn't, and you don't know what it is
and it's not good.
It's it doesn't work.
So yeah, I hope she lands it as well.
I assume most of these critics have seen all six.
Usually when it's something that short, they all just watch the whole series,
but you never know.
Speaking of pulled up by aliens, our next episode will be no one can save you.
No one will save you.
Stay tuned.
Actually, you might be right.
Let me check.
I think it's canned.
I think.
It's not super important, but now I have to know.
It's all right.
No one will save you.
Oh, it is will.
All right.
Let's go to that movie corner.
Let's do it, Joe.
So yeah, I want to recommend this podcast called Talking Pictures.
It is a podcast from Turner Classic Movies.
And the first three are up with Nancy Meyers, Steven Soderbergh,
and Emerald Fennell, who did Promising Young Woman and Saltburn.
But it's great.
It's Ben Mankiewicz, who is the TCM host, the main host.
Actually, his brother is the Mankiewicz from Dateline,
and I might be mixing up their names, but they're similar guys.
But he asked them the eight questions that Joe and I always talk about.
What's the most excited you've ever been at a movie?
What's a movie that never fails to make you cry?
What is your mom's favorite movie, your dad's favorite movie?
And they're very revealing conversations.
It's great.
I recommend highly.
So I wrote down so many movie recommendations from there,
especially the Emerald Fennell episode that I had not seen,
and I'm excited to watch.
But on SmartList, which I do listen to because it makes me laugh
and they have such huge great guests all the time,
the Jeff Bridges episode, I highly recommend.
He's as cool and delightful as you'd want him to be,
and he's a guy who never does interviews.
And they talked to him about the car chase in this movie called Against All Odds,
which is a remake of an old noir movie called Out of the Past.
I never knew that because of the Phil Collins song from that movie.
I just assumed that that was, I always thought Against All Odds
was like one of those like romance during wartime movies or something.
Well, the cover is them rolling on the beach making love,
like from here to eternity.
So I understand why you thought that.
But I had always heard of that as just kind of a shitty movie.
I love the song.
The Collins song is a banger, but I had just never watched it.
So Bateman is raving about how it's the best car chase in movie history.
And he's like, it's down the sunset strip.
I don't know how you shot it.
I don't know how you did it.
And it got me thinking about the great car chases, which are like,
you know, usually they say Bullet, which I think is a very boring movie now, but
French Connection, et cetera.
Ronin is a really great one.
Dark Knight, Matrix 2 has a great one.
Terminator 3.
Ronin is a good one because not just the way it's shot,
it's the only, it's testament to De Niro as an actor.
It's the only car chase I've ever seen where I'm watching.
I remember I was watching that movie with Pinkstone and he goes,
they were showing the way De Niro was like, he's like laser focused.
Yeah.
And Pinkstone was like, that's how you would be in a car chase.
You would be like super focused.
And I was like, I can't believe nobody before Robert De Niro figured out like,
no, no, I would have to be like so focused.
Yeah, it's probably because they want to seem cool.
And they're like, well, my guy does this every day.
So he doesn't, but no, you'd need to focus.
Yeah.
Regardless of your cool level.
Like, I feel like Steve McQueen was always like one arm around the passenger seat,
you know, driving these car chases one handed.
And I don't buy that personally, but I thought, look, I love bridges.
I love woods in his sleazy eighties era.
You know, like I talked about that movie Cop, which blew me away in its level of sleaze and hatred.
And I'm like, I'm going to check this thing out.
And sure enough, it's got a really awesome woods bridges car chase.
But the fun of it is they're two old friends who like used to race and they're like,
let's see if we still got it.
So they're risking the lives of like everyone on the sunset strip running red lights.
Apparently they did it by shooting down the sun or shutting down the sunset strip for like
five minutes at a time and just shooting like awesome shit and then opening it back up and
doing that all day.
I bet it was a great day to be in L .A.
I would be furious.
And there was a Hollywood Bowl concert that night too.
So it was, I just made that up.
I don't know.
It was awesome.
It was cool.
You buy that it's bridges and woods.
They're in convertibles.
So they're like yelling out, like, fuck you and taunting each other during the race.
And it's in the first 10 minutes of the movie.
You know, you're like, holy shit, like, how did I miss this gym?
The movie itself is okay.
I watched Siskel and Ebert's original review,
which I would always recommend doing when you watch an older movie from when Ebert was alive,
is just Google Siskel and Ebert and the movie you just watched.
And it's like having a great conversation with two friends about the movie,
but they both really liked it.
I liked it.
Bridges is awesome in it.
It's probably bridges that is hottest like bridges in the last picture show.
You're like, wow, he looks so young and like perfect.
But this is when he's like got some bulk to him.
And you're, I mean, he's blowing Gosling out of the water.
And you don't think of bridges like that necessarily.
Although anyone that handsome at 80, you know, he was a looker back in the day.
It's, it's interesting.
It's a movie with like 18 double crosses.
It's Jeff Bridges and Rach Rachel Ward has top billing
because she had just done the thorn birds, which I've never seen.
But Rachel Ward is a very limited average actress.
I don't know how she got top billing in this thing.
Well, you just said off the thorn birds.
The thorn birds was massive.
My mom and every one of her friends, like they, the thorn birds was massive.
That was a huge like television event.
So I'm not, I'm not surprised.
Yeah.
She's actually the issue she's, she's, you know, in a movie like that,
in a noir movie where it's like men, smart men, willing to risk their lives
and everything to get one more taste of that pussy.
The woman's gotta be, you know, not just gorgeous, but like something
otherworldly and compelling about her.
Like a, you know, like when you Margot Robbie and Wolf of Wall Street or
something like that, where you're like, holy cow.
And you completely understand everyone losing their mind.
You don't get that with Rachel Ward.
She's not exuding in any intelligence or charm or charisma.
She's attractive, but that's, that's the downfall of the movie in my opinion.
Woods is great as a sleaze.
There's a million twists and turns and look car chase alone.
Highly recommend against all odds.
The ending is awesome.
It just, well, I won't tell you the ending, but it plays the Collins song
over the kind of end credits.
And I highly recommend, you know, it's not, it's, it's a B plus or something,
but it's a good movie.
I recommend against all odds.
Rachel Ward also starred in Sharky's Machine.
That's correct.
Shout out again to Pinkstone who gifted me unbeknownst to the
conversations about the movie on this podcast, a VHS copy of Sharky's Machine.
Hey Chris, there you go.
That's where you need to watch Sharky's Machine.
Yeah.
It also has Alex Karras because the Bridges character is playing a football
player who kind of gets fired from his team.
And Alex Karras, I guess was a football player.
He's in Blazing Saddles and he was the dad on Webster.
Was he like a big star of the time?
Do you remember that guy?
I just, just, just as Papadopoulos.
Yeah.
Papadopoulos.
Like that's the only thing I remember him at.
But you know, I think he was one of those guys.
He was a big enough sports name and you know, the team is like, we're going to,
not the football team, the agent team is like, we're going to put you in the movies.
And then they plop you into a few things, see what works.
He's believable as a football coach.
I'll tell you that much.
I'm going to do, I might only do two because I really get stuck on theme
with my movie corners.
But since we're talking about older films, that period, I'm going to do two rewatches here.
And the first is from that same period, a little older, but I rewatched Injustice for All.
Al Pacino, Jack Ward, Warden.
Helicopter.
Helicopter, Jeffrey Tambor at his finest.
That's right.
Everybody's at their finest in this thing.
John Forsythe, the first time I saw Injustice for All, I was expecting,
because you know, everybody knows the final scene.
I'm out of order, you're out of order, this whole courtroom's out of, you know.
So I was expecting this very gritty 70s drama with Al Pacino, you know, blah, blah, blah.
I watched it when I was in college.
That was the last time I've seen this movie and I didn't get it.
Why is this music upbeat?
And like, wait, that part seemed like it was supposed to be funny, but I don't understand.
I just didn't get it.
I rewatched it just the other day and 100 % I got it this time.
It is a comedy.
It's a movie that's kind of like a comedy first and drama second.
But when that drama comes in, it is heavy and it is real and it is so well executed
from the direction of the film to the script to the acting.
The basic plot is Pacino is playing sort of the last believer of the system.
He's a lawyer who's the sort of the last great believer in the justice system in
United States that has betrayed everyone around him and has become a business and a show and
all this stuff.
And he's at odds with a judge who's a real hard -nosed conservative, you know,
classic sort of prick played by John Forsyth.
John Forsyth's character gets accused of rape and charged and he asked Pacino to rep him
because it will be good for optics.
Because why else would you represent a man you hate unless that man was innocent?
And from there on out, the concept of justice is explored through the different characters
in the film.
And my takeaway from this movie was how this system and working within this system
will make a man break.
And I do say a man because Pacino's love interest in the film is a woman and she is the only one in
the movie that seems to have a full understanding of this is what this is.
So you either accept this as what it is or you get out.
That's it.
You're a defense attorney.
Your job is to defend people that are often guilty.
And the way you do that is by can the law prove that they are guilty or not?
And if you play by the rules of the law and they get out, that's the name of the game.
And Pacino has a hard time accepting that.
There's a devastating scene with Jeffrey Tambor where he comes in.
He's Pacino's partner.
He comes in talking about what a good lawyer he is and he's talking about this case where
he got this guy off on a technicality.
And he's shitfaced and he's like, I'm a good lawyer, right?
And then he reveals the guy he got off murdered two children and he's like, he did it again.
And he has this mental breakdown from it.
You watch Tambor's character break.
Jack Warden plays a judge who's suicidal throughout the film.
You're watching him break.
There's a scene where he stomps out of the courtroom.
It's the same bullshit every day in here.
Half these people should be in a goddamn loony Bentley.
John Forsythe's character clearly breaks because he thinks he can manipulate the system
and wield his power to the point of doing absolutely heinous things to a woman.
And then finally, in the great climactic scene in the movie, Pacino finally breaks,
but breaks in the interest of his ethics instead of sacrificing his nervous system and mental state
or compromising and succumbing to the system itself.
So it's really, really a wonderful, wonderful movie.
It's a perfect balance of young Pacino and then the Pacino that comes in the later years.
He's right on that fence of he's kind of raspy, but not fully raspy.
He's explosive, but it's not showy.
That's you're out of order.
This whole courtroom's out of order.
So it's a very balanced, perfect, it's exactly what you want.
It's the exact Pacino you want, a la Glengarry Glen Ross, a la the Irishman.
When he does it the way you need him to do it, it's perfect.
And then other movies, sometimes he goes a little too far, but whatever.
I highly recommend Injustice for All.
And the Metallica soundtrack is terrific as well.
That's right.
I saw the Iron Claw big time awards contender for my consideration.
I did watch over the pandemic and I don't have a strong memory of a lot of the things I watched
or did over the pandemic because I was just brain dead.
But I watched a lot of those vice behind the ring, the dark side of the ring documentaries,
and I definitely saw this one.
But it's about the Von Erich brothers.
So obviously professional wrestling has a long, long, rich history of sad, tragic stories,
but the Von Erich one is about as bad as it gets.
One of the worst in wrestling history.
It's these four brothers with a lot of promise.
They're a very domineering father who had a career in wrestling prior to them
and just him kind of driving them further and further into despair and depression.
Um, it's a sad fucking movie.
It was extremely, extremely well acted by believe it or not, folks, Zach Efron, top of the heap.
Um, he, he used whatever he has done to his body.
There's clearly some sort of steroid, uh, situation going on.
He's, his jaw has become massive and block like he, he says he got some like plastic,
like he said he broke his nose so he had to get surgery, but that's not true.
These celebrities are always lying to you.
He's done something to himself where he looks, uh, beyond human.
He looks like he's playing the thing in the Fantastic Four movie.
Just when he wakes up out of bed in his underwear at the beginning of the movie,
you're like, what's happening to him?
And believe it or not, none of it's prosthetics.
It's all none of it's prosthetics.
Okay.
And that's really what gives the movie its power.
He's just like this big block and he's really, really, really good in it.
And he's a bad enough actor that like, we're kind of starting to cast this show I'm doing.
And all I keep saying is like, I just don't want the Zach Efron version of this guy.
Don't we're not casting Zach Efron, pretty boy.
And I I'm wrong.
You know, he, he taps into some real pain in this and he's fucking good.
I, I can't believe I'm saying it.
Jeremy Allen White from the bear is great as his little brother.
I didn't know how short that dude was till I saw him standing with his brothers in this movie.
The great Maura Tierney from news radio.
Delivering an awesome performance as their just completely uncaring, unfeeling mother.
Holt McAloney from one of my favorite shows of recent years, David Fincher's Mindhunter.
He played the kind of big burly older daddy style cop and he's so good in this.
Everybody's great.
It's a sad picture.
You know, it, it, it doesn't really go much above a dramatization of the events.
You know, it's kind of like a fox catcher or something.
It's just telling you a very dark story in a very realistic manner.
There's not a lot of flash to it, but it's really, really well done.
It's definitely deserving of all the praise it's getting.
I highly recommend it.
My second and final movie corner is another rewatch.
Not quite as old a film, but a film that does have to do with justice.
I rewatched Training Day.
This is an astounding piece of work, this movie.
I cannot believe I was texting my friend, my friend Phoebe while I was watching it.
I go, I'm watching Training Day for the 10th time in my life.
Phoebe Waller -Bridge?
Phoebe Waller -Bridge.
And Phoebe Bridgers.
We're on a thread together.
And Phoebe from Friends.
Phoebe Cates.
And then, yeah.
And Lisa gets mad that we call her Phoebe from Friends in the thread, but.
That's how you're known, Beb.
I was texting my friend Phoebe.
I go, I go, I can't believe this is the 10th time I've watched this movie.
How is it this tense every single time I watch it?
It never is not, like.
Training Day is so good.
It's a modern classic, it's so good.
It's so tense the entire time.
My only criticism with each passing watch is, it becomes more after school special,
like at the ending, when all the gang members are sort of shaking their head like,
oh, brother, we've had enough of you, Denzel, you know, and kind of walk away.
It's a little too, it's a little schmaltzy, or not schmaltzy is the wrong word,
but you get what I'm saying.
It's a little too, like, just storybook, school lesson kind of thing.
But that said, it doesn't matter.
It gets you to where you need to go.
The other thing is, is clearly the studio stepped in and said,
when he gets killed by the Russians, it has to be massive.
Yeah.
Because you're like, the Russians wouldn't kill him like this.
They wouldn't pull up in four jeeps with 80 machine guns, like, this is ridiculous.
But clearly, the studio was like, we need an ending on the movie, guys.
Like, there's, it can't just be this wonderful character piece,
which it would have been fine.
It would have been fine if Denzel lived at the end of the movie.
It would have been fine.
Great character piece for both Hawk and Washington.
Hawk is great in it, too.
They're both tremendous in the movie.
Everybody in this movie is awesome.
Anyone hotter than Eva Mendes in Training Day?
Say again?
It's funny you say that, because I was watching it, and I thought to myself,
when she came on screen, I literally thought in my head,
if I was watching this even with my mother right now,
I would have to say out loud, there was nobody hotter than this woman.
And they give her a two -second nude scene.
It's probably the last time I paused a movie for that purpose,
because I was too old to be doing that, but I was just like, look at this person.
The cast, Denzel Washington as Alonzo Harris, Ethan Hawke as Jake Hoyt, Scott Glenn.
Love of Glenn.
Tom Berenger as Stan Gursky.
The names of the characters are awesome.
Harris Yolen as Doug Roselli.
That's my mom's maiden name.
Raymond J. Barry as Lou Jacobs.
Cliff Curtis as Smiley.
Snoop Dogg as Blue.
I'm reading the names for one reason.
Dr. Dre as Paul.
Man, you got me playing Paul?
That just makes me laugh that his name is just Paul.
I forgot he was in it, but yeah.
Yeah, Dr. Dre playing like one of the dirty cops.
Everybody in the movie is great.
Snoop Dogg is really good in it, man.
It's just an awesome movie.
And Denzel Washington, there's a thing with acting in acting classes,
there is a technique where they'll say, what animal is your character,
and try to emulate that animal.
I've heard Pacino talk about it and stuff.
But in this movie, quite literally, Denzel Washington says,
you got to decide, are you a wolf or a sheep?
Yeah.
Denzel Washington, if you watch this movie with wolf in your head,
he's doing like the big bad wolf, like through the entire mo -
Like he is so -
Especially in that scene where he blows that house down.
Yes.
You know, they get those close -ups of him really huffing and puffing,
and yeah, it was crazy.
He's just so deceitful and sinister.
And then when he asked to show the fangs,
and you never see Denzel play a bad guy, by the way.
And again, Hawk is just -
Man, the way Hawk is doing the stuff where he's laughing nervously,
and he's like, come on.
Come on.
You don't -
Stop it.
You're joking, right?
The movie is just fucking awesome, man.
It's just an awesome, awesome, awesome movie.
And the scariest scene in the film,
and always in the discussion for me,
and scariest scenes that aren't in horror movies,
is when Denzel ditches him at that gang's house,
and they start being like,
do you ever have your shit pushed in?
And all that's -
You're like, oh boy, this is very frightening.
Training day, highly -
You never want somebody asking you if you've had your shit pushed in.
You never want that questioned.
No.
And especially when one of them is the guy from Three Amigos.
The one guy at the table is the guy that's like,
the guy when El Vato is like,
or Guapo, excuse me, is like,
would you say I have a plethora?
He's like his assistant guy.
What's that?
Alfonso Arrao?
Yeah, I think that's him.
See in there?
Well, check the cast list.
You were just reading it.
Also a film director, that guy.
It's a tiny -
Hold on.
You know, it's a small part,
so he's not in the like Wikipedia.
Hold on a second.
It's probably not him, is my guess.
I'm pretty sure it's him.
I mean, goddamn, the guy is fucking peeled off of him if it's not.
Hold on.
No, no, no, no.
Alfonso is El Guapo.
Who's his assistant?
That I don't know.
That it could be, yes.
He, the like little guy where El Guapo is saying to him,
he's going, would you say I have a plethora?
The guy's like doesn't know what plethora is.
I think he's one of the guys at the table in training day.
It's like wild.
Anyway.
No, I'm wrong.
I'm 100 % wrong.
This is Tony Plana is the guy I'm thinking of.
That's not him.
Oh, well.
I gave so many true crime documentaries a chance over the pandemic
because they would, you could binge them and they would kill a lot of time.
And Tiger King was just such a blast that I was like, I got to find my next fix.
And I just never did.
And the Netflix ones are so frustrating because there's so much filler
and often you watch like a four hour thing and they don't tell you how it ended
because they never caught the guy.
And you're like, well, then what did I, what was I doing here?
A really good new one just dropped called American Nightmare.
I had never heard about this story before.
It's a three -part or a little less than three hours.
You get all the answers in the end for the most part.
So you can start it knowing that they're actually going to tell you what happened.
This thing starts.
It's a young, attractive couple about 30.
The guy has just had a pretty bad breakup with his girlfriend.
The girl he's dating has found texts where he's been reaching out to his ex
saying, I still love you.
I still have feelings for you.
So there's plenty of motives, plenty of shit going on.
There is a home invasion where men dressed in scuba gear.
This is what he's telling the policeman.
Men broke into my home and scuba gear.
Blindfolded me, held me in my girlfriend hostage and kidnapped my girlfriend.
And the cops are like, are you fucking kidding me, dude?
And he's like, I mean, they look like frog men or something.
They were wearing goggles.
And he's like, come on, come on.
And I can't tell you much more than that.
The whole purpose of this is the twists and turns of a real life case,
but it is really good.
It winds up having a lot of social impact in the end
because of how the case was handled.
Fascinating.
And I highly recommend it.
It's just something you want to watch soon
before somebody kind of tells you what happens.
But it's what you want from a true crime documentary.
It's really, really well done and just keeps you guessing the whole time.
Now, speaking of keeping you guessing, let's get to this.
I guess we'll call it a film.
Uh, leave the world behind has some ties to training day, actually,
because I learned that this was originally a reunion of Julia Roberts
and Denzel Washington from the Pelican brief.
They ever made dear friends.
And Denzel was originally cast in the, uh, Maharashtra Ali part.
And then Denzel said, read the script, this movie's not good.
I'm not going to do it.
In addition, we have Ethan Hawke playing Julia Roberts' husband.
So the gist of the movie is this.
Julia Roberts, a difficult, unpleasant, ball -busting woman, a Karen almost,
and her sort of whipped husband, Ethan Hawke, and their kids, boy and a girl.
By the way, I like that you just interject.
I don't mean interrupt, but just interject.
I like that Hollywood is finally now portraying Karens as liberal women.
I like that.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like that it's not just the unsavory whites are no longer just MAGA whites in Hollywood.
Now they're starting to show like, no, there's like liberal women that think they get it,
that act like, and men too, men too.
I'm not picking on women.
I'm just saying.
Right.
Yeah, sorry.
Go ahead.
No, for sure.
Um, they go with their children, a boy and a girl to a, a very nice home rental,
you know, like an Airbnb, but a really nice place.
They go to the beach and there is a giant, you know, almost like a battle ship that,
that pulls up on shore at the beginning of this thing.
That oil tanker.
Oil tanker.
They run and escape from it and go home.
When they're back at the Airbnb, the owners of the home come back
because they have tried to travel and have learned that bad things are going on in the world.
They've come back.
Julia Roberts does not trust them.
She says, look, we've rented this.
You can't stay here, but Ethan Hawke is the nicer guy and he allows it.
The rest of the movie is these two families trying to figure out what is going on in the world.
And boy, it's arguable if they even let the viewer know.
I'll tell you that much, especially for a two hour, 20 minute movie.
You'd hope that you would get some sort of better explanation than what is here.
But, well, I felt they did explain it in the end.
I won't jump to the end just yet.
And this is going to be filled with spoilers here, but I felt they did.
But I'll get back to why.
And it's my main criticism of the film, but you are, I'm glad you mentioned the link.
There's no reason for this movie.
To be as long as it is.
By the way, I noticed something.
This really bothered me about the movie.
And I'm not going to go down a political road here.
But the movie is produced by the Obamas, which I have a problem.
Who have an overall deal at Netflix, believe it or not, folks.
I have a problem with that.
Not because it's the Obamas, because it's politicians producing cinema.
That reeks of suspect to me.
I don't want politicians creating art and being involved in Hollywood.
And I don't want Hollywood being involved in politics.
And now the fact that we all know that they both are synergetic.
And we've always kind of known, now that it's just out in the open,
and it's just a thing we're supposed to accept, that troubles me.
And I texted you while I was watching this, and I said,
this feels to me like the scene in The Godfather when the politicians are at the mob wedding.
And he's going, it's all part of the same hypocrisy, K.
It's like, this should not be happening.
Politicians, I didn't want Reagan as a president.
I don't want an actor in the White House, and I don't want the White House in movies.
I just don't.
This should not be mixing.
I didn't like it when Hillary stepped off the plane with Pharrell for a perfect press shot.
I find all of this very unsettling, and I don't care for it.
And that was all driven even further home.
And I don't think it was...
Maybe it was a commentary, or I don't know, because she's not a very likeable character,
but it shows her phone at the one point with her news feed,
and every news alert is from a major corporate liberal outlet.
And I'm like, this just feels weird to me.
It feels like a subtle way of advertising for a certain political party.
Well, if I may interject, I read up on this a little,
because you and I were talking about this the other day,
and my viewpoint was, I don't really care.
It's all a big clusterfuck anyway, so who cares if politicians do this and whatever.
I like Barack Obama, so be it.
But what I learned in doing a little research was that...
So this was based on a beloved book that was on Barack Obama's best of list
that I'm sure he has an intern do every year
when he puts up his favorite music of the year and all that.
He loved the book, he's producing it.
Apparently, the movie makes like 10 significant changes from this beloved book,
and all reviews that have read the book and watched the movie are like,
every change is for the worse.
The reason the book was great is because it didn't do these 10 things that the movie did.
And the writer -director Sam Esmail, who did Mr. Robot,
which was a brilliant show for one season and then continued to fly further and further off the rails,
he said, believe it or not, Barack Obama gave me extensive notes on this script.
A man who has never done any film writing, giving him extensive notes on the script
and on the book and how to make it better and how to do this,
and he wants to make a great movie and blah, blah, blah.
And he goes, and this wasn't stuff like Barack saying,
hey, you know, because the movie is about sort of a political,
you know, there's political stuff in it.
He's like, his notes weren't like, this could never happen.
I'm the president, that would never fly.
He was like, there were story notes and extensive story notes.
And I, you know, so I'm giving more credence to your theory
that like Obama did have a big influence on the content of this film.
And then also the one clear cut asshole is the American flag, Kevin Bacon guy.
Yeah. Quick pause.
So good to see Kevin Bacon in anything.
He's awesome. He's awesome.
Love him.
Everybody, by the way.
Listen to his smart list.
If you want to love him, if you want to love two men even more than you do now,
listen to the Jeff Bridges and the Kevin Bacon smart lists.
And they go through their career movie by movie.
Everybody's performance in this is great.
Nobody's bad in it.
But Bacon.
Well directed too.
You know, this is the convoluted part.
We talked about earlier, Hal, I did, you know, I did, I mentioned earlier,
I like that Hollywood is now starting to portray some of these
more unsavory folks as also left leaning versus just right leaning.
But there's never really.
Well, I shouldn't say that.
It's fair.
Julia Roberts is called out several times by the daughter of the
guy's daughter when they're staying with him.
She calls him out and she points out her racism or her subtle racism,
whatever you want to call it.
So I shouldn't, I'll be fair.
And also too, they also initially make Kevin Bacon seem like an asshole,
but then what he says is actually correct.
Yeah.
When he's like, when he goes, it's Korea.
And then they're like, Korea is doing all this because wait,
but what starts happening is, is unmanned machines,
meaning cars and boats and planes or whatever,
are crashing and creating disasters.
Nobody knows what's happening.
It's a blackout happens.
All this hysteria starts happening around these events.
And then these pamphlets start falling in select areas on the West Coast
and East Coast that say death to America and different in an unknown language.
And one of the more effective scenes,
there's like a thousand self -driving Priuses that have crashed into each other.
They have some good little moments that show you that shit's going down.
And then there's also an element of potentially a virus spread because the kid,
the kid, even though he got bit or something in the woods by a tick or whatever the hell it was,
his teeth start coming out.
He starts throwing up blood.
You're not quite sure what's going on.
Anyway, when they go, they go to Kevin Bacon's character's house,
because they need medicine for this kid who's sick.
And Kevin Bacon says, it's Korea.
And the way they stage it, they actually do this well.
I was going to criticize this, but I'm wrong.
They do this well.
He goes, it's Korea.
And both Ethan Hawke and what's the other guy's name?
I'm blanking on his name.
Maharasha Ali.
Yeah.
So yeah, yeah.
Hawke and Ali both turn and they're like, what's that supposed to mean?
Almost like, what are you being?
A typical American finger pointing racist guy, whatever.
He's like, no, it's Korea.
He's like, or China.
And he starts talking about the enemies we have in the world.
And then you're slowly like, yeah, he's got a point.
It says death to America.
Where is that coming from?
And then he says, he looks at the little pamphlet or the thing that says death to America.
And he goes, look, man, my buddy did three tours of duty in Iraq.
And he goes, I can tell you this.
He sure as hell knew, would have known if this was written in a Middle Eastern language, basically.
And it wasn't.
He doesn't know what language this is.
And then they get into the car and Ali says,
we've got a lot of enemies in the world and they might just all be working together now.
And so that was actually well done.
Look, my biggest gripe with the movie is this.
That is the part in the movie where the soliloquy finally happens of what is happening.
And he says, there's a three -phase procedure that we have theorized exists
that could be being enacted on us right now to destroy us.
It's these three steps.
First, create the confusion.
Second, take away the resources.
Third, they'll turn on each other and do the job for us.
This is exactly the monsters are on Maple Street from The Twilight Zone.
Now, in the original version, it's aliens doing it.
And the camera pulls back at the end of the episode and reveals
the chaos and the riots starting on this one street and as it's going to spread.
And it shows two aliens saying, they're simple.
If you take away their means for any device that's fueled by electricity or power,
meaning their lights, their cars, anything like that,
they will eventually start to blame and turn on one another.
There was then a remake of that episode in the Forrest Whitaker reboot of The Twilight Zone.
And the remake of that episode starred Andrew McCarthy.
And that was during the George W. Bush Gulf War.
And they updated it.
So it turned out it was our enemies doing it to us and being like,
look, this is all we have to do is to cut this stuff out and they'll just kill each other.
It's great. They do it for us.
So this rips off both the original and the remake of the Monsters are on Maple Street.
And I got to tell you, folks, Monsters on Maple Street is the hands down,
most famous ever Twilight Zone episode.
We saw it at the theater, you and I.
Yeah, it is studied in sociology classes around the country and colleges.
It's literally in textbooks.
And Rod Serling told this story.
In 22 minutes, more effectively than all of this flash and bullshit did in two and a half hours.
There was no this.
This is a 90 minute movie at best, at best.
Yeah, well, I've learned that the reason all the, you know,
the reason Netflix movies in particular are so long is because they count by minutes streamed.
Right.
They encourage their movies to be bloated and over long and don't edit it.
And that's what we get.
Netflix announced this week that this is now hit their top five all time
viewed movies in the span of like two months, a month and a half.
That means that more people have seen it than
probably anything except maybe Barbie and Oppenheimer, you know, of the past year,
like tons and tons and billions and billions of people have watched this.
And have you heard a single person in your life, Joe, mention this movie to you?
No, one, Pinkstone, and that doesn't count because he's like us where it's like,
yeah, you know, so, and that's what Netflix has really done to us.
Everyone has seen it.
No one is talking about it.
There's no, there's no compelling reason to talk about it.
Um, I know people are kind of frustrated with the, the ending and the ending.
I think I like, I like an ending like that.
The friends ending the girl, the entire time the daughter is trying to watch the
series finale of friends.
And since the wifi is out, she can't do that.
Interesting.
Since Julia Roberts dated Matthew Perry and was a guest star on friends that they
would include this in the same world.
But, um, I like the ending.
I like an ironic quick ending.
Like, you know, about Schmidt is the ultimate example of a,
of a gut punch ending.
Um, but while you do sort of know what happened, it's like, it's hard to get
behind a movie that takes two hours and 20 minutes to get to its point and then
rushes through the climax.
Yeah.
This really jerks itself off with all the, I mean, God, there is a brutal scene in
this word.
I don't, I don't know if it's supposed to be funny.
I laughed them dancing to Julia Roberts dancing to hip hop.
Dancing kind of close.
Yeah, it was tough.
Oh my God.
I'm like, what, what are we doing?
What are we doing?
I thought we weren't supposed to be whitewashing anymore.
Isn't this whitewashed?
I'm watching a 60 year old white woman who has never exhibited soulfulness ever.
Yeah, never.
Dance to hip hop, not only dance to it, but instruct the black guy in the room.
What is danceable funky music?
What the fuck is going on right now?
Yeah.
Julia Roberts now only works with Sam Esmail outside of that ticket to paradise movie,
which was about as average as that's about the most average movie ever made.
But, um, Julia Roberts did homecoming with this guy, Sam Esmail, and he's mostly.
I did too.
He's mostly a TV guy and I do think he's a really strong director, visual director.
And I didn't hate this movie.
You know, I just sort of, it's a.
It's not, it doesn't compel you to go any further or deeper with it.
And it's, it raises such big issues, but there's just something about it.
That's like, okay, you know, all right.
It's, it's boring.
It's, it's, it's, it's sort of pointless.
There's no payoff to any of the mistrust.
Not a lot of suspense.
Even as I give it a credit for the way they ultimately execute the Kevin Bacon sequence,
it actually is also a disservice to the movie because it's yet another example of
not one person in this turns out to be dismissed.
Maybe that's the point is nobody is untrustworthy.
It's about, but there's just nothing.
There's just nothing.
There's no indiscretions.
There's no, there's nothing.
It's just, who cares?
Like there's this conflict for no reason.
And then it's just fine.
Cause everybody realizes, oh, I actually do like you,
even though I didn't trust you to begin with.
It's stupid.
You know, yeah, the theme is really, we're all paranoid, but we're paranoid for a reason.
And maybe we should get on board with, you know, but listening to each other more, I guess.
But is that really what they want to say that we want?
We want to be listening to the Trump people that doesn't seem like they want us to sit.
They want us to be doing that.
I don't know.
But look at 12 angry men.
You know, the most perfect example ever of a bunch of people locked in a room,
different personalities, good guys, bad guys, whatever.
There's a process that happens in a story like that.
There's moments where you go, oh my God, this guy actually is an asshole.
Or, oh my God, this guy I thought was, but isn't.
And oh, this guy is good hearted, but he's too weak.
And this guy I thought was being annoying, but he's got a point.
There's turns and an evolution that happens with the characters.
There's no evolution in this outside of I didn't like you and I didn't trust you for no reason.
And now I do.
Even at the beginning when Ali shows up with his daughter in a full tuxedo.
Yeah.
And he's like, I'm sorry, we live here.
This is our house.
You're renting it from us.
It's our Airbnb.
We're in a jam.
We need help.
That is such a solvable in two seconds thing.
Great.
Can you show me some ID?
I'm sorry.
It's the middle of the night.
I want to make sure they don't do any of that.
They in fact have to call it out when they go into the next room.
I never asked for his ID.
Maybe I should.
It's like, yes, you should.
Somebody's at your door.
By the way, do you think this is how the criminal works?
He puts on a tuxedo and creates an actress to play his daughter.
Yeah, like create some ambiguity here, guys.
Like, come on, man.
They never explain why Julia Roberts doesn't like people.
This is the other thing I want to say about this movie.
And this is another thing that's bothering me about modern cinema.
There are multiple moments in this where it feels exactly like May, December,
the way it's shot, the way the musical stings work, the camera movement, everything.
And I'm just sitting there going, OK, both were Netflix movies.
There's no fucking way.
In my opinion, this guy from this thing isn't going over to the editing bay at the other one
and seeing the thing and going, you know what, why don't we do this here?
And that push in at the beginning and where Julia Roberts goes, and then I realized
I fucking hate people.
What a terrible deuce chill opening, by the way.
And then it cuts to the credits.
It is identical.
It is identical to the thing with the push in with Julianne Moore in May, December.
We don't have enough hot dogs.
It's identical.
I don't believe that that's just an accident.
I just don't.
And there's stuff in No One Will Save You that I'm going to bring up along these exact
same lines.
But I'm not offensively hogged down by this movie, but no flaccid hog, very flaccid hog.
I think even getting 20 minutes out of this and taking it to your standard two hours would
have made a lot of difference.
And then just, you know, I can't see myself reading the book, but everyone who's read it
that all the choices made here to differentiate it from the book are wrong and worse.
So, look, it held my interest, but it didn't satisfy me.
I think it was well done, well acted, well shot, well everything.
But yeah, it's just left me cold, like so much of this Netflix stuff coming down the
pike.
And that to me is the biggest testament to imagine if a movie like the amount of
fucking Barbie's Oscar snubs.
We're still talking about Barbie and Oppenheimer all these months later.
And we're not talking about leave the world behind a month later.
No one is talking about it.
And I think that is what is going wrong with our culture.
And the reason that Barbenheimer was such a wonderful thing.
It got everybody talking again.
I miss that.
I really do.
I miss that shared experience because nobody's it's really what the movie's about.
You know, we're not, we're not connecting even on art anymore.
So it sucks.
My hog is limp, but, but, but has blood in it.
There you go, folks.
It's like, if somebody, if somebody were to say, hey, send me a picture of your
dick, it's how I would get it sort of fluffed up to like where it's almost getting hard.
We'll be back with no one will save you plugs going out.
Listen, folks, I'm coming to the, what is it next weekend?
Week from this coming week, whatever the hell it is, the first week, the second full
weekend of February, the sixth, seventh, eighth, whatever the hell it is, whatever.
I'm in Nashville.
I'm in Charlotte and Charleston.
It's, it's a Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
Please come see me.
And then the following weekend, I'm on the West coast, San Fran, LA and San Diego,
joderosa .com for tickets.
And as always, please come to Joey roses in New York city.
joeyroses .com open seven days a week at 1130 AM each day, sandwiches and drinks.
The Patrick Walsh on Instagram, see you in hell pod on Instagram.
If there are still people out there, I still see it once in a while.
Hey bummer, you guys don't do the pod anymore, you know, tell your friends, we're out there.
We've, uh, we've been picking up business recently.
We thank you.
So somebody's spreading the word.
Um, we love you all.
We'll be back as Joe said, with no one will leave.
Wow.
Both such long, clunky titles.
No one will save you.
All right.
We'll see you then.
And we'll see you in hell.