I'll see you in hell...
If you, if you!
If you're shining your screens
There comes a thing on my dreams
You know I say...
I'll see you in hell...
You, the sun news...
Welcome to, we'll see you in hell
with your favorite podcast
that discusses, converses about rates, reviews,
genre films, what's not a thing?
Same thing, I was saying.
Oh, I mean, converses about,
we're off to a great start, just needlessly wordy.
Up top, you try to hook people quick.
I feel like this shows needlessly hosty.
One, two minutes.
Yeah.
Folks, actually we can do whatever the hell we want now
because we've got you.
You are a Patreon subscriber.
It means nobody is tuning in just to check us out
at this point.
You're the fans and we thank you so much.
We sort of pulled this switch to Patreon off
without a hitch and we greatly appreciate
your continued support of the show.
Yes, thank you, everybody.
With my more or less permanent residency
on the East Coast now, Pat's diehard allegiance
to Los Angeles.
LA to lie, die.
This new setup is making it so we can continue
doing the show and it's nice
that you've come along with us, so thank you.
And people still will tweet at me and stuff.
What would the fuck happen to the podcast?
It's like, I don't know what to tell you.
I guess I discussed it with Emily.
I guess if you don't follow the Facebook page
or the Instagram page, how would you know?
I guess.
I would think if you're that mad about where the podcast is,
you'd be checking in on those things.
Sure.
I write people back.
I tell them, but if anyone's out there,
even people on the Facebook page where it says
quite clearly at the top, people are like,
what happened to the pool?
I mean, if I love to show and I wasn't seeing it for a while,
I would Google the name of the show
which would then bring up the Facebook group
and the Instagram.
That's true.
I click on one of those and see if there were any updates
and would immediately learn, oh, it has switched formats.
That's what you used to have to do.
In this day and age, you can just directly contact the person.
Yeah.
Which is what makes social media great.
It's been fun.
Great, is that sarcastic?
There's a hint of sarcastic.
All right, all right.
But that's what I didn't want to actually mind people writing me
because I don't know.
No, I don't mind people writing me either.
I'm just always surprised to hear that one.
Yeah.
I get a couple here and there on Twitter.
But it used to get like buns picks sent to me and stuff.
Doesn't happen anymore.
I know I'll often...
Not from the Helians, but others.
Reach out directly to David Harbor.
I'll say when is Stranger Things 4 coming out?
I'm sure he gets it all day.
That's not this episode.
Stranger Things 3 will be the next episode.
So this episode is another sequel.
Another chapter, if you will.
It's going to be it, chapter two.
The sequel to the 2017, blockbuster.
That one was just called it.
Did they fix the problems that they write the wrongs?
Did they, if you love the first one,
did they follow through tremendously on the second one?
These and all questions will be answered.
On today's podcast, but we've got other stuff to get down to first.
Pat, how are you?
Joe, I'm pretty good.
You're in town for what, three days?
It's all I get anymore.
I got here Sunday.
I leave tomorrow, tomorrow's Wednesday.
By the time this comes out,
I'm going to Austin Dewall have transpired,
but I'm going down to Austin to do a show.
Okay.
The Peppaton thing?
The same festival that Eddie Peppaton is on, yeah.
And then I go back to New York
and continue my run of stand -up shows in New York City.
Sounds great.
It is great.
I wish you seemed a little bit happy for me.
I'm happy.
But you know, it takes you away from me, Joe.
Let's be honest, I've been gone for a long time.
You had checked out a long time.
When I last night to the,
so it's not a VFW hall, it's an American Legion post.
And I got to be honest, I don't understand
what the difference is.
I don't need it there.
And I didn't feel comfortable asking.
But it was specified last night that it's not a VFW.
It's a, it's a Legion hall, but yeah,
the Legion post 43 here in Hollywood are good for in John Stites.
Thank you for your service.
All of you.
He brought us in.
And I'm a member now.
And he was gracious enough to bring new friends in,
such as you and Trevor.
More.
And we hung out and had drinks.
Fun.
Yeah, it was fun.
We talked a lot about,
well, we talked about a lot of, you know what?
What happens at Legion 43 stays at Legion 43, right?
That's what I say.
I was on a podcast yesterday.
My friend Josh Adam Myers has a podcast called The 500.
Why does he keep the middle name?
I don't know.
And quite frankly, I've never cared enough to ask.
Well, Seth Meyers, brother is Josh Meyers,
who's like an actor.
Maybe that's the reason.
Okay.
And then there's Mike Meyers.
Unrelated.
But yes.
I was on his podcast doing it.
It's a podcast where every episode he covers,
he's counting down the list and he covers
one album from the top 500 albums of all time.
Okay, Rolling Stone.
So he started at number 500, he's moving backwards.
I just did EPMD Strictly Business,
which was a joy to discuss that record on a podcast.
But is it a comedy podcast?
It's humorous, but I mean, the focus is the music
and what the album means to you.
And how does he know, like, do you get to pick one?
Or how does he know who to ask?
He finds people that have a relation to the album somehow.
It's got to be a tremendous amount of work to do that.
But he asked me on the podcast as a close friend,
ever done anything to you that you know,
where you feel completely betrayed
and it broke your heart.
And I said, yeah.
And he said, what was it?
And I said, I honestly can't discuss it here.
I don't feel, it was so hurtful.
I don't feel comfortable discussing it.
Was it me?
No.
Oh, good.
And then he immediately said, all right,
we're going to cut this part out.
I thought that was a great answer.
Well, it's not an answer.
I thought it was interesting.
I like the mystery of it.
It's nothing.
It's like when somebody tells you,
I really need to talk to you.
We'll do it eight hours from now.
And you're like, no, fucking tell me now.
Right.
I need to tell all it was was annoying.
He was right to cut it.
It was bad radio.
Woo.
Bad radio.
It's interesting to stern this morning.
Howard stern.
By the way, if you get one of these trials in your car,
I got a three month trial.
I got my, I got a new lease
and it has stern and everything.
And then it was over and they go,
hey, you know, I get four pieces of mail a day from serious.
You want to pick it back up?
You know, it's $9 .99 a month.
I call, I go, yeah, I just don't need it.
I plug my phone and I listen to what music I want to
and podcasts.
What about seven a month?
No, what about six a month?
No, about five a month.
No, what about four a month
and we'll throw in the Howard stern,
which is like an additional $20 a month?
I go, yeah, fine.
I mean, so if you're in a position
where you get one of these trials,
just keep saying no.
Right.
And they give it to you.
Wasn't Nikki Glazer on this morning on stern?
Yeah.
Not what I heard.
They were talking about impossible burgers when I checked.
I would have liked to hear the Nikki Glazer.
I saw her post that she was going to be on it.
I thought it was today.
Maybe it wasn't today.
She might have been.
You're just an listener.
You hear a woman's voice.
You turn the dial.
We all know that unless it's Robin.
How is that stern show these days?
It's always good.
I mean, to me, the songs about cupping and stuff
just don't really make my day.
But when he's interviewing a celeb, there's nobody better.
I call them celebs.
Okay.
Would you say, would you say that he gets them in the hot seat?
Yeah, he puts him in that hot seat.
They open up to him.
All right.
Joe, do you see any of the Emmys speaking of celebs?
I would have rather cut off my eyelids.
It was something, man.
No, I didn't know.
I refused.
I mean, the posts made me sick.
They had no host.
Yeah, of course, because God forbid, a joke gets made.
They were wheeling up people and just selling them down
the fucking river with the shittiest material I have ever
heard performed.
I guess people wrote it.
I apologize.
But you need a host.
You need somebody to make the thing hold together.
Jesus Christ.
You know what?
I don't apologize.
It's a shitty show.
It's poorly written.
And if you're writing for it, you should be aware of that
as a writer.
And if you think that you're writing great stuff
and that these are great people you're writing it for,
you're wrong.
There you go.
And of course, the speeches, you know, I guess.
You would have thought cancer was being cured.
I saw a guy, and I didn't even know who he was.
Some fucking jackass with a fucking fedora on with a brim
that shot out like three feet.
I mentioned him to you last night, but it was.
Oh, that was the same guy.
Massive brim.
He's on a show called Pose, which pose.
It's an FX show about trans runway walkers, I want to say.
Okay, models.
Cool.
I would watch the show.
The guy seems like a fucking jackass.
I mean, I saw him.
I didn't know who he was.
I saw it on mute on a TV.
And I literally said out loud to myself,
this is why I don't watch this fucking show.
Because I'm just looking at his hat
and it was making me so mad.
The speaking of pose, the pose of the hat.
For God's sakes, people, how much fucking attention
do you all need on television when you lose to this guy
and then he goes up there with that hat.
It's got to be an extra slap in the face.
It's like, it's like.
And I'm not just talking about the brim hitting you
as he walks up the aisle, folks.
Yeah, it looked like some kind of like some sort of like
Charles Nelson Riley variety show sketch about Indiana Jones
or something, you know what I mean?
Or like, or he's playing Sherlock Holmes.
It's like the hats that didn't make it.
Right.
You know, it's just fucking terrible.
What about a cowboy named had a long Cassidy?
Keep mine Paul Lin's doing this.
This is a my material.
Now that I watch.
Yeah, sure.
But I mean, it's just, I didn't realize
I was the guy you were saying one for pose or whatever.
That was a different guy with an eight foot hat brim.
I honestly didn't remember to be honest.
Half of what you say doesn't register with me.
The look, I told you a story last night.
And as I was telling you the story,
you were asking me questions that I've literally
had just said the answer to.
I last night was getting a lot of flack
for asking questions during stories.
But I'm like, you got to paint the pictures
so I don't have these.
It was being painted.
All right, it was, but have you ever heard of suspense?
I like to set up a story before I jump in.
But here's the thing.
I, the, yeah, everything you're saying is true.
These shows, if you, this is at a point.
Celebrity is at a point of politics, right?
And vice versa.
It's like if you're still watching this shit
and somehow thinking that, you know,
when Elizabeth Moss, for example,
gets up there and gives some speech about liberty
and freedom as she's winning a golden trophy.
Yeah.
It's like, if you still think that means something,
you're fucking stupid.
You're either stupid or you're kidding yourself.
I agree.
I mean, it's come on, guys.
This is like believing in what Trump is saying.
This is a fucking sham.
Jason Alexander never won the Best Supporting Actor Emmy Award.
I'll rest my case.
Well, it's more political now than ever.
I mean, there's no concern.
Look, I love Jason Bateman.
Jason Bateman won for Best Drama Direction.
Direction?
Best Drama Direction.
What was he directing?
He directed an episode of Ozark.
Anyone.
Yeah, overactual directors.
And then he gets up there and he's like,
look, a whole lot of people helped me do this.
But you got the feeling they really helped
him do it.
Then the girl from Ozark, the kind of like white trash team,
who's fine in the show?
Laura Winnie.
Come on, Joe.
Although she'd appreciate the team, folks.
She's a good actress, but she's up against like six Game
of Thrones actresses and her.
So of course she wins because she splits the vote.
Everybody who loves Game of Thrones picks a different person.
And she wins, but she doesn't even acknowledge that.
She gets up there like, wow, you all love me.
And it's like, no.
And you told me, this I did remember you telling me,
Michelle Williams gets up apparently.
I love Michelle Williams.
And this is it.
I love her in Fawzi.
I couldn't stop talking about.
She gets up and actually gives her speeches
if she's in the struggle.
Oh, 100%.
So these people were sick.
And I hesitate to even go into it because this speech has been
discussed and praised and quotes post for all week.
I'll say all the, listen, we've, we've, we've finally,
we've turned full on skexies and mystics on this podcast.
I'm the skexies.
Sure.
I'll say all the hateful shit you don't want to say.
All right, great.
Because I don't fucking care anymore.
Well, no, I have some issues with the regardless,
but she, you know, I watched most importantly,
the after interview where they talked to the press again
because the five minutes they talked about themselves
wanted enough.
They go out and talk to the press.
And Michelle Williams goes, look, you know,
it just seemed like no matter how many awards I won,
no matter how many accolades I received,
I just never got into a place where I felt like I was able
to retire comfortably.
And you know, somebody tweeted this and then put up her
net worth, which is $16 million.
And you're 33.
Right.
Who the fuck deserves to retire comfortably at 33?
She's talking like like she's a 68 year old person.
Exactly.
And what?
Forgive me here.
She also got Heath Ledger's money.
I would have to imagine, which is not was not her goal.
Believe me, I fully believe they loved each other.
But like she's taken care of and she's up there
and doing all this.
And so she says, I told them, I needed extra pay
and I got it, you know, standing ovation
with people crying in the audience.
And folks, literally crying, they cut to about money.
They cut to busy films crying in clap.
So here's the deal.
And by the way, crying about money is okay
when you don't have money.
Yeah, crying about somebody that's getting a lot of money,
getting more of that money is sick, that's sick, it's psychotic.
I want to be abundantly clear that I think Michelle Williams
does deserve the same salary as Sam Rockwell.
She, look, if I had to put it to a vote,
I'd say I would have paid her more than Sam Rockwell.
In some of these cases, people will say, like, you know,
it's Jody sweeten from Full House.
And she's like, I didn't make the same as Tom Cruise
and people get upset.
That's not a fair comparison.
But Rockwell and Michelle Williams is a very fair comparison.
I'm glad they made a lot of money off it, fine.
But she says it, the tearful audience applauding
that she, at the salary that she's made
which is weird to me, then...
And I will go, let me say this.
I will go this far and I'm not saying this
to somehow counterbalance my criticism of this.
I think she does deserve more than Sam Rockwell.
She is a more notable actor.
For sure.
She has made more money for the industry.
She has garnered more awards and more notoriety.
And Sam Rockwell is my favorite male actor.
Yes.
I think she does deserve more.
If there was ever a time where he was going to get more
than her, that is truly insane.
And in my opinion, sexist.
Now, that all being said,
I still think this is fucking batshit
that people are crying,
as if this woman just came out of a box off the street.
And that it's being discussed publicly
just seems really gross at a time
when people can't afford insulin
to be up there and like, I made five million
instead of 3 .5 and people are like, yes, yes.
It's just, it's appropriate
that they make the same
and yet it's disgusting to be up there talking about it.
Bizzy Phillips has that talk show, right?
Not anymore, she did.
She did.
I found her to be an idiot.
I don't know where I am.
I never met her.
I'm gonna base it on two things.
The clips of the talk show I saw
and then her name is busy.
Well, that's not her fault.
Well, you leaned into it, didn't you, Bizzy?
Yeah, I guess so.
And is it her real name?
I'd like to know.
It might not be.
But anyway, I know that's an unfair judgment.
Michelle Williams, and she's not,
she's not done there because she says,
you know, I told, I also told them
in addition to making all this money,
I told them I would need six extra weeks of dance classes.
I got it.
I told them I would need six extra weeks of voice coaching.
So when a woman tells you,
particularly a woman of color tells you
what she wants, give it to her.
So again, quick pause, quick pause.
In theory, what you're saying is a positive thing.
And I believe she got us like a standing ovation of it.
However, you're not a woman of color, Michelle Williams.
And the point that you're making is if a woman,
meaning an actress because these people don't know
that there are other jobs,
when an actress says she needs something,
you have to give it to her.
It's a crazy statement.
Also in this world where shows that you have such a limited amount,
you know, FX has a nice luxurious schedule,
and they're very artist friendly and stuff.
A lot of times you got to gun to your head
and they need a product by Friday and it's Monday morning.
You don't have a script.
She's saying, if I need six additional weeks of prep,
give it to me.
And I just don't understand that attitude.
Look, in her defense, unless she's like,
if you want the work to be greater.
In her defense, it's been a tough, it's been tough for her.
I mean, it's only been a straight ascending smooth shot
from being a regular on Dawson's Creek,
one of the most popular TV shows of its time,
directly into movie stardom.
So in her defense, it's been a rough ride.
Her husband did pass away.
Let's not forget.
They were split up at the time.
Not to say that that's okay.
I'm not being like so, so, I'm not being like so pooo.
I'm just saying like, you know, I love Michelle Williams.
I just, and I believe these are all great issues.
I think there should be equal pay.
I think there should be equal preparation.
I think a lot of times male actors,
I've seen this on shows.
I've been on male actors are allowed to act out
and behave like children and be ridiculous
and women actors are not.
I think that's all great.
However, when you get up there on a night
that's supposed to be connecting with people,
it was the lowest rate as Emmys of all time,
not to become Donald Trump, all of a sudden.
But it like, I understand why it was so lowly rated.
At a time when the world is in chaos,
these people are like, thank God,
we've reached a point where I'm now making $5 million.
I find it gross.
There should be, look, this is the specification
and it does not, this is not the case and it needs to stop.
But the specification is this to me.
There needs to be equal pay when it is equal power.
Let's put it that way.
Meaning not power, meaning what are you,
if you are able to generate the same revenue,
there should be equal pay.
For sure, period.
But I'm getting a little sick of the argument of like,
somebody gets their breakthrough like lead part in something,
opposite, like fucking John Ham.
And then they go, well, I didn't get the same money as John Ham.
It's like, because you're not John Ham.
He's more popular than you.
He's bringing more people in front of the screen than you are.
And just because you're in the room with him
doesn't mean that you guys are in equal levels professionally.
Okay.
When I did your sitcom, I never once complained
about being the lowest paid person on set.
Because I, even though my part was instrumental
to the pilot, because I knew that I was not Cameron Mannheim
or David Cremholz or Sarah Gilbert.
Sarah had three lines.
He didn't hear me going, why the fuck is she getting four times?
You know, it's like, guys, male or female, you have to realize
you have to generate, now I do agree though
that it's unfortunate and needs to stop
that there are men and women in equal power positions
where the women are not getting as much.
That sucks.
And that's stupid and that's bullshit.
I think, you know, like, and I don't even know
people's salaries on this, but a good example of this is like,
and it's just because I read that crazy interview
with Joel Schumacher.
Like Joel Schumacher made The Client,
which is a very entertaining John Grisham adaptation.
My guess is that on that movie, Tommy Lee Jones made $10 million
and Susan Sarandon made $2 million.
That's unfair.
Those are actors who've been around the exact same amount of time.
I agree that's unfair.
They've both received a tremendous amount of accolades.
So yeah, I think there's just these blanket statements
about everything now and progress is fantastic,
but you're going to lose people
when you don't take into account other factors, is all.
You have to respect everybody's struggle.
Just because you're a male or it's now been reduced
from straight male, straight white male to just straight male.
Yes, it's now been drawn back because everybody got
mad at Dave Chappelle for making one joke
that pissed people off or whatever,
and then all of a sudden it was no longer
straight white male after that,
because now there was a black guy, they were all yelling it.
So it's been now reduced to straight male.
Within, I'm going to bank within the next year,
though there will be a very popular gay man
that pisses people off in some way,
and it will then be reduced to just male,
which now we have defeated the entire point
of this progressive discussion we're trying to have
in the first place, and we're right back
to men versus women, because why?
Because at the very beginning of this discussion,
people didn't step back and say it is possible
to be a straight white male and have had an awful life
or to be poor or to have struggled.
And then those people retaliate by going,
and we'll then fuck you, we're going to vote for this asshole
and get him in, and then it becomes a battle of wits,
and then that battle of wits turns into a battle of spite,
and it all fucking deteriorates into dog shit.
And then we're right back to square one,
and nothing gets done.
And then that's why you can say,
oh, everything that is happening literally right now,
you could compare it to exactly what was happening in 1987.
This is why history repeats itself.
I will say this.
Do you not agree with, are you being quiet
because you don't agree or are you being quiet
because you're not sure if you want to make one
very important point, okay?
Men are from Mars, and women are from Venus,
and that's always going to be a problem.
Can I take us down to Pat's movie corner?
Very good, Walt.
What do you got, Joe?
I got a bunch, let me grab my phone, you can start.
I will.
And I am going to, by the way,
I mentioned this on the shout outs.
I did it like, I don't know if you,
I'm sure Joe didn't listen to it,
but I did it like a half hour two part shout out episode
interrupted by food being delivered to my home.
Did a lot of riffin and scatting,
so give it a listen.
It's not your usual, just a list of names.
And in the future, at least once a month,
I'm going to do an extended Pat's movie corner
that I'll just record at home
to thank you guys for doing the Patreon.
So that will become,
I guess I have to do something now.
You don't have to, but I'm going to do it.
And I think the first one will be,
I have just re -watched, or in a few cases watched
for the first time, all the films of Oliver Stone.
And I think the first one will be sort of a look
at his filmography.
And I'll be doing that in the next week.
So look for that too.
Actually, no, because we're recording,
we're stockpiling needs because Joe's going out of town.
So watch for those, that's probably already up
by the time you hear this.
Just watch for those.
All right, what are your three?
Do you do the first to your three?
I will do the first of my three, which is,
I am Patrick Swayze.
I'm not, I am Patrick Walsh,
but I am Patrick Swayze was a documentary
that aired on the audience channel.
Ooh, choked on my gum.
Can I put my gum on the ridge of this cup, or is that gross?
All right, I don't care.
All right, I'll get it.
I'm sorry if I've been smacking in your ear, folks.
I am Patrick Swayze.
So of course, I love Patrick Swayze.
And he's one of those guys,
because he's from the 80s,
when you didn't know everything about everybody,
where I didn't know anything about his life.
I knew he died, and that it was sad,
but I didn't really know anything.
It's a great documentary.
It's, they did one also, I am Chris Farley,
which was very well done,
but yeah, they take you through Patrick Swayze's life,
his hardships, his really extreme struggle with drinking,
and then his wife is painted throughout this thing
as this big beam of light, until you go online
when it is discussed that she may have been like beating him
as he was dying and like this complete tyrant.
So I went down a real Wikipedia hole with that.
I will say clearly they needed her cooperation
for the documentary.
She comes off looking like a saint.
If you want a great part too,
read what's going on online regarding Patrick Swayze
and his wife, which seemed to be a pretty problematic marriage.
But I wouldn't say warts and all,
but it's very entertaining,
and just everyone the guy came in contact with seemed to love him,
and it's terrific. Check it out.
This is the one we don't do,
but there's a new YouTube series called Most Iconic Rolls.
Yes.
And they interview an...
Cinnamon, honey buns, hot buttered.
Hogi. Hogi roll? Yeah, I guess so.
You guess so.
I guess it's a roll. Yeah.
Is this how you talk to your staff when you're at the...
Oh, the head right, this is who Pat,
that's one of these headwriters.
I saw your stuff goes into the script.
No, not true.
Most Iconic rolls.
I watched one episode of this with John Goodman.
Yeah.
I was excited to watch it.
I love John Goodman.
Wait, where is this area?
YouTube as I said, two seconds ago.
Oh, I didn't catch that.
The...
I enjoyed it very much.
It was fun to watch him talk about rolls in...
You know, the Big Lebowski.
Raising Arizona.
Yes.
Oh, brother, where are they?
Rosanne.
Who's interviewing them?
So on and so forth.
It's like a speaking -to -camera thing, you know?
And then they show clips or whatever.
But apparently most Iconic rolls means every roll he's ever done.
Because at one point, they're like,
King Ralph.
Oh, boy.
So it at the dollar show.
The babe.
You're like, what, what?
Yeah, he's like, he's like,
I really wish I could do the babe over again.
I could have put more time into the batting and the...
Nobody wanted to see the babe again.
It was not good the first time.
But I enjoyed it.
And it was Goodman's very endearing man to watch it and interview.
And on the eve of the Conner's...
I think it's tonight, the Conner's reprimiers.
It was nice to see him talk about Rosanne
and talk about it in a endearing and nostalgic way
and not in a, you know, sort of bitter way.
Sure.
So I enjoyed it, but so anyway.
Okay.
In the news is Memories of Murder,
directed by Bong Joon Ho.
I'm actually not going to go into it
because I don't want you to know anything about the movie.
But the best movie I have seen in the last several years
is Bong Joon Ho's Parasite.
As we get closer and closer to the release,
you're going to just have to cover your ears and eyes.
The trailer does a pretty good job
of not revealing too much, but it still reveals too much.
Go see Parasite.
I'm dying to see this.
It was genuinely incredible.
And I saw it with my wife
and we both at the end of it looked at each other
like we were in a double mint commercial.
Like we both went like mouth open,
turned to look at each other in the face like holy fuck.
Talked about it the whole way home.
Talked about it the whole next day.
It's awesome.
Bong Joon Ho also did Snowpiercer, which was very cool.
He did the host, which was awesome.
He did Mother, which was very cool as well.
But often cited as his masterpiece
is Memories of Murder.
It is also compared to Zodiac.
And it's on a lot of best of the 2000s list.
Zodiac being one of my favorite movies
I couldn't wait to see it.
I get the comparison.
It is tracking the very, very slow process
of finding a serial killer who maybe cannot be found.
They turn up, you know, bad lead after bad lead.
It goes into the really methodical nature
of that kind of work.
As does the show Mind Hunter on Netflix.
I really enjoyed Memories of Murder.
It's in the news this week because they caught this serial killer.
These crimes went on like 30, 35 years ago.
One of the country's only known serial killers,
which is kind of fascinating, but they caught him.
So you can read about the real life case that did it.
And I recommended highly.
It's a really good movie.
I think in my opinion, not as good as Parasite.
We're ranking all the great movies of this guy.
Parasite, to me, is his masterpiece.
But go check out Memories of Murder.
You're going to want to see everything the guy's done
when you see Parasite.
I watched Joan Jett bad reputation.
It's a documentary about Joan Jett.
It doesn't get too deeply into the runaway stuff
because there's already been a runaway documentary
and they also did the biopic about the runaways that Joan Jett.
I think produced, she might have co -written it.
I don't remember, but I think she was an EP and whatever.
Anyway, this gets into more or less all of the ins and outs
of Joan Jett's actual career.
I found the movie fascinating.
I have always been a fan of Joan Jett.
She is a real deal activist.
She is a real deal feminist.
She is a real deal fighter.
And I just love seeing somebody that they talk about
where she talks about nobody wanted my first record.
We literally ended up putting it out ourselves.
And hearing her say things like, it pissed me off
when they treated me like special
because I was a girl in rock and roll.
She was like, I didn't fucking want that.
I want to fucking just go in and play and be, you know, fuck you.
I just love that attitude.
I think it's awesome.
And she's had an incredible life.
She's done an amazing amount of charity work
and a lot of really wonderful.
She's just a perfect actor.
Like she's super into vegetarianism, but she's like, look man,
I'm not gonna yell at you if you to cheeseburger around me.
I just, you know, but if you want to talk about it,
I'm gonna tell you why I believe in this.
Like she's, that's what makes an awesome activist to me.
Like I'm gonna pick my battles.
I'm gonna pick the times to get behind the thing I need
to get behind every waking second of life
isn't a fucking war of ethics.
And fuck you, don't call me a victim.
I've gotten the shit knocked out of me
and I'm standing back up on my feet again
and I'm gonna keep fighting.
She's just fucking awesome, man.
She's absolutely awesome.
I couldn't have more admiration for the woman.
I think she's the coolest, just probably the coolest
lady I'm playing on earth.
Were you a fan of her music?
Yeah, I like her music quite a bit.
I like the, I like, I was gonna say I like the runaway stuff.
That's not true.
I like Joan Jets solo stuff too.
I mean, I like them both.
I just don't know if I like the runaways better or not.
That's always a tough call because
I saw Joan Jets at the Hollywood Bowl
a week ago.
How was she?
She was really good.
She was, to be honest, blown out of the water by heart.
Heart, if you get a chance to see heart,
they're out touring the country now, holy shit.
Really?
I mean, the pipes, the woman,
remain absolutely incredible.
I was just never a big heart guy.
I love the 70s Zeppelin style heart
and you know, the power ballads are great,
but they, I don't know, with them being older
or something like her singing alone,
I mean, there was no dry eye in the house.
They covered stairway to heaven
and Wilson, former wife of Cameron Crowe
is just an absolutely amazing guitarist
and they're funny, you know?
It was a great night.
How was that?
It was really cool, except she had this guy
who I guess was her managers
who was a problem server in the documentary.
The old like sort of Jewish guy.
Yeah, yeah.
What was he doing?
He was playing what appeared to be a not plugged in keyboard.
You couldn't hear one note of this keyboard.
He, a big part of the documentary is their relationship
and how they're basically,
they're for all intents and purposes,
they're married, but they're not married
and they're not lovers.
Right.
They just have formed this bond.
I mean, it's a really endearing part of the documentary.
Their relationship is really funny.
They definitely should not have had him up on the stage
because every third song, he'd be like,
you know, it was in really 1974,
when the journey came into my office
and we're like, dude, enough.
He would, it was like your dad at a wedding
like giving a long, long,
it's an odd pairing.
If he looks like he could be her actual father.
Yeah.
And they're the same age.
But she, there was another great part in that documentary
of something
I can't remember.
Oh, well, it doesn't matter.
Go ahead.
I speaking of Michelle Williams,
I saw her after the wedding
with Julianne Moore, Billy Crutup
and as I mentioned, Michelle Williams,
the movie, again, I mean, it's twist after twist after twist
based on a foreign film.
Not a comedy at all.
Very much a drama.
But like,
it made me realize, Julianne Moore in this movie
is like sobbing uncontrollably.
And at some point, I started laughing.
It was so embarrassing.
And it made me flash back
to the last 30 years of life
where in every movie, Julianne Moore,
sobs and sobs and sobs,
every movie she's in,
she's hysterically crying.
And it's just starting to look desperate.
And like, it's like in Wayne's world
when he's like, I never learned to read
and they're flashing Oscar clip on the screen
and he's splashing water in his eyes.
I mean, it's such a blatant grab.
I feel for a wards
and I don't need to see her sob anymore.
I'm tired of it.
I think a lot of actors have that problem.
And it wears me out after a while.
The first one I remember getting tired of was Tom Hanks.
Yeah, I love Tom Hanks.
But I was just like, can you stop
every fucking thing has to be some new accent
and some new, it's exhausting.
Johnny Depp got caught in that fucking, in that rut.
Joanne Moore, also, and I love these actors,
but it's the worst boss in the world.
It's ever seen 30 rock.
It's just like, my God, guys, stop it.
Yeah, you know, I really truly love Magnolia
and I loved it at the time,
but like you go back and watch it now
and she's sobbing every scene of this thing
and I know her husband's dying, but I hate Magnolia.
I think that entire thing is one big fucking look at us
and give us an award jerk off.
I get why you would feel that way.
I absolutely loved it, but I don't know.
The movie did nothing for me.
It's also like, it's directed by her husband, Julian Moore,
and it's kind of incompetent.
I mean, it opens and closes with these tracking shots
where the camera's like being bobbled back and forth.
It's like somebody's like, whoops, whoops,
and these are the shots that are in the movie.
I was sort of confused.
These are the shots.
It was, you know, melodramatic to say the absolute least.
I can't recommend it, but you know,
if you and your mom wanna cry together, go ahead.
My last, for this week's corner,
or this episode's corner rather, Wu Tang and American Saga.
I watch this on Hulu.
This is the scripted dramatic series
about the rise of Wu Tang clan out of Staten Island,
out of basically out of a life of crime
into a life of music.
Hey, who are the real criminals?
You know what I mean?
Which business?
But anyway, I wasn't gonna, I wanted to explain to the fans.
I wasn't gonna swatch it because I was like,
this is not gonna be good.
And then my friend who was a big Wu Tang fan said,
no, dude, it's a really solid show.
And I said, all right, well shit, I'll check it out.
As I was checking out for the first time,
I realized like Rizza was behind it.
He co -wrote every episode.
He does all the music, him and method man.
And I think every member might be an executive producer
on this thing.
I was excited, that made me excited.
And lo and behold, it's an awesome, awesome show.
And the funny part is, is the story is so intriguing.
This could stand on its own without Wu Tang.
Like, meaning like, if you took the music storyline out of it,
it would obviously there would be less of them to play against
with the concept of what they're struggling and fighting for.
But if you remove the, we want to be famous rappers
element out of this and just told their criminal story,
it would be like a fucking awesome huge brother style
like TV series.
It's fucking incredible.
It's super intense.
It's super raw and it's super well written.
And I was telling Pat last night, like,
they never once do that stupid thing.
Like, I literally had to look up who each person was
because they never do the dumb thing
of like, you're so methodical man, you know?
Like, and you're like, oh, that's method man.
They never do that, like ever.
In fact, I've missed for the first two episodes
who Ghostface was.
The only easter egg was he's talking to his little brother
who's in a wheelchair about comic books.
And he says to him, he's telling him about like,
Iron Man is his favorite superhero.
That's literally the only nod to like,
this is gonna be Ghostface killer.
So like, it's fucking awesome.
And then seeing the turmoil between the members,
which I never knew about before they became friends,
which spoiler alert, Rayquan and Ghostface
literally want to murder one another
as rival factions of different gangs
from different projects.
I just thought it was fucking riveting man.
It's not over yet.
Hulu is releasing this.
They're not putting it all up at once.
So I've seen about four of them at this point.
I will definitely check it out.
I watched the showtime documentary of Mike's
and then the Wu -Tang clan.
Four parts, four hours.
Super entertaining.
And I thought, well, I've seen the real story.
Why don't we need to see that?
But if it's great, I'll watch it.
It's awesome.
They do some interesting stuff, directing direction wise.
Every episode I think has a different director,
but they do some cool kind of weird,
there's almost like a Ralph Baskey sequence in one episode
where it gets animated for a minute.
And at first you're kind of like,
I don't understand what is that?
And then it somehow makes sense and works.
Like it's just really fucking cool, man.
It's a great, it's a great, great, great show.
And it deserves a lot of eyes on it.
And I think it's probably, unfortunately,
going to get the reaction that I first gave it
from a lot of people which is like,
oh, it's going to be another one of these biopics.
And yeah, but it goes far, far, far beyond that.
And there's also never Jay Okerson always makes the joke
of like, I hate music biopics,
because nobody has that many profound moments.
Sure, you know, and he's like,
you ain't going to change music,
you're going to change the world.
Yeah, you know, and we were really laughing about that
at one point, but it's like, they don't do any of that shit
in it either.
All right.
It's literally just like, they'll be like,
yo, y 'all heard, trap car quest just got a $100 ,000 advance
and they're like, yo, we got to work hard on our music, man.
We got to get this, we got to get this money, right?
You know, it's awesome.
I'm sold.
I got to get some water.
Why don't you, Pat, let's skip the other segments
because we're running along here.
Let's get right into the flick this week
because I got a lot to say.
I do too.
So Joe and I both were in strong agreement
on the original it.
We saw it together and just felt very let down by it.
I, as I have been for the last several years of my life,
it seems like I'm still listening
to the Steven Weber audio book of it.
It's a fascinating book.
There's a lot of fat in that book,
but it is just very well written and great.
The CBS mini series, which we have also discussed in the show,
is a pretty spectacular adaptation of this work
and we didn't like the original movie.
It chapter two, I'll say this.
I saw it in the IMAX format.
I'm an AMC Stubz A -Less member.
I get to see it for free.
Joe, you didn't see Madame Press by then.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I see Stubz A -Less member.
You've thrown it around so much at this point,
I think it's gauche.
But IMAX helped.
IMAX can help almost anything except Hobbes and Shaw.
I didn't help that.
But I went to see IMAX Landis problematic.
Oh, IMAX Landis, his documentary, they'll let him make
in probably six months when he's back as the Toast of Hollywood.
Look, he should be gone for not just for the Me Too stuff,
but also he should have been gone before that
for being the ugliest man I have ever seen.
When I did a stand -up show and he was the MC
and he was like, what is this fucking obnoxious character
this guy is doing?
I can't believe this shit.
Somebody goes, no, that's him.
And it was his personality.
I thought it was like a Bobcat gold -weight character.
Oh, good.
By the way, Kevin Spacey had that guy killed, right?
You read about that?
I don't think Kevin Spacey's rolling like that.
The young man who accused him of sexual harassment dies?
It wasn't the main one.
It was a masseuse or a massage therapist.
But they had something.
I bet they had proof.
I mean, look, the guy's done either way.
Oh, but I guess he could have went to jail, man.
I mean, I don't know.
Do you think Kevin Spacey's rolling with fucking,
I got hit man money?
Not really, but somebody should look into it.
Anyway, it chapter two, the IMAX helped.
I thought, so I'll tell you.
I mean, you know this, but it chapter two
is basically the adult half of the story.
We're picking up with all these characters as adults.
Jessica Chastain, who was good, Bill Hader steals the show.
He's very funny in it.
James McAvoy and assorted others.
I thought the adults did a nice job.
I liked this half more than part one,
which might come as a surprise to you, Joe.
But I enjoyed it to some degree.
And in fact, it felt shorter to me at three full hours
than it chapter one felt at two and some change.
I, for whatever reason, was not bored.
I was kind of into the thing from start to finish.
And a big part of that was the bizarreness of this movie
and some of the choices in it.
I admired that it made some awful, embarrassing,
huge swings and misses,
just some really fun, weird, special effects
and set pieces.
I admired that.
It felt less homogenized and down the middle
than most Hollywood product.
Like when a giant Paul Bunyan statue gets coming to life,
I was like, look, this is very dumb.
I'm not scared at all, but I like that they're doing this.
I know that's in the book as well.
I was extremely excited to see this film.
I thought the trailer was tremendous.
Great trailer.
And that scene really works in the movie.
Yeah, and I couldn't wait to see this thing.
I thought it looked like they were basically
going to create the mood.
I wanted to see in the first one,
which was primarily jump scares.
I loved, I was hooked in from the beginning of this thing.
I loved, I was just in.
I loved all the introductions to the adults.
I loved that every one of them basically
was physically peeled off of the kid.
It literally looked like these children
had grown into these people.
I thought that that was fantastic.
Even Ben, they found a guy that was like,
well, if this kid grew up and did get into shape,
that's what he would look like.
Right.
It was really incredible.
Very boring after that guy.
But I thought they went balls to the wall
by showing some of the more disturbing moments in the book.
I mean, the movie opens with the gay bashing sequence
from the book and they really stick to it
and it is extremely, like I saw people posting
trigger warnings about that on Twitter
before I went to the movies and I thought,
I kind of thought it was like people being a little too sensitive
about a violent sequence in a movie.
And then I saw it and I was like,
my god, yeah, if I was gay,
this would be extra disturbing to me right now.
This is an upsetting scene and I'm saying that as a straight man.
So I was in from the beginning.
I was a hundred percent in.
I thought it got a little slow in the middle.
But I did enjoy the ending and it picked back up for me
and all in all, I enjoyed it.
I saw it with my parents, my mom and dad loved it.
My mom was crying at the end when Eddie dies
and when Ben reveals why he killed himself.
So it was a really nice movie emotional experience
to go see with my folks and it was a lot of fun.
We left the movie, we went and got dinner,
we talked about it, we enjoyed talking about it,
we were having a great time and it was during that discussion
that I realized not only was this not a good movie,
this movie was worse than the first movie.
This movie is a fucking disaster.
And it was one of those things that smokescreened me
in the theater at the time.
They got me with a couple of things.
Again, Ballsy move opening up with this very edgy,
violent sequence that was very alarming
and caught your attention.
Some nice spooky sequences in the film that made me think
they were capturing the mood of this book.
Good actors playing the children as adults now,
making me think, oh this is interesting,
these are good characters.
And the more we talked about it at dinner,
I was like, wait a second, it just opens
with a gay bashing scene and they never explain
what that significance is.
In the book it represents the hatred
that comes up every 27 years in Dairy.
And in the 1980s when the monster comes back,
gay men are first starting to come out in Dairy
and show their sexuality to everybody.
And the first instance of Pennywise returning
is this gay bashing because he spreads hatred in the community
and that's why he, or the community is filled
with hatred and dark secrets and violence and all this stuff.
And that's why he nests there.
Something they completely missed in the first movie as well
by skipping.
They did, but how would they have explained that
in this one?
The way I just did with one sentence.
But who would know?
I don't know, maybe the guy that lives in the attic
and has studied the fucking sequence of the monster
for the last 20 seconds.
But I got it, but maybe it's because I read the book.
It's because you read the book.
I got it.
It's 100 % because you read the book.
The mini series touches on all that.
This town is filled with hate.
There's a lot of secrets here.
This movie touches on none of the,
they go to a point in this fucking movie
where the goddamn clown is going to Bill Hader.
I know your dirty secret and they never reveal
what the fucking secret is.
Well, that I would love to talk about
because after it, I'm like, look,
I thought by and large, the movie was a complete mess,
but I enjoyed it.
It was a fucking disaster.
It was a disaster.
Every goblin scare, like every,
that sequence in the commercial is ruined by the fact
that when the lady does run out
and the commercial when she runs out of the dark,
she's a crazy old lady.
That's scary.
In the movie, it literally looks like large margin.
It looks like a Tim Burton fucking cartoon.
They have, it looks ridiculous.
They make Pennywise into the mask.
Jim carries the mask.
His tongue rolls out, you know, like,
I'm not kidding.
His large dog tongue rolls out of his mouth
and he licks a window at one point.
There are bizarre choices up the ass
and speaking about the ass,
I was looking to see what were they talking about
with Bill Hader?
What was his dirty secret?
At the very end of the movie.
They said he was gay.
Dops, they don't let me say they never say he's gay.
I'm saying in the interview,
they're like Bill Hader was gay
and they interview Bill Hader
and he's like, you know, I turn to the director
and I was like, let's just go for it.
That's going for it.
That you watched for three hours
and it's not clear.
This is the big reveal.
At the very end of the movie,
he caught, he goes back to a heart on a bridge
that he carved when he was young
and it says Eve L, E loves, whatever,
the kid, the kid that died.
But still, I mean,
weird for two little boys to do that,
but it seemed like a friendship thing to me.
I think it was a secret thing he carved
that even Eddie didn't know about.
All right.
Now, not clear.
I want to speak on you talking about Bill Hader
stealing the show.
Bill Hader ruined the fucking movie
in the last hour yet.
I mean, it was just non -stop.
They're literally about to fight a spider clown.
And also, you want to talk zero stakes in a fucking movie.
My dad point this out.
My dad, I love my dad, dearly.
I love him dearly.
Could be the most unobservant man I've ever watched a film with.
I mean, I watched one of the Harry Potter's in the movies
with him once and he turned to me at the end of the movie
and he goes, I don't get it.
Who's this Voldemort guy?
Like, like, Mrs, like,
when we went to see the Star Wars prequels,
it was like, dad, that's not Little Luke Skywalker.
It's Darth Vader.
He's Luke's dad.
No, dad, that's not Little Han Solo.
He wouldn't be alive yet.
You know what I mean?
My dad at dinner was like,
and this is when I started to be like,
this movie sucked.
He's like, how could the kid get stabbed
with a knife through the cheek
and then just not only just keep talking,
but he's joking.
Cut your, cut your mullet, bro.
It's been like 30 years serious.
Are you serious?
That blew my mind.
And they put like a bandaid over it.
So the entire movie, and they do it from the jump,
and they, let me ask you this,
did you fall out of your seat
when Peter Bogdanovich made an appearance?
And they call him Peter.
He's playing himself directing a modern big budget
horror movie still with the Ask God.
My mom turns to me because she didn't know he was,
but she was very obvious, this is a cameo.
And she goes, who was he?
And I go, that's Peter Bogdanovich.
He's sort of a famous director.
30 years ago.
I don't understand why he's in the movie.
His last big movie was Noises Off in 1992.
I mean, they must have asked a million people to do it.
It would have been that was wild
like if they had like Nora Efron
dragged down on a crane.
But yeah, why would they be directing this movie?
And it's a cameo that means nothing to anyone.
If it was, and I know he just passed,
but if it was Romero, or even Stephen King
who has a really great cameo later on in the film,
but yeah, why didn't they make it Stephen King?
That's what I don't get.
Because if it was a horror person,
then it's a nod to the fans.
And they'd be like, you know, the Marvel idiot,
but not idiot, whatever.
I mean, they got people.
Now look, let's get to the bare bones
of why this movie sucked for me.
They cut so much out of the second half of the book.
That again, to me was instrumental
to caring about these characters ultimately.
They changed so much.
They completely changed the ending again.
Well, that's what I was gonna say, real quick, if I may.
Is that at the beginning, they make jokes
right from that Bogdanovic scene of no,
you don't know how to end it.
You're bad with endings.
And I'm like, they've made now 30 jokes
about how nobody knows how to end it.
So clearly they've come up with something great.
And when that ending hits, and it hits for an hour,
it's a terrible hour of film.
They completely botched it and it makes zero sense.
And they do.
I got all excited when Mike is like,
it's the ritual of the chud.
We need to do this.
And I was like, holy shit, they're gonna finally do this.
And they do it like half.
Yeah.
And then there's this whole thing where they kill Pennywise,
again, the exact same way they kill him in the first movie.
It looks kind of creepy when he becomes like a clown baby.
He still becomes the spider like they did in the...
He becomes the spider in the book?
Yeah.
But I mean, here's the thing.
I think they were clearly going,
we need to leave the door open for a third movie.
They'll do it.
God forbid these fucking pigs ever have enough money
in these studios.
Honestly, when I saw chapter two,
I was like, they're making another it.
They're going off the book.
So then that happens and then fucking,
they replace it with all of this horse shit
that doesn't need to be there.
One of the things they do, and I'm scratching my fucking head
at the end of this thing.
You got, who's the main character, Billy?
I don't know any other names.
Well, McAvoy, split, right?
You got him going, Mike, he's talking to Mike on the phone
and Mike is still in dairy and McAvoy isn't.
And he goes, he goes, Mike, I remember this time.
It's not like this time, I remember it.
It's like, no, they forget immediately again
at the end of the book.
That's how this works.
They cut out the thing about like, you meet his,
McAvoy's wife character at the beginning of this thing,
and it's supposed to be that they have this strain marriage
which they do in the book, and then the whole meaning
fullness of that is she comes back to dairy to find him
and she goes looking for him in the sewer by herself
and then Pennywise puts her in the dead lights
and he somehow wakes her out of it
and that sort of reignites their love for one another.
And it's like the last thing he's able to do
with his memories and dairy or whatever.
And in this one, that never happens.
It's just like, hey, check out his bitch wife.
That's literally all it is and then that's the end of it.
And then what's it called happens to?
You mean the heavy wife?
No, no, that's Eddie's wife.
Eddie's wife, McAvoy's a big part of the book
and in this she really exists, you see her for one second
so that everyone can call his wife fat.
Yeah, that's all it is.
Which is, I guess, fine in 2019 for some reason.
That's all it is.
And then they're letting Hayder riff
like his job of the HUD impression through, you know.
It's like how every movie Kevin Pollock was in
for 10 years he had to do his shattering.
Yeah, yeah, including like serious dramas.
Like Ricochet, he's doing shattering.
Yeah.
And then what's it called to?
So, um, fuck, what's it going to say?
McAvoy's wife never comes back, Eddie's wife.
Oh, God, dammit.
I don't know.
They just, they cut out so much good stuff.
So much simple stuff.
It just would have been simple.
The scares would have been, they would have been better.
And the part they decide to keep is this fucking stupid
Paul Bunyan statue scene.
Yeah.
It is absurd.
It looked like a fucking Lego thing came to life.
Yeah.
What are you guys doing?
For me.
And then that thing with Eddie and the basement.
Why is his, why does the leper throw up on him?
Why is it just played off as a joke?
Why does it play Angel of the Morning when the puke comes out?
The entire theater was silent.
No one even laughed.
Like if the, if the, if it was supposed to cause people to laugh,
it didn't, if it was supposed to be scary,
it certainly didn't.
Why would you put that music to it?
It was supposed to be funny and it was a bad joke.
And then on top of all this, it's just like, you know guys,
we're dealing with some real loose logic here already.
Yeah.
You're asking me to go on some suspension of disbelief here
with the book and, and then with the book as is.
And then you're going to cut out every detail in the book
that allows you to nudge me into believing this shit.
Talk like, if you're going to get rid of the whole Pennywise
likes the flesh seasons with fear, it tastes better.
Then have him act on that.
Don't have a little girl go under the bleachers
and have him be like super nice to her
and not do anything scary to her.
And then he just eats her.
And it's like, well, she wasn't seasoned with fear, Pennywise.
She wasn't scared of you.
And if you're able to do that to kids whenever you want,
why are you not killing Eddie and the basement
of the pharmacy?
Yeah, why are you not?
You've got to show me how they're escaping.
And then at the end of the movie,
they walk by a marquee, movie marquee,
it says Nightmare on Elm Street 5.
And before that, I'm sitting there going
in that final climactic sequence.
I'm going, what are they doing?
Nightmare on Elm Street?
Everybody's going into their own little dream world,
like in dream warriors.
What the fuck is going on here?
And then they walk by, and I'm like, oh, for God's sake,
they did that on purpose?
Probably, yes.
And then all these articles came out like here's why
it chapter two is basically another Nightmare
on Elm Street movie.
And why I think there's going to be a lot more.
And Pennywise is not scary.
You felt that in the audience.
They, if you have to put CGI on this fucker's face
every time he appears, the actor has not done his job.
We discussed mostly in our first review
about what bad casting it was to cast somebody their age
to be this scary clown.
The whole thing is that it's an adult.
And people like, kids are scared of adult clowns.
Remind me to make a point about that when you're done.
All right.
But him, you know, it's basically Beetlejuice or the mask.
It is constant like, things are coming out of his face.
He's morphing into other things.
And none of these things are scary.
There's no basis in real fear.
You're just watching, you know, shitty like modern day
special effects shit that doesn't even look very good.
So Pennywise doesn't work.
Obviously then the movie doesn't work.
The last hour for me, the humor killed it.
And I mean, they went beyond the Marvel shit.
When they're looking at the scary, not scary scary
and very scary doors, there are like five wise cracks
before they open the fucking door.
And then the little dog bit.
And I'm like, guys, you've lost us.
You've lost us that it's what you're saying
about how it's already a hard thing to buy.
No one is even sure what's going on in the last hour
of this movie.
The rules aren't made clear.
Nobody knows how to kill it.
So that doesn't work.
And they're riffing and joking the whole time.
So you can't get your footing in anything.
The last hour completely lost me.
But they do keep it loud and moving around so much
that you're kind of like, all right.
I see how afterwards you said, okay, this didn't work.
I came away like, all right.
That was like going in a amusement park.
It didn't make any sense, but I had a nice time.
And that's really the difference.
But it's not an effective horror movie.
And even the thing with like the kid,
the little kid getting killed by Pennywise and the maze.
Yes.
And then that's the reason George goes in.
George, no, George, he was his brother.
That's the reason McEvoy goes into the tunnel by himself.
Yes.
It's like, no, in the fucking book,
it's because his wife goes in alone
and he has to go after her.
Why are you complicating this with other elements
that are making it a less intriguing story?
I don't believe that Pennywise killing this kid
who you've now added in this insignificant fucking character
who's there in the beginning as a joke with Bill Hader.
When the kid goes up and he goes,
the fun's just about to begin.
And then Bill Hader's like, you little shit.
You can't scare me, you fucking clown.
You know, and then the kid's like, no, it's your catchphrase.
And then you're supposed to believe that a comic in 2018
has a catchphrase with dates and Reno coming up.
The fun's about to begin.
And then the little kid comes back and McEvoy's like,
you run, you run as fast as you can or whatever.
And then that kid gets killed and he's like,
Pennywise, God, I'm, I gotta go.
And it's like, no, this is, none of this is believable.
This is bad writing.
Oh, here's more bad writing.
Wait, what did I say to remind me of?
Remind you of.
Yeah, remember when I said remind me to make a point about that
after you finish your point?
No, Pat, you gotta be kidding me.
You said you didn't say remind me,
you don't know what you're talking about.
No, you were talking and I said remind me to make up
to say something about that when you're done making your point.
You said, okay.
Okay, so what was I talking about?
That's why I said remind me.
Joe, you're getting too amped up on it.
I'm not amped up.
You literally have no recollection of it.
No, you, because I'm started to talk,
you go remind me I got something to say about that after.
Remind yourself.
You just said, yeah.
Two minutes later, go, okay.
You said yeah, I'll remind you.
Joe, what do you want me to say?
I'm talking about the CGI, Pennywise.
That's what I talked about.
Yeah.
Oh, it was not scary.
Yes.
Yeah, there you go.
That's what I need to remind you.
Why don't you ask me what you were talking about
and not making it about you?
You know, you need to remember what you were talking about.
You know when somebody says to you when you go,
I'm supposed to remember what I'm saying
and remember to remind you of something.
This is what you do.
Let me just give you a life lesson here.
With somebody, if I'm walking with you out of the house
and I leave soup simmering on the stove
and I go, do me a favor.
Remind me while we're out
that I got to shut the soup off.
I'm gonna forget.
Don't go, okay.
And then later go.
It's not my problem.
I was probably just trying to return to what I was saying.
Go, you say, I'm also gonna forget.
I can't remind you.
All right, I'll let you know, I'll tell you the truth next.
That's it.
Except I didn't, I remembered it.
Yeah, after you said, I don't know.
After you acted like I'm crazy for saying,
what did I ask you to remind me of?
Oh, I'm right here.
I'm right.
No.
I would never say to remind me of this land.
You're an adult.
What are you talking about?
Say what you need to say.
I gotta talk about my side of the conversation
and remind you of yours.
I said, remind me to make a point about this part
of what you're saying, but finish your point first
and you said, okay.
Well, I didn't mean it.
And yet, here I am reminding you
that I was talking about CGI Pennywise.
Let's, I'm gonna put this one to the fans
and I look forward to these influx of people
telling me how right I am.
Joe, you're just not.
I am.
No, we'll put it to you.
You're responsible for your own conversation is my,
is my, I am aware of that.
But when somebody says, do me a favor, remind me
and you go, okay, at the very least, if you forget,
go, sorry, I forgot.
Don't go, hey, asshole, it's your problem.
That's what I'm complaining about.
But I've already told you what it was
and you're still not telling us about.
No, I know, but your initial reaction was,
was like, fuck you, I didn't say that.
That was not by the power.
And it's like, no, I said, remind me, remember?
And you're like, no, I didn't say that.
It's like, dude, you could at least just be like,
sorry, I forget.
I feel like I need a nap.
Are you, do you know the words I'm sorry?
Are you able to say those words?
I am so not sorry.
I know you're not.
That's why you're wrong.
Are you kidding me?
I am absolutely not sorry.
I know you're not.
That's why you're wrong.
We'll put it to a vote.
I can't wait to hear what the fan says.
Loot of course.
It's not ludicrous.
I think it is.
Do you want me to play back the tape?
I don't understand what you're mad at me about.
I'm not mad at you at all.
I'm just wanting you to finish your fucking CGI point,
which I reminded you of.
After I said, go back to what you were saying,
your initial response was, I don't fucking remember.
It's not my problem.
That's all I'm pointing out to you right now.
I got it.
God damn it.
Well, fans send us your thoughts.
I'm curious.
Anyway, what I was going to say is,
is you make a great point about the CGI thing.
Oh, it was the casting of his age.
Yes.
This is why that's an extra excellent point
because they show him in this one without the mega -bod.
And they have to age him out to be like 50 years old.
Why didn't they just get a 50 -year -old actor?
And it doesn't even really look like him.
It's like this weird, it's like an Irish -ed kind of thing.
It kind of looks like Paul Giamatti.
It should have been.
Who I said in the first review, it should have been cast as Pennywise.
I usually, when these things happen,
you know who gets offered roles and stuff.
I haven't heard of anybody who was,
they were interested in except this kid,
which boggles my mind.
Unless they decided early on, we won an unknown.
But I need that IMDB trivia page.
I need to know these people were offered the role of Pennywise.
I need to know.
It's the second one to have it.
The first kid to have it was that kid from We're the Millers
and Mid -Summer, who looks like he's 15.
Yeah.
They at least got a guy.
So they made a decision.
We need a young, cool Pennywise, which is the wrong decision.
And I love it.
I love this fucking business.
These people are so foolish.
We've got to bring diversity and everything.
We've got to, until it's time to make some money.
And then their literal thinking with this is,
we have to put a hot guy in the role of the scary monster
because if we have a freaky guy going out there doing press
for this, young women won't want to see it.
Probably.
That's exactly what it fucking, or I shouldn't say exactly.
You know what I mean?
Anyway, this was probably it.
This was a great episode.
Woo!
Got some heat in there.
Walsh.
We got to squeeze another one in before Vince gets over here.
Yes.
Coming up, our next, I mean, these are all,
we're recording kind of in advance,
but our next episode will be season three
of Stranger Things.
I'm occasionally on Instagram and Twitter
at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe.
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
I will be, you know what?
This might make it out in time for,
I'll be at the Come and Take it Festival in Houston, Texas
in November.
Let me pull out the dates here.
I'm going to take it.
Kind of an aggressive name.
It's better than come and give it.
I guess so.
You know, that sounds dirty.
The seventh and eighth of November,
this might be out just before then actually.
So, I hope to see you there.
I don't have any specifics about my shows yet.
The schedule is not up, but I will be there.
I'm usually there every year.
It's at the secret group.
That's the name of the venue in Houston.
If you're in Houston and you're a comedy fan,
you're probably familiar with it.
It's one of the coolest, coolest venues
in that I've ever played in general,
not just in Texas, but it's three venues under one,
two, three venues on one campus.
There's the outside stage and then the two inside stages
and then it usually, and then there's the awesome bar party area.
Usually devolves into a great time of drinking
and Valley Hoey, is that the word?
Valley Hoey, I think it's just Valley Hoey.
So, it'll be fun.
I'll be there, show, come in, come and take it.
That's it.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you in hell.