I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's the second episode.
This lovely month of April, I'm going to be talking Justice League today.
I'm Joe D 'Arosa, and I'm Patrick Walsh, how are you Joe?
I'm doing okay.
I hate to correct you right out of the gate, but we've already done Justice League
three years ago.
We're actually doing a little something called the Snyder Cut.
It's cold, but Justice League or vice versa.
I'm doing well.
Today, I get my second dose of the vaccine less than a week.
Okay.
I'm very excited about that.
Yeah, I guess I'll say as well.
It's highly controversial, at least on Twitter, which I have to remind myself more and more
lately is fake and not the real world.
But yeah, in Los Angeles, it was this weird thing where everyone felt like the worst thing
you could do would be to take a vaccine away from an underprivileged person.
And I was like, I agree.
I'm going to wait my turn.
I'm not dying to get out there.
We still have to wear masks anyway.
What do I care?
I'll wait till they call my name.
And a little by little, my friends just start opening up to me and I realize everyone I knew
was vaccinated or halfway there.
And who knows who didn't feel comfortable admitting it to me.
But I just was like, oh, shit, I'm being left out.
So I asked people how did you do it and a lot of them stayed at pharmacies until they closed
and then they were going to throw away doses and stuff like that.
I had a buddy who got vaccinated at Costco just by walking in the door and saying, oh, you guys
do vaccinations here?
And they were like, yeah, we'll do you and your wife.
Right.
Immediately.
So I'm like, well, shit, I'm going to get this done.
They're opening all of Los Angeles to get the vaccine in two weeks anyway.
So beat the rush.
But I was on the phone with my attorney because finally, I have some work to speak of that I
can't announce yet.
But congrats.
Thank you.
Some work coming in.
It's been a while.
And been a while since I could.
So yeah, she goes, have you been vaccinated yet?
And I said, no.
And she goes, you know, a few of my friends went up the other day to the hospital, which is
five minutes from my house.
And there was like a two minute wait, no appointment needed.
I go, are you serious?
She goes, well, yeah, let me just hear it clicking.
She goes, what's your birthday?
I tell her.
She goes, you have an appointment in 30 minutes.
I'm like, all right.
I go up there.
There's no one there.
I walk in.
I got my first shot.
So on 420, which I found extra special, I'm getting my second shot.
I get my second shot this coming Monday, April 5th.
And I mean, man, did I get fucked though?
Because every story that I hear, yeah, is your story.
Of course, the place I went to, it's an hour drive.
And it took two hours of standing in line in a very tight hallway with a bunch of other
people.
At one point, a guy in the line goes, hey, maybe we open a window in here.
It's like, what's going on in here, guys?
We're on top of each other.
You just hear the doors shut and see a lot of the other side of you.
Yeah.
But so, so, so New York announced that they're going to do this thing called the vaccine
vaccination passport, I believe it's called.
And it's basically an app you get on your phone.
And you can register that you have been vaccinated on this app.
And you know, it's one of those little weird, they're not barcodes, whatever those things
are called, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
You scan or whatever.
You use it with your camera on the phone.
Yeah.
And it's one of those.
And it says, you know, and it's like big venues are going to do it like Madison Square
Garden and stuff like that.
So, you know, it's like you scan it and it says, yeah, I've been vaccinated.
And then you can go in.
And I don't know what the rules are once you're in.
I don't know if it's only vaccinated people allowed in or there's a vet, whatever, but who
cares?
Like I like, okay, cool.
Like, yeah, I get it.
But you know, of course, now that's becoming politicized.
And now that's it.
So the governor Florida is saying that he is going to ban this method in the state.
And for what reason, like, like how dare you and it's, it's just political.
It's like, it's like, and it's like asking for your papers or something like that.
Yeah.
And it's, it's just, it's obviously you have to prove your, you have to prove your clearance
in many ways as an, as an independent senator, pointed out and criticizing the governor
Florida.
And he was like, if a restaurant says you have to wear shoes to come in, it's because it's
their private property.
So you have to wear shoes to come in.
Yeah.
If Disney World wants to say you have to do this to come in, they're allowed to do it.
It's their place.
But it just takes me back to this thing I've always been furious about with everything.
This is on all sides of this argument.
I don't understand why places can't just do what they want to do.
And if you don't like it, you don't go to that place.
If I want to have a restaurant where I say everybody smokes if they want to, yeah.
And you are against the don't come to my smoking restaurant.
Why is this a blanket rule?
Why is it a thing?
I don't get it.
I gotta say I'm sure somebody could, could find a, a devil's advocate argument or poke
some holes in it, but I don't disagree with that either.
And in fact, I, even when the smoking thing was happening in New York and all my friends
were really bitching about it 20, you know, whatever it was 15, 20 years ago, I never, I've
never smoked.
I didn't care.
Never cared.
But I did wonder why wouldn't there be certain bars you can just smoke him where people
know that, okay, I'm a smoker, I'll go to the smoker bar.
It makes no sense at all.
So, so what this becomes now is this, it becomes the socio -political pissing contest, right?
So, so, so the no smoking in bars is certainly a more liberal type cause than a, than a conservative
type cause, right?
Yeah.
So, that's been imposed now and that's a law and you just can't do it.
You can be fine.
So, so quick pause and I'm sorry.
Smoking is about the best example you can use.
Smoking anyone's smoking knows the health risk.
You know that you're endangering like doing it.
It's on the package for Christ's sake.
So you've, you've made that decision.
Which you could also say by the way about anyone choosing to go drink in a bar, alcohol does
the same thing.
Exactly.
But if you are in a, so I get that they don't want people who are trying to enjoy their
dinner.
Like let's say, I understand why Danny doesn't allow smoking.
I don't even get that.
It to me, it's like, then don't eat at the smoking restaurant.
That's it.
But when I'm saying, Danny's wouldn't be a smoking place.
Yeah.
Danny's wouldn't do it because Danny's needs to appeal to the widest audience.
But I'm saying, if you have a bar that's known as a smoking bar, in the way there are
bars known as cop bars, there are bars known as St. Louis Cardinal bars, etc.
Why the hell shouldn't everyone there?
And by the way, these places would do bang a business because all the smokers would go there
and they'd be allowed to smoke and be around others who have decided and accepted the risk.
And anybody walking in off the street, you just put a big sign up and says, this is a smoking
bar.
Right.
Well, and make it obnoxious.
Make it like the ABC system.
Make it a giant fetus with a with a ghost buster sign over it and say, like, don't come
in here.
It's bad for you.
Make it the ghost buster sign with him smoking a cigarette.
But people would still go, you know, because people love to smoke.
It makes no sense.
I didn't even know I had an issue with this until you brought it up, but now I do.
Well, the bat and so the backlash now, so this, this is what I mean, though, that this becomes
a social political thing, right?
So now people, conservatives now are going to go, well, the liberals got their way
with this.
And it's like, they did.
And it's annoying.
And it bothers me.
But, but now, so now they're going to go, so we're not going to play your pandemic passport
game or what it, you know, it's like, right, Jesus Christ, guys, can we just just open the
door?
I don't give a shit at this.
I actually was a person who thought contact tracing wasn't a good idea when I first heard
it.
Because that's how they always slip in, you know, it's for your own good.
We, your phone is listening to you for your own safety.
You know what I mean?
I never would have done contact tracing.
That's a different, yeah, but it's, it's just at a point where it's, and they've said in
the passport, they're like, they can't get any of your information.
They just see that you, they, it's just verified.
And of course, I understand why somebody could argue that's bullshit.
They'll say whatever they can't find.
But is this really any different than them scanning my driver's license?
They've got me, they've got what they need.
They've got my soul.
They've got it.
Yeah.
What, what else are we getting here?
What, what, what is the difference?
We're all fuck.
Look, I bought a pair of pants from Bonobos in 2011.
I don't even know if the company still exists.
But Bonobos sends me an email two weeks ago.
Somebody's hacked into our system.
They 100 % have all of your information.
You need to take steps to correct this.
I bought one pair of pants literally 10 years ago.
And this, I get these emails all the time,
GrubHub, DoorDash.
Hey, we had a hack in.
They, it happens constantly.
So it sucks, you know, but like that,
it's the world we live in.
And this pandemic, it calls for different rules than normal.
You must know that.
You're fucking idiots.
I just don't get why it's, sir.
Why can't just go to the venue you like?
I just don't get, if there was a, you know, I don't,
if there was a, yeah, a fucking doughnut shop in my neighborhood.
Yeah, they put a big silo doors as if your Arab,
you're not allowed to eat our doughnuts.
I'd be like, that sucks.
I, I guess I can't eat there.
Yeah.
And even if it wasn't my own race of the way that I would go,
their assholes, I won't eat there.
They, they seem shitty.
Now this is obviously an extreme example.
But my point is, is like, you could literally put a sign
on your window that says, we will not serve Joseph Jared
Derosa, and I would just go, okay, I'll go to that.
Like, the other place, I wouldn't get on a podium.
This has got to, it's like, guys, we're, we're,
these are different stakes, man.
You know, I understand fighting the good fight when it's,
for instance, civil rights.
Yeah, we're the right for women to vote
and be treated fairly in the workplace.
Then you fight the fight.
We're going to fight the fight over the fucking pandemic passport.
This is ridiculous.
It's so dumb.
Is that, is that going to be everywhere or just New York?
No, it's, well, that's why the governor of Florida is saying
he's going to ban it.
It's going to be, I mean, I don't know if it's going to be everywhere.
It's going to be in many places.
So, you know, I'm just curious.
I mean, also too, and I say this fully as a bachelor, ladies,
anybody, I don't care what your political persuasion is.
If you love Biden, if you love Trump,
if you love the Indies, whatever the hell you love,
if your political convictions supersede your ability
to go party and get laid, you're out of your fucking mind.
Yeah, then it's a religion at that point.
You're out of your fucking mind.
They could be telling me at the door of every bar right now,
you have to register as a Republican or you can't come in.
I'd be like, sign me up.
That's fine.
Sign me up.
I want to come in.
I want a party like, I'm tired of this.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Right.
It's also like, why would you, I mean, these people,
there are people who don't even believe this pandemic is real,
but why would you trust your fellow man?
We can't trust our fellow man anymore,
but we never could, by the way.
But if nothing else, you know,
we, Joe and I have talked about how this pandemic proves
that we are all alone in this world.
For sure.
As, uh, as Tony's parents and mother said,
you'd die in your own arms.
And it's a booboo sheet, booboo.
Yeah, Joe, how was that?
Was that a decent, Joe?
Joe's on season six of the smurfs
won't watch the soprano because it's unrealistic.
No, was that a good impression though?
I was just having fun with the impression.
It was okay.
Now you try to kill me, bye.
Nah, that's all right.
I do a pretty good Gandalfini,
but the best one I ever did was that little voice note I sent to you.
For some reason, like one morning,
my throat had the right amount of gunk in it
and I hit it perfectly.
Right.
Yeah, Pat will often send me little voice messages.
The man will not pick up the phone.
No matter how many times I call him,
he'll text me 77 texts in a row.
He'll get upset if you don't respond right away,
which I do too.
I mean, I also do that.
We're fragile.
Yeah.
I hate the phone I always have.
I was in a long distance relationship for a lot,
several of them actually, so it's just not for me.
But full, he sends me full songs he makes up.
It's just a man unraveling.
You should count yourself lucky, Joe.
I do count myself lucky.
You're getting these.
I used to put those on Vine.
I'd get 50k likes.
Oh, I think we're shortening vinyl.
I think you're saying you like sold them this record.
No, no, no, no.
I don't even remember where we started.
This conversation went into so many tangents,
but we were talking about the pandemic.
The point is get out of the house, people.
And what I was saying is you can't trust your fellow man.
I'm saying, like yesterday, so I said,
I went to see nobody in the last podcast at the theater
and I was honestly conflicted and I have been conflicted
and I was nervous about it.
And ever since I heard that story
about the guy walking into the dark night
and shooting people in a theater,
there's something about whenever I sit in the theater
and they close those doors,
I'm just like, yeah, I don't know.
It's not an issue, but it's like,
boy, you would be just a fucking sitting duck in here.
Yeah, it's horrifying.
And then when me and my buddy John saw midsummer
on July 4th, 10 AM, they had this massive earthquake.
And I saw it in the valley,
which was like the center of the earthquake.
And the picture went off the spools.
Like it shook the film off the spools.
And we all were like standing up, didn't know where to go.
It's a very vulnerable dangerous place.
This fucking asshole walks in.
Of course, gorgeous girlfriend on his arm.
He walks in and saw we talk it.
You can't just say, asshole.
What type of asshole we talk?
I would consider this asshole a muscle guy
who's letting himself go, asshole.
Like a thick, man, he got the girl when he was,
he got the girl when he was cut like a diamond.
And now she's still gorgeous.
And he's starting to look like dog shit.
Yeah, yeah.
I love seeing that in either.
Steroids are slipping, you know,
the, it's just like the after effects of all the,
the HGH, she was taking her, starting to deal with him.
I love seeing that in either direction.
When you see it sometimes with the woman
and the guy's hot, you're like, oh,
she was, she was smoking it.
I love watching.
It's like, uh, your investment went to shit, didn't it?
You're, you're riding it out.
You won't close the shop.
Well, they come, they come walking in and they sit down
and the two of them in unison pull off the masks
and they come out at the beginning.
They're like, if you're actively eating or drinking,
you can take your mask, which by the way,
if you're eating popcorn, that is it.
That means you're taking the mask off for the entire movie.
It's just, it should have just canceled popcorn,
but they care more about money than your life.
This guy takes the mask off,
his girlfriend takes the mask off and they, the guy,
she didn't start looking around like anybody want to say
something, like, bro, there's four people in here.
Like, I, it's that, that attitude to me is the worst.
If he had walked in, no mask.
What'd you say?
I could kick his ass.
If he had walked in, no mask.
I respect that more than the guy who's like,
I'm going to do this just so I can get an argument.
Well, here's the thing.
Put it, you're putting our lives at risk.
We're in an enclosed space.
The pose, the pose is stupid.
I also think the rule of if you're eating,
you can take your mask off.
Otherwise, wear your mask is stupid.
It's like, it's really those are that,
if you, but here's my point,
if you guys are at that distance, you, you run no risk.
You run no risk whatsoever.
If you're that spread apart, so you can just,
they could say, once you're in your seat,
you can take, it's no different than the restaurant rules.
I endorse, once you're sitting, you can take your mask off.
Please don't walk around with no mask on
because then God forbid you sneeze or you spit
or whatever you could endanger people
other than those at your table.
So I'm not, I'm not going to Godzilla Kong on Friday night,
even though I got my AMC pass
because that's going to be 40 to 50 % full.
And that is pretty close for comfort
in an enclosed area for me.
Oh yeah, I, and there will be those people there too,
up in the valley who are going to walk in,
mask off like somebody want to say something.
And that's always been my whole take
with this entire thing.
Jamie Killstein had a thing on YouTube or Instagram,
I can't remember, but it was a video where he said,
here's an approach, here's a new idea
for an approach to the pandemic.
Don't be a dick.
It was like, you want to wear a mask?
You don't want to wear a mask?
Don't be a dick.
And it's like, I totally agree, bro.
It's like, I was in a Best Buy recently shopping sound bars
as I do.
You know me, I love sound bars.
What's the appeal of the sound bar quickly?
Do you not have one?
No.
Well, I bought one that has a talk feature on it,
meaning you can act, it has a feature
where it brings the dialogue up.
Okay.
It helps me greatly, because sometimes
because the way movies are mixed
and they don't know how you're going to be watching it,
like they're mixed.
And if you're not watching it in 5 .1,
surround it, it doesn't sound right.
Right.
And that feature alone was great.
And then also too, you get the subwoofer
and you know, you're watching like Star Wars or something,
and it's a little more of a theatrical experience.
Okay.
But, and you can get him cheap now.
But anyway, I'm talking to the salesman.
He's got his mask, he's not being a dick,
but he's got his mask under his nose.
You know, it's not bubbles or flying out and shit.
And I just was like, I don't care.
I'm just going to talk to him.
Like, I'm talking to him.
Like, I'm a little freaked out, I don't care.
But the point is, it's on me
to then not turn to the person next to me and go,
well, why do you care?
You can care.
Yeah.
It's okay if you care.
It's okay if I don't care.
It's okay.
The point is is when I approach you,
I'm going to be very careful out of respect for you.
That's it.
Like, that's how I roll.
And if somebody else doesn't want to roll that way,
that's their deal.
Am I allowed to get annoyed at them?
Yes.
Am I going to start a confrontation over it?
No.
And am I going to not give a shit sometimes?
Yeah, it's just, let people just do what they need to do.
Let people just live.
I'm of the belief that if I go to the bowling alley next week
and they tell me at the door that I have to swear my allegiance
to the demon Pazuzu, I'm going to fucking do it
because I want to go into the goddamn bowling alley.
I don't care.
That's who I am.
That's me.
And I say you should be allowed to be that.
I am, I'm stricter than you.
There are people who are way stricter than me,
but people should be sort of allowed at this point
to kind of do what they want to do in that framework.
I agree with you.
But don't be, but don't turn around like Mr. Pose guy,
like you said, stop it.
Take your mask off and just sit there and face forward
and don't drag anybody into your shit.
Well, there's an elevator.
You got to go on at the Burbank Theater
and this guy, as we're waiting, he turns to me
and he goes, hey, are you cool with two in the elevator?
And I said, yes.
And thank you very much.
Like I thought it was kind of overkill,
but I was like, thanks.
You didn't realize he met your asshole.
We get in, you know, going down, going up
and down, both work fantastically.
But then when I left, there's this couple on the elevator
and I was like, are you guys cool if I get on with you?
And you could tell they were just relieved, you know,
that I wasn't some guy who was gonna be like,
you're gonna have a fucking problem.
Now if I get on, it's how you say things.
And just understand that everyone might not share
your world view and act accordingly and be nice.
It's all you can really.
The world will not remember if you a virtue signaled
in front of a store about why you need to wear a mask
and everybody who doesn't is an asshole and a murderer
and be whether or not you wrestled the Walmart reader
to the ground because you felt like
your freedom right was not to work.
Nobody's gonna remember either of you.
Never, nobody's gonna remember the dumb lawyer
that goes to the beach in the Grim Reaper costume, okay?
Nobody's gonna remember the character.
I remember that guy.
The caring that fist fights our way into a burger king
with no mask on it.
Nobody's gonna remember any of it guys.
It's not, it's not about a worth fighting.
This is not the hell to die on.
What you should care about right now is you haven't had sex
in a year, get out of the house and get drunk
by all means necessary.
Well, I don't agree with that.
I mean, don't be careful with your sex
and your drinking.
I mean, we're still not out of this thing for Christ's sake.
I, you know what I mean.
I'm not saying I know what you know what I mean.
You know what I meant.
What you mean?
You know what I meant?
Speaking of, this is an appropriate conversation today
because we're gonna be talking justice.
That's right.
You, yeah.
But first, do you have, do you have a scream and end
or can I go directly to the, the movie corn?
Uh, did I have a, I think I did hold on one second.
Oh yeah.
Oh God.
I sent this to you.
You didn't respond.
Episodes of SpongeBob Squarepants have
not been removed because they've been deemed inappropriate.
What the fuck is going on man?
This is, I've never seen SpongeBob.
I thought the beauty of it was that it was for adults and kids.
I mean, what were the issues?
Um, it was one of them, uh, I guess it was Mr. Crabby
one of the characters is so absurd.
One of the fish men, uh, was depressed.
So they took him out on a night on the town for night on the town.
And then he said at one point, let's do a panty raid.
It'll be funny.
We'll go on to that lady fish.
House and still do a panty raid and they took it off
because they said, this is not appropriate.
It's like, did they go do a panty raider?
Why wouldn't they just trim the lawn?
I don't know.
And then two other ones were coming to the Nickelodeon HQ
should have flagged the panty raid scene five years ago.
I don't think they actually do a panty raid.
It's just, I mean, how about this?
How about a parent says to their kid, you know,
you shouldn't do a panty raid, right?
And he goes, yeah, I know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that probably work.
Hey, hey, buddy, I know it's funny when the coyote sticks
a stick of dynamite down the pig's pants.
You know, you shouldn't do that, right?
Yeah, no, I know that.
I'm not a fucking moron.
Yeah.
Watching a fish talk for Christ's sex.
That, yeah.
So, uh, uh, that's my, that's all I got.
I, I think that, I think that will slow down.
It's showing no signs of it, but I think it will slow down.
Mm -hmm.
Yeah.
Well, we'll see.
Joe speaking of fish men, I saw a picture called humanoids
from the deep.
You know, I own it and I haven't watched it yet.
I, it's, I mean, it's not a good movie.
It's, uh, warming raves about this thing, man.
Yeah, it's got this kind of weird, uh,
cult appeal.
It's very much, um, you know, men and fish suits.
They look a lot like the creature from the Black Lagoon.
They kind of come out of the water, uh, and rape women.
That is essentially the plot of the movie.
They come in and sexually assault women, um, just to,
to breed with them or just, yeah, because they're rotten.
No, to breed with them.
The rape scenes are not, uh, graphic, per se,
but there are a lot of them, um,
and that's kind of it.
I mean, it's a, it's a, it's a manverse fish beast action picture
to some extent.
It's not really scary.
Um, I, I, I guess certain aspects of it were kind of fun.
At the end, they do a, uh, you know, a birth.
That's a complete ripoff of alien, you know,
a baby comes out from one of the women that got fucked
by the humanoids from the deep, um,
oh, the deep, the deep, I get it.
No, I get it.
And that, and it, and I was like, oh, this must have been a precursor to alien.
But no, it was after alien.
So I don't know why people have such love for this movie.
It doesn't necessarily make sense to me,
but it's got kind of a, uh, you don't normally see a grindhouse movie
involving monsters.
They're usually like just all human, uh, you know,
just humans, humans from the deep.
Yes, this was, you know, I don't know why it's got the, uh, the love it does.
It's not a great movie.
I remember Roger Corman in an interview saying he was like,
I, I believe that a movie's title should tell you exactly what you're getting.
You know, humanoids from the deep, and that was the example of use.
But, uh, yeah, okay, good, good title, but, um, doesn't have a great title,
but it's fun.
Yeah.
Uh, I watched, uh, I finally sat down and watched the Ocean's 11th, uh, Trilogy.
Okay, starring Brad Pitt, George Clooney, Don Cheetle, that Damon, Julie Roberts,
uh, Gould, Elliot Gould, uh, I'll start with Ocean's 11.
What a wonderful picture.
What a wonderful, fun, heist movie, lovely,
Caper picture.
I enjoyed every moment of it.
The banter is wonderful.
The snapy dialogue.
It's just great.
Sort of a pinnacle of, of popular entertainment done right.
Yeah, it's just like just packed with laughs and twists and stars and love.
The romance is effective, you know, like you're actually
give a shit about Julie Roberts and George Clooney's to get in together.
Great movie.
I loved it.
Andy Garcia plays a great villain, likeable villain, which is always fun.
Well, Garcia is not, oh, Garcia is in one.
You're right.
He's also, no, Garcia is in all three.
He's on, they team up with him a little bit, right?
Yeah.
Well, but we'll get to that when I talk oceans 12.
All right.
Uh, well, I want to say, I'm doing a special Mike Nichol's edition of my, uh,
side podcast on here that I do.
And I've always bothered me.
Really?
Yeah, it's an hobby to you.
Yeah, it seems like a, like a real like hipster snotty, a little bit.
I don't like it, but, but he does good work that that said he does good work.
We could work.
I can't deny that.
I just read this huge biography that came out and I thought it was great.
And his movies are for the most part good.
He had some turns, of course, but, um, I did post my movie corner this weekend.
And the next one will probably be the Mike Nichol's issue.
I saw, you know what I rewashed was a scape from New York.
Mm hmm.
And so I, I had this weird thing where I always held a scape from New York as an
all -time classic in my mind.
And whenever anybody said how much they loved it, I would be like, yeah, it's fucking great.
And I knew that I did not like a scape from LA near as much and that it was kind of awful.
It's just a scape from LA is terrible.
But as I grew up, I was always like, well, I do like John Carpenter.
I like a lot of his stuff.
But like, if I'm being honest, the things I truly love of his are the thing by a, by a
mile and Halloween and past that, I think you're getting into kind of levels of, of
quality.
And on a rewatch of Escape from New York, and I also recently rewatched They Live.
I thought these are both great B pictures, but not great movies.
They don't elevate the B picture status in a way that the thing does.
In my opinion, Kurt Russell is a badass.
I love the character of Snake Pliskin.
The movie just kind of, it lacked a certain energy to me.
There's a lot of great moments.
I like the vibe of it, the whole Carpenter, like the music, the way it's shot.
I dug it all.
And it just sort of left me cold.
I think there's a reason that I've always sort of been like, yeah, it's great.
But never I couldn't really remember anything from it.
Even watching it again now, I was like, yeah, this always just sort of slips out
of my mind for some reason.
I don't know.
I don't hold it in the esteem that most do.
It's not quite as eventful I think as you want it to be.
Yeah, it's a prototypical 80s.
It is the prototypical 80s movie.
There'd be no Mandy without Escape from New York, you know, and I mean, like it is
the, it is the diagram to follow, but, but I know what you mean.
It's fun.
I, it's not one that I returned to often.
I actually kind of always thought the character of Snake Pliskin.
I was never that crazy about it.
I always thought the name was kind of dumb.
It's Clint Eastwood.
I mean, and I thought that like I've seen Kurt Russell much better in many other
things playing a bad at like big trouble in little China.
I think he's better in that.
I prefer big trouble in little China, yeah, I really do.
And at a time of Indiana Jones and Han Solo and all these cool male ass kicking
guys that had these great names.
I never thought Snake Pliskin was a cool name.
In fact, they, you know, they kind of make fun of it on the Simpsons, right?
I mean, that guy's name snake snake.
It's like it, you know, snake is the name of a Stephen King bully.
Yes, not a, not an action hero for me, but, but it is, it's not a bad character.
It's just not something.
Uh, yeah, you start talking the thing Halloween.
Yeah, uh, in the, I'll say it in the mouth of madness.
Yeah, there's a lot better carpenter out there in my opinion.
Not that just came from New York is bad, but it's just, it's, it's, you know,
I like his other, some of his other stuff better.
Same here.
I prefer big trouble, um, for sure, but, uh, yeah.
I, I liked it.
I do.
I think it's a B plus movie.
I just don't hold it in the steam.
Something might.
Oceans 12, um, the brilliantly name, the weird one.
It is the weird one.
Uh, again, very charming, very funny.
Uh, you can see that Soderbergh got, you know, they loosened the reins on him on this one.
Uh, cause it shot much more Soderberg style.
The, the first one is shot very Hollywood.
This is a Hollywood, heist movie, you know, and, uh, it plays by the book.
The second one, not only, uh, in, from the director's perspective,
does it get a little looser, takes more chances.
It also gets very meta with the script, uh, in self -right,
for rental, down to the point that they throughout the movie,
make a joke that Julia Roberts character looks exactly like the actress,
Julia Roberts.
And there's a part in the middle of the movie or toward the end,
where to pull the scheme off, they have her pop pose as Julia Roberts.
And then Bruce Willis comes in as Bruce Willis.
Yeah.
And he's like, Julia, what's up?
And it's pretty funny, but it's fucking insane.
Uh, it's not as much a heist movie as it is a caper movie.
Uh, Andy Garcia comes back in the sequel.
And says, basically, if you don't pay me back every dime,
you stole from me in the first movie, I'm going to have you all murdered.
Uh, and that's why they have to pull off this scheme against a new adversary,
played by, uh, is it, is it William Castle, whatever his name is?
Um,
I've seen one in three recently, not two.
Something castle, you know, uh, the guy from irreversible, right?
I can't see more.
Or is it?
Right.
Isn't it Vincent Cassel?
Vincent cat.
I thought it was Castle, Vincent Cassel.
It may be, but the guy from, yeah, from irreversible.
Yeah.
Uh, so that's two.
Uh, again, enjoyable.
It is the empire strikes back of the trilogy.
Yeah.
It's like longer and a little bit darker, but still very funny,
still very enjoyable.
And you get what you want out of your characters.
And, uh,
I mean, is it tofer grace or Adam Brody in that one?
Oh, that's right.
Tofer comes back in that one.
He's also in the first one playing himself because Brad Pitt,
when you meet Brad Pitt's character, he's teaching young Hollywood stars how to play poker.
And hats off to Tofer Grace and the, the crew of guys,
I forget who the other ones are in that scene, but they really,
they really don't make themselves look good.
Like they're so dumb and they, they don't understand anything about the game.
And then in the second one, when you see Tofer Grace,
he's in that like CD hotel room in Brad Pitt's hotel that he owns.
And there's like booze bottles everywhere.
He's just like a fucking wreck.
And I was like, ah, this made me really, I like Tofer Grace already,
but I was like, this really made me like Tofer Grace.
Like this is really funny.
Tofer Grace is the poor man's Adam Brody.
And I like Tofer Grace.
So that tells you how much I love Adam Brody.
But, um, I love him both.
It doesn't matter to me because I done him both.
Don't know both.
Um, I saw police story starring Jackie Chan,
which is new on criterion with a, they released police story one and two,
which are generally considered sort of the high points of Jackie Chan's career
and of martial art film in general.
Um, you know, maybe not on a level with enter the dragon or something like that.
But police story is, uh, is worthy of it, of its hype.
It's got incredible stunt work.
They actually show, he jumps, he's in a mall and he slides down this big ring of lights
with all the lights popping around him and it's very, very dangerous.
They actually show it twice in the movie.
They just re -show you the stunt again in the middle of the movie.
It's actually the end of the movie.
Um, so that goes to show you how seriously they're taking the plot of the thing.
And, you know, it's sort of like a very generic cop story,
police story, with incredible, incredible stunts,
which is kind of the, the M .O. for Jackie Chan's whole career
until he found a real niche in goofy comedy,
which I thought he really excelled at with rush hour and then the Shanghai noon
and nights.
Actually, maybe the only one who prefers Shanghai noon,
just because I thought Owen Wilson and him were so funny together.
But, um, yeah, he's, he's starting out.
He sings a full song in the, in the middle of the movie,
like he's clearly kind of finding himself as a performer.
But, um, yeah, it's a thrill to see somebody like,
it was when we were introduced to Jackie Chan, he was way past his prime, you know.
He was like a 45 year old man.
But he was still able to do the crazy shit.
Yeah, he blew us away.
So to go back and see him when he's 25 years old kicking ass,
it's a whole different thing.
That's not true.
Uh, I really recommend police story.
And I'm excited to watch police story too.
Was that your third?
That was my third.
Uh, my third is oceans 13,
which was rated PG 13 for brief sensuality,
which I wrote down just for that.
It said rated PG 13 for brief sensuality.
I didn't know that meant for our next podcast.
By the way, brief sensual.
Yeah.
I've been saying it to women on dates.
Would you like to come over?
Not for sex, just for some brief sensuality.
Uh, oceans 13.
I really liked quite a bit for a few reasons.
Number one, it gets back to the heist plot line of the first film.
It is, you know, it is a return to form.
Uh, the entire crew is back.
And now you have also actually Roberts does not come back.
And there's Catherine Zeta Jones.
But the rest of the crew is back.
And now you've added Ellen Barkin,
who is at her most.
Wow, you're just like,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, and she's great.
And then you've added Al Pacino.
And it's a great Al Pacino part because it's,
yeah, he's great in it.
It's fun.
Just hammy Al Pacino.
Like it's a lot of fun.
That sea of love reunion that everybody wanted.
I mean, Barkin and Pacino.
They said, when can we get the stars of sea of love together again?
Uh, my favorite line of the movie is when he's bullying L .A.
Gold at the top of that, the, the open construction floor of the casino.
They're building together.
Yeah.
He's telling L .A. Gold he's cutting him out of the deal.
And L .A. Gold, it goes, I won't sign that agreement.
And he goes, you're going to sign it.
And then he goes, what are you going to do?
Throw me off the roof.
And an opportunity goes, I don't want to.
Uh, it's a fun film.
Does Bernie Mac appear in any of these movies?
Or did I dream that?
No, he's in all three.
Bernie's in all three.
He's one of the 12.
Yeah.
Well, the 11.
He's one of the 11.
He's the reason he's in the original crew.
Man, I got to rewatch the whole thing.
I've only seen, I've only seen two in the theater.
I'm going to watch them all.
Yeah, three's the one where they like,
they rent the, the drill and they have to like make
the fake earthquake thing happen.
Right.
Um, so they can shut down this like security device.
And then three also has, uh,
Bob Einstein in it.
He plays Matt Damon CIA, dad, who comes into savings.
Yeah, it's great.
It's great.
There, there, there, it's a,
it's a really wonderful trilogy of films.
It made me want to see.
Oceans eight.
I've never seen it.
But I was like, shit, man.
I got to go see oceans eight now.
Cause I'd never really watched these either.
But then I got sad because I read that they say at the beginning of the movie
that Danny Ocean is dead.
And I'm like, well, I don't want to start the movie with that.
My, uh, wife and I saw oceans eight.
We've almost, I know together we've never walked out of a movie.
I've only done it once with suicide squad maybe twice.
We walked out of oceans eight.
Really.
And I will, I will say it was, it was her idea.
I wouldn't have been comfortable walking out of, of oceans eight.
But yeah, it was, uh, I wouldn't say it was any worse than anything else.
I just feel like that night or whatever.
We were just kind of like, fuck this.
Yeah.
You know, the, it just wasn't hitting.
But I'll give it a shot.
I'll give it another shot.
Speaking of suicide squad, little news psycho.
Did you see the trailer for the new suicide squad?
I did.
Uh, yeah, we discussed that this week.
That's right.
We did.
So I, Joe, Joe didn't think it looked good.
I thought I don't think any of these movies look good.
But this one looks more fun than most, I would say.
I was so excited to see the trailer for this thing.
I have friends in the movie.
Steve A .G.'s in it.
I love Steve.
Pete Davidson's in it.
I was excited for it.
I really was.
But this trailer, man, it was, I just felt like the jokes were really bad.
And it just, there was nothing captivating about it.
And, and I think.
I'll see it.
We'll probably review it on the show at some point.
It comes out on my birthday this year.
So I'll see it.
But.
I think I, you know, I fear that it's suffered.
It's going to suffer what a lot of these movies in the last year of suffered,
which is something great was on paper.
And then the pandemic hit.
And there was a lot of shit to work around.
And it affected the movie.
Like the trailer in and of itself doesn't even feel like a James Gun movie.
Like if you compared it to the Guardians of the Galaxy trailer, it's not.
It's not as eventful.
It's like there's just something about it that feels flat to me.
And I couldn't quite put my finger on it.
I mean, you know, trailers of misrepresented movies before.
I'm fairly optimistic just because he's one of the few guys making superhero movies
that I enjoy.
So I feel like I'll check her out.
Yeah, we'll see.
But anyway, speaking of superhero movies, the Snyder cut.
You know, I've waited for this for a long time.
And you know that I watched it for a long time.
Four hours to be exact over spread out over 18 days.
I watched justice.
I thought, okay, I'll watch a part a day.
I couldn't even do that.
I watched it all in one sitting.
I thought I was going to split it apart.
I couldn't stop watching.
I was pulled in 100 % from the beginning.
And every review of this film, it's got a very nice rating.
And it's gotten positive, positive reviews.
And every review has finally proven what I've been saying for the last few years.
Which is Batman versus Superman was a good movie.
This is the same tone.
It's the same characters.
It's a direct continuation.
They sang the reviews like Batman versus Superman.
The reviews like justice.
Everything they credit justice league with is what I thought was cool about.
Batman versus Superman.
And now you have people going like, in hindsight, Batman versus Superman now makes more sense.
And it's like, yeah, no, no, I know.
That's what I've been saying the whole time.
So I take it.
You didn't like the film, but I really, really enjoyed it.
I think I would have enjoyed it even more had it come out at the appropriate time.
Had I not had to sit through a terrible hatchet job by Joss Whedon.
Yeah, I mean, we saw that one together.
And I will say very few scenes in this even felt familiar to me, which either means that justice league was unmemorable,
which is very possible, or it's a completely different movie.
He said that 70 % of this new movie was different.
And they used about 30 % of his original stuff in the old film.
I remembered the old film.
I saw it twice.
So I remembered enough of it that I knew what from this was in that.
And this was I can't believe how much shit was on the cutting room floor with this.
Some of the new stuff he went back and shot.
I didn't think was necessary.
I was very, you know, I was very pumped for the new, this new Joker,
Lido scene that they kept talking about.
It felt very tacked on.
And I would say that I felt it was kind of pointless.
And it was one of my least favorite scenes in the movie, unfortunately.
And also added a very ambiguous.
I understand what the ending is supposed to mean and what it was supposed to set up.
But when you're doing something like this and you've got your shot to kind of bring closure.
And then you're going to have your shooter set up.
And then you're going to have your shooter set up a shooter set up a shooter set up a shooter set up a shooter set up a shooter set up an open ended thing.
Just, just ended that said.
I thought the redemption a resurrection rather a Superman, and this was handled far better.
I thought that the addition of Martian Man Hunter was awesome.
them, I thought they filled in all of the plot holes that Joss Whedon's version of this
film made either bigger or the new ones they created. They took out all of the stupid
fucking jokes that Joss Whedon added to them to the film.
I got all the stupid fucking jokes. Most of them. Most of them. There's very few jokes in
this. Well, the Flash Kid only speaks in jokes for the entire run.
Yeah. That's his character and that's the Flash character. So that's like saying like deadpool jokes
a lot. You know what I mean? But like Joss Whedon had Batman making jokes and shit. It was bad.
It was it was the Marvel thing that I was complaining about. Everybody talks like Tony Stark.
Everybody makes jokes, you know? Right. Well, every movie seemed horrifically depressed.
Yes. That's why I like it. And I guess that, you know, to me, the Marvel movies are they're
trying so desperately to be fun at every single moment that they become the opposite of fun to me.
They become numbing, deadening. And I hate them. The and just like loud and incest the tone is
the same throughout. So this movie which I watched all of it felt like no moment was trying to be fun.
And they both sort of met at the same ending of me not having fun, basically.
This felt super depressing and everyone just I'm depressed. I believe I get it. But like
God, when you're watching Aquaman bitch and Batman bitch and they're all rich and incredibly
attractive. And it's like and also everyone has parent issues, mom or daddy issues. Everyone has
the same kind of issues. And it's like, I guess that could be a theme. But it also is just kind of
stupid that everyone has some hang up with their dad or their mom. But that is those are the classic
storylines. I mean, look, this movie, to me, the great justice, no pun intended of this film, is that
it really laid out for every person out there who likes comic books. How much Marvel has stolen from
DC? Sure. Dark side was first. Thanos was ripped off of dark side. Dark side was first.
I mean, so quick pause when you're meaning that because I don't know anything about the shit.
Darks that you're saying dark side came first in the movies or in the comics or both.
In the comics. He was a character first. But did the Thanos be dark side to the screen?
To the screen. Yeah. But the character in the comics, it was like dark side was first.
As far as I know, the mother boxes, which are very similar to the infinity stones, were first.
When they started talking in this, mother boxes and all that shit, which is probably injustice
leaked too, I don't recall. But when they're going through all that stuff, I was like, God, this feels
exactly like the Avengers. And it's because that just and DC did it all first. Justicefully existed
before the Avengers. Deathstroke, who shows up at the end, existed before Deadpool. It's crazy.
How much shit Stan Lee ripped off? Yeah. And everybody that loves his shit. And I get it,
dude, like I like his shit too, man. I do. I really do. I actually like the classic Marvel stuff.
I don't like what the movies have turned it into. But everybody just gives him this pass.
Like, oh, big deal, man. It's like when you talk about like, you know, Zeppelin stole all that
shit. People go, oh, who wasn't still. It's like, that's not an excuse, man. Yeah. That's not that's
not a justification. Like you can't just that doesn't just dismiss it. And I felt that this film
really showed if you really look at the roots of where all this came from and everything they put
up there on the screen and how similar it felt to Marvel. And and if you go back and read two things
on the internet and realize, oh, my God, DC did all of this first. And if you guys remember and think
back 30 years, which I know for some of you, it's tough because you're young. But you think back
that DC were the crown, like they were the reigning champs of superhero movies. It was Christopher
Reeves Superman. It was Tim Burton Batman. It was DC, man, on television. It was Adam West Batman.
It was the original Flash series. It was Lois and Clark. It was it was Marvel fucked up repeatedly
over and over and oh, you couldn't fucking find a good Marvel movie or TV show out of cartoons
before this new batch. The original Punisher movie with Duff Lundgren is terrible. The original
Spider -Man made for TV shit is terrible. The original Hulk stuff is passable, but they change a lot
of bullshit. The original incarnate, the original Fantastic Four that Roger Korman did was bad.
It's like people just dismissed the history of this. It's like, no, guys, DC did it first and did it
better and laid all this groundwork for Marvel to swoop in and be able to take their little notes
and do this and then make a great thing after they fucked up a million times. The original two
Fantastic Four movies are awful. One of the Sam Raimi Spider -Man movies is good. The original
Ang Lee Hulk is terrible. These are terrible movies and they just get this pass. It's like, no, man,
this is what DC does. They did it better. They did it first. I'm sorry. I like brooding.
I cared more of this. When I watched this movie, I was less interested when they weren't showing
the characters as their real selves. I was less interested in the superhero parts.
I was so into Bruce Wayne and what was going on in their lives throughout this movie. When it went to
the cyborg arc, all of a sudden, now cyborg was this amazing character that I felt sorry for. He was
like this Frankenstein character. I thought that part was so much cooler than any of the fucking
superhero shit I saw cyborg do. I thought the emotional journey of the guy was what made it so
cool. That's me. That's what I like and I enjoyed this. Was cyborg completely cut out of Justice
League or just way minimized? He was in it. No, he was in a good amount in the Joss weed one, but
they just turned him into like, it was like, who cares? You're just like, oh, this guy's like half
robot now and he kind of doesn't even give a shit. Yeah. Look, and I started all these with the
look. These aren't my thing. These movies are my thing. But the positive, I will say, Zack Snyder
clearly has a lot of talent. The only movie that I have loved of his is his remake of Dawn of the
Dead, which I think is fucking incredible. But I do, that was a James Gunn script and I don't know
that he writes all these other ones. I think he at least has a hand in writing them. But
James Gunn wrote Dawn of the Dead. I didn't know that. Yeah, he wrote the remake. Oh, that's great.
There's just like this real thudding quality to it, like a glum morose deal. And while the
burdened Batman's and certainly the Nolan Batman's had that, it just felt more real to me,
more alive. Those are the ones I like that are basically those Batman's and I liked actually
all three Spider -Man's, which maybe puts me in suspect in some of your minds, but I thought three
was kind of stupid fun. But I like Rami or some director like that who's injecting it with a lot of
visual style, a lot of personality, a lot of I like color in my movies, frankly, and this was very
one note, but fun. The style of it, the man can, why, why this, why the slow motion, let's,
let's address that. Why loves to slow, I agree. Yeah, he does John Woo. He out does John Woo
with it. It's, yeah, it's insane. He's too much slow motion. Sure. What's her face? Amy Adams
walking down the street with two cups of coffee and slow motion. Yeah, it's too much slow motion.
I agree with that. In a four hour film, but I'll say this, I agree with that. The comic book
that made me fall in love with comic books as a kid was Batman, Death in the Family, where the Joker
murders Robin. I read that when I was, I had liked comic books before that, but I read that when I was
11 or 12 and that was what set me off and got me into comics. Zach Snyder gets DC like he put on
screen every DC graphic novel I ever read, and I liked it. I liked Swamp Thing because he was
tortured. I liked, I liked all that, man. I never was a huge Marvel guy because, and Stanley will say
it like he was like, we wanted our stuff to be big. And when a guy got punched, he was flailing back
through the window. You know, everything's exaggerated in Marvel and it's big, bright colors or whatever.
And some people, and it's much zany your plots, too. It's, you know, yeah, it's a guy controls the
weather with his mind and shit like that. Fine, it's fine. If you're into that, that's great. But I,
I just as a DC fan from a very young age, I felt like this guy captured exactly the mood of Kingdom
calm of death and the family of the killing joke. All the Alan Moore and Frank, what's his face? Frank,
not a son of a bitch. Guy wrote Dark Knight Returns. Frank Miller, Frank Miller, all the Frank Miller
stuff. It's like he just captured it. Like DC was never bright and bubbly. Like, you know, I think a
lot of people remember that Justice League cartoon from when we were kids. And it was a kid show and it
was, you know, it was, it was, it was a kid show. So, you know, I played like one where people think
of the Adam West Batman, which I love and don't realize that that was meant to be a sort of deconstruction
of this stuff. And it was meant to be sort of a borderline satire. And people look at that stuff and
they go, well, why isn't this fun? You know, it's like, you know, and that's not criticizing you. I'm
except the flash kind of is the flash is kind of a smart ass and whatever. But I mean, the flash
annoyed the hell out of me in this as he remembered him standing out and annoying me in the original
Justice League for sure. He had even more quips. But yeah, I don't like the way the Marvel movies are
quote fun either. I'm not having any fun watching them, right, bend over backwards to try to make
you laugh at some stupid joke. But like, and I can't even say I'd like something in between the two
polls. I just think this, you know, people have their blind spots and this is my genre. Sure, sure.
It's got to be right and weirdly dark man, which we talked about is right up my alley. I like them
sort of with that bigger over the top feel to them, I guess, especially in my villains.
Although when Lido when Lido showed up at the end of this in the third epilogue that the movie
a four hour movie has, you know, that scene I was like, are they just is I actually had to check
to make sure that they didn't just add deleted scenes to the end of the film. Like they were supposed
to still be a part of the movie was kind of nuts. But I get that he wanted to give the fans basically
every piece of film he shot. That was new. He went back and shot that. No, that's great. Which is why I don't
get and it was it was a scene to set up the idea of the nightmare world where Superman has been
corrupted and and reigns, which is what I guess Justice League 2 was going to be. Right. Which is a
cool idea. I'd I'd pay to see that the new Gotham Knights video game coming out is that is like
is Superman gone crazy and then the suicide or the Gotham Knights have to have to take down. No,
it's a suicide squad game. They have to take down Superman like corrupt super. That's a very
cool plot one. I would love to see it. But don't put it on the end of the movie as this big cliffhanger
where because for a guy like you. I and I thought of this. I was like, it's going to be confusing.
Like people that don't understand like didn't read up on like what his next two movies were supposed
to be all that shit. What the fuck is this? So and they just because it was a failure, we're just
never seeing this this Justice League world or team again. We're seeing the flash right in his
own movie. Yeah. And but who knows? You know Zack Snyder said that this Snyder cut didn't exist
and then it did. Now he's saying that he started out saying I have no interest in doing any more
DC stuff. I'm done. And then he said we're not going to do anymore. This is it. Now he's saying,
well, it's up to it's up to Warner Brothers. If they want to do it. You know what I mean? So like who
knows who's telling the truth about anything anymore? You know, but who knows? My point is
is that's a hell of a dice roll. And look, I respect it. I mean, George Lucas did it with with
Star Wars. But like that's a hell of a dice roll to put that big of a cliffhanger on the end of a
movie like this that was designed and rebooted to bring closure to fix what the first version of
created when you might never get it. Zack put it in there. You know, if this thing really
takes off, maybe they'll let you make Justice League too, you know. And I'm sure that's probably
what Warner Brothers was saying too. Let's see how it does. So you might as well do it. But yeah.
But overall, I completely get why somebody like you wouldn't like this movie. I don't disagree
with you. I get it. It's not for you. And I totally get why and I totally get why you didn't like
it. For me, it felt like a love letter to the fans and it felt like a guy saying, this is what you
deserved. You deserved a sequel to Man of Steel and to Batman versus Superman. And this is it.
And this is what I was trying to do. And this is why there were these open ended things in those two
movies. It was leading to this and to finally get to see that come to fruition was very cool for me.
I love that the man was given a chance. And I'm a huge sucker for any time a director puts out
their vision. Are they're giving a little extra money to or they get a blu -ray 20 years down the line.
I'm pro that anytime it happens, whether I like the end result or not, I just ordered the godfather
three. I'm going to give the new one a watch. Coppola puts out, you know, he did apocalypse now. He did
cotton club. He's rebooting all his old movies. I guess he's run out of ideas. But like I'm going to
watch the Rocky Ford director's cut that still has to do it. Oh yeah. Yeah. I'm always a fan of it.
I think it's great. This one was kind of cold. What I do like about it and about the DC as opposed
to Marvel is I like that there's a feeling of control and a mastery of tone throughout where they are
paying attention to a experience and how it feels as opposed to Marvel and certainly that other
justice league where it's just like people throw and like it's essentially multi -cam sitcoms
with superheroes and people go nuts for it, which is crazy to me. But yeah, just no caring about
character or tone or anything else. I do like that Snyder just makes it this miserable thing for
four hours. I just didn't enjoy watching it. You know, I that's all I can say. The scenes of
Amy Adams and Superman back home. I mean, that was rough stuff. And it took me back to seeing that
man is still in the theater and being like, who, boy, all that farm stuff and the Diane Lane stuff,
you know, it's rough. It's rough for me. I'm never going to like it. I do like the old Chris
Reeve joints one and two. I like a lot. But I don't know. I think I think people tend in this genre,
people like what they grew up with. Yeah, absolutely. That's why people are such diehard Marvel fans.
That's why I'm such a relentless DC fan. That's what you liked as a kid. And for some reason,
as an 11 or 12 year old boy, I liked a brooding miserable superhero. Right. Sure. So that's it. Yeah.
One hog got one hog down on the Snyder cut. Yes. That's our show folks. Jotaro's a comedy on
Instagram and Twitter. Jotaro's a comedian on Facebook. Listen to taste buds. Salvo kind of myself
to bait food every Monday morning. It drops at 11 a .m. Eastern time on the no pressure network YouTube
channel. Thank you for your support of this show. We appreciate you staying with us and we love you.
Very much. We do indeed. Thank you. As always to Emily for helping us out. Emily just moved.
So she said she apologizes for the lack of posts of late. But she's going to get back on it.
Did you leave Texas or she just moved in Texas? I don't know. And I don't think we should discuss.
You know, who knows? I want people to know. Maybe she's fleeing a gunman. We don't know.
These are trying times. I hope you're not fleeing it. What a terrible thing to say. She's not fleeing a
gunman. I know, but you know, I feel bad for even putting it out there. But yes, thank you to Emily
for all your work and just so you all know, there's more posts of coming. My new solo movie corner went
up this weekend. It goes into all kinds of shit that I've been watching. The next one will be a
chronological look through the filmography of Mike Nichols, much like my other Oliver Stone one.
So if you want to catch up, he's got a lot of classics graduate. If you're a George Siegel fan,
who's afraid of Virginia Woolf is a fucking classic by Mike Nichols. And I see. Yes, RIP Siegel, who is great always,
but I bet that Turner Classic movies in the coming weeks will be doing a tribute to George Siegel.
And I bet they will show where's Papa. Because I have gotten a lot of DMs and comments and things
like that, asking where I saw where's Papa. It was on Turner Classic movies and they like to do
tributes to actors. So if you're trying to track that one down, watch for it. Otherwise, you can buy
the DVD for 40 bucks or something. I'm the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram. We'll be back next time,
not sure yet what we're going to see. But one of them will be Kong versus Godzilla. Yeah. It's
cool. We'll probably do that for May. But yeah, but Godzilla Kong, whatever the fuck it's called.
And then yeah, something else cool. All right. Thanks to all of you for joining us on the Patreon
journey. We love you. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.