I'll see you at hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you at hell.
Folks, it's We'll See You At Hell.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
It's the Halloween season, and we're here to review some scary movies for you this month.
Today, no exception, Oddity.
The new smash, it seems to be a big smash hit, I guess.
I mean, who knows what that is anymore?
Everybody says it's a hit, and you just go, okay, I'll take your word for it.
I know it's doing well on Shudder.
I was surprised that it just came out, and every single person I know on Letterboxd has watched and reviewed it.
People seem to like it.
We'll get to it.
I've got a lot of scary stuff to talk about today.
What have you got?
Well, let's start with one that will be more of a conversation piece for you and I.
The Shocktober sale, I guess it's over now, but Scream Factory, as you've pointed out, they do a sale every other week at this point.
But the Shocktober sale, I felt, was very good because there was a lot of horror 4K, stuff that had never been on 4K, stuff that had never even gotten 4K scans or anything like that.
The latest iteration of a lot of these movies was the 1080p Blu -ray, but they were available now on 4K and they were on sale for just about half off.
So I got a ton of 4Ks for like 20 bucks and some good ones that are usually pretty pricey, man.
Did you indulge?
I didn't look.
I'm about to start work, which is usually the point where you're kind of stretched about as far as you can go because we keep having work delayed.
So I'm not really shopping.
I'm just kind of lying low.
But I have been going through my own 4K purchases, namely The Stepfather, which I just watched, which I love the way these old movies look.
The 80s horror.
Oh, yeah.
Just fantastic.
I'm a fan of the format.
But yeah, I have kind of stopped buying.
I also have run out of room.
You know, I'm at a place where I'm like putting large piles of movies into like cabinets in my kitchen.
And I'm just like, this is stupid.
Stop.
Yeah, that's crazy.
You can't do that.
You can't.
Yeah, I'm not.
And it's next stop hoarders.
You know, I had I'll tell you what I got here.
I got Halloween.
Yeah.
4K 20 bucks.
Life Force 4K 22 bucks.
Imagine how dark those boobs are going to be.
I love Life Force.
So I think that's going to look awesome in 4K.
I have Life Force 4K.
I haven't opened it.
Prince of Darkness was 19 bucks.
And I said, all right, everybody keeps telling me it's great.
It looks great.
I'm just going to grab it.
It's fine.
Piranha.
Yeah.
19 bucks.
Silver Bullet 22 bucks.
Tales from the Dark Side.
22 bucks.
Now it's telling me it charged me $44 for Night of the Demons.
It said it was $20.
That's wrong.
Something's not right there.
Shot Factory, you're about to receive a strongly worded email.
You go chat or you go email?
I go email.
Chat is worthless.
Some bot being like, does this answer your question?
No.
If I can make sure it's not one of those where it's just a robot constantly trying to confuse me
and I'm actually talking to a person, I think chat is where it's at because you don't have to talk to somebody.
Sure.
And they usually handle it pretty well.
I'm a big fan of phone call.
Sure.
Did you do Amazon Prime Day sales?
Well, hold on.
Let me finish my hall here.
It's gluttonous.
I'm sorry.
All right.
No, please.
I understand.
Dark Man.
I did not own Dark Man.
Love it.
I can't believe I didn't own it already.
I was like, I must have that.
I only have it on VHS.
Exorcist 3, 4K.
Very excited about that.
The Blob remake 4K.
I've been wanting to upgrade on this movie for years.
I only have it on DVD.
Yeah.
The Dead Zone 4K.
Beautiful.
See, I made all these purchases on the last sale.
I feel like a lot of them.
And finally, Halloween 3, Season of the Witch.
I felt like if I was going to own two Halloween movies on 4K, three and one.
No, I'm not saying I don't like the other Halloween movies, but I felt like three and one are the ones that would benefit most from the 4K treatment.
Sure.
I can see that.
Yeah.
So I almost bought two.
And then I was like, once you buy the first three, you're going to take the gum off of the hole in the dam.
And you're going to be like, well, now I have to get all of them.
Well, also, you know they're coming out with a Halloween 4K box set.
Probably next Halloween.
Yeah.
They've got us over a barrel.
The stupidest thing I've purchased in recent years was the first four Rocky movies.
A box set on 4K.
They had a box set of one through four.
And then I bought it going, Pat, you know, there's going to be a complete set that goes all the way through Balboa, maybe even through Creed.
What are you doing?
Yeah.
And sure enough, sure enough, even when you know what's going to happen, you fall for it.
I have the full Rocky Blu -ray.
And I think that's good enough for me with Rocky.
I think Blu -ray is fine.
I'm not mad at it, you know.
Horror, strangely, as you know, I was always a big proponent of like, I like to get horror on DVD because it looks grainier and whatever.
And some of it on DHS.
But I will say the 4K treatment to old horror, it's a very noticeable, enjoyable experience.
And I'd put it next to like, why I wouldn't want a Scorsese movie in 4K, you know, or something like that.
Fair enough.
I almost always prefer the format unless it is blowing up something that looks shitty, in which case it often looks a little worse, in my opinion.
Right.
And then sometimes these, let's say, Saving Silverman Through Stepbrothers era of comedies looks awful in 4K.
It looks like not how they're supposed to look.
They look too HD.
Are you telling me you bought Saving Silverman in 4K?
I do own Stepbrothers in 4K and I did not like the way it looked.
I thought it's like, you know, the rear projection like Hitchcock style when people are driving.
Yeah.
There's moments of that in Stepbrothers that look just as bad as like, you know, in North by Northwest or something, but only in 4K.
And then Saving Silverman, I imagine, will never be released in 4K.
Although you never know.
The things that get a release are sometimes pretty insane.
I, yeah, like with comedies, it's like I'll take Big Lebowski in 4K.
It's Coen Brothers, but like I don't need Kingpin in 4K.
Yeah, same.
Same.
It's not going to improve much.
I did not hit Prime Day.
Did you hit it up at all?
I guess not if you're not shopping, but did you?
I looked, you know, and by the way, I say I'm not shopping.
I would have shopped had there been worthy sales.
But Amazon, then they got outed for this the last time they had a sale.
They increase what the starting price was so that the sale price looks better, but it's all a lie.
Somebody who's on Amazon all the time, like myself, will go, wait a minute.
The ring's always been $21 .99 in 4K, but your average person's like, holy shit, it's 60 % off, but they're lying to you.
Well, yeah, there's tells on Amazon too.
If it doesn't have the sticker, like on a normal day, forget Prime Day, but just on a normal day on Amazon, they'll always do the price slash to make it look like you're getting a deal.
Yeah.
If it doesn't have a sticker next to it that says like limited sale or something like that or like today's deal or whatever, it's like, no, that's what it's always priced at.
Yes, exactly.
I also got, this isn't scary stuff, but it was a hell of a deal.
I was on Merch Bar.
Yeah.
I got all the David Lee Roth Van Halen records in a box set, all the vinyl, the first six.
Okay.
It was a hundred bucks.
Not bad.
That's a great deal.
I mean, I liked the records too.
I wanted them.
Not bad, yeah.
I didn't buy it just because it was a deal.
Yeah.
But I don't listen to Halen or I was certainly not Hagar, but they're just not for me.
I've been on a real 1984 kick.
I saw a clip of the George Orwell novel.
And I put the album on with it and it syncs up.
Like Dark Side of the Moon.
No, it's, I saw this clip on Instagram of David Lee Roth talking about the song Jump,
and it moved me so much that I pulled the album out and started listening to it.
And I was like, I want to get all the other Van Halen vinyls.
So I did.
There you go.
Are they all good?
Diver Down is terrible, but the other ones are, yeah, they're solid, man.
They've all got great moments, you know, it's, it's, they were legends for a reason.
Okay.
It's funny though.
They also had the Hagar box set of his albums and that was like 50 bucks.
It's like, yeah, who the fuck cares about this?
Comes with a free $40 Amazon gift card.
Yeah.
Sammy brings it to your house.
Got a margarita spilling all over himself in the, in the console of his car.
Trying to fit that margarita glass into the cup holder.
Yeah.
He's got the glass with the stem on it.
Hey, pal, I know you can't drive 55, but this is a neighborhood.
So if you could just cut that in half, that'd be great.
Yeah.
I, I wanted to do a quick update.
A lot of people were asking, I went out on a, I went out with the girl who was kitchen
table, non -monogamous and semi nested.
And unfortunately we had a really lovely time.
It was the best date I've been on in quite a while.
Of course, I knew that going in, that it would be that, you know, a situation, this unusual
would probably be great otherwise and forced me to make a difficult decision.
But she is engaged in a full relationship with a married man who lives across the country.
She's close with the wife.
They're all close.
That's the kitchen table aspect of it.
They all sit at the kitchen table together before making love.
She doesn't make love to the wife.
It's just him and her and her and him.
And I was like, okay, well, how often do you see him?
She lives in his house here in Los Angeles.
And once a month he comes to stay with her at the house during which time I would not
be able to see her.
That would be her time to bang Bruce or whatever his name is, Gary.
But wouldn't the kitchen table thing happen then?
Isn't that the point?
I asked like, am I going to be required to like zoom with this guy or meet him?
And she said, I obviously would never ask you to do anything you don't want to do.
She's like, if we become serious, he will want to meet you.
That doesn't mean you have to meet him.
I said, okay.
So I said, he just comes in once a month and that's your only contact.
And she's like, well, no, we text and talk and, you know, we're in a full relationship,
but he's also married and in that relationship.
And then once a month I'm with him.
And obviously that would not be a weekend where you and I would hang out.
But otherwise, you know, we just sort of pretend that's not happening.
You know, I promise him that I will be respectful and honest if I'm catching feelings for you.
We all get tested regularly and we just have a good time.
And I went home after the date.
We saw Drag Me to Hell, which was a blast.
Had a really fun dinner and drinks type situation.
And then I've just been thinking about it now for like a week.
Can I do this?
And the answer is probably no.
Will I do it?
The answer is probably yes.
All right.
I feel like maybe this will lead to I'm not going to become that guy.
As Jerry Seinfeld said, a low rise brief guy when they were talking about the orgy guys on Seinfeld.
That's never going to be me, but I think I can give this a college try.
Maybe I learned something about myself.
Now you texted me.
Yeah.
And you said, of course, the kitchen table girl's awesome.
By the way, can you hear that?
I have the window open.
Is it too loud?
No.
OK.
I didn't respond, not out of ignoring it.
But I was wondering and I wanted to give you some time.
Do you think that part of why you think she's awesome is the allure of the thing you can't really have?
Yeah, I have thought of that.
It's certainly not the allure of her being in a relationship because that's something that five years ago I would have been like, fuck off.
Like, of course I'm not doing that.
But things change.
Seasons change.
I'm like, is her being so unavailable the appeal?
Is there a reason that the people that I have liked at all since my marriage have been unavailable, either out of the city, not local or some weird thing?
Maybe.
But I don't think so.
I think it's that I rarely like people.
And unfortunately, I always like the people that have some complication, you know?
But this is a big complication.
I can't deny that.
She said, you can ask me as many questions as you want.
And we wound up having a lot to talk about in the first date, so it didn't come up.
Before we go out for a second date, I'm going to ask my questions, which are, what is your end game with this guy?
Like, are you waiting for his wife to die?
Are you planning on marrying this guy someday?
Because she says she doesn't think she is a non -monogamous person, which means she probably doesn't love the lifestyle.
I don't know.
Everybody's got something.
The older you get, they got more.
Yeah, that is true.
That is very true.
Would I rather a lady who bangs another guy one weekend out of the month,
or would I rather someone who can't figure out that you can't go to a 530 yoga class if you want to make a 630 concert?
It's a tough call.
Yeah, I know.
Well, you know, I wish you well with it.
Thank you.
You know, keep me posted.
Keep us all posted as this unfolds, you know.
Yeah, I appreciate that.
It's not easy out there, folks.
It's not easy out there.
One bad date, do you write anything or do you just ghost?
No, one bad date.
I'm not, I'm not.
No, it's just there's...
There's no reason to, in my opinion, to have a breakup.
To reject someone.
Yeah, after a bad date.
It's just like we had a bad date.
Now, it's maybe it's a little different if you sleep together and, you know, that's obviously a step.
Right.
So then maybe then you have to have a conversation.
But, you know, just a regular old bad date.
No, it's just, you know, we're done here.
Set up by a mutual friend.
Well, that's why so many people are against that is because then you have to, you have to deal with that.
The one time I've done that in the last two years or whatever, it was completely fine.
But I just, I think neither of us were feeling it.
And I didn't text.
And I was like, all right, no big deal.
And even my mutual friend was like, no big deal.
But then I ran into her and it was mucho acuerdo.
Yeah, I don't I don't know, man.
I don't know.
It's we don't really live in a society anymore.
So it's no, that's gone.
Real tough call.
That's gone.
I wow.
This was the other scary stuff I had was I don't know why I'm holding it up because nobody can see it.
But this book came out that I got a copy of the art of Rick Catazon and Anivision.
This Rick is the artist.
He's designed a lot of things.
But the most notable for me was he did a lot of designs for Creepshow.
Yeah, he did the drawings in the comic book sequences.
And he's got this book out now that that, you know, documents the work he's done.
It's it's I guess it's a soft cover, but I guess you'd call it a coffee table book.
It's not like a memoir or anything, but it's great.
It's great.
He actually did some of the design animation stuff for the TV show as well.
So it's nice that there is some connective tissue to the TV show, to the movies.
But it's a great book and I highly recommend it.
And his son is DJ Kaz, who's a rap producer who I'm friendly with.
And DJ Kaz does great music.
So they got a good family over there.
These Catazones.
Check out the book.
I'm not it was given to me by a friend, Nick, who works with my management team.
But I guess you just get it on his website or something.
I really should have looked that up.
But I bet if you Google Rick Catazone book, you're going to find how to buy it.
But it's it's worth grabbing.
If you like Creepshow or if you just like art.
OK, OK.
What's the price point?
I don't know, because it was a gift.
I'll just look it up.
I can't imagine it's more than 20 bucks or something.
Rick Catazone book. Let's see here.
No, I'm wrong.
It is on Amazon.
It's thirty nine fifty.
A little pricier, but it's I think it's one hundred eighty seven pages.
All right. But it's like a coffee table style book.
It's it's interesting.
And there's a lot of great artwork.
And there's like it shows a lot of the artwork through the different stages and stuff, the sketches and whatever.
It's pretty cool. And he's done a lot of cool stuff.
Very, very cool.
Anyway, check it out if you like that sort of thing.
And you can get it on Amazon or you can, I'm assuming, buy it from him directly somehow.
Yeah, here's his website.
Yeah, shop. Let's see if it's on here.
I'm sure it is.
Oh, look at this on his website.
If you go to it, you can actually buy cells.
Creep cell from Creep Show 2, 200 bucks.
That's pretty cool.
I would do that, right?
Theoretically, it's up to you, Joe.
Well, in lieu of having children or.
Yeah, in lieu of children.
Sure. Yeah.
You can get the option.
Autograph stills on his website.
I don't. Oh, yeah, there's the book.
The book is actually forty five on his website.
I hate so I'm not telling you to go to Amazon.
But anyway, support an artist if you if you can afford to spend the cash and you like that sort of thing.
It's a great way to support an artist, I'd say.
I would just like to shout out, you know, Joe and I always speculate pontificate on here about sort of the freefall of the movie business in particular.
And I read.
Two different kind of in -depth profiles this week of things going horrifically awry.
The first is just how bad this joker fully I'll do is doing fully a doing it is as bad as they say.
It's it's nearly unwatchable.
I had to walk out of it at about the two hour mark and just read how it ended.
I couldn't do it anymore.
Terrifier 3 had zero promotion budget.
They did not do any ads for Terrifier 3 and it made 18 million over the weekend.
It's incredible what those guys are doing.
It is.
Joker had one of the steepest drops in movie history, the steepest drop in D .C.
And it fell off.
They're calling it a freefall.
Eighty one percent.
In its second weekend, falling into not just second place, but third place after Wild Robot, an animated cartoon robot vehicle.
Obviously, the reason for that is the movie is is terrible.
The cast and director seem to acknowledge that it's terrible.
Everyone seems embarrassed.
They keep showing clips of them at the premiere while everybody's doing the 11 minute standing ovation.
And they had a lip reader where Joaquin Phoenix is saying to Lady Gaga over and over.
It's terrible.
It's fucking terrible.
There's not one good song in it.
It's just terrible.
You just keep saying it over and over and over.
She's going, no, be nice.
But it is.
It's really terrible.
The other sort of big and growing worse by the day story is Lionsgate.
Lionsgate for a very long time, one of our top second tier studios, like a new line.
Lionsgate is known now as being kind of the only home of comedy.
Seth Rogen's production company and all these big comedy people tend to have deals at Lionsgate because they still make it.
But here are their last six movies.
Borderlands, The Crow, which did come out.
It was released.
The Killers game.
I don't know what that is.
Going to look that up real quick.
I was just about to ask you what is that?
It is Dave Bautista.
So another new one from him.
Never Let Go.
What's that one, Joe?
Isn't that the Anne Hathaway?
No, it's Halle Berry in the Woods.
That's called Never Let Go?
It is.
Terrible title.
That got bad reviews.
The trailer looked all right.
It did look kind of cool.
Yeah, but I think it's just another Quiet Place derivative.
White Bird, which I did not know existed.
That's the Larry Bird story.
This is the one that's in the Wonder Universe.
The Owen Wilson Wonder Universe.
But it's a period piece.
So believe it or not, this didn't connect with viewers.
Wait, that's what White Bird is?
Yeah, it's literally promoted as being a Wonder story,
meaning it's not a sequel to Wonder, but in the Wonder family.
Now, Wonder, not a big hit that I even recall.
And then their sixth most recent film to be released, Megalopolis.
Now, yes, Joe.
Most of those, if you looked at that slate pre -release on paper,
you'd think we're going to have a pretty good year.
Yeah, you might.
Boy, oh boy, man.
That is a cursed studio.
Jesus Christ.
They have lost, over the course of a year,
in the ballpark of like a half a billion dollars.
Like they're just completely collapsing.
There's no way that they continue.
And they're laying off tons and tons of people.
And it's basically like, let me see what it said here.
Like the reason they gave people for laying them off is like,
it's just been an unprecedented disaster here at the studio, basically.
Like they're just being honest about it.
Oh yeah, so Lionsgate is offering employees voluntary severance pay,
meaning like, hey, I'm out.
Like catching out like at Blackjack.
Offering employees voluntary severance amid, quote,
disrupted business environment.
Never even heard these terms before.
So it says this has been in the works for a long time
and is not even related to the company's recent bum box office run.
Doubt that's true.
But yeah, Megalopolis is going to lose $200 million.
It's got a D plus cinema score.
Joker has a D. That's a different studio, of course.
But like we're in some big trouble.
And like for some reason they're not learning the lesson of
Terrifier while being a sequel
is just this tiny little thing with no promotion.
They're still making the big juggernaut movies.
My hope, and it could happen,
is that we see a gradual shift to like bringing back adult $40 million movies.
Yeah, I think it's barreling out of control at this point.
See, this is the problem.
We got five years until we're just left in ashes,
but I just mean it might lead to something good,
like how we got good movies in the seventies.
Once they conglomerized everything,
and once movie studios became like oil companies and banks,
where it's like there's going to be four,
and they're going to own everything,
and it's all connected now to not just the movies and the production studios themselves,
but it's being owned by a company that probably,
I am assuming, owns various products and services and whatever,
because they want to tie it all together under one roof and blah, blah, blah.
You know, now it becomes this investor mess of you've got a board of investors
and you've got all these people to answer to,
and none of them are going to understand go small to create more.
There's just too many hands in the pot at this point.
I just, yeah, I think, I mean, once you hear that HBO is potentially collapsing,
you're like, what the fuck have you guys done, man?
Like this, this was, it's just wild to me. It's wild to me.
There's so many ins and outs,
and I'm not well read enough on any of it at this point to speak on it,
but it's just a shame. It's just really, really a shame, you know?
I do. I do indeed.
We were going to do that Crow remake.
I go to three theaters out here by me that are all close to each other,
and I don't even know that any of them were showing the Crow.
It played for about a week, I think.
It must have pulled that hard and fast.
It made nine million dollars.
It looked ridiculous. It looked terrible.
Nine million. I mean, that's like an indie numbers, like a tiny indie.
It's terrible.
Now, where does something like Edgars, whatever his name is,
Nosferatu fall in this because that's not an A24.
It's clearly not a big studio flashy movie,
but it clearly cost a bit of money.
I mean, the thing looks fucking incredible,
and it's got a slate of massive talent, including Skarsgård.
So where does that fall in all of this,
meaning there are clearly still outlets that are making things of quality
that have money to spend also?
Yeah, well, I think you're winding up more often than not.
The smaller A24 neon oscilloscope type movies are the breakouts.
Their bigger ones tend to not be the successes, like The Green Knight.
That cost a bunch of money but did not make a bunch of money,
and I thought that while looking cool was kind of dumb.
So I don't know.
I think Nosferatu probably costs somewhere in the 60 mil range is my guess.
My guess is it'll make about a hundred, but I don't know.
I don't know.
I mean, I do think that quality is actually making money these days in a good way.
They've got all the big shit that's making stuff,
but people are still going out to see a small, well -reviewed thing,
which is encouraging.
Have you seen the trailer for this Billy Crystal horror show?
It's horror?
Oh, that's a mistake.
I mean, they never even had him do horror in his prime.
Well, it was beneath him in his prime.
Now horror is sort of in its own way prestigious.
And look, he's a good serious actor.
I'm not saying I wouldn't buy him in it.
The trailer, it looks somewhat intriguing,
but it's just one of these, I'm a guy, my wife's dead.
A weird mystery starts to unfold around me.
I'm exploring it and it starts to become obvious.
You killed your wife, didn't you?
Uh -huh.
And they tell you, I mean, they don't say it in the trailer.
They hint at it strongly, but I'm just kind of like, that's a bummer.
This actually looks quality.
It looks like it might be well done.
I'd like to see Billy Crystal in a dark role.
That's interesting.
But the premise alone, it's just not intriguing, guys.
It's like, you know, what lies beneath and all these other,
it's been done so many times.
The guy, his wife is dead.
How did she die?
A weird supernaturally mystery starts to occur.
He's exploring it.
And as he does, we will find out he's not as,
who he portrays himself to be or whatever.
It's just not interesting.
Yeah.
Speaking of, by the way, here's a new psycho.
Speaking of not interesting, uh, uh,
Gil Keenan just said in an interview regarding Ghostbusters.
We are definitely continuing the conversation of telling big
Ghostbuster stories on the big screen.
The answer is yes.
Jason Reitman and I,
we take responsibility and the joy of being the keepers of the flame of
Ghostbusters very seriously.
We definitely are continuing the conversation of telling big Ghostbusters
stories on the big screen and stay tuned.
There will be more.
There will be more about that later.
So even after the disastrous frozen empire,
which I guess, did it make money?
It must have if they're still going.
Um, they're going to keep telling Ghostbusters stories.
Um, I just don't know how this stuff gets so fucked up.
This Gil Keenan, he did Monster House.
Then 10 years later, he did the poltergeist remake.
Like that.
What a weird career.
The animated Monster House.
10 years later, poltergeist.
Then he does Ghostbusters frozen empire.
And he's, he also, I guess he's Reitman's right hand man now.
He did Saturday night, which I just saw,
which should take us to that movie corner while we're, while we're here.
Tell me how it was.
I'm curious.
Let's kick that off.
So Saturday night is like a lot of movies these days getting terrible reviews,
but as also for my Oscar consideration, um,
they're having to push bad movies for the Oscars now because we don't have
enough good ones.
They're literally pushing Hugh Jackman or a Deadpool versus Wolverine as best
supporting actor.
Jesus Christ.
And in addition, there's like 12 other nominations, like, you know,
best original screenplay stuff like that.
But, um, Saturday night I feel is getting a really weird bum rap.
I think I liked it way more than most because I'm a huge comedy nerd,
a huge Saturday night live nerd.
I actually sat down and watched all those box sets of the first five seasons
of SNL,
which were often brutally unfunny after 50 years,
you know, like some of that stuff holds up, but a lot does not.
Um, and the movie, you know,
the audience was full of like really young people there to see, you know,
the Rachel Sinatra of the world and all the kind of hot young talent that's in
it.
But I would imagine they would come away from this movie going,
why the fuck did people think this show was so great?
It's like on studio 60 Aaron Sorkin show about like the workings of an SNL
type show.
The material we're seeing presented is so unfunny that with everybody
running around being so intense and like, uh,
driven and screaming at each other about it comes off as kind of ludicrous
because then when we see the sketches, they blow like the movie ends with the
first sketch of the first SNL, which is John Belushi going,
I want to feed your fingertips to the Wolverines.
Yeah.
You know, he's repeating that it's a bad sketch. It was bad then it's bad now.
Well, and let me interject and I'm going to just say this.
I don't care who gets mad because somebody always gets mad when I say it.
There has never been a funny John Belushi sketch.
John Belushi was fun down this road.
I mean, I, I hear you.
I, I don't, I disagree to some extent,
but I also think he's the most overrated of all those guys because he died.
Yeah. It's, it's, it's, it's like everybody loved the guy.
He was talented.
Yeah.
He's great in blues, brother. He's great in movies.
Like I'm like, yeah, okay. I see it.
Yeah.
Obviously, but like this one, this, this reverence for him on SNL,
it's like, guys, everybody was coked and weeded out of their fucking minds in
the seventies and you saw a guy that was equally as coked and whatever on live
television being weird and crazy.
And it's like, okay, fine.
Like, but my God, man, like the cheeseburger thing, the samurai.
I'm like, none of this is funny.
I hear you.
Because it's the 50th anniversary,
they keep asking people and doing like super cuts of everybody listing off
their favorite SNL sketches of all time.
And it's not just my age.
I mean, I really have seen all this material, you know,
from the beginning to the right.
I watched Saturday night's brand new one.
I still watch the show.
Like there's, there's stuff that people have reverence for that just,
I don't get, like when somebody's like, oh, for me, it's gotta be,
I think Mike Birbiglia or somebody was like, it's gotta be samurai
delicatessen.
Really?
Oh, come on.
You know, and I don't get anyone, even adults,
like even my dad who grew up with Belushi,
like my dad kind of was Belushi in the seventies, you know,
like this insane party animal.
And when Farley came on the scene,
my dad immediately switched allegiances.
Like Farley is the funnier version unquestionably.
Yeah.
But anyway, Saturday night,
what's good about it is if you like, like I love the movie Noises Off.
I was in that play in high school and doors slamming and find out like behind
the scenes of something.
That's the fun of this.
Everything's paced, you know,
as fast as it can possibly go.
Everybody's running around like crazy.
It's interesting how young everyone is,
like Lorne Michaels just looks like a kid.
And that's kind of cool and fun.
A lot of the people impersonating Chevy Chase, Dan Aykroyd,
et cetera,
don't really look like them,
but they kind of get the vibe.
A lot of the people doing impressions and trying to get like the feeling of
Gilda Radner do a good job,
but you never,
they smartly aren't doing bad impressions of the people.
Somebody in this movie is doing a Billy Crystal,
who I guess was waiting in the wings to do his standup.
That's an amazing impression of Billy Crystal.
It's like everyone in the audience was like, Ooh, you know, like it's a,
it's a really good impression.
And then the best, maybe just cause I, I, you know,
a little bit of a name drop, I worked with them for six years,
Garrett Morris,
but Lamorne Morris from The New Girl is doing an astonishing impression of
Garrett Morris.
And to me,
there's enough fun and like good stuff in the movie to make it worth your while.
It's not funny.
It's not great.
But if you care at all about SNL and the history of comedy,
I thought it was really well done.
I liked it.
I just looked up the reviews.
It's getting well reviewed.
It's got an 80 % on rotten tea,
86 % from the audience.
So I don't know if it's making any money.
It might just be people on my letterbox,
which it would be a lot of comedy friends who are snobs.
So that explains it.
I'm going to dedicate my entire movie corner.
Yeah.
To speaking of bad comedy,
Ellen DeGeneres.
For your approval,
I believe it's called.
Man, I guess so.
Folks,
I just want to talk about this before it's completely outdated to talk about.
If you want to see a sociopath in full form,
watch this fucking special.
This thing is a disgrace.
It's a disgrace.
She opens with a self -praising sequence of all of her triumphs.
She then walks on stage to a crowd that I believe was excited to see her
and was enthusiastic.
But I don't have any doubts in my mind that many moments in this were sweetened.
I think Vulture documented that it had 70 applause breaks or something like that.
Relentless.
I guarantee some of it was sweetened,
but also this special was written, designed.
And there are comedians who do this,
Bill Maher being a chief one of them,
stuff written just to get applause,
delivered in a way that almost holds a gun to your head
and makes you applaud.
It's what Tina Fey calls claptor,
which is like she always tries to avoid it.
It's gross.
And that's the whole special.
And when it's not that,
it's her doing the most benign bits,
and some of them are kind of funny,
and these things are getting applause breaks.
I snapped at an audience the other night.
I did a joke about ingredients in the food you buy,
and one of the ingredients I saw in tortilla chips was may contain coconut.
It's just a dumb little joke about how do you not know if there's coconut in there.
And it did okay.
And I was like, you know, guys,
if I was fucking Ellen DeGeneres,
I would have gotten a goddamn arena applause break
because that's how low the bar is set.
You know, she's doing parallel parking stuff.
It's cute, it's humorous,
but people are going bat shit, man.
Like it's a Malcolm X rally or something.
Like they're going nuts.
It's wild.
But my biggest grievance with the special
is not the quality of the jokes or anything like that.
It's that she never once owns any of it.
She never says, hey, guys, look, having a TV show,
I know it looks like a lot of fun and games.
I know I'm blessed to have had one.
I know I'm blessed for the success and the money and everything.
But hey, it's really hard and it's really stressful.
And I probably didn't act at my best.
That's all she had to fucking say.
And she doesn't even say that.
And a quick pause.
There's not a single person in the home or theater audience
who would have a problem with that.
No.
We all know, Ellen, that you didn't like
aggressively finger an intern in the copy room.
We know you're not some monster in that way.
People can forgive almost anything up to sexual assault and murder.
And they will forgive it if they like you
and if you've built up a whole career of goodwill for people.
She still has her fans.
My fucking stepdad watched her every single day until she went off the air.
But it's like she won't do that.
She won't be vulnerable for one second.
And in fact, her whole tone is angry at us forever questioning her.
She's mad at those who called her out instead of being apologetic.
It really is nuts.
It's nuts.
And the last line of the special is if I have a choice
between being remembered for being mean or remembered for being kind,
I choose to remember, be remembered for being kind.
She's literally saying, I am telling you how I will be remembered.
I am deciding it, not you.
It's just the whole thing.
It's psychotic.
And then, by the way, it's also peppered with stories from her life
that involve like, I was invited to Usher's house for dinner and shit like that.
And you're like, Ellen, for the love of God, talk to us like a human being.
Just because before you talk about going to Usher's house, you do a story about...
And by the way, the Usher story is literally like her talking about,
if I'm in my sweats, I'm not going.
I got invited to Usher's house and I didn't go because I was in my sweats.
That doesn't make you normal, Ellen.
It doesn't make you normal.
If you think we're like, that's me when Carol invites me over on a Saturday night
and I'm in my sweat.
No.
We already are a million miles away from you when you talk about your Usher parties.
You know what parties you're not talking about, Ellen?
The P. Diddy parties that you went to every single year.
Did she?
He's been on her show a million times.
And he talks about the parties.
He talks about weird shit on her show all the time.
Well, what she's really saying when she says because I was in my sweats
and I didn't take the fabulous invitation to the big celebrity's house is,
what she's really saying is, hey everybody,
think about your piece of shit life and the things you pass up.
Yeah.
Now listen to what I pass up.
Can you believe it?
That's how much better I am than you that I pass up this.
Yeah.
And in your little shit life, it would be equated to that.
So you can just imagine the sacrifice I'm making if you think you're making a sacrifice
by or being selfish or whatever.
It's just fucking gross.
I'm not going to say it's without laughs.
I did laugh a couple of times.
But I have just never seen psychosis on ice like this.
My God almighty.
Like what a spectacle.
It's worth watching just for the spectacle.
But the reason I say it was sweetened, by the way,
is there are moments where there's huge applause breaks happening
and it cuts to a fairly wide shot of the audience from behind
so you can still see her on stage and you can see nobody is moving or clapping.
Yeah.
It's odd, man.
It's really fucking odd.
When they put the clips on online and people are like,
I can't believe I'm saying this, but this is a real clip.
And you'll see the audience applauding from like 20 different camera angles.
It goes on for a full minute.
To be sitting in the editing bay and leave something like that in,
even if it is real, is a form of psychosis.
To give you an example, when we did the Living Biblically pilot,
it went really well, especially considering the ultimate fate of the show.
But I told Andy Ackerman, the director, the Seinfeld director,
I was like right before the big scene with Joe where he gets hit in the head with the rock,
I was like, I got to tell you, I'm terrified because if that moment doesn't work,
we're fucked.
And Andy's like, Pat, the moment's going to work.
And we're like, I don't know, I don't know.
And I was really nervous, stressed out.
When they throw the rock and hit Joe in the head, the audience applauded,
laughed, clapped, lots of noise.
It went on for about a minute.
It was exhilarating.
It was one of the best moments of my professional life.
It kept going and going.
I knew it worked.
When you sit in the editing room and you watch that moment,
I included maybe three seconds of that reaction.
Anything more than that, anyone watching the show is like,
what the fuck am I watching here?
You want to include it to say, look at how well this moment did.
But at the same time, it's the definition of having no awareness.
It just makes her look nuts.
And when you're making some lame ass parallel parking joke
and then cutting to people spitting out their coke,
I mean, come on now.
We didn't buy this back in the America's Funniest Home Video days.
She is also, I've known many people who have worked for her creatively
in administrative positions.
At least six people who worked in a major capacity on her show.
She and a nice person, to put it very mildly.
And the final thing I'll say, and then you can hit your next one,
is for her to spin her mistakes at the end of this special,
for her to spin these mistakes she's made and mistreatment of people
into it's because I'm a strong woman.
Fuck you, Ellen. Fuck you.
To make it about feminism is disgusting, yeah.
That is a disservice to the cause.
It's a disservice to women that do have to fight and push and whatever
that are up against it and have to show strength and resolve
in terrible moments and terrible situations and unfair and sexist environments.
For her to spin it like that is so gross.
It really, really sickened me.
And, you know, take care, Ellen.
Boo hoo.
By the way, I got kicked out of showbiz.
No, you didn't. You lost your TV show.
Any one of a thousand movie producers and directors would cast you in something.
Anyone else get kicked out of show business?
You're doing a stand -up special you got paid $10 million for.
Yeah.
For an hour of content. What are you talking about?
And then cancel your own tour dates.
You weren't kicked out of anything. Stop it.
Brings her wife out at the end as if to say, like,
somebody loves me, somebody attractive loves me.
What do you think about that? It was so bad.
And by the way, which she says this about three times over the course of the special.
Yeah, I mean, who would have ever dreamed that somebody could be mean in Hollywood, right?
There's really, there's nothing different between that and saying,
oh, yeah, nobody ever assaulted an actress on the casting couch in Hollywood before, right?
Like if that was Harvey Weinstein's defense.
Yeah, it has happened.
It was his defense. He said, I came up at a different time.
That's what he said. It was his defense. Yeah.
But like you're no different, Ellen, you know, like you can't just say,
hey, it's happened a lot. So that's why it's okay.
No, a good person would say this shouldn't continue happening.
I'm making $300 million a year.
So maybe I don't have to be a giant C word to everybody in my path.
Imagine the love she would have gotten if she just took a moment in the middle.
You can wash away an entire, that's what I thought she was doing.
That's what we all thought she was doing.
An apology.
I'm really sorry. I'm sorry.
There's no excuse. Boom. End on a laugh. End on a lovely, whatever. Anyway.
I'll do one more. Joe's got a heart out here. Will and Harper, new to Netflix.
This movie is a fucking delight.
I urge all of you with parents who are kind of stuck in the mud on these issues,
trans issues, gay issues, whatever.
I'd say 50 to 75 % of your average American parents are very anti -trans.
Consider it a joke. Don't want to talk about it.
Even quote good parents, parents who see the right way on a lot of issues.
You press them on trans issues.
They say some generally pretty horrific things.
In my experience, now I am from Missouri.
I'm not just talking about my parents. I'm talking about everybody.
This is one, if your parents will watch it, that can change their life
and change the way they're thinking about things.
It's that effective.
It's Will Ferrell, who everyone loves, who learns that his very close friend,
I'm dead naming, which is a mistake, Andrew Steele, but that was his name when I knew him.
I worked at Saturday Night Live and he was one of the head writers there, Andrew Steele.
He wrote a letter to Will Ferrell saying that I think I'm a woman.
I'm going to start living my life as a trans woman.
Will Ferrell picks up a camera crew.
They go on a cross -country trip together and Will's learning about his new friend.
The friend's name is now Harper Steele.
These guys have known each other forever.
Their whole comedy career has been together,
but they kind of have to learn to now be something different.
Already I'm tripping up.
I said, these guys, you know what I mean, folks.
Harper and Will have to go across the country together.
What's beautiful about the movie is A, that Will Ferrell is super accepting of him,
as you might expect, but they also include many moments where Will Ferrell is stumbling over
how to use the pronouns, how to say things, how to ask questions.
He leaves it all in and at this moment in time, it's a risk.
It just is, but he leaves it in there.
He leaves in a moment where they go to this dinner in a really kind of dodgy part of town,
like I don't know if it's the Midwest or what, but they go to this steakhouse
and Will Ferrell dresses up like Sherlock Holmes with the big magnifying glass
and he thinks he's going to be hilarious to everybody,
but everyone is hyper critical and taking pictures
and saying, get the fuck out of here, to his trans friend.
And Will Ferrell's like, even a giant movie star dressed in a funny costume
being in this small town, because I'm with a trans person, they hate me now.
You can see it rattle him in real time because Will Ferrell's a good person.
I don't think he expected when he went out there how awful people were going to be,
even with Will Ferrell there.
So that's sort of the underlying power of the movie is you realize
how much more difficult this trip would have been for Harper
without a giant celebrity on his side, but on her side.
Thank you, Jim. I absolutely loved the movie, the message of the movie.
I have heard some people saying like, well, this is just a puff piece for Will Ferrell.
Fuck off.
Like, you know what else he could have done with his time?
Made $20 million doing some fucking Santa Claus gets kidnapped movie.
He took his time to do this.
And this movie I think actually has the power to change people's hearts.
If I were to, my dad went and saw this at the theater
and he's talking a whole new thing about trans people.
You know, he's like, you know, it really made me realize
how stupid I've been on this issue and blah, blah, blah.
And I think what people don't realize is that doing a fucked up R rated,
you know, made by trans people movie is a great thing, a wonderful thing.
But people's parents are never going to watch that.
You're in an echo chamber to some degree.
I think this is the kind of movie that can actually affect change
because older people will actually watch it.
And it's really well done.
And it's funny, as you can imagine.
I mean, Ferrell's great.
There's great cameos.
Will Forte, Molly Shannon, et cetera, et cetera.
Tina Fey, Tim Meadows.
They meet up with a lot of old SNL people.
Highly recommend.
All right, I'll check it out.
On to the movie of the day, Oddity.
It's not a Shudder original, I don't think, but it's being showcased.
A film that they picked up, yeah.
And you can tell because it looks like it cost a little bit of money.
Yes.
It stars nobody I've ever seen before, but they're all very good in it.
The basic plot of the movie is a husband and wife have purchased this big,
giant castle -esque house on the countryside of Ireland, I guess.
The opening of the movie, it's one of the best openings I've ever seen.
The woman is alone in the house.
It's empty because the husband is working and he's always working nights.
He's a doctor in a psychiatric ward.
A man comes to her door.
The man looks suspicious and he says, you need to get out of the house right now.
Somebody walked in when you just went outside to your car and you need to let me in to help you.
It obviously seems like a guy that's up to something.
She doesn't trust it.
But the more he talks, the more she starts to believe him.
And it hits the title sequence from there.
You don't know what her decision was.
Did she let him in? Did she not?
It's a very scary scene.
And from there, you find out that the woman was killed,
that the man who came to her door was accused of the murder.
And now that man has been murdered at the hospital.
And it's sort of a whodunit.
Her twin sister, who also claims to be psychic and who believes in ghosts and whatnot, comes to the house.
The husband is still living in this house.
He does not want her there.
But she shows up with this wooden man that her mother carved that contains elements of her and her sister inside of its head,
meaning like a lock of one of their hair, a vial of one of their blood, blah, blah, blah.
And he's there with his new girlfriend.
He goes to work.
The girlfriend does not want the sister there.
And I know this sounds crazy, like I'm not explaining it very well.
But basically, she takes the wooden man and sits at the kitchen table
and then proceeds to sort of psychically solve the murder of her sister.
And things unfold from there.
As you can imagine, spoiler, spoiler, spoiler alert.
It turns out to not be the guy that came to her door.
It was somebody else.
But why did this other person kill her sister?
Is the husband guilty? Is he not?
It goes on and on.
It's a short film. It's about 138 minutes.
It is genuinely spooky.
It relies a little too heavily on jump scares.
But I gotta say, the jump scares are effective.
It got me a couple times.
It's moody.
It's well acted.
The woman who plays the wife also plays the sister.
They're twins.
And she is great because I didn't even realize it was the same actress until, like, until she said we're twins.
And I was like, oh my God, that's the same woman.
I didn't even realize that. So she's really good.
I didn't realize it until right now.
And in fact, I was like, because the opening scene is so good and so effective,
I was like, man, it's crazy that they just got this amazing actress to do the one scene.
She's gone. I didn't even notice that.
That's a lot of some good hair work there, too.
Yeah. So I don't know that I need to tell you what happens in the end.
I've spoiled a couple things already.
I think it's certainly the kind of movie you should just kind of watch and take in from a review standpoint.
I'll focus personally a little more on just the film aesthetically and constructively and whatever the construction of.
It's well put together. It's very well directed.
It's very well acted.
It's beautifully shot.
And for a 90 minute kind of spooky murder mystery that does ultimately contain some fun supernatural elements,
I thought it worked. I thought it worked.
Is it something that I would be dying to tell somebody else they have to see?
Not necessarily, but it's certainly something I'd recommend if somebody said, hey, I'm looking for something to watch.
I'd say this is without doubt worth a watch.
Yeah, totally agree. It's a very solid ghost story.
It's Irish, which it kind of has that feel where it's a little nasty.
There's a little revenge quality to it.
What's weird is there is one kind of really gory moment.
Like it's just, well, it's just a giant basically head explosion.
You see the aftermath of it and it's super violent.
But beyond that, there's not a great deal of violence.
It's kind of just creepy moments, but not really of the jump scare variety.
It's a classy ghost story where like everything adds up.
Everything makes sense as long as you're willing to accept clairvoyance and et cetera.
It's got kind of weird ties to long legs because she does arrive with a weird wooden mannequin in a trunk.
And it's not as fun as long legs by any means.
It's much more of a controlled, composed, kind of classy, old fashioned ghost story.
But it really works. I thought it was suspenseful and I agree with everything Joe's saying.
I thought it looked awesome.
Very first like establishing shot of Cork there in Ireland.
I was like, okay, this is not a Shudder original.
It looks like they put some time and effort and work into it.
I really enjoyed the movie.
My favorite little detail reveal, and this is a spoiler again.
When they find the guy that you think killed the wife dead at the hospital and his head has been smashed into pieces, it's pretty gross.
You assume that the man that's revealed to have ultimately murdered the wife is the person that killed this patient.
But it's not. The blind sister who is solving the mystery psychically or whatever, she says at one point, she goes,
I pulled him from his bed and killed him.
And this is right after she realizes he didn't kill the sister.
And she goes, I pulled him from his bed and killed him.
And she goes, I'm going to pay for that.
And I was like, that's a great fucking detail that you see that this virtuous person who's trying to solve the crime is actually capable of horrific things and did kill somebody out of revenge.
But she killed the wrong person.
And she realizes like, I'm going to pay for that.
And then shortly after that, spoiler, she dies a horrific death.
So everybody kind of weirdly gets theirs.
The only person that doesn't have any blood on their hands is the wife at the beginning who's murdered.
But it's a fun movie. It's a fun movie.
I would say, yeah, definitely in the long legs family.
I didn't like long legs. I did like this.
Again, very spooky, very moody.
There are one too many jump scares, but they are at least effective jump scares.
So I can forgive it for that.
Yeah, I mean, the white man figure, you know, is super effective.
It's not like an old lady popping out and being like, I've got the candle you wanted.
And they scream and jump or whatever.
There's a craft to the to the jump scares.
I guess that's what I'm saying.
They didn't feel like, yeah, they didn't feel as shitty as your average black phone style jump scare.
Yeah, the director, let's just before we hold on oddity.
I think we did his other movie or at least I watched it.
It's called what is it called?
It's with the rabbit.
Oh, wow, this guy doesn't even have a Wikipedia page yet.
Yeah, Damian McCarthy.
What was his other picture, Joe? It was on Shutter.
It was called, there was a rabbit.
Caveat.
Caveat?
Did I watch it?
Maybe I didn't watch Caveat.
I don't think I saw that.
I think I was just told it was cool and I didn't see it.
Yeah, I thought this was well done and worth a watch.
I kind of base everything, not everything, but I base a lot ultimately now on would I buy it, would I not.
I don't know that I would buy this movie, but if I was gifted it, I wouldn't be mad at it.
Yeah, I thought the final reveal was fun and yeah, it's good.
And again, now here Box Office just made 1 .4 million.
Okay.
And the budget of this thing, this is a million dollar movie.
I mean, this is, you know.
It looks a lot better than that for sure.
But, you know, and a great payoff ultimately with The Wooden Man, which that I won't spoil, but check it out.
It's worth seeing and it's definitely a nice addition to Shutter.
Oddity, Hogs are Up, I'd say.
Hogs are Up.
An enjoyable film.
We'll be back, two more episodes this month, potentially The Substance, which I still need to see.
And then, I don't know, maybe we'll do a classic for actual Halloween, you know.
But we'll figure it out, people.
We'll keep the hits coming, don't you worry.
Until then, I, again, I've been pushing this date, but I will be in Summerville, Massachusetts, December 7th.
And I think I can safely announce this now.
Salsa Windfall will be playing on the show.
It's not just me.
I'm going to do stand -up, my new hour or whatever it is.
And then Salsa Windfall is going to do a full set.
So this is a big holiday special show for me.
I wanted to do something special right before Christmas.
And this is it.
I'm very excited about it.
We'll be in Summerville, December 7th, having a good time at the Crystal Ballroom.
And then past that, tons and tons and tons of new dates for January 2025.
Please, please come on out.
All tickets available at joderosa .com.
As always, if you're in New York City, pop by Joey Roses.
Have a sandwich, have a drink.
We're there.
We're having fun.
And Tires Season 2, which I've been working on, is coming.
So it's been pretty great.
So that's it for me, folks.
Folks, I'm at ThePatrickWalsh on Instagram.
We are at See You in Hellpod on Instagram.
Thank you for listening to us.
Thank you for your patronage and patronage.
We will see you next time, and we will see you in hell.