I'll see you on the train.
Folks, welcome to we'll see you and how it is the month of November.
We're getting up to Thanksgiving and we're thankful to be here with you and thankful to be
talking about a little movie called The Substance Today.
And to the gentleman in the comments, who comments every couple of days, are you guys ever
going to do the substance?
Yeah.
We're doing it now.
What's it put out for three weeks?
That's what I'm saying.
It's like giving you a goddamn break.
Yes, we're doing The Substance, the new French slash American body horror, Cronen
Berghian, Dupalmian, Kubrickian, yes, aught film, very Cronen Berghian in the visual
sense, not in the tonal sense.
But now I watch this or I got to watch this, this is I guess maybe a scary stuff.
I watched this at home last night.
Amazon Prime in the app, there's now this new extension you can add called MUBI.
And I've never seen it, but I did the seven day trial last night, got to watch the substance
for free with the seven day trial.
But what MUBI is, it's movies you can watch, it sort of cherry picks from all the other
services to provide you a selection of movies.
But then you also get a free movie ticket every week.
So you can pick a theater of your choosing.
This is new, you usually have to go to one place with their subscription or whatever.
But you can pick the theater, you can go see a movie.
And it's on sale right now for 10, 99 a month, it's usually like 25 bucks a month.
So I might actually keep it for a little while and see if it's worth it.
I mean, I figure if I see one movie a month with it at 11 bucks, I think there are some
restrictions like you have to see one of three MUBI releases or something like that.
I don't think it's go see whatever you want.
Okay.
Yeah, MUBI, their gimmick was always a movie a day, each day, it's like the new featured
movie gets added.
And I've done it using different email addresses, gotten that free trial 30, 40 times in my
life.
And I saw the substance, the actual I didn't have to do it.
But MUBI is usually pretty good.
The only problem is they only get like six movies a year and they get the stuff you can't
really find.
The rest you can find on criteria or find elsewhere and you're paying kind of a stiff
premium, but they're what they're smart.
They get like one big coveted exclusive title every quarter or so this quarter.
It's the substance.
And it's smarter by the way to get MUBI and remember to cancel it than it is to buy the
movie for 1999.
Also, stiff premium, now that you say that, that's the name of the porno script you've been
writing.
Yes.
Correct.
Yeah.
You got to pay a pretty stiff premium around here.
That premium do the time.
And then after each session, the woman looks at the camera and goes, that premium is stiff.
It was stiff.
You took care of that, Tuts.
Um, I throw a towel, I had her an exit completely nude out, out double saloon doors.
I, uh, I haven't eaten yet today.
It's for the double saloon doors is a nice touch.
Yeah.
And I would like it close on my bare ass to end the movie.
I'd like it says the end in cursive, looney tunes, cursive.
I would also like it if when you went out of the doors, it made the BingBong noise like
a store makes when you walk in ding, ding, ding, yeah, yeah, that would be a good, uh, would
have been a good joke for once upon a time in the west or, uh, what was that called?
Seth McFarland's failed western spoof, six million ways to die in the West, a million ways
to die in the West.
Yeah.
Once once upon a time in the West is a great movie.
I don't know that move.
I mean, I've heard of it.
I've never seen it.
Oh, it's really good.
It's really good.
I mean, uh, not, not, not Seth McFarland's, but that's not good.
At once upon a time phrasing, that is your go to, if you don't have a title for your
movie.
Yeah.
I'm shocked that Tarantino, which many think his best film, and I can't argue that if that's
what you think, but I'm shocked he went with it with once upon a, it actually makes sense
for his movie and it makes sense for what, once upon a time in America, uh, I think some
other ones, you know, the, the third installment of the Desperado series, I was like, come
on guys.
Well, yeah.
And his, that's one of his favorite movies, once upon a time in the West.
So I'm sure it's like, I had to wait to use that title until I was sure.
All right.
Like, I had nailed it.
Right?
Um, could have called Pulp Fiction once upon a time in LA would have been a good title.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Um, uh, Joe, how was your Halloween?
Halloween.
I did a nine movie marathon here on the podcast, um, but I didn't do anything, um, outside
of the home for Halloween.
Do you mean you watched live on recording yourself watching nine movies?
I did.
I did it the Saturday before Halloween, but I woke up, had coffee watched eight movies.
Now I'm sorry, nine movies, but they were all around 90 minutes.
But you recorded the whole thing, like you didn't just do reviews of the nine movies.
I'm asking, well, I only recorded myself doing, okay, now I've picked this movie and
I'm going to watch it.
Then I would go, all right, I'm back and here's my review.
But around 12 hours into this, I was like, I didn't even need to watch all these movies.
This could have just been a normal solo movie corner and I pretended to pause and watch a
movie.
And, uh, for those of you at home, this is how little I know what Pat's doing.
This is like when they come to you and they go, your accountants have stolen all your
money.
He could be doing anything on this movie corner.
I have no idea.
I see, I would listen to yours for fear that it was going to be some sort of eight speech
with my name on it in the hashtags, um, the, do anything for Halloween.
My last Halloween was spent with you and, and cue from the, the jokers thought him and
I would become dear friends.
It didn't, didn't happen, but, um, that's okay.
I never see him or talk to him or was friends with him prior.
So it makes sense.
It could happen.
Um, no, I didn't do much.
I, I, I was in Austin because, because my friend, uh, tone bell got married, uh, on
that Saturday.
So I flew down the night before late, the night before Halloween.
I figured, all right, I'll, I'll spend Halloween in Austin was the hashtag wedding bells.
No, but it was called the bell liberation.
He called it narcissistic.
It doesn't include his wife.
Well, her name is built, her name is doomed.
All right.
Well, uh, her, her name is bell now because she follows the rules.
No, okay.
I'm just, I didn't, um, yeah, on that, uh, so I, no, but no, I really didn't do much.
I went to, um, a couple comedy clubs and, and had some drinks with some comics and some
friends.
And then that was it.
Like it, I didn't dress up.
Yeah.
I didn't do anything.
Uh, so no, I did nothing.
Girl, I've been on a few dates with sent me 18 detailed costumes over the course of the
last week.
I'm like, what, I, I guess I'll keep complimenting these, but like, what's the matter with
you?
You pick one costume for the year.
There was like a Ricky Bobby.
There was a, a Parisian princess.
There was a, uh, you know, a Harajuku girl, I don't know, you'd get one costume.
It, so she bought, what, what was she like?
I'm going to return this seven.
I don't wear.
She had, I mean, she had made her, you know, they all looked like professional store bought or
made costumes.
I don't know what the game plan was.
I don't talk to these women jump.
That town is just sick.
Uh, yeah, I haven't dressed up in forever.
Maybe I should, but the older you get with no kids, it's just a weird look at a certain
point.
I mean, I don't mind, I, the reason I don't like dressing up is because it obviously always
involves something to your face that you have to do.
And as a guy that wears glasses and doesn't wear context, putting a mask on is impossible
because you can't see and you can't wear your glasses under it or over it.
And then face paint sucks because it gets all over your glasses and it, and the glasses
at every turn ruin the costume.
So what if you, you're just a big old nerd?
Yeah.
Well, my buddy had a Halloween party a couple of weeks ago and I went and I wore a suit
and I wore a name tag that said, hello, my name is Stan.
And I said, I'm a drunk traveling salesman because I knew I was going to get drunk.
And that's about as far as I'll take it.
I would have thought with a hello, my name is Ann Stan that you were doing an M &M homage
with two references to M &M.
That's a good point.
I didn't even think of that.
But my homage was to Stan from the Golden Girls, his born act.
Yeah, he was a door to door guy and a traveling salesman.
So I thought, all right, it's kind of like I'm dressing up sort of as Stan.
But you put a election night, nothing, I went to bed pretty much Sam.
Yeah, you know, turn it on for like 10 minutes and then I was like, all right, yeah, I went
to bed and let's not, you know, nobody needs to hear anymore nonsense, all whatever.
But I will say this to our listeners, America is great again.
You got to be good, you got to be bad, you got to be wiser, you got to be tough, you got
to be strong, you got to stay together, right?
Who sang that song?
I'm going to, I don't look it up, you got to be, it starts with maybe Des Ray, I want
to say, one hit, C .C.
Peniston, but that's not C .C.
Peniston.
You got to be bay and you got to be tough.
I haven't eaten yet today, yeah, just by because I've been running around and I just didn't,
I thought I was going to have time and I just, I haven't eaten yet and I just got back
from a huge grocery shop for the week and I bought four bottles of wine and it took everything
in me to not open one and drink while we record because I was like, I can't drink wine without
having eaten.
That's not okay, I don't think, you know, pour the wine into a bowl and dunk some bread
into it.
I won't tell anybody.
It was Des Ray from the 1984 album, I ain't move them, it's Des Ray, it's not Des Ray,
like a play on the name Des Ray, it's D E S apostrophe R E E Des Ray, all right, listen
as your day unfolds, challenge what the future holds.
What year is that?
That's one of those songs.
I don't know what you, you could tell.
I literally just said, all of the, I said 1994, I didn't hear you say it, I was too
focused on the name 94, you could tell me that song was from 78, 94, 2010, I wouldn't
know.
I'd be like, yeah, that's what we like to call in the music business, I'm this Jack, timeless.
What, did you see they, they did the, another scary stuff, I suppose, they did the, I
guess, D 20, whatever that fucking Disney thing is called, they announced the new Tron, okay,
Tron Aries, I think it's called with Bridges, I saw a bootleg of the, somebody recorded it
on their phone, like the announcement trailer, the announcement trailer was just, you know,
like the big ship that looks like an arc comes down, and then there's like two of the light
speeder things, and then it says, it spells out the name and neon, and then it says music
by a nine inch nails is doing the soundtrack, last time it was deaf punk, and then the lady
hosting it, this is, you want to talk about, I mean,
just what a fucking, it's just so funny to me, how thrown together all this shit is,
the woman on stage who's moderating the event at the Disney thing, they're announcing a massive
sequel to a massive property, so the way she's going to bring out the cast to surprise everybody
who's in this thing is she goes, I'm going to need a little help up here, and then she
announces them three times, while the trailer is still playing, she's going, I'm going
to need a little help up here, I'm going to need, she doesn't even know when the trailer's
done, they didn't even prep this poor woman, I mean, it's just like guys, get your shit together
help, I need help up here.
So she says I'm going to need some help up here finally at the right time, and then she
announces Jeff Bridges.
The Bridges comes out, so he's back in this one, and, hey man, he's, it looks like I'm
back in the trot.
Yeah.
At this point, he's fully become the like cowboy from that dead zombie cowboy movie, the
department of dead people wherever it's called, I'm sorry, Joe, it's way worse, RIPD,
yeah, and he's on stage, he's going, we didn't, she's something up, he's about to pan
for gold, I mean, it's ridiculous, we did this thing 40 years ago, man, I'm like, the hell
is happening now, you know, Trent, Trent, resident, the boys coming out to record a couple
of tracks and stripping, man, yeah, so I see, listen to the, the deaf punk, tron soundtrack,
when I write, I love it, it's great, but I don't recall a lot of positive public sentiment
for that last tron movie, I wasn't, it wasn't good, it was, I mean, it was cool,
3D, you know, and I, like I said, deaf punk, some fun visuals, I was down with it.
Look, the original tron, aside from the effects, is not a great movie, like it's not, it's
not a riveting film, it's just like cool looking, yeah.
So I think legacy was probably on par with that, I don't think Lido is back in this one,
I think it's just, bridges is back, I don't, wasn't he dead in the last one?
But he would, but his younger self was trapped in the, some shit, I don't know, I thought
he was like Obi -Wan style ghost in the last one.
It was like his young likeness had gotten stuck in the thing and then like had become evil
or something, something stuck in the goddamn tron, yeah, all right.
What else did they announce?
The sequels just keep piling up, that's the only one I saw, I didn't even know it was happening.
I heard, I was asking around about stuff, just on my own career wise, and I've learned that
they dropped the Will Smith, Kevin Hart, planes, trans automobiles, that's no longer
happening.
Okay.
He switched it up in favor of a lady, planes, trans automobiles, okay, now they're working
on that.
It's literally just like spinning a wheel now.
They've got a movie and we're going to do it with spin, Filipinos, you know.
It's like not really how this thing is supposed to work and have an interesting take on why
we need to do it again is usually the best method.
And the only way I'll see that, not the only way, but they better have Melissa McCarthy in
the John Candy role.
You got to have, then you got a reason for the movie existing, yes.
You know, you got to have a heavy set funny person in that role.
It doesn't work the same.
It's not, it won't work with Kevin Hart, no, as the John, which I assume he would be the
John Candy.
It makes way more sense that Will Smith would be the tight ass.
For sure.
Yeah.
It doesn't work.
You got to have like a little rail or something.
You got to have, you know, phase on love, you got to have a, you know, that's, there's something
to the body type in that role that that sells it over the fence.
It just does.
But, you know, we'll see what they do.
We'll see what they do.
I think, yeah, I already talked about that last time.
Yeah, that's, I guess that was more of a news cycle, the Tron announcement than a, than
a scary stuff.
But yeah, I don't know.
They also announced another news cycle, and this could lead us into the corner, but I think
they announced officially that the next Batman universe TV show will be the Joker series
is, you know, in the patents in the universe, which it'll be nice to have some Joker -based
content out there.
Christ.
It's a lot of Joker, it's a lot of Joker, too much Joker.
Yeah.
I'm surprised they would even continue with it after folia do.
Well, I think I could be very wrong, but I assume what they are doing is, so they have
already said that Penguin and Sophia Falcone, E. Falcone or Falcone, will be pivotal roles
in the next one after how established they've become now in the sequel series.
So my assumption is that because they also teased Joker in the patents in one, they
will further establish that character in the universe.
So then in the second movie, it can be Penguin, Sophia Falcone and Joker are there and
already well established, and then they'll bring in, you know, two -face or whoever, and
like really get this rogues gallery going, which by the way, since the Adam West Batman
movie, they have never had a Batman movie with a rogues gallery in the movie.
They've done movies where they take two of the villains from the rogues gallery and that's
that movie, but they've never done one where it's like the gangs all here, which is kind
of how the comics go a lot of the time.
So I would like to see that.
So if that's what they're doing with the Joker find, I think that's is how they should
do it, but I don't know if that's what they're doing.
Who knows, you know, are you watching the Penguin?
Yes.
Did I send you my impression of the Penguin the other night?
No.
Oh, okay.
I haven't seen the Penguin.
I just do an impression of the Penguin.
Are you caught up with the finale came out last night.
I haven't seen it yet.
But, but the, the show, well, do this is my first movie corner.
I'll do a, I know, I know some, I'm not going to say it, but every, every article now has
to be, you know, we're gagging for that blank moment and then it tells you exactly what happens
in the finale of a show that aired three hours ago.
Yeah.
So like, I'll, I'll just make up a show that doesn't exist dragon, dragon time.
So then it's like, you know, we're still reeling from the death of Pegasus on tonight's
dragon time is the headline of the article.
Yeah.
Do we just decide that nobody gives a fuck about anything anymore?
We're just living in a nihilist society.
Yeah.
I know exactly what happened in the end of the Penguin.
And I've been thinking, maybe at some point, I'll watch the Penguin
but now I know how the 10 hour thing ends that sucks.
I will say this, it's a great show.
I am shocked when they announced this show.
I was like, I have, I couldn't have less interest.
I was not a big fan of the movie, but everybody kept saying this show was awesome.
The show was awesome.
I put it on.
I was like, holy shit, this show is awesome.
It's a great crime show.
It's just, there's no Batman.
It's just about the crime workings of the Mafioso families in Gotham and the Penguin
manipulating and trying to gain power over the city.
It's, and they use the end of the Batman movie very well where because of the terrorist
attack that that Ridler does, where he blows up the levees of the dams or whatever,
and all the water floods.
What that does is it basically ravages the lower income neighborhoods of Gotham
and it throws the whole city into fucking chaos and like it's a free for all,
which is what originally the third Nolan movie was supposed to be.
The third Nolan movie was supposed to be Gotham falling into chaos and the Joker
being the catalyst for that and taking advantage of it.
And then Heath Ledger died.
They had to switch everything up.
But that's what they did with this Penguin show.
They're both tremendous in this show.
They both deserve awards.
Christine Maloney, I think her name is, and then, and then, um, Farrell,
like they're, they're, they're incredible in this show.
It's really, really, really good.
I'm shocked just a mob show or are there elements that make it a superhero show?
Also zero superhero, they don't even mention Batman.
It is just very odd to me.
Well, it's, it's only odd because it's a sequel series.
It's not a prequel.
So I said last night to my friend, I go, that is my one criticism.
It's like, guys, mention Batman once in a while pretending you've never
met Batman.
Yeah, it's weird that they don't mention him, but, um, but it's awesome.
It's, and it, and it, it was Pat.
That was my gripe with the movie was that you've created such a convincing, gritty,
crime, new R world.
And then this guy shows up in a bat suit and it looks kind of ridiculous.
In this, Dave removed that and then also injected some fun into it.
So I'm like, this is what the movie, this is, wow, this is what was lacking or whatever.
So it's very good.
It's very, very good.
I, uh, I give a, uh, a strong hogs up to, to the Penguin series.
I look forward to watching the finale.
And just to confirm you find Colin Farrell's impression of James Gandalfini
to be a more convincing mobster performance than James Gandalfini's mobster performance.
I don't find that he is doing an impression of James Gandalfini in any way.
He said he was at least on the TikTok.
I mean, maybe he's inspired by Tony soprano, but it doesn't sound like he's doing an
impression of Gandalfini.
And to answer your question though, yes, I think it is a better mob show than the
sopranos because it doesn't have guys with high hair going into a Starbucks, uh,
ranting about how cappuccino belongs to the Italians, uh, or mob hits happening
at the college campus during parents day or whatever, you know, or horrific
conversations with Carmella going, oh, you got to go with Bobby day.
Bobby day is the, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, I can't, I can't even get
them to it. I like the show.
I like the show.
I, I, you know, it's also only nine episodes or eight episodes.
So the Sprouts went six seasons.
So if this went six seasons, I might have a similar opinion of this.
Sure.
Uh, that I do have the sopranos, but for now, it's very good.
Um, I was going to talk about season three of the bear and I can't watch it.
I, uh, show that I once praised on here is now as far as I can tell,
completely up its own ass and unwatchable.
The first episode of season three is like a moody montage with nine inch nails
music.
Again, this is the most innovative show on television using the same score as
Tron part three.
Um, but yeah, the show is just a classic case of Emperor's new clothes at this point.
You, we were fooled by the constant use of pop songs that we all love from our
past, or at least I did.
The constant montages, how great Chicago looks, um, the mood, the vibe,
there were great individual episodes along the way.
Don't get me wrong.
But when they're trying to just become an art show in the, in the 21st episode,
you used to have to earn that sopranos would be a great example.
The sopranos is a classic mob show.
That's also a comedy that's also many other things.
But it becomes a much stranger, almost linchy and weird thing in the home stretch
when it's earned our trust and then you can play with these characters.
The bear is acting like it's one of the all time great television shows because
we pretended it was.
Um, and now we're stuck with stuff like this where it's just embarrassing.
And the second episode, I'm like, all right, that one took me a full month to watch.
Tows got to be better, just a return to form.
Let's get the gang back together.
And the episode is basically one take of six characters arguing over a plastic tub of spinach,
which is what like your grandma would jokingly refer to the bear as,
but that's what it's become.
And the show probably costs like $25 million in episode at this point.
And the best they can do is six people arguing over a tub of spinach.
I'm sure many people out there will say it gets better.
You got to give it a couple of episodes and I know that's every show.
But generally kicking off the third season, let's go to sopranos again.
That's when you got the awkwardness of season one out from under your belt.
Two brings everybody to the party.
Everybody's on board.
And then soprano season three is the best television season of all time in my opinion.
The bear season three is like, fuck you.
Y 'all came to the party.
Well, now fuck you.
And that seems to be the attitude of a lot of television nowadays.
And I hate it.
We're going to go do something completely reckless and weird.
And it's because that's the only way to get clicks.
And then suddenly you're watching a musical episode of a medical drama.
And you don't know what the fuck's going on anymore.
And I'm tired of it.
All right.
Well, that's fair.
I have never seen the show.
Well, it's lost its way.
It's lost its way.
Um, I will stay on theme.
I rewatched the Batman because of my enjoyment of the penguin.
I still don't love the movie, but I will say on second watch and having it all
reframed by the approach to the, to the TV series, I enjoyed it much more than I did
the first time around.
I think a lot of the pressure was off because you know,
I saw that movie excitedly before my superhero fatigue had set in.
And I love Batman watching it this time around, you know, kind of took my foot off
the gas a little bit and just said, let me just try to take this in.
And maybe I'll understand the choices they made a little bit better now that I've
a better understanding of the universe because of the penguin.
And I did things in the movie made more sense to me.
Batman, you know, one of my biggest criticisms was it always bothered me that when
Batman goes to meet the penguin for the first time in the movie, he goes through the
front doors of the iceberg lounge and just walks through the crowd and starts beating
the shit out of anybody that challenges him.
And I was always like, Batman wouldn't do that.
Batman would like sneak in through the window and just be standing behind him or something.
And then I'm like, no, that's the point.
It's supposed to be that he's clumsy that he still doesn't quite know how to do this.
He's he's a rookie.
So all of those little moments made a lot more sense to me.
Dano's performance was more palatable, especially given the fact, well,
the third thing I'm going to review, I can speak to that a little bit more.
But it just made more sense.
Do I still do I think it's a great movie?
No, I think it's a well made movie, but I'm just I'm not that into it.
But I have hopes now for the second one.
I think the second one's going to be more enjoyable.
Was Dano the riddler or the Joker, the riddler, Barry Coneg or the Cogan, yeah, Cogan,
he's the Joker, gotcha.
But I think the Batman's at least worth a rewatch.
If you've only seen it once and didn't like it, but enjoyed the penguin, I'll say that.
How about that?
Very well.
I watched on Apple TV, presumed innocent.
I was pretty taken with the movie, the Harrison Ford movie when I was a teenager.
I thought it was pretty good.
I remember its twists and turns.
This presumed innocent goes with entirely different twists and turns.
Just like another question mark with with a lot of what's going on in TV development these days.
You pay top dollar to buy a property like Scott Taro's book, presumed innocent,
and then you change every single detail about it.
It doesn't make sense to me.
They also bought the rights to a different book for season two, which will not have Jill and all.
Will not have any of the same people.
It's a whole new story.
I don't know what you're even doing at that point.
Why not just make your own legal thriller with Jill and Hall?
Why even use the name, presumed innocent?
I have a question.
I have a question for you about that, because I think about that a lot.
It perplexes me.
Do you think the reason they do that is because they say we own the property
and we want to shave close enough to it that theoretically we could get sued
if we don't just call it presumed innocent.
So let's just call it that and then do whatever the hell we want and we don't have to worry about it.
Yeah, I think sometimes that's probably the case.
When I have talked in the past about doing something like plans transorbitals,
they're like do it like due date and don't buy the rights.
Right.
Because a movie with two guys traveling, you can do whatever you want.
But I'm sure, yeah, it's it's case by case.
But this show is fun in the in the manner of it being a legal thriller at a time where they're rare.
You know, like anatomy of a fall, I think got all that Oscars attention and Oscars.
Because that's another genre that we just let go by the wayside, the legal thriller.
It used to be a very big part of going to the movies.
It was like 10 % of dramas or 10 % of Oscar bait.
You know, if you good man, ghosts of Mississippi, all that objection, your honor, et cetera, et cetera.
Now it's pretty rare.
So when one comes along, it's fun.
This one is fun.
It's well made.
It's David E. Kelly, who along with Ryan Murphy makes about 50 % of television these days.
His shows tend to be pretty good.
The ones I've seen, big little lies was great, probably his biggest recent success.
But David E. Kelly's been doing these shows, legal shows dating back to Allie McBeal and beyond.
So it's good, you know, it's like an old master kind of stepping into the new streaming era.
And for the most part, it works.
Jill and Hall is good.
I would thought I was in trouble at first.
It opens with this like monologue over black in the courtroom.
And he's like, ladies and gentlemen, who amongst us hasn't been presumed?
Presumed to be innocent.
I was like, oh, no.
Like just some, and it's a most generic monologue, you know, like every one of these things starts.
But by the end, it won me over.
Most of the winning is done by the supporting cast, particularly Lurley, the great Peter Skars guard,
or is it SARS guard, exactly where you want.
I think it's Alexander Skars guard, Peter Sars guard.
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
He is right where you want him to be.
My all time favorite SARS guard performance is in a movie called Shattered Glass.
Very interesting.
I love that movie.
And Sars guard is right back in it as like a weasley.
He's a, he's a, he's a, is a lawyer that works with Jill and Hall.
But he clearly is just jealous of him.
And he's one of these guys where he like is so angry at the world,
because he can't connect with women.
And everything he's doing with women makes him come off even more creepier.
So it makes him matter and matter.
It's a great character.
And few people play a creep as well as SARS guard.
He's him and then Bill Camp as Jill and Hall's mentor.
Steel the show.
They make it worth watching.
And it's only eight episodes.
And the twists are fun.
However, I'll say this.
The twists they chose to go with is a lot less effective than the twist in the book
and in the Harrison Ford movie.
So it's not like they came up with a better take on it.
I'm confused as to why they went that route.
But it's a good solid show.
I recommend presumed innocent.
So my last one is this is the zodiac speaking, which is the new docuseries on Netflix
about the zodiac murders.
And it ties, excuse me, it ties to the Batman because I must have heard this at some point.
But after I watched that and then I watched the Batman, I was like, oh, the riddler is supposed to be the zodiac killer.
Because the zodiac killer would send these cryptic sort of riddle messages into the San Francisco newspaper.
And that's what the riddler does in this.
He wears the hood with the glasses over the eyes.
I was like, okay, I get, I get now why they did the take on the riddler that they did.
It's an extraordinarily dark take because the zodiac story is extraordinarily dark.
But this documentary I thought was awesome.
It made me want to watch zodiac again, but it's not streaming at the moment.
I remember seeing zodiac in the theater and not being interested enough in the zodiac story itself to throw myself into the movie.
But after seeing this, I really would like to see the movie again.
But anyway, the documentary interviews a ton of people who are very relevant to the situation.
One being the character Jake Gyllenhaal plays in the movie, that reporter.
It is Jake Gyllenhaal, right?
Yeah, yeah.
They interview the friends and who are the children of the girlfriend of the guy that is the main suspect in all of it.
They get into like, they show videos that he sent the mother.
They get into a lot into that guy.
I mean, that guy is the zodiac.
I mean, there's not a doubt in my mind.
There's a part in the documentary where they talk about he gets put away in a silent slash prison for three years.
And suddenly all the zodiac activity stops.
And as soon as he gets out, a new zodiac letter has clearly this guy.
But they could never get enough evidence to condemn him while he was alive.
So there is still a bit of a question mark, but all fingers point in the one direction.
I watched all three episodes in a row.
I was glued to it.
I found it riveting.
And I'm not a big true crime guy, but I thought that this series was really good.
And not, it didn't feel sleazy and exploitative the way a lot of true crime stuff does.
It just felt like, no, this is, we're going to tell you this story because it's newsworthy.
I really enjoyed it.
I think you would enjoy it, Pat, as a fan of the movie.
Yes, I am pumped to watch it.
I just watched Zodiac on 4K, which came out on Halloween.
Got to say I could go back and forth for days on which his finchers quote masterpiece.
But I got to go with Zodiac.
Seven is probably a little more in your face, a little flashier.
Maybe it sticks with you a little longer.
But for me, Zodiac is one of the most endlessly rewatchable, fascinating, absorbing movies ever made.
It's about two and a half plus hours.
I could go for an even longer cut.
There is a director's cut on Blu -ray that's not much different.
But, you know, somebody asked David Fincher why he thinks this movie failed to connect.
And he's like, it's a three -hour movie without a resolution.
He's like, the day after it came out, I realized why it didn't connect and I was kicking myself.
But that's what the movie is about.
A lack of resolution.
It is about how if you have an obsession, whatever it is, a lifelong obsession with something.
And it doesn't pan out.
It's going to drive you completely insane.
This movie is really about three different men whose lives went to varying degrees out of control as they pursued answers in who was the Zodiac killer.
You got Robert Grace Smith, the cartoonist slash reporter played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Very young already coming off a divorce and steadily working on another one with his wife Chloe Savigny.
He completely ignores his wife and children in pursuit of this.
You got Mark Ruffalo back when he still tried and gave a shit as a more established reporter at the station.
Sorry, as a police officer at the station.
You got Robert Downey Jr., who goes more of the drug and alcohol route to cope with not being able to find the Zodiac.
And these men come into and go out of each other's lives for decades.
They look for the killer for so long that dirty Harry comes out and they're literally being mocked by this very real story in their life.
Now being shown in movie theaters as like this unsolvable action movie.
It's just great and all the supporting cast every single person in this movie is famous.
It seems like it's one of those when they used to pony up for the great character actors.
Brian Cox, Anthony Edwards, the guy from Fargo, her husband in a very creepy role.
Charles Fleischer, the comedian who voiced Roger Rabbit in a terrifying role as a guy who may or may not be the Zodiac killer.
Contains probably the most disturbing on -screen murder ever, which is the murder at the lake of the teenage couple very early on in the film.
I just think Zodiac is the shit and I love it.
The Fargo guy is the guy who John Keralynch.
Yeah, that's the guy who is basically it seems to be the Zodiac.
That's who Fincher seems to think it is.
Yeah, that dirty Harry, the interesting you mentioned dirty Harry because they talk about the cop on the real cop on the case.
And they're like, this is the cop that dirty Harry is based on like this hard -nosed cop or whatever.
So there you go.
All right.
We got the movie at hand.
The substats, starting with great.
Demi Moore and Dennis Quaid are leads in this film.
Margot quality is also in it.
I mean, she is a lead.
It's like it's them Demi Moore, Margaret, quality movie and Dennis Quaid is your support.
I think I feel like I saw more of Quaid on screen than Quaid, but maybe I'm just, I don't know, maybe just because he comes into it sooner or something.
It doesn't matter.
It's this Quaid role, by the way, was supposed to be Ray Leota.
Oh, wow.
It would have been his last role.
It's a great satire slash horror film about female aging in Hollywood and all the components of it.
I really, I mean, the basic premise is what?
Demi Moore plays a character who is getting aged out of unfairly aged out of her job in Hollywood.
She's like an exercise video instructor, a lot, Jane Fonda back in the day.
And they, she has offered an opportunity to try this product called the Substance,
which is a one time injection that causes a younger version of yourself that's like perfect physically to come literally out of your body.
And you then switch living with this younger version of yourself every seven days.
They have to switch back.
And of course, as you might expect, as things transpire in the film, the urge to switch back lessons, particularly on the younger version of her side of the table.
I mean, that's basically the premise, you know, her younger self.
What's that two worlds start bleeding into one another, colliding, you know, as usual with these things, it's like you fuck with the rules, the rules fuck with you.
And it turns into like a pretty explosive gross out or bananza.
Right off the bat, I think Demi Moore gives, I would argue, the performance of her career.
I mean, I mean, she's been in a lot of stuff and she's always great, but I mean, she really is tremendous in this.
And she commits 110 % to the role, including being fully naked on screen quite a bit.
Now, I know a lot of people think, well, big deal.
It's easy for Demi Moore to get naked on screen.
She looks great. She does look great, but she's still a woman in her six days.
And she's still getting fully naked on screen because it is called for.
This is one of the few movies where I was like, this is the most justifiable nudity I can think of in many years in a film.
Where I'm like, no, the nudity actually plays, is it is an incredibly important detail to this thing.
Yeah, she's naked throughout, quality's naked throughout, quality used prosthetic breasts to match Demi Moore's voluptuous rack.
But otherwise, she is naked as well.
It's a very violent sexual, gross, graphic movie.
Coralie Farghit.
I'm definitely pronouncing that wrong for a shot, probably for a shot.
French filmmaker who did revenge, which we maybe did on the show.
I know I talked about it personally. I'm not sure if we didn't do it.
No, we didn't do it.
I love that movie.
That is a classic rape revenge story, you know, like a woman getting revenge on her assailant.
It's an Australian extreme, very, like, you know, NC -17, rough, violent, but really fun movie.
I prefer that to the substance ultimately, but it is awesome that it's like getting her to a bigger level because she clearly has a vision.
And the movie, while being influenced by a lot of things and wearing a lot of influences on its sleeve, definitely feels like its own thing.
A very modern kind of feminist statement.
For me, the only issue I had with it was it's at a 10 for most of the runtime.
Of course, the ending it goes to like a 12.
But it's too long, too much for too long.
This kind of like extreme thing does not need to be two hours and 20 minutes in my opinion.
220 seems to be the new two.
And every single two hour and 20 minute movie sub zodiac, which I mentioned would be better at two.
I almost think just like you said, the nudity is called for here.
The length of zodiac is called for it to let you feel how long this thing took.
Yeah, my issue.
I've seen this substance twice now.
I liked it more on the second viewing for sure.
But you just start to feel that length at a certain point, especially for a script with very little dialogue where it's just kind of craziness.
You know, it just didn't have to be like that.
Quaid, Quaid is great in a supporting role.
He's playing like, you know, a super misogynistic TV producer.
He's great in it.
Maybe a little one note.
I think that's my only real grievance with it is it's a little.
I'd like a little more variance in the tone of the movie.
I guess I would say.
I enjoyed the tone throughout.
I thought it really worked.
One thing I really enjoyed was, you know, it's very much embraces the satire of it all.
It doesn't get bogged down in worrying about the details.
Like, well, how did that happen?
Or how did she know how to administer all of the treatment of this thing to herself when they don't give her any instructions?
And the people that are providing the treatment are very ominous and don't answer any questions.
There were a lot of moments where had it not steered into the curve of the satire, you would have been like, this is not making any sense.
And it's too much of an ask.
But because from immediately they jump right into and primarily through the Dennis Quaid character, they make him so heinous
and so unlikable and so cartoonish, it really helps set the tone for the whole thing.
The fact that Demi Moore is a fitness instructor and she's famous for it on television when that's not been a thing since the 80s.
Uh -huh.
Little details like that where they're just like guys, we're just going for this.
We're pulling, we're pulling all of the details from every direction to make the commentary we want to make.
And if you go with it, you're going to have a great time.
This is one of the first movie.
One of the plot points is is if you, if your younger body stays out of the older, doesn't do the switchback on the seventh day when it's supposed to and takes extra time, your original body will start to decay in different ways,
uh, which is mainly extraordinary aging.
Yeah.
So the first time that happens to me more is one finger is like almost rotting off of her body.
And then as that continues to happen, she becomes more and more physically hideous.
I also like that as when it when they first start to split from, you know, when the two bodies start to live their own lives, there seems to be some concept
that the dormant body can sort of remember what the other body does.
And then as it goes on, they become completely two different people, even though they are the same person.
So there's really great stuff where they're fucking each other over.
Um, the young girl is like partying and leaving like a mess of bottles and whatever else in the house that that to me more has to clean up when she comes back.
And then to me more starts binge eating and gorging herself and leaving like chicken carcasses all over the house and whatever.
I thought all of that the weird competition between the two was very fun.
And it felt a little death becomes her actually.
Yes.
But as, as, I mean, there's just some great sequences where as, primarily as you're, as you're gunning towards the third act, there's a scene where, you know, quality stays out of Demi Moore's body for like three or four weeks or something.
Some ridiculous amount of time you're not supposed to.
So you know, whenever Demi Moore wakes back up, it's not going to look good.
And they do that great scene where.
Krawi's body starts to collapse and she she has no choice. She has to switch back with Demi Moore and Demi Moore like wake awakens and you see the feet on the ground and you're just like this is.
This is going to be rough like whatever she looks like and it's very much like the fly.
You're like, oh boy, what's what's he, what's he going to look like now? That's what you're doing through the entire watching of the fly.
What is he going to look like now?
And they kind of looks like the fly in the home stretch.
Yeah.
Yeah. And then all of this builds to also to the, the, the great plot point that that Margot quality's character is going to host New Year's Eve live.
A New Year's Eve workout show.
Yeah.
And a simple push to make it a New Year's day workout so that you like start the New Year with fitness, at least that would have made sense.
Now they go for it.
They're like, and then the way they do the New Year's Eve, you think the whole time it's going to be like, you know, Carson daily and time square style thing.
And it's not.
They're in a theater with dancing women who were topless.
It's a network TV show and all the women are topless.
It's so crazy.
And it literally looks like a beauty pageant.
And quality's, quality at this point has murdered Demi Moore in a fit of rage.
And now when her body starts to deteriorate, she has nobody to switch with.
So she readministers the, the substance injection thinking she will now split with her current self into an even more perfect version of herself.
And that is not what happens.
It goes horribly wrong.
And she produces an abomination.
And the abomination going, that whole sequence, I was like, this is one of the greatest things I've seen in cinema in 10 years.
Like the, that like monstrosity, putting on the lipstick and titties at one point.
Yeah.
Curling the one strand of hair.
Putting the dress on, showing up at the pageant.
And then everybody freaking out.
And it starts just inexplicably spewing a, a fire hose of blood on everybody.
I was like, this is insane.
I loved it, man.
I loved it.
Yeah, the ending feels kind of like carry.
It's, it takes from a lot of things much in the way Tarantino does without it ever being a problem.
But you definitely see its reference points.
It's got a big point of view without it kind of shoving its point down your throat.
But you get what it's saying pretty clearly.
And then I had heard, I don't think people realize now that I think just because things are so bad that when something is good, the hyperbole gets out of control very, very quickly.
Yeah.
And on this movie that really happened, the talk of like, you'll, people were vomiting and, you know, having a massive heart attacks in the end.
And, you know, people were running for the doors at the end of this, this movie.
It, it, it just does these movies such a disservice.
You know, it drains them of any surprise, it drains them of any.
You know, it's like I was saying about the penguin earlier.
It's like, okay, now I kind of don't need to watch that.
There's this casualness about everything where it's like nobody really gives a shit anymore about most stuff.
But this movie, it really does.
It's not, you know, it's not one of the all time most violent or gross movies.
But it's disgusting.
It seems like it was influenced by Brian Yuzna and like society.
Oh, yeah.
Especially that last creature at the end where it's like heads coming out of assholes and, you know, assholes shitting out breasts and et cetera.
It's a wild, wild ride.
The makeup is awesome.
The effects, which I assume are practical are awesome.
I doubt this was done on much of a budget.
And it's really, really impressive.
Like I said, my quibbles are what are always my quibbles these days length for the most part.
But I dug it.
I love the performances.
It's a very sexy movie.
There's so much TNA on camera that it's sort of the point that by the end, you're almost like put some clothes on these women.
But that's the type of movie it is.
It's just very extreme, very in your face.
As all the best satire is.
It's a very good movie.
Certainly one of the best horror pictures of the year.
And comedic to the end, you know, one of the things they do is the only clean part of the monster at the end is Demi Moore's face is on its back.
Yeah.
And her face is pristine.
It's the only clean, unobstructed part of the body.
And she's writhing in pain.
She's going like whatever.
And then at the end, when they're at the pageant and everybody starts to scream and they're going to attack this thing, you think she's going to be like, thank God, the sweet release of death of suffering.
And then she starts going, no, guys, it's me.
It's me.
It's really funny.
So it's not just, it's not just a great commentary on sexism and how unfairly women get treated with again aging and beauty standards and all that stuff.
It also does take no prisoners in the vanity of it all.
And somebody who is being unfairly treated still lusting after the acceptance and the praise.
I thought it really hit the conversation from all perspectives.
And like you said, Pat, without ramming it down your throat, doing it in a way that was fun, that was crazy, that was hilarious, that was disgusting.
I really enjoyed it.
And I will say this, I actually felt a little more strongly about the grotesqueness of it all than pat it.
I was trying to eat because I was like, yeah, right.
It's fine.
And I was eating while I was watching it.
And yeah, I was like, I've made a mistake.
I should not be eating right now.
This is kind of turning my stomach a little bit.
So gross outstuffs, always in the eye of the beholder, certain things, texture things, get different people differently, etc.
But yeah, it's very cronon burggy in that way.
It's just a lot of goop and goo and pus and etc.
Awesome movie.
Hogs way up.
My hog is way up for the substance.
Hogs so far up, it's almost producing a substance of its own ladies and gentlemen.
I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
We are on Instagram at see you and help pod Joe.
Jota Rosa comedy on Instagram.
Jota Rosa comedian, I believe, one tick tock.
The summerville show was coming up quickly December 7th.
Saturday to summer 7th.
I will be in summerville, Massachusetts at the crystal ballroom, salsa windfall also doing a set.
I'm going to come out do a full comedy set.
Then salsa windfall is going to do a full set.
And then there's some surprises and fun things happening.
Please come on out.
And the tour starts in January.
The jewelry stick tour.
Jota Rosa .com for all tickets.
If you're in New York, please swing by Joey Roses.
JoeyRoses .com if you want to check out any info.
We thank you.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you.
And hell.
Bye.