Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM gamesense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Where's that presentation you need for your boss?
Slack, email, drive, lost, like your sanity
after wasting hours searching 76 tabs.
Your work tools shouldn't take so much work.
Dropbox stash finds what you need fast across all your workouts
so you can focus on what matters.
It's been less time searching, more time creating.
learn more at dropouts .com backslash dash.
Howdy folks, welcome to a new episode of we'll see when how the podcast is part of
the Fangoria podcast network for more information about this network including other programs
how to follow our show or how to find episodes of any show please visit Fangoria .com
And now, on with the show, Pat Walsh, hey guys, in full deluxe stereo, new format.
New format in case you missed it, we are kind of keeping it as it was, a free -flowing
conversation, but we're not tying it to a film.
And each week, the loose theme of the episode will be a sin, we're starting with the big
Seve, the Deadly's. Today's going to be Wrath, which we just had to look up. I thought Wrath might
be murdering someone, turns out Wrath is just anger, which is a sin that everyone has. And I have
every second of every day. And I think Joe has it more than I do. I got it bad, baby. And that ain't good.
No. It helps me. It fuels my writings, my comedies. I feel like it makes me a more interesting person
and perhaps. But it is a sin. You're comedies? Is that what you just said? My comedy, my writing.
Oh, I thought you said you're comedies like you were like a Greek playwright. It helps both my
comedies and my tragedies. I'm currently wearing a black shirt and I have the two of the drama and tragedy
masks and glitter on them. I teach a class over at the learning annex. I'll tell you I'm annoyed with
you already, because I'm looking at your value versus mine. I mean, why are you so much
lower than me? Am I that much lower than you? And look at the waveforms. Look at, look
at mine. It looks like a cardiac arrest is happening. Should we restart? Now, I'll just
adjust it all and post. How do we restart? We don't have anything good here. No, the people,
the, the, the, we don't need to restart. The people afterwards won't know. Just hold the
God damn my cup a little closer.
I'm holding it.
There you go.
Maybe I'm just too loud.
Look, the people that sit at home going,
what are you talking about?
It sounds fine.
Because I'll mix master this at the end.
All right.
See, I'm not getting raffle.
I'm getting angry at the whole affair.
I know what anger's you.
What's angering you right now?
I think let's start off big picture.
Country is in serious danger.
I don't pay attention to politics.
my anything I do politically does not matter and will not change the world in any way sorry
that's how I feel right uh you're looking at these candidates uh obviously Trump's a goddamn
monster right Clinton and this has zero to do with her being a woman you can think somebody's
not gonna do a great job even though they're a woman I she has a way of just you know sniping at
at Sanders and just like this like one liners thing to him all the time and well you did
this you said this you did this I don't want that as my president Bernie Sanders is better
about it but he's an old cook and he can't deliver on these promises there are no good options
and it's going to be one of those three people there are no good options there are no great options
let's say there have never been great options I feel like Bill Clinton at his time was a great
option. Barack Obama was a very important president for this country to have.
I think it was nice that we had Obama in there. I'm sorry, I just called him
Barack Obama, like I don't know how to speak. I think it was nice that we had Obama
in there. But I mean here's the thing. Everybody goes
it's a mark of progress and it's not really because all that happens is is the
people like us that try to think progressively at least
say well that's good that that happened but we would have thought that anyway.
And the people that didn't want that to happen just became more racist and angry about it. So nobody changes
Which pushes people more towards a trump type?
Nobody changes nothing can get fixed. Nothing will ever change. Don't vote. It's a waste of time
It is and I will still vote. I won't but
You know and I this is something I said at the last election was like
If you don't clap at a concert
you're an asshole. It makes no difference if you clap at a concert, but if you don't do it,
you're an asshole. It's my opinion. And that's how I feel about voting. It makes no difference.
You should do it. People have fought for your right to do it. You should do it. When? When did
they fight for our right? How long do I have to be indebted to that for? I fought for my right.
I mean, I'm not a historian. I should go or something. Somebody did something. I got to still
fucking player. That's like that's like somebody tell me my great -great -grandfather came over here.
I don't fucking know that guy. Yeah, it's a different world.
Other countries don't have that run. Wow, it sucks for them. That's shitty.
Shit way to live. I couldn't agree more. But these people, you know, I'm watching
the new season of House of Cards, and obviously Kevin Spacey on that show is, you know, just
to complete monster. They got this new guy coming up in the ranks. He's like 40 young families,
good looking guys. He's got big ideas. And they reveal him to, you know, have some scummy
ties as well. My point is, where are these people? Where are the good like 40 -year -old men
and women with like bright ideas who are excited and can't wait till they turn 40s? They can
run for the presidency. If you're talking about a fantasy show, I am talking about a fantasy show.
talking about a baby child TV show.
And that person would, of course,
not be as great as you want him to be.
Barack Obama was in a way that person,
but where are they?
How are these ghouls when the best America has to offer?
Because when you have one,
people start to refer to him as they refer to Bernie Sanders,
as this guy's a cook and an idealist
and none of this can ever happen.
Because deep down everybody knows,
change will never happen.
Yeah, that's true.
And if Trump is our president,
And I don't think that changes America in a big way either it sadly probably won't it'll change it
It'll slow it'll slightly swing the pendulum
To the advantage of like the maniacs that like that guy for eight years
Yeah, and then or four or four, but there are a lot of people in place
Braggobona can't get done when he wants to get done and neither will Trump
That's what I'm saying. There are a lot of people in place who are gonna be like no can't do that
By the way, there are also plenty
plenty, plenty, plenty of people that are saying they know Trump personally that this is all
just stage antics so we can win. He's fully aware of what he's unable to do. It's all
just bullshit. It's bullshit. For four to eight years, if he wins, the people in his camp
will have it slightly better. And then it'll change again. And another guy will come in
from the other side or woman and and then it'll be able to it'll be that thing again.
Throw a can of soda at an Asian if you want. Look, I mean, I think the man's a god damn
nightmare.
Asian idiot. I just don't see any one president change in this country. And I think that's
what really bums people out and makes them full of wrath, bringing it right back home.
When you talk to the average political enthusiast, I find it very similar to talking to a religious
enthusiast.
When you really hammer logic at them over and over, they are reduced to the defense of,
well, you've got to do something and that's the religious defense.
Well, you've got to believe in something, well, okay, well, then here we are now at the
truth or at the heart of the matter.
You don't believe in something because you believe in it. You just feel better believing in it and to me
That's the same thing with politics. You just feel better believing in something right because at the end of the day
You know you have no real way of changing anything. No
And people get into these like these impotent
Rages where because they can't do anything they get more angry and
My dad and I think a lot of people my dad's age
Get in these holes where they can't stop watching Fox News because they start feeding off the rage that it gives
them. And then, you know, my dad, you'll, if somebody says like, George Bush in his presence,
you're getting yelled at for eight hours. I'm like, it's over. Stop it. And you look on
Twitter, funny people, people I respect spend their entire day responding to trolls,
who probably don't even feel the way they're expressing. And they're like, but Trump Hitler, Trump's
Hitler Trump, write a joke or get off of Twitter.
This is the thing.
It's driving yourself crazy.
I have a bit about this in my act right now
about like how much I hate social media
and the one thing I hate about it is that it's given us
Twitter activists who do nothing more for the fight
than tweet what they think.
Right.
And you know, it's a one sided conversation
if they want it to be.
It's like the weakest form of activism.
You could you could the most non -committal form of
optimism. Yeah, we talked about that on here.
And but I have a bit about it and basically the crux of the bit is like
this is why like true social change will never happen again. Like there are no more radicals like
we had in the 60s. There are no there is you don't have Malcolm X staring out the window with
the machine gun. You don't have Jimmy Hoffa fist fighting cops. You don't have Martin Luther King
marching on cities like Birmingham. You don't have radicals. You have these privilege
Privileged pampered, upper class, cushy fucking pussies, that have time to just kind of sit around and pontificate and read the New Yorker and have discussions to whatever elaborate ends they want and coffee houses and stuff.
Those aren't activists. Those aren't people that are going to get anything done. Nothing will get done.
and change is not brought by discussion.
It just isn't.
Change is brought by overthrowing horrific, horrific people.
And that's the only way change has ever been brought.
Ever, ever, ever.
It's a sad, terrible truth, but it's true.
And that's gonna tweet hashtag feel the burn
and then go to your yoga class.
What are you changing?
What are you helping?
You're wanting people to know that you like Bernie Sanders
So that maybe people who like Bernie Sanders like you, you're not trying to change anyone's mind. Who's mind has been changed by this?
Well, you say you know, I've made this argument before to people and they'll go we'll look at the change that social media made in like in
Egypt. They were uprisings. It's like, yeah, they were violent uprising. Yeah, this isn't the these weren't discussed
You can't do anything with this like and I'm not saying she so go out and be
violent because that first of all I don't I'm not suggesting that and second of
all that's also not an option here because they could induct martial law
here in two fucking seconds so you could never you could never take to the
streets the way people used to it's all bullshit this is it just fucking you're
in for the ride and you're fucked and nothing will help you yeah so just try to get
along with your neighbors and just and even that can hardly be done I just I went
over, I bought Joe and I a couple beers to enjoy for the podcast at a liquor store.
And I pulled into this parking spot, you know, there's a giant dumpster that rolls off
its wood block that was keeping it propped up.
And this thing swings into my car real hard, right?
Just like crashes into it, no one around, I was saying I'm not going to sue the liquor store
or something.
But I'm like, what the hell?
I look at, there's this old Asian guy there.
And he comes over and looks at me, he keeps shaking his head.
And he goes, the problem is, there's no accountability.
Yep.
Nobody cares?
You go in now, you say to them, hey, my car,
it got hit by your dumpster, they're not going to care.
The person who messed the dumpster up is not going to care.
Then he's getting really angry.
He starts going on.
He goes apparently the other day somebody walks by with a light Scottish accent was well
I was I was so worried about doing an offensive
Asian accent that I opted on the side of Scottish right yeah, so
He goes walk
Tell you this patty I'm Asian
No, but he went on and on we had a nice conversation, but he was getting matter and matter and something had happened to him recently
You could tell but he was just was like these kids walk by they knock over my trash can
the trash spills out.
They walk off laughing.
They don't even know that I saw them.
Why would they do this?
Why are they doing this?
I'm like, I don't know.
It's just a horrible time to be alive.
Yeah, everybody is just like,
this is the best we can do.
And it is, I think.
Yeah, look, man.
It's sad.
I'm heavy on this stuff right now.
I'm real heavy on this stuff right now.
What makes you what makes you angry on it on a day -to -day basis all this picture break it down to a small I
Tell you what makes me angry as in a day -to -day basis the fact that
The few fleeting moments of happiness. I have each week or found somewhere in a bottle
And then I and then I carry all this guilt about that like I like sure
I should feel bad because everybody around me is some kind of fucking
and asshole that runs through runny and canyon
and eats fucking quinoa three times a day.
You know, it's just, I just got nowhere to fit in.
Those people are miserable too.
It's what they're doing their own stupid thing.
I mean, Christ almighty.
Where's the, where's the action anymore, man?
Nobody takes any risks, nobody has any fun.
It's all fucking stupid.
I, you know, the outrage that people have,
of particularly on social media,
which we've talked about in here too,
about this offends me, that offends me.
I think everyone is just so angry,
and they don't know where to put it,
and they feel like online is a safe space
to kind of bitch about things that are definitely
not upsetting them, definitely not bothering them.
Sure.
And it really drives me insane.
There's a bigger shit to worry about.
Well, I'll tell you this too,
So, you know, I was knocking the social media activists earlier, but I'll tell you, pardon
me, pardon me, does empathize with them or sympathize with them, because I mean, that's
the other side of it is we live in this fucking freak show where if you do try to stand up
against somebody on the right, they will fire shots at you or, you know, come back with
you with some sort of racial onslaught or something just horrible.
Sure.
If you stand up to people on the left,
they'll try to have your job,
they'll try to take your money away from you.
And I mean, it's, you got bullies on both sides.
Nobody feels safe just speaking their mind anymore.
So then it gets reduced to these bullshit platforms
where nobody gets heard, but then nobody gets hurt.
And yeah, I mean, Jesus Christ.
I'm a good person, you know?
I don't have a hateful bone in my body
for a racist bone or a sexist bone or anything like that and I feel terrified to just calmly speak freely
anyway. And I know that I wouldn't be saying anything that would piss people off but you don't know what will piss people off anymore.
I can't even deal with it. I don't know what to do. I don't feel I find myself staying home more because of it.
that's very frustrating yeah it's it's the anger of just you know this might
bleed more into envy but when you see what is being released to the God damn
movie theater every week when you see what's coming out on TV every week when
you look for the past 18 Fridays I've looked at Spotify new music Friday by the
way when did they change release date from Tuesday to Friday when did that happen
Like six months ago that happened it everywhere. Yeah, the music now comes out on Friday and not Tuesday somebody just decided that
I don't like that. I don't like it either. I like a Tuesday it breaks up your week. You have something to look forward to
I got a best buy on a Tuesday when I was a kid. Yeah, I don't need all the fun stuff happening on Friday
This is not because I am old. I believe me. I
Long in there every week and I'm like there's 40 albums here that I would rather
fillet my dick then listen to yeah everything is homogenized now to a point
where I mean you really have to dig to find the good stuff yeah but I mean the
good stuff's out there let's give a little shout out to a band called the
Shrine that I was introduced to this week see now you I think you tweeted about
them and I looked to their Twitter page and they had 300 followers there it's
not a lot of followers. Yeah. Um, but they they're constantly
touring Europe doing huge festivals over there and stuff, which
made me happy that they didn't have a lot of followers. I was
like, here's some guys doing it. And fuck all the bullshit.
They're doing it still. They don't need 150 ,000 Twitter followers.
They're doing it. Right. Um, but I mean, I found them because I went
into old vacation records on sunset. Boulevard stop in there.
If you ever have time, that's not a, that's not a plug with
They don't sponsor us, but I'm just a fan of the store and I said
I love Fumantue
I love deep purple. Yeah
I'm looking for some good old stoner rock. What can you suggest? They said you might like these guys
I brought the album brought it home. I fucking love it and
But you know that that you're not gonna find that on the front page of iTunes or Spotify. I mean you're just not well
I mean Spotify goes pretty deep, you know, and I go all the way to the bottom and I don't see anything Fumantue
for example I just bought some of their old vinyl records I saw them and they
were amazing on a tour but they were playing one of their best albums in its
entirety one of those deals yeah and I love when that happens I was listening to
the lead singer of Monster Magnet Dave Windorf yeah he's on the best show with
Tom Sharplin which is my favorite weekly podcast little plug and he was talking
about how he'll say hey we've got some really awesome new music we're really
excited about it. Um, can we book a date at your theater, your small theater and Oregon
or whatever? I go, no, but you know, I'm looking here, you're about to hit the 15th anniversary
of your big hit album. Maybe if you played that, we could book it. And he's like, if we want
to make any money, we just have to keep churning out the same stuff we've already done that
we know. Oh, the monster rating guy is saying this, this is a hypothetical example. No, he's
saying that's the only way he can make money is he's like, I got to go out and tour an album
that's not in my heart right now.
The album that I love and want to play,
no one will book me even though Monster Mac,
you know, they're not huge, but they got a fan base.
It's pretty good fan base.
And they're a good band.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just a dark time and then people say,
well, look at all these Netflix shows
or look at it, look at that.
Well, the truth is there,
the people get in these shows have huge followings.
As the season's already, it's not some up -shoed.
You know, yeah, maybe that show the characters is cool. That's a cool idea giving 10
10 little comedians are up not little that's so insulting. I love three of them. I don't know the other ones
They're own shot. That's a very cool idea. What is it? I'm at lesser known not little. It's called the characters
It gives each one of these different comedians there. They're shot. I never heard of that. What shows that?
It's called the characters, I have said it's on Netflix.
Don't turn it on me, I've never heard of the show.
You know, there is cooler kind of niche stuff happening,
but as a rule, it's happening with huge people attached to it,
which is no different than anything else.
I don't know.
Yeah, it's sort of that vibe with like the 90s when
And it was like, oh, the undergrounds taking over, but all the bands that were coming
from the underground were still like, you still had to be on Subpop or something like that.
That's exactly right.
We're like Geffen.
And Subpop, for an indie back then, was as close as you could get to a major, and I'm a
fan of the label.
I'm not, that's not a knock.
I'm just saying, that was a huge independent label.
Epitaph records.
Blood, honey, melvins, all those bands, none of them fucking got rich.
It's the bands that used their sound and took it to a bigger level.
Well, it was all the bands that went to there was a Geffen sampler called DGC
Rarity's volume one and it was like yeah, it was yeah, it was obsessed with it. It was like every
Popular band from that movement. Yeah, it was like Nirvana and Kroes were on that yeah with a great song
I'm sign on the beach. Yeah, yeah, jinx by me another 24 ounce paps
Yeah, you know, I'm getting off a little bit here on a tangent and the truth is
Shit does get made, not much gets made without a do -ploss endorsement, an apatow endorsement.
But those people are helping people with creative original visions that might not make
it to the screen in a big way.
Sure.
This isn't anything I'm feeling a great deal of wrath about.
I'm just mad that every time I go to the movies, I'm like, ugh.
Well you loved, we saw 10 Cloverfield Lane the other night, you were floating after
that.
I think 10 Cloverfield Lane the best movie in about six months.
I liked it. I didn't love it as much as you did. I loved Goodman's performance. I loved
Mary Elizabeth Winstead. Yes. One of the saddest things you'll ever hear. Loved her so much
in it. Googled her to see if she was married. Because I thought, what are the, the chances
aren't slim that we might cross paths in this kooky town we live in. The chances are slim
that she would want to spend more time with you. Right. Well, of course. Yeah. She looks
like a regular gal though she does yeah but then you look at her her red carpet
pictures and you realize she's like the hottest woman ever yeah in in movies
you're like oh that's like a normal pretty girl and then you look at like the
red carpet stuff and you're like oh no she's ridiculously hot for sure but I you
know she's somebody I'd like to marry in theory
This is just where I'm at these days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I liked the movie.
I didn't love it.
And I told you primarily because, you know, I'm a big fan of anthology horror and sci -fi
and the premise of the guy in the bunker, is he crazy, is he not, is something really happening
outside, has been done many times on many classic anthology TV shows.
So it wasn't my first rodeo with that premise.
Yes, but they did a good job with it.
I just can't imagine they would have been done that well.
I thought it was a very extremely well -directed,
it was great, well -written, well -shot, tense movie.
And honestly, nowadays, even though I think it's way better
than a competent movie, the movie is competent.
I'm thrilled.
It was done very, very well.
But there are sort of plot devices
is that kind of going along with that story.
So that's where some of the surprise got taken away
from me because I was already thinking like,
they're probably going to do this thing
because that's kind of how this goes usually.
Yes.
Whereas you were massively ignorant to this,
to the existence of this type of story.
I've seen plenty of Twilight Zones.
I know that type of story exists.
I thought it was extremely well done.
It was for every movie you go to see has been done a billion times for the most part. It was well done
But I thought John Goodman
Deserves to win best actor and what is best stock acting role ever which is a hard thing to say because he's always very good
Never less than great and it's like John Goodman not nominated for supporting actor for the Big Lebowski
You know, I don't know how it's possible Jeff Bridges not nominated for the Big Lebowski. I don't know how it's possible
I think this is one nomination is for flight, probably the movie he was his worst in.
Flight where he plays Denzo Washington's drug dealer.
Yeah, but like he was, he went over the top.
He was, he was over the top.
He was good in it.
I liked him.
He was nominated for that though.
I believe so.
It is a very good movie.
It's a movie that I think a lot of people would write off and think of.
You know, oh, that's a mainstream whatever.
But I thought that movie was surprisingly edgy.
and I liked it a lot. Great nudity at the beginning that I wasn't expecting.
Huh? Great nudity at the beginning I wasn't expecting.
Well, that shot of him just staring into her couch as she bends over was mildly disturbing.
I'll tell you what took flight was my penis.
I bet that day you had a bone in your body.
No, I love Denzel Washington in a way that I still get upset when he plays anybody sort
of skeevy or bad.
Sure.
It still upsets me.
I still feel like I'm seeing my dad or my uncle play like a do something mean, you know.
But he's great.
He's great in it.
I preferred, we talked about this the other night and you scoffed at me, but I preferred the
which to ten clover field lane and I don't understand why you don't get the
which but you don't. I don't think that's completely absurd. I thought the
which was massively dull. It had a nice tone and it was shot in kind of a
cool way as well. Maybe if I watched it again with subtitles it would help
because I had no idea what anyone was saying. And I didn't care, frankly. That's
a shame. And then you know the 10th time they did a slow zoom on a on a
rabbit's nose twitching I said yeah I'm not I'm not scared right now and my buddy
I saw it with hated it more than I did he said it would have walked out if I
wasn't there with them I love the movie I love the movie I think it's idiotic
what you're saying right now that's fine I said I think you sound like a stupid
asshole it had a couple scary moments it was trying to go for a David Lynch thing
it was nowhere near I didn't get David Lynch from it at all I got just that
feeling of dread. I got William Peter Blattie. I got William Friedkin. I got Kubrick. That's
what I got out of that movie. I mean, that's just crazy. It was very much like the Shining.
The Shining is an extremely slow film and an hour longer than the witch I might add. I
had way more echoes of the Shining and Cloverton Cloverfield. Oh, thank you, fucking asshole.
Which also reminded me of movies like misery die hard
I thought it had a lot of homage misery and die hard. He says yeah now please
Well, she crawls around on the fence. I don't want to spoil too much
I come that's so it reminded you of that's what it took to remind you of die hard
It's essentially the plot of misery a woman wakes up tied chain to a bed
There were little nods to it throughout nobody is nobody's taking issue with the misery comparison
You said die hard and then you also an event forever and you all like this remind
I think the director and the writers and the producers and everybody in that J .J. Abrams camp are always trying to create the feeling of those movies from their youth
80s and 90s movies 70s probably for them Spielberg as well and
Kubrick I think this is as good a job as they've done with it
Have a lot better than super eight which you claim to like I love super eight
They wanted to make a goonies and they made a goonies
They could have called that goonies, too, and I would have been like yeah, this is the goonies goonies is wildly overrated part
Well, yeah, look I like the goonies, but I just want to I want something on the record
Your honor if this could please be marked in the record
Highlighted with stars and asterisks next to it for any time we have a discussion or a difference about movies
On this podcast. I want our listeners to remember the time you said
10 Cloverfield Lane reminded me more of the shining because I got echoes of misery and
die hard from it.
I don't know, not because of.
I just want everybody to remember that.
That was your argument that it was more like the shining and in an express, you mentioned
die hard.
You're telling them what I didn't say because of is now what I said.
I'm saying it had nods, I think, stylistic nods that the director might even admit to,
to a lot of those 80s.
You know who else crawls around in a vent, Harry Crumb.
You're goddamn right.
Did you get Harry Crumb at a clover feeling?
No, but I did definitely get tired.
Anytime anybody goes up in a shaft, I think of dying.
Well then you think of Harry Crumb.
But I did not think of Harry.
Did you get Bert Wunderstone when the knife was coming through the walls
and almost hitting her in the fucking face?
No, I don't remember Bert Wunderstone.
It was directed by Don Scardina, who's a great man.
I love Don.
He is a great man.
You know Don Scardina?
I do not.
We had a meeting many years ago. He's very nice to me. Yeah, he's great. Uh, here's the thing.
Uh, and this disappointed me slightly. I did read an article on movie web today about 10
Cloverfield Lane and what the original ending was supposed to be. Probably shouldn't say it. It's too
no. It's, I'm not gonna say it. All right. But in discussing what the original ending was supposed to be,
they were describing the current ending and some other things about the current crowning, you know,
It wasn't great for me, but the the the I don't know who the interview is with the writer whoever wasn't with
I don't think it was with JJ Abrams, but the guys just literally going yeah
So this happens in the movie which we ripped from battle Los Angeles
And then this happens which we took from this he's just exciting like yeah
We just took this from this other movie. Yeah, I found that a little disappointing which again back to my rich ripoff battle Los Angeles
It says it in the article it says it in the article but brings you back to my original premise or point
It was a good movie, but there were many things in it where I was like I've seen this already, so I'm not that excited about it
Where's the which I've never seen anything like that in my life?
Have you I've seen it done better a billion. Oh, please
What the village? Oh?
Oh, fuck you, Pat.
Honestly, yeah.
That's idiotic.
Yeah, I prefer the village to the witch.
Okay, everybody please, Fangoria Fanger.
Remember the time Pat Walsh said,
I prefer the village to the witch.
Strongly.
That's, that's Asinine.
That's an Asinine thing to say.
If I go to a movie with a completely open mind
expecting to enjoy it and I'm bored, not scared,
don't like it.
Don't understand a word that's being said.
I'm not gonna apologize and say I did like it
And my buddy hated it more than I did your buddy, you know, I don't know who your buddy is
I talked to numerous people who despised it and then a couple who really loved it and that's fine
Everybody I know liked it because they were able to keep up with it
No, I understood the plot. I'm saying the way they were speaking. I was like, I don't know what's being said. I got used to it
But that's just me, you know, I adapt to an experience. I thought that the girl was a good actor. I thought there were a few effective moments
But at the end of it, I was like, yeah, they were the every actor was unbelievable in it
They had those six -year -old kids speaking like that old English. It was crazy
It was crazy the shit they were pulling off that fucking the little boy
When he's doing that monologue about Jesus. It was like it was one of the best act. It's the only movies ever been
It was one of the best acting things I've ever seen my life. I
Mean we're just coming out of from a different place. No, Christ go watch die harder
You know what you're hearing, folks, is wrath.
Well, you brought it out to me today, babe.
I mean, but like, like, see, you still do that.
When I was like 20 and earlier, maybe even longer than that.
My friends would say, oh, I hated this movie that I loved
and I would wind up screaming or vice versa.
I loved this movie that I hated.
You still do it at age 56.
You still get this upset.
And I respect it. I love the passion.
But now if somebody hates something I love I'm like fine. I'll watch it again
You know what you want don't get me wrong if we were at a cocktail party and you were a lady in a skirt
I wouldn't be yelling like this. I've seen but we're doing a podcast of cocktail parties, but
We're doing a podcast at 4 p .m. No, you have absolutely have not seen that we're doing a podcast at four o 'clock in the afternoon with two
to be on tall boys, I don't know what you call the 24 ounce cans.
Well it is 6 .30, you haven't set your clock forward yet.
And I refuse to.
I'm not playing ball with this daylight savings anymore.
You're just gonna be an hour late to everyone.
I just don't care.
All right.
No, I'll be on time, but I'm just gonna, in my head, I'm gonna say I'm on Deroza Central
time.
All right.
Well, for six months of the year, you won't be rebelling at all.
It'll just be.
That's fine.
Normal.
And then I'll look at that as they finally adapted to me.
Yeah.
But every time I get an email on the west coast, they say house 3 p .m. And I'm gonna say 3 p .m. PST 2 p .m.
MST, which is my standard time
So they know because this is what I'm doing from now on because fuck these people it is it is really stupid
I guess it's it's a farming thing apparently something like that. I don't know
We did a monologue about it on the Pete home show years ago and
Got a lot of hate mail on the behalf of farmers
Well, and it was we were joking obviously they'd be in bed at 12 30 in the morning and wake up at
330 to harvest the grain thought we were safe
We thought it was like making fun of the amish, but apparently no now you I've heard you speak very
Angerly about certain movies you you've yelled at me at a restaurant about enjoying aliens
Which I thought was a universally beloved movie by everyone in the world
But you screamed at me as though I had the craziest opinion by enjoying a
And acknowledged classic. I never screened you about aliens. I said you you said it was superior to the first movie
And that's what I yelled at you about yeah, and then I said I enjoyed Terminator 2 when you were upset about that shit pile that movie
Watch it again. Most people don't think that
Most people are idiots. We just talked about that for the first 30 minutes of the podcast
Most people I know who are not idiots and beyond got news for you. I've been to your parties folks
um good is Juliet Lewis and idiot Joe she was the famous person at the last one
uh Johnny Galecki man Johnny Galecki that has had two parties
he'd homes so I've had both kids from Christmas vacation at my house yeah
Juliet Lewis came to the first one these this is very true she came to the first one
I missed her I missed the second party where I could have gotten some Johnny Galecki
yeah I got that Galeck's who do you think he's gonna show up at the third one
can I throw some I hope that really is Angela when we keep riding round and out
those Griswolds. That'd be great. Yeah. Richard Karn possibly. Oh, Richard kind. Or Richard
kind. Dickie kind. I don't think right. Yes. Yeah. Uh, now my birthday party. Yeah. Uh,
building showed up. Oh, now building is a big, alleged co -cat on the haul. And I used
to go after tape nights over to this place. Dimples karaoke. And he would be there.
A grass -ively alleged leave.
And I saw it, groping the wadruses,
and I'd be like, is he in here every night doing this?
And they're like, yeah, it's a real problem,
but he tips well.
So to dark -town, we live in here.
Going to the bathroom for five minutes,
come out like eyes bulging,
start grabbing wadruses' asses.
Mr. Belling, oh boy.
Dennis Haskins, y 'all.
And everyone was like, I wonder if he hangs out here
across from NBC in the hopes that somebody strolls in,
has a few too many, and offers him
like a Mr. Belding spinoff boy well he showed up at my birthday apparently he
walked in looked around walked out but you know who did hang out for a little
while was uh ex mr. Simpson Nick uh yeah Nick Lachey rolled in for quite
some time where was your party I was at that bar remember oh yeah I remember I saw
Nick Lachey there tiny man yeah yeah yeah I always thought he would be like a big
like kind of like South Philly type and he's not. He's like a little guy.
Jessica Simpson went public saying that he had a very small penis and couldn't
pleasure him. She did? Which, yeah, I thought was a little shocking but yeah.
She just says a giant ass and pussy. We know that that's possible.
It's anything's possible. Well look he's a tiny man usually tiny men of big
hogs but I wouldn't be surprised if he's told me he only had a little button on him
Because he was so small.
Usually tiny men have big hogs.
I think that's usually the way, you know, nature kind of does it, you know, that you're
a short guy that give you something to throw around.
I'm a tall guy.
I have very average penis.
Now when I was building two, before we get into your smut any deeper, was that something
that seems to upset you and a lot of people that never bothers me.
I was talking to a woman at work today.
She's great.
I have no issue with her at all.
But she was talking about 10 Cloverfield Lane.
She was like, I loved it so much.
And me and my daughter on the edge of our seat,
and I had the best time.
And she's like, but that ending just ruined
the whole thing for me.
That is not an outlook I've ever had in my life.
If a movie keeps me under a spell for 90 minutes
and in the last 10, they do something stupid.
It never pisses me off.
You seem to get pissed off by a bad ending.
Endings are hard.
I get that you can be let down by it, but I don't forget the 90 minutes that came before if I love it
If it gets away from itself
Anywhere in the third act amount and that's a lot of fucking movies. I'm out
And I will tell you I wasn't crazy about the end of 10 Cloverfield Lane
It seemed a little too was crazy about it convenient. I agree
That's what I you know when I read the tweeted about I said goodman was perfect. The movie was almost when I read the original
original, original ending. I was like, oh, this is much better. But yeah, I didn't,
I didn't fully care for, for the ending. It was, did they say the studio said, do a
different ending? Or who made that? I didn't read that part. I just read what it was originally
in the script. But I mean, there's a great twilight zone with Joe Montana, it's from the
80s twilight zone, where he builds a bunker. There's a guy, his neighbors in the bunker with
them. He same kind of thing. He's like kind of psychotic. He
won't let anybody in. He won't let anybody out. That doesn't
seem like a good role for Joe Montana. Yeah, to me. He's
good at it. All right. He's good at it. Did you mean Joe
Montana? No. Okay. But I'm glad you resurfaced a joke from
Joe Montana's SNL monologue in 87. I swear to God, that's a joke
they do. Alright, well, a little kid wants to leave. And
they dad goes, I'm sorry, my son thought Joe Montana was hosting
and he's like, can I talk to you, kid?
Yeah.
And the dad's like, sure, he pulls the kid backstage
and he's like, I play a lot of bad men in movies.
It's not an act.
I suggest you stay and watch the show.
It's really funny.
That's good.
Anyway, anyway, same type of thing, and then the guy,
there's even the part where the guy's like,
I hear people out there.
We got to go.
We got to get saved.
Joe Montana's like, you can't go out there.
The guy runs out, Joe Mantini is like, you're out, fuck you, you're dead, whatever.
And then in the end, it cuts to the outside world, and there's a tour group in front of
a huge dome.
Yeah.
And the tour guide says, this dome was built in memory of the buildings and the people that
were here before the bomb hit.
that the dome itself is containing the remaining nuclear fallout or whatever.
So you realize, Montana, when he heard the people upstairs, it was them building.
He could have escaped.
He doesn't.
And now he's sealed into this thing forever.
And his meters all say, it's dangerous outside because it's all been sealed in.
To me, that was such like a great twist on the ending.
Yeah.
And it's more of a TV ending than a movie ending, I realize.
But yeah, I have a feeling with this with this 10 Cloverfield lane
There were like we've spent three million dollars on this blockbuster movie like that movie costs nothing until the end
You know like again again, I don't want to spoil anything but like they probably I guarantee the studio was like
You can't call this Cloverfield get people's expectations up for action and then deliver this like very tense little
Three -character chamberpiece with no big stars because
You know it's not an indie movie. Well, I think the movie still could have ended similarly to the way it ended
Yeah, I just thought they could have it could have had a little more depth
Yeah, no, I'd read the ending yeah, like I said wasn't my favorite, but what do you know, you know Pat what can you do
What else is pissing you off because we're gonna wrap this up in a few because we're gonna do two today guys
And we know there were some complaints about the length of the last one you missed these two -hour marathon
on fucking talk sessions.
And then somebody today was like,
hey, I thought if you guys were only doing it for an hour,
at least we could get it once a week or something.
It's like, hey, just be happy you're getting it at all, baby.
Listen, I'm very flattered.
Thank you so much for all of your comments.
It's very nice.
That never makes me mad.
No.
But these are gonna probably be around 50 minutes today
because we have to do two
because I'm going on tour for three weeks.
Yeah, we're trying to bang them out,
which I should plug, I guess, right?
Okay.
Yeah, maybe when we're done.
Hey, nothing else really pissing me off, Joe.
Well, we talked about how much I hate social media.
We talked about how much I hate your opinion
on many movies.
I think it was just the witch.
Talked about how much I hate politics
and the people that believe in it.
Talked about how the arts seem to be at a real low point.
Talked about the lack of accountability out there.
I mean, these are my big ones, you know?
This is, this is, I mean, I have huge bits
about this in my act right now.
I mean speaking of a of accountability Joe had a dog walk or the other night and the dog got out lost my dog
You know the dog is back now and we're all very relieved, but like you can't trust anyone to do a good job with anything
You know, it was a very traumatic experience and the the reason was he left the front door open in the dog right now
I was like, well, what did you do that for?
The answer was I don't know
Yeah, I mean there's nothing you can do. It's like dealing with
This is the problem these days.
It's like, you know, I hate to reference Cosby,
given the current climate of things with the man.
But he has that thing on Bill Cosby himself
where he talks about kids and he's like,
they just say I don't know everything.
Yeah.
And it's like that's how infuriating that is.
And that's what adults do.
And so the part part is is we're living in this time
where nobody has to be accountable
and everybody can just be like,
I'm sorry, I didn't know any better.
When you know they did, yet it's also the time
where if you hit somebody you're more, I mean the lawsuits are going to fly at you faster than anything.
So there's no more like let's just go duke this out please because you're really fucked up and then
there's also no more just admitting to stuff. People have found the life loophole where they're able to
just go oh you can't do anything to me and I can just say I don't know and that's it. And the internet
internet is fostering it. Everybody says glaringly obvious, soothing, everyone agrees with
your opinion things all day. Then you get back all this feedback of people going,
I agree with your very obvious boring opinion that everybody thinks. Right. And then
you're like, ah, yes, we all agree. Everybody, everything's cool. Then when one person attempts
to say something different, original. I disagree, whatever else.
People can't handle it and almost force them off the internet.
Now, granted, if that's something is hate speech, that's not good.
But people having a different opinion than yours is not fucking hate speech.
And it's often regarded that way.
You don't feel like me and all of my friends who share my exact same opinions
and feel about this topic, and therefore you're a monster.
We got all slams, but it's not the case.
And that's my point about the pendulum swinging.
When Bush was in office, the big joke was that all
of his supporters and everybody that was on his side,
and the criticism of them and the joke about them
was that these fucking people all hang out with each other.
They have the same opinion.
They don't want any outside views coming in.
If they do your trader, your treasonist,
you're against America.
Those people that were all complaining about that are now the people saying if you don't
agree with us then you're a sexist or you're a racist or you're that you can't win on
either side.
No.
You can't call the assholes assholes, you can't call the dickheads dickheads, you're just,
you're just, you can't talk to anybody about anything anymore, there's no gray area.
No.
And then you and I, dear friends, our friendship has with stained many arguments, some small
some miners say many I think there's been one or two but I'm I'm saying us arguing about the
witch is an argument that's what I'm saying all right we have a more contentious friendship than
most of my friendships but that's what I love about it and now you and I are both horror fans both
movie fans I wouldn't very excited to see the witch I didn't feel the same you and I butt heads
on it you think I'm an idiot you y 'all fuck you at me but I know that you that we're fine and
And that sort of discourse should be happening a lot more.
And it doesn't.
If I was talking to people, and I'm like, ah fuck you, 10 chlorophyll lane was awesome.
You know, people get shaken up by it because everyone has become massive, massive pussies.
Oh yeah.
And actually, you telling me, you speaking this passionately about the witch, we usually
agree on a lot of things.
It makes me feel to myself, okay, maybe when the witch comes on cable, I'll check it out
again.
Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe I should watch it with subtitles.
These arguments can lead to maybe change in your opinion, maybe helping you see things in a different way.
I don't have to be the end of the world.
Joe loved the witch. I didn't like the witch.
Are we still friends? Yes.
And I have frightened a few people with my opinion.
Yeah, sure. I'm a rough around the edges.
You know, I'm old school.
But that's fine. That's what I love.
I was going to say one other thing about the...
Shit about the people the people. I don't know anymore. I don't know anymore
It's an upsetting time now wrath in the movie seven was when he killed John
Don't that's why I made the confusion when he kills Kevin Spacey John
Don't yeah, yeah, yes, that's it completes the cycle so that was just it like that
They're they're filing him murdering a man as anger. Yeah, okay cool what a
well but I mean it is and it literally is the the truest definition of
wrath that's feel my wrath see that's I guess that's what I was saying for a
movie man then that for to be a mainstream blockbuster movie that's a pretty
hardcore ending I watch seven once a year my thinking is okay that was one of the
first R rated movies I saw I couldn't watch until late I was probably 14 or
something and I'm always like our movies not much worse now and the answer just
simply is yes. It's not because we were kids and movies seemed better. Right. And there
was shit coming out of that time too. I think the same week, seven was out Congo wasn't
these. But with the fucking Tim Curry and the apes. Right. But it's just seems like a really
bad time in seven in terms of a screenplay as such a fascinating and dark and perfect
screenplay. And there's a movie where the ending you're like, holy lord, a. That was
completely unexpected and be the absolute perfect ending for this movie.
And that sort of thing just doesn't happen anymore.
No, it doesn't.
It doesn't.
And as much as I can say, chlorophyll lands affair movie in a few months, I really, really
loved it.
And I really did.
And with scared the whole time, when it ends, I'm kind of like, all right, it ended bad
and I figured it would.
And what are you going to do?
Because that's what everyone's doing.
They're like, eh, what are you going to say?
It is what I can tell you.
I found the original ending to be it's not as dark about that as seven
But it was a little more along those emotionally satisfactorily missed had a dark as shit fucking ending
And you know the crazy trivia about that. That is not the end of the story. Yeah, no, I know the story
They just drive into the mist and you don't know what happens. Yeah, they were like let's put an ending on this thing
And I stick with people. I saw some interview with Darebot and he was like, you know, it was Iraq and Bush and the world was so dark
I just wanted to dive right into how bad I was feeling at the time and things have gotten significantly worse
Yeah show everybody follow me. Joe Derosa comedy on Twitter. I'll pat at the Patrick Walsh
On Twitter. I'm coming your way possibly. I'm barking on a three -week tour
Starting Wednesday March 16th
this might or may not be out by then, I don't know, but if it is, look here are the dates.
The 18th of 19th, I'll be in Wilmington, North Carolina. I believe the 22nd. I'm in Greenville,
South Carolina. I think that's a Tuesday, that Thursday I'm in Hattiesburg, Mississippi,
the next night I'm in Lafayette, Louisiana, that Saturday night I'm in New Orleans, Louisiana,
And then the following Tuesday through Saturday, I'm at Acme Comedy Club in Minneapolis, Minnesota so come on out doing the new hour ramping up to
Something special with this one so come check it out. I
Will be performing with the thunder from down under all male nude review at the Mirage hotel in Casino from June 12th to June 19th.
The 19th is a very special night because I'm going full dick.
yeah so please come out show your support when I take that deck out I'd love to
have a lot of fans showing at the respective deserves. Go see it it is a sight
to see you've been listening to we'll see you in hell it's a presentation of
the Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail executive produced by Ken
Hanley a Fangoria entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiries
and information about we'll see you in hell contact Ken at Fangoria .com
See you later, bye guys.