Hey, folks, it's we'll see you in hell. The podcast you turn to
hear fucking Christ. Keep going. When you want to hear a movie talk. I couldn't even get that out.
Jesus God. It might be time for me to take over those reins. I mean, let's be real. You got it.
You got the job. I don't want to do it anymore. All right. All right. I'll put in the necessary
rehearsal hours that you refuse to do for our openings. Yes, folks, this is we'll see you in
hell. We're talking today about the empty man, which is steadily becoming. I think cult classic
is a little extreme, but I've noticed it getting a cult following. They dropped it on HBO Max. Also,
I spoke about it dismissively on here before I saw it. I was thinking of it as like the bye -bye man,
slender man. I was just associating it with that shit. And now having seen it, it's much different
and much better. I assume movie. I never saw those other two, but a really interesting movie
that we'll talk about in a bit. Joe, what's new with you? Old friend. So in between episodes,
I went. So this Instagram account called turned yellow turns people into Simpsons drawings.
It's a fan. I guess it's I don't think it's run by anybody that's actually with the Simpsons,
but anyway, they DM to me and they're like, can we do? Would you? Can we do one of you?
And I'm like, of course. Thank you. Pick whatever picture you like. And that I'm flattered. Thank
you. So they sent it to me today and it was pretty cool. And I was excited and I posted it.
And the comments under this thing, it's just what is wrong with everybody? What are the,
what's the issue? What are they saying? Some of them were funny. Like it doesn't look self loathing
enough. Like those ones are funny. Okay. There's 87 fucking the shoulders are wrong.
Why does he have shoulders? But those are half funny. It's just, it's where does that come from?
Who started the, you don't have shoulders thing, Patrice O 'Neill. Okay. And then it was, it was
around the seller for the first five years that I was in New York. And then it leaked to ONA when
I started to go on ONA. And then that was over after that. Yeah. So the shoulders thing is,
it's followed me forever and it's, it is what it is. There's another siren coming by for this
episode. That's good. Have you considered implants or Paula Poundstone style? Just,
you know, slip some pads in your sleeves. I do squat on a stool these days on stage
and wear a tie. So I should just add the shoulder pads. No, but the,
so the shoulder comments are whatever it is. It's part of the course, but then the ones that
there's ones that are just like epic fail. What, you know, this sucks. Why isn't your hair curly?
It's like, what is wrong with everybody? What is wrong with everybody? This is on Instagram,
by the way, it's not even Twitter. Now, remember when it used to be, you'd see that shit on Twitter
and everybody on Instagram was like, Oh, your vacation looks so fun. That would be the credit
you got. It's just fucking miserable everywhere. Everybody's miserable. There's no other way to
slice that. So anyway, bad time. It's a bad time. I mean, I, I've stopped essentially posting anywhere
and you feel better when you do it. You know, I just watched the scream trailer.
Yeah. You're not missing much, Joe, but I didn't have a chance to say, damn it. I forgot. We said
we were going to do that. No, it's I'll walk you through. I mean, it starts with an unknown
actress to me anyway, getting the phone call. Hello. You know, same voice, same guy, same voice.
Sounds a little older. Sounds like he's, he's been through some shit through the years, but yeah,
you know, she's like, wait a minute. How did you know my landline is ringing? You know, like it's
already like, they're just taking extra steps that don't need to be there. It's clunky as hell.
Nobody has a landline anymore, but she opens the door. The guy slashes her and then it's like,
scream is back. So they cut to Neve Campbell, who's jogging, of course, around a reservoir,
as these characters always do when they get that call that things are happening again.
And she goes, they go, do you have a gun? David Arquette asks her because why wouldn't you ask
that question? Do you have a gun? And she basically into camera says, of course I do.
I'm Sidney Prescott. And it's like, I mean, look, I'll keep an open mind. I already saw Scream 4
and Scream 3 and this, this franchise, you know, it's already kind of limping along.
This was the plot of four, wasn't it? That after all these years, it comes back for her.
Yeah, exactly. But for her to say, well, this one, it looks like she's coming to town to help a new
group or something. But of course I have a gun. I'm Sidney Prescott is like that. Who is that line
for? Who is it to that? That's, that line is strictly for the viewer. It's like, we're not
even giving it the slight effort of making it appear that it's happening in the real world.
Uh, it looked, it looked boring. It looked lethargic to me. It's Cox and her running around and
you know, it's like the wisecracks suck. Like she goes, Hey, are you ready for this?
And Courtney Cox goes for this never. Cox, by the way, plastic surgery to the point that she now
resembles the actual ghost face mask. I said, look, we got two ghost faces here. And then my
eyes kind of adjusted. That's a novel twist, two ghost faces, but, um, no, it's the same.
Have I talked on this podcast yet about the Nicole Kidman AMC thing? Um, that show that is
the exact same thing as the other show. We kind of talk. No, no, no, no. When you see it now,
I'm an AMC Stubbs member. And now before every movie, there's like a two to three minute
infomercial type thing where it's Nicole Kim and walking up the stairs of an AMC
and narrating it. I mean, I of course was reminded of her because we're talking about
horrifically botched faces, right? She's walking up the stairs and then the narrations like the
movies are back at AMC week. You know, it's, it's a disgrace. And then they show her sitting
in a theater and they cut to what they're watching. And at first it's a clip of,
professional boxing. Like it's not even a movie clip. So she's like, we come to cheer on our
heroes to be scared. And then it's like her biting her nails. I mean, it's, it's just awful.
It makes me not want to go to the movies. It has the exact opposite effect of what it's supposed
to have. I'm the, I'm in the regal club. Yeah. For no reason greater than the, the, the title
AMC stubs has always grossed me out for some reason. It's got a Porky's ring to it. Something's
weird about that title. But I'm in the regal club. And when I go, they have one of those videos,
but it's a character. It's not a celebrity. Like it's a character talking about like the movies are
great. Again, he's called like captain watch them all or something. And he's like an explorer that
like watches every kind of movie. And I would have liked to see Nicole Kidman as captain watch
them all with a hat and a cloak kind of, um, did I tell you, I, I must have told this story
when I went to regal, one of the first times I went back and I was at the counter buying,
you know, an $8 and 50 cent water. Sure. And, uh, the, uh, the girl behind the counter goes,
would you like to just make it an even nine to donate to donate to, to regal?
Are you who it was? I think it was, yeah. Like support your theater. Like, like it's like,
it's some mom and pop or something. I was like, are you crazy? I'm already doing a $14 pin on
M and M sweetheart. Exactly. Take it out of that. Exactly. Which by the way, Sal made a claim
yesterday that Reese's peanut butter cups are readily available in every movie theater. I have
never seen them once in a movie theater. I don't think I've seen them either. Uh, AMC carries a
very delicious Reese's mix, like a checks mix type thing with, with all kinds of different things
in the bag, but I've never seen the, I've seen, I've seen pieces and I've seen the snack mix.
I've never seen the cups. What's in the snack mix, the pieces and like pretzels. Yeah. It's pieces,
pretzels. It's a salty, it's a sweet. It's very good. All right. All right. I'm listening. I'm
Stubbs is very good about giving me like perks. So you'll have like $10 added to your account
out of the blue and you know, why not? I, for a while there, when I was, uh, not, not exactly
thriving, I would buy the small bottle of Jack Daniels and a large diet Coke and pour the bottle
into the large thing of diet Coke. I don't do that so much anymore. I try to have a little
respect for my, myself. Um, but yeah, I, uh, I don't think scream looks good. They can prove
me wrong. We've got several months till January, but I don't have the highest of hopes after seeing
that. Uh, it's a tough time. I mean, we got over the next couple of weeks, I'm going to see bond
tomorrow night and IMAX, which I'm very excited about, but this three hour runtime is really
sticking in my craw. I mean, I, I just rewatched the, the Craig ones and like casino Royale is so
awesome. I forgot how good it was. And then like, as, as you go, they get longer and there's just
like, he's like sad all the time. It, I don't get it. It's just this sad, miserable bond,
like looking out at the ocean. And, uh, I hope this one remembers to include some action. That's
off. So I guess they pulled out all the stops. It sounds like Cavill is in the running for the,
to be the next one.
And I really didn't go with it. I thought that they would go with them. It's time and it's not a, um,
you know, it's not the old, like we're trying to be controversial thing. He'd be perfect in the role.
He'd be a great, uh, I don't know. I don't, I'm curious to see what they do. Did you, um, or
aren't we ready for a Jane Bond? I'm sure it's been discussed. Yeah. Yeah.
Emily Blount is Jane Bond. I was talking with Joe this week because they had, well,
I don't know how we've, we've haven't talked about this, but, uh, hell raiser, the new one,
also David Gordon green is, uh, who's doing Halloween kills. It's a female pinhead.
And I'm all for this blind casting and everything else, but it's really hard to wrap my head around
that. And then Clive Barker's like, that's how the character was intended all along.
Well, I will say this. I will say this. I, first of all, I received that text when I was in the
middle of driving. That's why I didn't respond initially, but I will say this in the hellbound
heart, the original novella, the main centibyte is not pinhead. In fact, he doesn't even have pins in
his head. He has shards of glass instead of pins. Um, it was redesigned for the movie. The main
centibyte is the female centibyte that has the wire, like through her cheeks in the first two movies.
She's more of the leader. That's why if you watch the original hell raiser,
pinhead, they both talk like it's not like pinhead is the guy. It's in the second movie. All of a
pinhead is the guy because everybody just like loved it, loved the character. So there is truth
to that. I don't think it should be a female pinhead. Make it that other character, like make
it a different centibyte. It's, it's, you know, to go, to go back to the, to the, when I was bitching
about the Kevin Smith, he man stuff, it's like, I don't have a problem with you doing a masters of
the universe show that's based around this Tila character, but don't call it he man and the masters
of the universe. So why does this character just have to be a genital switch on a male character?
Just make it the other character and be like, we're not going to do pinhead. We're going to
follow the book a little bit more closely. Um, also it's a fool's errand to try to recreate pinhead.
Like it's just not going to work. It didn't work with Freddie. It's not going to work with pinhead.
They've tried it with pinhead. It didn't work in two movies. So, um, you know, so hopefully that's
what they do. But, um, but yeah, it's just the, the, I have a joke about it on stage with like,
you know, how about create some new characters, like put some effort into these solutions. Like
it's, it's so insulting. It's such a bandaid fix to just take, you know, Batman or whatever.
And then all of a sudden he's just, you know, now we, now it's gay Batman or what,
you know what I mean? Just make a new character. Well, that's, that's the news this week. So when
they say that Superman is bisexual now, that's not canon. It's just one comic book that has him as
a bi Superman or what? It's his son. They just, they're designed in a lab basically to upset
nerds. These, these news announcements come out every day. And then of course, then Fox news gets
and it's, this is what they're trying to do to our children, a bisexual Superman.
I, unless I'm mistaken, it's one comic book, right? They're not making it like,
that's the new thing, right? It's his son. It's not Superman. It's John Kent,
John Kent. So I guess that's super, I don't, that's not even super boy. That's super boys
different. Um, so it's his son. So I guess his son. Yeah. No, I think that's like the permanently
for the character now. Like the new Robin is, is by, okay. Robin's always been by them. He
might not have been out, but in my mind, he's always, I agree. I agree. They really toughened
him up on the Titans TV show. Yeah. You know, they got rid of the green booties, right? Right. Right.
And the boy shorts, but at one time, I think Marlon Wayans before it became Chris O'Donnell,
the world's most boring actor, I think Marlon Wayans was going to be Robin. And then I guess
decided to just make him a boring white guy. But yeah, he was for Tim Burton's third. Yeah. Yeah.
There's a great story. Tim Burton's told it in endless interviews about that, where he,
where he's pitching. He's with Keaton and they're pitching the third movie. Yeah. And he said,
the executives start going like, Tim, you don't want to make another one of these. Are you tired?
Don't you want to do whatever? Right. And then finally Tim Burton goes, you don't want me to
make this movie, do you? And that was what it was. So they could go turn it into Batman forever. That
fucking travesty. Yeah. I was weird. I've never heard that story. But yeah, I was telling Joe,
you know, I'm sure Michelle Myers and Betty Krueger cannot be far behind, you know, and
look, there is no notable female horror icon to my, am I, am I wrong here? There's witches,
of course, but I can't think of like a great female horror icon, unless you,
maybe you want to talk about Linda Blair, but that was possession. No, there there's, yeah,
Linda Blair, you know, that's certainly one of the faces you see on the collage poster is,
is Reagan from The Exorcist. That's kind of it. Like, you know, I agree. I think there needs to
be one. And I think every time they do it, or excuse me, every time they attempt to do it,
they fuck it up with still in some way, victimizing the woman,
you know, like, no, even I was going to say monster, but that's a true story. But like,
even in that, it's like, she's a victim of men, and then she becomes a serial killer. Like,
it's never just, yeah, man, like, like, you know, and I guess, I guess I shouldn't talk,
because I'm working on a thing right now about that centers on a female character. And there is
an aspect of her being wronged by men in it. So I do find that interesting. So I saw a hypocrite,
I guess, right now. But yeah, it's there should be there should be an icon to me. That's just
it's a it's a lady that kills people. And she's got a fucked up face or something. And right. And
why does she do it? Because the town's people threw her into a well or something, for some reason.
Yeah, I mean, there's there's Kathy Bates in Misery. But that's, you know, it always is just
a regular woman like our buddy Scotty Landis wrote Ma. And that was an attempt and a fun attempt.
At doing sort of a female horror lady, but it's always just a lady. You never get like the,
you know, the Freddy Krueger or the somebody who's got a big legend behind her. And it's time.
They tried with they tried with Darkness Falls. It didn't stick. They tried with Dead Silence. It
didn't stick. Yeah. Well, Dead Silence was a puppet, wasn't it? Yeah. But it's a lady that
it's like a witch behind all the puppets that are right with children's souls into them or
shit like that. It's a terrible movie. But but a cool premise. I'd love to see a good old
like, yeah, like, like a witch, you know, like a creepy fucking witch. Yeah.
That comes in your dreams or some shadow. No. Yeah, it's time for a good old fashioned witch
and the witch. For some reason, wasn't it? You know, there wasn't like a memorable
witch character in that. No. So we go to the corner, Joe, the movie corner, if you will.
Sure. Let's do it. Let me see. Hold on. There was something I wanted to mention. Give me one
second. Sure. I want to see if. Oh, oh, this is perfect. I'll do it in the movie corner. I
got a new mean old bitch. Oh, great. Rex Reed's review of Free Guy.
Well, I hope he hated it because I know I did. I keep seeing that hailed like I'm seeing Oscar
talk for Free Guy. This movie is a D, folks. Did you say D? Yeah.
It's not we talk about it. I just remember talking about how much you thought it was stupid.
Yeah, no, I don't know if I did talk about it on the show, but I despised it. And it's it's like
they give roles sizable. I mean, not supporting, but pretty big roles to these like PewDiePie
types, the kids who do like game commentaries on YouTube. There's some of them in the film.
Then they cut to at one point, Chris Evans, Captain America, like free guys, like let me call
a friend real quick and calls Chris Evans. The theater exploded into like applause and
cheers when they saw him. And I described it as being like Travis Bickle in Taxi Driver when he
over the TV because couples are dancing and he can't understand them and he can't relate.
I just looked around this theater like I don't want to be a part of the society anymore.
But in what what is the context of him calling? He's playing Captain America,
like because it's Disney and they own everything. Now there's a lightsaber gag. Captain America
makes an appearance. It's like they're doing the fucking Ready Player One shit in Free Guy.
I'll say this really quick, really quick because it relates directly.
It'll count as a sort of movie corner thing. I started finally watching The Letterman Show
on Netflix. I enjoyed it very much. David Letterman's a pleasure to watch and it's really
lovely getting to see him sit in a real interview setting and actually talk to people. What's the
best one? What should I watch? I watched Tina Fey and maybe Jay -Z, I think. I loved the Obama one.
It was so cool to see what I consider to be our last charismatic president because then you got
Trump who was very boorish or charming I should say is a better word because Trump's got charisma
but he's boorish and gross, whatever. And then you got Biden who I believe is a hologram at this
point. I don't think the person exists. So it was just great to see a president in that casual
setting. I don't remember ever seeing anything like that except for when Clinton did like Arsenio
but that was before he was president. And Obama is really fucking funny, man. He breaks Letterman's
balls in the way a comic would. He's making fun of his beard and he's like, you got a staff
somewhere to go with that thing? I was like, Jesus, he's fucking funny, man.
They always say the whole reason Trump ran for president was Obama breaking his balls at that
White House Correspondence Dinner and making great funny jokes about him and they cut him in the
audience fuming and apparently that's the moment he decided to run. That's amazing.
I know, I know. Out of spite, a spite presidency. But I watched, I'm bringing it up because I like
the show, but I watched the Robert Downey Jr. one and at one point Letterman, when he introduces
him, refers from his Mr. Box office, which is true. They talk about how he's come to the end
of the Marvel thing. Robert Downey Jr. says, you know, look, it might sound a little arrogant or
whatever he goes, but I don't mean it this way. I think I'm pretty much in a position where I could
do whatever I want now, which he can. Yeah. And Letterman goes, would you, would you do like a,
if the story spoke to you, would you do like a million dollar picture? And Robert Downey Jr. goes,
million is tough. Right. I like that honesty. Yeah. And then he turns to the audience and goes,
that's my dry cleaning bill. Like it makes that joke. Sure. Which is funny, but like,
I do appreciate the honesty, but it's like, what, how much more do you need?
No, I know. You made it like go make, go do an awesome small thing that like will still get seen.
By the way, you'll make it back at the box office, pal. You're Robert Downey Jr.
And then it's these little movies that got him where he is. He did kiss, kiss, bang, bang. And
then Favreau was like, I'd love to see this guy as Iron Man, you know, like that's, they forget it
quickly. You know, they get dazzled by the money. I have a couple of friends in this business who are
multi, multi, multi, multi millionaires. And they'll complain about not having money and needing
to work. I won't name names, but I said to the one guy in particular, what the fuck are you talking
about? Like you have more money than you know what to do with what are you talking about? And he goes,
no, I, unfortunately, my wife and I started living like people who have a shitload of money.
And then you have to keep up that lifestyle. And then you're scrambling. Like me, I'd always want
to keep my overhead low. When I made good money, I saved it. And that's why I'm not scared to death
that I haven't worked in two fucking years. But it's like, yeah, I think that's what they do. They
just start living and going bigger and harder and like, okay, we need the five gardeners instead of
one. And you just got to keep up that lifestyle. And then you never do anything good and interesting
again. He owns. He owns it occupies with his wife. Who is a lawyer, by the way, in Hollywood. So
they're both making good money. But she produces his shit, too. Yeah, yeah. She was his handler on
a movie. Yeah, because he was so fucked up. And he said they start the date. And then finally,
she was like, Look, it's the drugs are me. And he got sober. Yeah. But uh, but they live on a,
like a huge farm that has like, they just rescue all these animals and stuff. They're not all
rescues with it. They got like llamas and shit. Yeah. And it's hilarious because they're walking,
they show footage of it. They're walking around at one point and let them in every question. He's
like, he's like, No, what is this thing? And Rob Jones years like, um, I think it's um,
and he's, he's trying to make it look like he has. He's, you know, such a big party for these
animals. Yeah. At one point, he starts naming them to his wife in the audience and they cuts
her and she's shaking her head. And he goes, am I getting the names all wrong of the animals? And
she goes, yeah. And he's like, sorry, hon. Anyway, when I was doing Chaplin or whatever the fuck they
were talking about, right? Anyway, I guess there was that judge movie with it with Krumholtz in a
little role. And other than that, has he even done anything that wasn't a giant budgeted
spectacle? I mean, there was, it's like in his downtime from Marvel, he did fucking do little.
It's like, dude, don't you want, don't you want to be in things that are good and challenge
yourself? And I guess not. You know, so I don't know. He's a brilliant actor. Um, yeah, he's
great. He's great. But he's, he's a, well, he, he doesn't follow the scripts at all. Right. Yeah.
He says, he thinks that there's always room for improvement, which is such a fuck you to an actor
like that. Yeah. Uh, he said that he went in, he told a story about going into Chaplin and goes,
he goes, I go to Dickie Attenborough and Letterman laughs at like the audacity to call him Dickie
Attenborough. And, but he's not kidding. He's like, cause I'm Dickie Attenborough. Right. And
how this movie should be. And this is what you've left out. And he said, like Attenborough was like,
indulged him to do a read through of his version. Uh, and then just at the end of it went,
okay, great. Everybody. Uh, we'll see you with my script on Tuesday. And, uh,
wow. Fuck yourself.
That's crazy. I mean, I just saw circling all week on Twitter, bro. They had the succession
premiere. I'm, I'm excited. I love succession, but, uh, Brian Cox, star of trick or treat
is saying, you know, like the writer is the only thing he's like, I I've been working in this
business for such a long time. I know now that the script is the key, the writer is king.
And he goes, and, uh, I gotta tell you the, the UK values the writer about a million percent more
than the U S he's like, it's embarrassing how little respect and regard they have for the writer.
And boy, is that true. I don't know if the UK is, is I, I assume, I guess it's better, but like,
man, it just, they're nothing here. We're like below the line at this point. You know, we're,
we're the crew, which I support the crew fully. It's just like, you almost don't have much say
at a certain point. They think that writing it, I don't know, they don't have any respect for it
because they don't understand it. It's a shame. Yeah. So I hope the Otsi, by the way, the crews
get what they deserve. When I was coming into work at 8 AM and leaving at 9 PM,
my life was a living hell, but the crew had already been there for two hours when I showed up
and they were there for an hour after I left. And they're the people who make these things happen
and they deserve everything they're asking for. Uh, I agree. And there's been some excellent points
made about like the waste that goes on on these sets and how the product suffers. And it's, it's,
this needs to spread to everything, to craft services, to all of it. It is an exorbitant
waste of fucking money and time. Yeah. And it's money that could be on the screen for sure.
Uh, let me, let me take you to the movie corner because I really want to showcase
my favorite movie of the year. Although it's, it hasn't exactly been a banner year,
Titan, uh, a movie that I saw. It's, it's from the lady who did raw, which we taught,
which we reviewed on this show and both really enjoyed the cannibal movie. Uh, Julia do Cornell.
This is her follow -up. She's got more money and it is just an amazing, amazing movie. It starts,
I mean, for, for almost an hour, it's pure horror. It's this lady who is in a car accident or as,
as a little girl and gets, it's never quite explained, but she becomes sort of half titanium.
She's almost like half car, half human. All right. Uh, at some point in the movie,
she fucks a car. Okay. I mean, kind of like Cronenberg's crash, but she's sitting in the back
holding onto two seat belts bouncing up and down. You don't see what's going on,
but it looks like she's being fucked by this car. All right. Um, she is a stripper. She is a very
sort of androgynous, interesting looking woman. She's naked throughout the entire film and she
gets impregnated by the car. Uh, so instead of blood coming out of her throughout is like oil
coming out of her. And look, if you need an explanation as to why this is happening or
what's going on, titane is not going to be the movie for you, but at some point she goes on a
kill spree. These are some of the most grotesque, exciting, violent, disgusting kills I've seen in
ages. My buddy who I saw it with was like, what the fuck was the first hour where she's killing
everybody? And I was like, that was my favorite part of the movie, right? It's an excellent horror
movie. And then it becomes something much deeper and more interesting because she pretends to be
this firefighter who has lost his son. She pretends to be his son. So she tapes her
boobs down. Um, you know, she already looks kind of androgynous, but to basically, to escape
being arrested for her crimes, she pretends to be this guy's son and the two find that they really
need each other. And it becomes kind of a beautiful story, even though it's very disgusting
and very violent. And I've never seen an audience look away more in my life. A lot of people walked
out, but, um, look, if you like the extreme in your cinema, if you liked raw, this movie is
fucking awesome. It's not always realistic. There's a scene where all the firefighters are
shirtless dancing to future Island. Like it's, uh, you know, a gay nightclub. And you're like,
I don't think firefighters do this, uh, in the firehouse necessarily, but it's, it's her vision.
It's a filmmaker that I am so excited to watch. Now you get these, maybe one a year,
you get a filmmaker where you're like, I can't wait to follow this person's career.
I definitely feel that way about Duke Cornell. If you haven't seen raw, see it and please see
titane because I think you're going to love it. I loved it myself. You can go three, three in a row
and then I'll just do mean old bitch. Okay. Uh, well I'll do the Joe Bob. I watched him this week
and he did, uh, terror train, which I had never seen. Jamie Lee Curtis, a good one. Didn't like
it. Got to be honest. I thought the, the, I mean, they, they talked about how Roger Spottis would,
who later directed a couple bond pictures or one bond picture is not a horror guy. Joe Bob just
saying there's no kills in this movie. He doesn't know how to do kills. It's like there's nothing,
but he loves the movie. He gives it a good rating, but, uh, basically he says the guy who came up
with it woke up in the middle of the night, told his wife, I want to do Halloween on a train.
What if we make Halloween on a train? So his wife says, that's the worst idea I've ever heard and
goes back to bed, but he wrote it down on a pad. They got it made. It is Halloween on a train,
but it's nowhere near as good. I, I was, I was pretty let down by territory and I got to be honest
with you. Um, and they also did angel, which I remember seeing the box for, and I also remember
using as jerk off fodder because when I was a kid, I used to just like take a mental picture
of a VHS box and that's what I used to jerk off. You, you youngsters don't know how lucky you have
with the access to pornography, but angel is, keep in mind, I was 10 because this girl's supposed
to be 15. Uh, it's a 15 year old prep school honor student who moonlights as a Hollywood prostitute.
I checked out of this one. I didn't watch it because I was like, this isn't a horror movie,
right? Or is it? It's not a horror movie. Apparently David Gordon green picked it,
which is a very odd choice for a middle -aged man to want to watch angel and acknowledge that
he wanted to watch angel, but, um, it's a serial killers who stalks and murders prostitutes. So she
is kind of going up against him, but it's not horror. The killer is a very weird dude who like
sucks the inside out of an egg at one point, which is a really unsettling scene. Um, there's
good stuff in it. It's kind of a fun trash eighties classic, but there's better versions of this vice
squad. Uh, Linda Blair did a couple of really good kind of movies like this about sort of teenage
then, uh, vengeance angel kind of let me down, but I do recommend watching Jason Bloom and David
Gordon green and Joe Bob. They, they had some really great conversations on this, this Halloween
episode of the show and I liked it. All right. Um, that's it for me, but lamb, the new, the new
one from a 24, I go in hard on, on my, uh, my little solo movie corner, which I'm recording
and I'm going to post shortly, but how little is the most a 24 movie that there has ever been
and they, it's, it's a shame. It's a shameful movie. Uh, how little, how not horror is this
horror movie that they're touting as terrifying and whatever. There's zero horror in lamb. It's,
doesn't work as horror. It doesn't work as anything, but it's a couple who has a baby
who's got a lamb's head, but the rest of it's human. It talks, um, and it's never explained.
It's just never explained. Did the husband fuck a lamb? The only reason you're watching really is
to find out, did the husband fuck a lamb or was the wife infertile? Like what happened? Never
addressed. It is such a dumb and bad movie that has nothing to say. And it's just this big empty
thing shot with the a 24 filter. At this point, it's like they put a filter over the camera to
make it look exactly the same as the other ones. But, um, no, I, I spend quite a bit of time
dissecting lamb. I really, I, a 24, I mean, you heard what I said about Blumhouse on the last
episode. A 24 is right there for me anymore. Like I can't stand this fucking company's product at
all. Yeah. And you know who you never hear mentioned and nobody knows is neon and neon,
I would say has a higher success rate. They put out titanium and you know, they must've gone to
a 24 as well, but, uh, I personally love what neon is doing. I see them lately as more of a sign
of quality, but whatever. So, uh, mean old bitch, here we go. Yes. Rex review. Rex Reed reviews
free guy, a zero star Ryan Reynolds vehicle with zero animation, computer generated action,
forced frivolity and a lack of originality define Ryan rent Reynolds latest nonsensical film,
which I think he means he only makes nonsense. Yeah. Yeah. Another Ryan Reynolds movie is hardly
anything to recommend or write home about, but he's undeniably wholesome looking, nautilus pumped
and camera ready, which is all today's movie industry cares about. True. True. He possesses
enough crude charm to make even a lump of forgettable fluff like free guy and occasionally
tolerable way to waste two hours in the middle of a summer heat wave. That is not a recommendation,
not a, uh, a recommendation at all. No, it's a good start. It sucks. I mean,
it's, it's exactly what it looks like in the trailer. It's Ryan Reynolds who has 14 visible
abs stuttering and stammering. And he's a nerd who can't talk to women. It's like we used to have
Rick Moranis play that part. Yeah. And now it's the best looking man in Hollywood and everyone has
to be amazing looking. I read that big article about Kumail. He had for some reason, three
different articles this week about his body that were released online. And, you know,
they were talking about how he got all jacked for this movie and he thought it would open up
all these kind of like big action star roles for him. But instead it opened up like dad roles
because to play a dad, now you have to be Jack like that. And it's, it's sick. And also I wonder
as a kid, as a kid, I had huge body issues that stay with me to this day, but if you're seeing
Ryan Reynolds playing a guy who's like ugly and can't talk to girls, what does that do for the
self -esteem of an actual chubby kid? It can't be good. I know it's not an even field for men and
women in this department. I know women get away worse with the body stuff, but it is a thing for
men. It doesn't make us feel like shit when, when the nerd is Zac Efron or whatever, you know,
right. You're like, yeah. So, um, anyway, Rex Reed goes on under the, I'm sorry. Oh no,
it's fine. Under the unfocused direction of Sean Levy, a tirelessly prolific director responsible
for an interminable list of gimmicky TV shows and sci -fi flicks, including the horrible night at the
museum franchise and written by the equally unimpressive team of Matt Lieberman and Zac
Penn. The unbearable free guy is another incoherent entry in the current disturbing trend toward
movies about artificial intelligence and alternate realities that take place inside computers. He is
hitting on all cylinders in this thing. Am I Rex Reed? I mean, this feels like how I talk about
every movie I see. This time, Ryan Reynolds plays Guy, a shy, brainless, button -down banker
whose empty life is defined by the same daily routine. Rise early and pale, freshly launder
baby blue pajamas, eat a bowl of tasteless cereal, select the same uniform from the closet filled
with neat rows of baby blue suits. You get the point. This is all because Guy, you see,
is a peripheral character called blue shirt guy in a video game called free guy. So he goes on
about the plot here. I don't want to read his breakdown of the plot. I will skip to the end.
Guy wants to be more than another non -playable character, but it's hard to become a leading
player when the game's inventors are planning a sequel and he's not even going to be in it.
Can he get off the screen and rejoin the real world? Can he bring his consuming passion for
gum ice cream to the video game? Can blue shirt guy find true love with Molotov girl?
The movie makes a feeble attempt to say something satirical about online gaming
and something critical about the evils of capitalism, but every idea is borrowed from
so many other sources from Wreck -It Ralph to Lego movie that you couldn't find a trace
of originality with a microscope. And then it just says free guy in theaters now.
It's honestly refreshing to hear somebody's shit on this movie because you start to feel crazy
when you read all these good reviews of something like this, something that is so shit. I agree with
Mr. Reed. Reed is in for, this is it, dude. He is like, this is it. He's out for blood, dude. He's
out for vengeance. Holy shit, that's fucking funny. Jesus Christ. He's on the money. Folks,
we're talking today about the empty man and no, it's not a story of me and my life. It was based
on a graphic novel. It stars James Badge Dale, who I guess had a little part in the departed.
You recognize him. He's a character actor. And then Steven Root would be the other actor that
you know as sort of a cult leader. The movie had a very troubled development. So apparently
they went, shot a bunch of it in South Africa. And during the final week of shooting,
production halted due to poor weather conditions. During this time, Mark Roybal left Fox,
who was the essential executive towards green lighting the film. This stuff happens a lot.
Somebody who's really passionate and like the reason your project gets picked up,
we'll get fired because executives get fired every week. Then they realized that the new executive
has zero interest in their movie. So the budget was approved for $16 million. They noticed the
budget started getting less and less. It went down to 11. The final week of production
resumed back here in the States. Test screenings occurred and they told him to assemble a cut.
This like this, the day production ended, they were like, just make a cut of it. And he's like,
well, no, it's a long movie and very involved and complicated. It got low test scores. The studio
panicked. The producers assembled a 90 minute version of the film, 45 minutes shorter than the
director wanted. And that tested even worse. This led him to do his final cut of the film,
which is I will say needlessly long. It's about 220. But there are so many movies that have these
just disastrous productions. And this guy may never work again. You know, the only way he's
going to work again is if this cult following builds and builds and builds. And people realize
he's a director with some talent because I enjoyed The Empty Man, although it is a very
unorthodox movie with a lot of problems. It's very unorthodox. The trailer doesn't do it any favors.
No, it looks like a teen horror picture, which it isn't at all. It's a slow burn of sorts.
It's got one of the best cold opens I've ever seen in a movie ever. Yeah, similar to The
Departed where like the credits come up and it's like 25 minutes into the movie and you're like,
wow, that was a great kickoff. Yeah. Awesome. And look, something I complain about constantly on
this podcast, that they nail a pet peeve of mine. They nail the logic of this thing. It's a wild
story. It's a wild premise about an urban legend where if you blow into a bottle on a bridge,
you hear The Empty Man, and then you see The Empty Man. And then on the third day, The Empty Man
takes you. Yeah. And the way they tie it back into the original cold open, the way they explain
why what happens in the cold open happens, it gets into this whole Scientology cult kind of
thing that is behind the summoning of The Empty Man. And that eventually ties into who your main
character is. It's really a lot to take in, but it all makes sense. What do you call that? It's
airtight. So I really like the film. It stars, I can't remember his name. The only thing I know
he was in, he was one of the kids in the Lord of the Flies remake. Yeah. James Badgerdale.
Yeah. I said his name. I said his name. I kept thinking, oh, you said his name. I'm sorry. Yeah.
I kept thinking he was the kid from Big, but it's not. Okay. Yeah. Not him. That's the kid
from American Werewolf in Paris, right? Tom Everett Scott. Tom Everett Scott wasn't in
Big, but I know who you're referring to. I don't know that that kid acts anymore. Maybe he does.
Okay. Well, anyway, I thought it was the kid from Big, but he's in Lord of the Flies.
Um, uh, uh, what's his face is a great cameo on this. Your boy, uh, Steve Root, who I also
mentioned. You really don't listen when I speak. No, no, no, no. I was, I know you met, I remember
you mentioning Steven Root, but do we talk specifically about his, his scene? I want to
speak to his scene. I really liked, I had, cause I've never seen him play this type of character
before. He plays like a real, he's, he's creepy. I've never seen Steven Root be creepy. I don't
think he's done it a few times, but this is like, uh, usually it's got like that crazy eye and he's
kind of hamming it up a little bit. This is a very like, he's a, he's like, feels like a cult leader.
You know, he feels like he could break your neck at any second. He's got a real menace to him.
And he runs the Pontifex Institute, which Pontifex, I believe is, uh, it means the pope.
It's referring to things to do with the pope. So I don't know if that's some sort of shot of
Catholicism or what, but, uh, yeah, the cult, you know, it, it winds up feeling like this big epic
sort of global movie because the beginning is set in this, like a gear, a wrath of God, like, you
know, uh, I guess it's South Africa, but like really out in the wild and there's this big, uh,
rope bridge that looks a lot like the one in temple to doom, but even more kind of scary
and intense. Uh, it opened, it opens when she's throwing everybody over that cliff. That was the,
the most effective throw over the cliff scene I've ever seen, even more so than cliffhanger.
It made my stomach do flips watching it. Um, and you know, the movie is always chasing that
opening. It never quite gets back to that good, but it's all done in, in, uh, in Missouri. Basically
he's inspect, he's trying to find out what happened to this girl who vanished, uh, and it leads him
to sort of piece together what's going on with this cult and kind of try to stop it. And in the end,
he winds up sort of elevated to the head of this cult. It's a wild ride. I mean, I, I will,
did you feel like the running time was warranted? It was a little long, but they made up for it with
certain things. I got to tell you that when she's throwing the guys over the cliff, that was amazing.
Yeah. No, I'm just joking. I'm fucking with you. The, uh, no, uh, I did think it was a little long
in runtime, but I did in the, in the very end, I was like, no, I, I needed all that information.
Like it was, it was, there was a lot to do here. And also too, I want to go back to the Pope thing.
Uh, I didn't know that. And I do think you're, I think you're correct. I think it is some sort of,
um, analogy on Catholicism because three days, the empty man, yeah, that three days Christ rose
from the dead. He's the God. He is the one that will lead us, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Uh, when is Jesus coming back? Well, seemingly never. We can't wait any longer. We now have
to create a Jesus. Anyway, I do think it was, that's an, that's an insightful thing, uh,
that you said. And I think, I think it's accurate. Um, and that's interesting because then that makes
Steven root the Pope. And if you're Catholic, you have to believe the Pope is infallible. That's
he is the conduit between you and God himself. And that's what Steven root plays. He'd say he
delivers the message to them directly from the empty man. Yeah. You know, so that's,
that's interesting, man. Uh, well, thank you, Joe. Um, you're welcome. Yeah. I mean, looking here,
it's the critical response to it was, you know, just, just as dismissive as a lot of critics are
with any horror movie, you know, so many critics just don't get horror, don't know how to separate
the good from the bad because all they see is people getting killed and they're uncomfortable
by that, you know, but, um, it got bad reviews. It says here, they started, they put out trailers
for it a week before the movie came out. Whereas even an indie, generally you start seeing previews
two months before. So they clearly just wanted to bury it, kill it. Um, film school rejects here
as happens with most cult movies, the empty man's audience has started to view the film's
alleged weaknesses as its strengths. I think that's a very insightful point because
oftentimes that those cults are wrong. In my opinion, Southland tales is a cult that,
that after rewatching that I can say that cult is wrong. Like sometimes when everybody hates
something, there are people who just decide that it's good and that because they want to be
different and contrarian. Just a quick diversion. I've never seen Southland tales. It's terrible,
right? It's, it's terrible. And I, I think I discussed on this show that I got the aero version,
which had like the three hour Sundance cut. And I was like, okay, now I'm going to see what I was
missing. And this thing was botched to hell and it just sucks. And I, I love Donnie Darko. It,
and I think the longer version is even worse because it's longer. He gives, you know,
dramatic roles to like John Lovitz, Sherry O. Terry. Like it's a, it's a rough, rough movie to
watch the empty man though. I think there's something to be said about that. The, the,
the film's alleged weaknesses are that it's, it doesn't make sense. It's, it's a bore. It's,
it's, uh, you know, there's so many critics who gave it bad reviews,
but I think the surreal elements of it are what it, what is most effective about it. And what Joe
is saying is, is totally correct. If you're paying attention, they do a really good job of explaining
all this and making it make sense and making it add up. So any critic being like, like this guy
here gives it a D minus and he's like, it's a total bore. The bastard cousin of the bye -bye man or
you know, that's just somebody who's not engaging with the movie. Who's not even trying.
And that's somebody who saw the trailer and made a decision. That's, that's why I thought this was
the bye -bye man. That's how bad the trailer did representing this film. But then you watch it and
you go, Oh, no way. It's so much more. I would equate this film. I almost, it reminded me quite
a bit. It's, it's, it's a less intense, but it reminded me quite a bit of like prisoners or
like that where you're following a guy on a very weird journey. You're not quite sure who you trust
or who you don't. And in the end, you don't really know how you feel about that guy anymore. You
know what I mean? Like it all kinds of turns, it turns on its own ear. Uh, but it's like, I, I,
I thought it was, yeah, I liked it. I really liked it. And I gotta tell you, I was dreading
the runtime. When you said it's cool, I was like, awesome. I want to see it. And then you,
then I put it on and I was like, mother fucker, this is two and a half hours or whatever it was.
Yeah. I was like, God damn it. Okay. But once that cold open hit, I was just like,
this guy clearly knows what the fuck he's doing. So what, you know, it's like a Scorsese movie.
It's like, you know, like you said, the departed, you get past, if you never saw a Scorsese movie
and you saw the departed, you get past that cold opening. And when that title hit, you'd be like,
all right, this guy knows what he's doing. Like, so I'm going to stick around and there's going to
remember in the theater when the, when the departed came on and the dropkick Murphy's or
what, I mean, I was pumping my fist. There's something about it. It's a real like dick on
the table move to just put your credits up that far into the movie. So I think the reason the
runtime doesn't bug me that much is that it almost feels like it's its own self -contained short. And
then the movie starts after that, even though they tie in together very well. Yeah. It feels
like two kinds of different movies, but that, that short film, that opening 20, 25 minutes is
some of the best horror filmmaking I've seen in a while. This guy, David Pryor got his start
doing DVD special features for David Fincher's movies. He was handpicked by Fincher to do all
the extra features. And if you own a copy of fight club or seven or gone girl or any of Fincher's
movies, he loads them up because I think he's a guy who kind of got his film school through
watching commentaries and extras and stuff. So if Fincher gives you the stamp of approval,
I would hope this guy would have a nice long career. But when your first movie is something
like this, that loses a lot of money, that, that gets really bad reviews on warranted or not,
he's going to really have an uphill battle. I think unless somebody loves what he did,
somebody loves the empty man and gives them another shot. And I think anyone who sees it,
especially a horror fan is really going to enjoy this movie, even though it's, it's an unusual ride.
You know, that's what I like about it. I like that it wasn't going through the beats of like,
because there's a version of the empty man that has the same premise and just feels like some
piece of shit, teen horror movie that gets dropped in theaters and nobody pays attention to the
problem is that everyone thinks that's what this is. And it isn't, I would advise you to check it
out and make, make your own mind up. And the randomness of that pisses me off
where first of all, you know, we liked it quite a bit if we're not giving major spoilers away.
Right. But also too, that's what pisses me off about the randomness of this business,
because this guy will, like you said, we'll have to scratch and claw probably to do another thing
when he's got so talented and he, and he, it's not his fault that they mismarketed this thing and that
they were hit with disasters. Yeah. You know, but meanwhile, they let this fucking fantastic
four guy, whatever his name is, you know, to give him eight shots at whatever, you know,
it's like, come on guys. So, um, my hog is up. Definitely up. Uh, this is on HBO max right now.
I don't know how long it will be there, but, uh, if, if you have that service, I'd add it to your
queue. It's the kind of generic nondescript poster and title that almost ensures that this movie will
fall through the cracks and less people talk it up and recommend it to their friends. And, and
that's why we chose to spotlight it this week. I think anyone with a fan for the off beat, a fan
of horror will get a kick out of the empty man. I agree. Treat yourself this holiday season. Uh,
and speaking of which, excuse me, sorry. Uh, November 1st will be another dose of Halloween,
uh, for you with Halloween kills, which we will review on that day. And we're kicking around what
the second film will be. It might be Dune. I'm seeing Dune. So if Joe can, if Joe can stomach
it, we'll do Dune. Yeah, we'll see. Uh, if nothing else, I think we'd have a blast discussing it.
I want to see it. It's the three goddamn hours. Isn't it, isn't it over three?
I thought that because he divided it into two, that it's a reasonable running time,
but I don't know. It definitely looks like it's going to be three hours, but I don't know that
it is. I think what they did is create this incredibly expensive world and incredibly
expensive sets and all that. And then just tore them down. And now if it's a hit, they'll have
put them all back up. It's so stupid on their part. It really is. But he, he divided into two
meaning he just shot half of the book. He didn't have the book. And apparently when it ends,
the story isn't done. You're just like halfway through it. So, well, and that's the thing that,
and, and, uh, you know, we all know Lynch's Dune was even though I kind of enjoyed it,
it's not good. Yeah. And then Jaredowski said his, his never went anywhere. And he said,
when he saw Lynch's doom, he rejoiced cause he was like, I'm not sad. I didn't get to make mine
now because it's clearly an unfilmable idea. I don't think he's wrong there. So that's what
worries me about this is that there's so much in that book that this first half of it is going to
be free fucking hours. Yeah. You know, no, even my, even my friends who re like, I got a buddy who
really loves hard fantasy, like that kind of like beyond, uh, uh, Tolkien stuff, like really hard
fantasy books. And he said, he's tried to read Dune 10 times and it's just so dense and he gets
nothing out of it and can't finish it. And I really do think it's a lot of people are going
to go to this thing, expecting some big wild action fun house and then get Dune. I mean,
Dune is so boring. And if they're faithful to the book at all, the movie is going to be boring too.
I do love Villeneuve. I think he's one of our best directors. However, when I saw that Blade Runner
2049, which everybody tells me I should revisit, blah, blah, blah, but that's a man who is no
stranger to making a long, boring piece of shit. And, uh, that may be what's coming up with Dune.
I don't know, but I will see it in IMAX. I'm excited to see it in IMAX. It's two and a half
hours. That's not terrible. It's less than Bond. And it's got a 90 % on Rotten Tomatoes,
which could mean it's great or could mean it's free guy. We don't know. Yeah. You never know
anymore. I think their reviews are being bought more than ever. I mean, I might. All right. I'm
closer to seeing it than not. Let's put it that way. Closer. If we don't do Dune, we'll do
something, you know, great for the Halloween season. Um, anyway, my, uh, my solo movie corner
will be up shortly. It's going to be over an hour because of the, uh, the kind of less than great
nature of my last one, but I've been recording a long discussion after each movie I watch and I,
it's, it's funny stuff. I'm excited to post it. We will be back. Uh, definitely Halloween kills,
probably Dune. I'm on Instagram and Twitter, the Patrick. Well, I don't even know why we say that
anymore. Everybody knows where we are. You know, I don't get anything to plug. Uh, I got nothing
inside. If you're in New York, go to Joe's sandwich shop. We are the empty men, Joe and I. Yeah. Yeah.
The pop -up is open at the stand every Wednesday to Friday, 12 to 4 PM. And the actual spot is
opening very soon. So keep your eyes open. Well, uh, I am going to pop in. Well, I don't know when
this is going to post, but I probably already have popped in to, uh, the discussion group that's
going on. We love that that's happening. We love that you guys are finding a friend group
out of this podcast. That's so cool. And I, I'm going to definitely pop in tomorrow night and say,
hello, uh, cause I'm home and I got nothing to do past few weeks. I've been busy. Is the movie
watched or just discussed in the group? They, from what I gather, they discuss a movie last week was
Donnie Darko and, uh, they also discuss mental health. I mean, I think it, it kind of spawned
off this mental health solo corner that I did where I kind of just put up, put my problems on
the line. And, um, yeah, just talked about the importance of connecting with people. You know,
I realized my most depressed times during this pandemic were, were the weeks where I isolated
myself. It didn't talk to anybody. So it's a good way to communicate with like -minded people.
All right. As far as I can tell from Emily, it's been a great success. Thank you to Emily,
uh, for all she does. Thank you to all of you for following us on Patreon and telling your
friends and the audience is growing, which we were not expecting. It's fantastic. Thank you all.
Thank you all. And I will also try to pop into the group at some point.
Uh, and, uh, we love you guys. Thanks for everything. We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.