I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell And when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say I'll see you in hell, you know I will
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell.
Today we're talking about the fog.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
It is a foggy morning here in Los Angeles.
A lot of rain coming down.
Amazing how quickly the citizens of Los Angeles go from, boy, we'd do anything
for some rain, just anything.
And it starts raining and then they'll all go, boy, good thing about this rain.
We can really use it, huh?
And then after it rains for 24 hours that everyone starts going,
when's this goddamn rain going to stop?
This rain is horrible.
I chose to live in LA for good weather.
What is this?
Just good to know that nobody else can be happy either, you know?
Well, yeah, yeah.
I love the rain.
I live for the rain.
It means the weather is matching my soul, baby.
I used to love when it rained in LA because it was like a snow day.
Yeah.
Everybody, you know, couldn't do their cheery fucking vapid hikes for five minutes.
You can get invited to walk up a fucking 85 degree incline
and as a means of having fun.
That's right.
I've dropped before we started recording several profanities.
I'm having a rough morning here.
My camera wasn't working.
I didn't sleep well.
I'm unkept at the moment.
Kempt, unkempt at the moment and unkept, quite frankly, as a single man.
Nobody's keeping you.
Nobody's kemping you.
I've been on a real barrage.
We had to stop and start again, not because of my attitude.
But Pat had a battery die out.
And I'm kind of glad we did, because I think we're getting off to a slightly better start here.
Is Kempt a word?
I guess Kempt means you're put together.
You look good.
Yes.
I mean, I never heard somebody say, boy, that guy looks really camped.
You only hear unkempt.
Yeah.
That's my favorite, uh, when I hear two great jokes.
I do.
I'm reading mine Kempt.
It was, uh, how Hitler looked each day, kind of his fitness routine and fashion routine.
I think I've told this before, but I, in my opinion, the greatest, the greatest
joke in any Rodney Dangerfield movie.
And it's surprisingly not Rodney Dangerfield, not that he didn't have great jokes in his
movies, but my favorite joke is from back to school.
And this could be my favorite joke ever.
Like gag ever in a movie is they're looking at the, the guy, Dick, whatever his name is
from son of a beach.
Remember that guy?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Dick Dietrich.
They're at the party with, with his Rodney Dangerfield's house where he's still
married to Adrienne Barbeau.
And she's like the awful wife that's just after his money.
And she's a star of the fog, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh yeah.
I actually, I didn't realize how appropriate this is, but anyway, they're looked.
She's got a clempt painting by the artist and, uh, Dick Dietrich goes to
Rodney Dangerfield.
Your wife was just showing us her clempt.
Yeah.
And, uh, Rodney, he goes, yeah, big deal.
She shows it to everybody.
And, uh, and, uh, Dick Dietrich goes, well, it's marvelous.
Uh, and he goes, yeah, I'm proud of mine too.
I don't go waving around at parties.
And then Dick Dietrich, he goes, it's an exceptional painting.
And then he goes, Oh, the painting.
He didn't need to go all the way to, Oh, the painting, but it makes it funnier.
It's it's great.
It's airtight.
And then, uh, I heard the other day, I watched a Dennis Miller
interview on Craig Ferguson and he told a joke and I was like, I know we
referenced Dennis Miller a lot on here and you know, some of you like them.
Some of you don't, but, uh, it's, I was like, Holy shit.
That's my favorite Dennis Miller joke ever.
And it's, it's so perfect.
So him, uh, he goes, uh, he goes, uh, yeah, I got into a cab.
That was making me laugh already.
He goes, I got into a cab in France.
The driver smelled like he was eating garganzola cheese while getting a permanent
inside the septic tank of a slaughterhouse.
I said, Hey pal, there's an extra five in it for you if you hit a fucking skunk.
All right.
Yeah, that's good.
That's that's good.
That's good old rapid fire reference.
Dennis Miller with the perfect placement of fucking in it.
What is he currently retired or is your radio host?
Uh, he, I think I looked him up for that exact reason.
I was like, I wonder if he tours or anything.
He doesn't have a website.
He has an Instagram that he seldomly posts to.
And when he does, it's like, it'll just be like him and his wife went to
dinner or something, you know, um, I don't think he's doing anything else.
I, if he's also, he's 70, I think.
Oh yeah.
You know, so I was like, he, and in the posts, he'll write like, you know, it'll
be like him and his wife having like a cake or something at a restaurant and
he'll say like, or, or, or, no, that's what it was he watched, he posted about
a movie and he was like, I forget what the movie was and he was like, but it's
so fricking funny, you got to watch it.
And he goes, who doesn't need a little joy these days?
Like it's, there's always like a little thing of like, Hey people, like if we
could all breathe for a second, maybe eat some cake cause everything is awful.
I think even he got broken by everything.
I think even he like was like, I can't even do this anymore, man.
Yeah.
Um, so I don't know.
That's, that's, that's all I know.
I mean, those guys are all kind of getting, yeah.
I mean, they show it, you never see Dana Carvey or spade
without sunglasses anymore.
You know, sunglasses indoors during a podcast is always a sign that
you're unhappy with your aging, but it happens to us all.
Spade, David Spade's got to be pushing 60 at this point, right?
Oh yeah, for sure.
For sure.
Maybe older.
No, he's not, he's not.
Cause that, when that, when that Polaroid book came out, he said he had just
barely passed 50 and that was only like, okay.
But people lie to people.
Yeah, that is true.
He's real.
He seems real big on me.
Like don't talk about, like he'll make jokes about it on the podcast.
Like, yeah, well, we don't need to name the year we did the sketch on SNL.
Like, let's just, you know, man, that's, that's just Hollywood shit.
That's gross.
Still a great looking guy and like hip and still, you know, funny.
And always got two models on his arm.
Yeah, we're all, we're all so broken.
We're all so broken.
I have had, and I can't go into detail on my dating lately, but I've had two
weeks of the wildest encounters, one after the other, but two of the women
have made large issues out of the fact that I am on a, not even a restrictive
diet, I'm doing keto for the month of March where I can eat anything but carbs.
So two of them, uh, came to me talking about how this really, uh, triggered
their disrupted eating from when they were children, eating disorders, um,
long conversations after like one or two dates about how my eating style
triggered, uh, an unhealthy, unhappy eating style for them.
And wow, you know, it's like, I, I like these people.
I don't know that I'm going to continue dating them or not, but it's, you
realize, I don't know if it's the therapy talk or everyone being in, in
recovery and therapy or what, but just me simply going and ordering the type
of food I wanted to eat for dinner, pissed off two different people here in Los
Angeles.
And these were nice, good meat.
It's not like I'm like, Ooh, how many calories in the miso?
I just ordered a bunch of food and ate a bunch of food, but because I
mentioned I'm keto and I can't have sushi rice, it became a big deal.
Really weird.
Disturbance was that you were eating two full racks of ribs in front.
It's my diet.
You've got barbecue sauce.
I'm dying.
Yeah.
Get that kind of like where you, uh, you're talking with the sauce
splashing all over her.
Waitress walks by.
Ooh, they have fondue.
What do you say?
Bring me a couple of the fondues.
Uh, that's just how I diet, babe.
No, um, just, uh, I just feel like even going about your day now, um, is really
hurtful to other people and I don't, uh, you know, of course, are people a little
too sensitive at this moment in time for sure, but it's also just that we're all
so broken that it just takes a light breeze to push us over.
I'm not mad at these women and we all have our past struggles and everything
else, but you're bringing this energy into date one, date two.
What are we going to do?
I mean, we're going to have a population problem because nobody's
going to fuck at some point.
It's almost like you're scared to death.
It almost sounds like you live in Hollywood.
Anyway, folks, listen, no, I, listen, it's tough.
It's, it's, uh, you know, not to pick on LA, but LA is definitely a place
where it's like, I'm going to let you know what I'm feeling.
Like it's very like just on the table immediately, a little more
so than most other places, but also too.
I do to, to, to, to give a point to the, to the, the people on the other side
of the dating table here that you're with.
I also do understand, I wouldn't say it.
I wouldn't say to somebody.
I can't date you because, or, or, or like it's bothering me because, you
know, or anything like that, I would just, I would just back away, but I
got to say, I can't understand.
I've been out with women that are like, yeah, I'm just not into drinking.
And I'm like, sure.
All right.
Well, I'm not going to, there ain't going to be no date to here.
I just wouldn't make it be known.
I just would say, oh, okay.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Or like put on your profile.
Um, no, this, no, that, that's what the profile part is for.
So you don't waste a bunch of your time on somebody who's going
to have a big issue with you.
I, one of these girls was also sober and I tried to kind of explain it to her.
I said, um, or I'm sure she saw it as mansplaining.
I said, here, here's my, uh, issue.
I said, like, we're here on this date.
We're at a sushi place.
I like to have hot sake at a sushi place.
I asked you, is it okay if I have some hot sake you don't drink?
You said, sure.
But if you had said, you know what, it makes me uncomfortable.
I would have said, fine too.
You know, it's not a big deal, but now that it's, it's food, I'm saying
the only thing I can't eat at this entire restaurant is rice.
I want you to order whatever you want.
Um, and you can have some of mine, do it, do whatever you feel.
I'm just saying, don't worry about me at all.
I'm just telling you, if we get a bunch of roles, I can't, I'm not going to eat them.
And I said, don't you see how this kind of is how people interact
and how like relationships work?
You know, like, um, you don't drink.
I do.
So I just have this thing of sake and we get along.
Uh, I don't eat rice.
You do.
So you order sushi rolls and we get along.
And she was just like, I don't understand you allowing me to have food.
I don't think that's how this needs to work.
You don't allow me to have food.
And it's like, I have found myself trapped in these situations.
And I really sit with myself when I get home and ask myself, Pat, look
at it from every other angle.
Could you have been in the wrong here?
Could you have said something offensive?
Could you, and, and, and these cases, I'm really coming up with
the answer of not really, but you find yourself trying to get out of these
holes because it's like, I don't, I don't know what to say.
I'm not telling you what you can and can't eat.
I'm saying, please eat.
Uh, it'll be great.
We'll have a good time.
Look, let me just tell you this.
And I know later you're going to get in your head that you told this story.
Don't it's okay.
I'm not this, this story is fine.
I I'm going to stop telling sex stories.
I don't feel comfortable with that.
All right.
Tilt your mic a little forward.
Little.
Yes.
Yeah.
Um, you, you, you're, you're a hundred percent not wrong.
This is not me being team bro or anything.
You're a hundred percent not wrong.
It's it's there is a way in which to conduct yourself in public
and around other people.
That thing has been, was, was taken away over the last couple of years
because of the lockdown and what you're seeing now are people that are
unable to now readjust to not living online 24 hours a day or people that
didn't get enough experience in real life before that lockdown happened.
And then the lockdown only amplified all of it.
Uh, and then there are people that are like, let's cut the shit and just
get back to it and they're too far in the other direction because they're
not having any sympathy or anything.
You're you're right on the money.
You're not wrong.
You didn't do anything wrong.
And I got to tell you, I, I, I went out with people like this pre
lockdown a lot in LA is it's not LA, it's Hollywood.
Uh, it's, it's, it's just a place where it's like, okay, I'm going to put all
my cards on the table and you're like, no, don't, don't nobody wants to see.
Nobody wants to see your cards.
Uh, yeah, you know, and it's like, but honestly, it's that old, like those,
those, those cliches are cliches for a reason, like your poker face, don't,
you know, you're showing your hand, never let them see you sweat, all that stuff.
Those are all cliches for a reason.
And people, especially in the dating pool, dude, people go on dates.
They start acting like they start acting like the way bar flies act at 2 a .m.
They're like, ah, fuck it.
I came here to drink.
I'll tell you my, what my, I think.
And you're like, no, no, no, no, don't, don't like, like, let's
see the amount of first dates I've had where the woman is just, uh, gone, you
know, by 9 p .m.
And I'm kind of like, God, look, I, look, uh, I, I couldn't, I don't, I
couldn't mean this as less of a threat, but I'm, I'm just kind of like, what
are you, what do you do?
Like, if you go out with a hundred guys and this is what you do on all of them,
you're going to be in some really dangerous situations.
I would never say that to a woman.
It's not my place at all.
Well, like I put you in a place where you're like, I have to get you home
safely and I'm worried about that.
But then you're like, I also don't want to be walking around with this
woman who can't stand up because that makes you look like a maniac too.
Let me interject with a little, let me interject with some, uh, course, not
correcting, but keeping us on course language, just, and I know that, I know
this is what you meant, but I'll say it too.
We can all pretend this world is the way we think it should be.
And it's, unfortunately it's just not.
I've been in that situation too, where you're like, I'm telling,
I've been yelled at by saying to a woman on a date, I don't think
we should go back to my place.
You're too drunk.
That like, for whatever reason that makes a woman, these are generalizations.
So some women, yes, some women and also plenty of men.
Don't get me wrong.
Men being rejected has led to a lot of horrible things, but we are just
guys sharing our own experiences.
Of course.
There's something about telling a woman.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to be able to have sex with you.
You're too drunk.
Even when you say, look, I'd love to have sex with you.
I hope to do it in the future when you're sober, but I can't do it.
I'm giving you my permission.
Come on.
It's like, yeah, sorry.
That's not going to work for me.
Stranger.
I just had four drinks with her.
You could, yeah, I'm going to need a chaperone of some kind to, you know,
maybe a glass up, but like police interrogation things.
So we have some cops sitting on the other side, watching us make
love, something like that.
Fine.
Yeah.
The cop radio is in from the other room.
I say, go for it.
I think you're in the clear.
The, yeah, they're completely respectful.
No matter how many times they do it, no matter how hot the couple is, they're
just, just really respectful and just, they're just there to make sure that
everybody's being considerate.
Definitely nothing like, holy shit, check out the chugs on the one we got going
in room three, none of that cops don't do that stuff.
And by the way, I am also shit faced.
I just happen to have the inkling to be like, in this moment, I feel like I'm
the one that's able to say, I don't think this is a good idea right now.
Yeah.
Uh, well, here's the thing.
Like, like you and I drink Joe, when we, when we go out to drink, we drink.
All right.
But like on the very rare occasion where I'll take a sip and I'm like,
oops, that didn't hit right.
It's time for me to get to bed.
You know that that happens rarely these days, but it happens.
I go home and go directly to bed.
Don't pass go.
I'm like, boy, I'm heading into a weird area.
I don't want to say something weird or piss anybody off.
I'm out.
There's, there's a real lack of that reaction happening now where you're
like out for a Sunday night dinner.
And it's like, what, what do you mean you're going to bed at 2 AM?
You know, I keep having these exchanges and I'm not dating much younger
women either, where it's like they're in college or something.
Dude, let me tell you, I have to work tomorrow.
Yeah, you're in, you're just stepping into it now because of your recent divorce.
Thank you.
Uh, I've, I can tell you from the experience of just being, you
having been in it for this, for the, for the, for all the years of my
forties and leading up, you're, you're in, you're in, uh, international waters
right now there, you're going to start seeing some wild shit because you're
going out with people who are grown.
Yeah.
Where everybody around them for the most part and around you for the most part
is like, it has a family and shit like that.
You're dealing with the people that chose not to do it or that are
getting out of it or whatever.
Or I had the choice forced upon them and the truly damage that too.
Yeah, but it's a lot of people now, male and female that are like, I'm turning it
on, you know, they're, they're full gassed.
They're like, Hey man, I save money.
I have a job.
I don't give a fuck.
Like I'm old enough to realize life is kind of meaningless.
I'm not worried about what anybody else thinks at this point.
You're, you're in a, you're in a, you're stepping into a wild rodeo.
And it can be a lot of fun.
Don't get me wrong, but it can also get kind of sideways, you know?
Yeah, I would say all of these, uh, encounters I've been having have been a
even 50, 50 mix of fun and, and horror.
It's a shame that comedy horror movies can't get as, as perfect to blend as
my dates have gotten of comedy and horror.
But, um, yeah, it's just, it's tough.
And I do think a lot of it is everybody, how they spent that time over the
pandemic, a, not interacting like you were saying with people and being in
their own heads, et cetera, but also reading a lot of self -help and
pseudo therapy and pseudo science and bringing that into the dating pool.
Well, and that's where, I mean, I've had women try to explain like, what, okay.
Here's what just happened here.
Okay.
And I'm like, look, I have two therapists, honey.
You're not, you're not going to blow my mind by, by trying to read into
whatever you think happened here.
What happened is you being a psychopath and now you feel bad about it.
And now you're bringing up a bunch of terms that you don't understand.
Well, and that's the thing too.
Everybody, the, the, the media.
Well, it depends on which, which version of mainstream media you watch.
There's a real left version and a real right version.
But if you watch the, if you watch, I'm a Newsmax guy.
News, of course, if you, I'm Joan, I'm an Alex Jones kind of cat myself.
Uh, no, but if you watch, if you watch the predominantly left leaning media,
which is Hollywood also, they would have you believe that the only people into
pseudo science are like the Joe Roganites and the libertarian crowd.
And then also anybody that leans conservative or whatever.
It's like, no, no, no, no.
Everybody is into it now.
People left, right.
Doesn't matter what your walk of life is.
Everybody is going down these rabbit holes on YouTube and thinking they
understand the human brain and I mean, Jesus Christ, dude, I know people taking
all my conservative leaning friends take ice baths.
Oh, it's so many people out here are taking these fucking ice baths and
are super keto.
That's all my conservative leaning friends or libertarian friends.
And then all my left leaning friends will not shut the fuck up about micro
dosing and it's like, none of you have any, and I'm not saying these things
don't work.
I'm not even saying I wouldn't try them or haven't tried some of them.
I've done keto.
It's, it's, but it's like, Jesus Christ, dude, you're, you are talking with the
authority of Neil deGrasse Tyson right now.
Yeah.
Like you, all you gotta do is walk into a room of people, preferably a bar and
say, I started working out recently.
I never did it.
And you are going to get, holy shit.
Oh, a windfall of experts.
Everybody is a fucking, uh, armchair expert at that point.
What you need to do, how your liver works.
Yeah, I, I can have this problem too, where if you want, I don't get into
YouTube, but I, I have people who are like, they'll tell you something.
They'll be talking to you.
Good friends of mine talk to you for 20 minutes with like passion and fire
in their eyes about some topic.
And you're just like, when did you become this expert on this?
This is, I didn't know you were this into this.
Oh, I just started watching the YouTube channel and you, you realize that
they're just saying what some guy in his basement says verbatim.
He's got no skills.
You've got no skills, but the tool you have decided that you're right.
And everyone in the world is wrong.
And sometimes, by the way, sometimes these people on YouTube are right.
And sometimes they have very interesting points.
Sometimes they're more right than the news that people watch, by
which I mean, correct, not right.
Sometimes, sometimes it's Neil deGrasse Tyson or somebody who is educated.
But the problem is, is now with bite size media, everybody thinks they can
watch 90 seconds and understand what somebody who has devoted
their life to understanding that they're, they have equal footing.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
And people will watch one YouTube.
This is, this is the biggest and nastiest version of this happening is Bitcoin
and how that, that destroyed so many people in America, but it's like,
people will watch one hour of something that, that proposes to have the answers
because everyone is looking for the answers, myself included.
There are no answers.
We're doomed, but everyone is looking for the answers.
So then somebody confidently looking you in the eye on YouTube and telling you
how to fix your life for an hour.
There are people who will just go, yep, that's my life now.
And it's scary.
You know, that's how people lost their entire savings.
It's scary.
Yeah.
And I know everybody into crypto now is an economist and everybody, you know,
Pete Holmes, uh, Pete Holmes phrased it very well once to me.
He said, roses, if you go on the internet, you're going to find
what you're looking for.
And if that's, that's the best summation of it that I've ever heard where it's
like, that's it.
If you have an idea in your head of why you're right about a thing, you can
find something supporting it might take a minute or two, uh, but you'll find it.
Well, these people aren't Googling Bitcoin and they're not Googling
Bitcoin pros and cons.
They're Googling things like how to save my life with Bitcoin or whatever.
And then all, all the answers you get are people who tell you how Bitcoin
changed their life, or it's like people who are like benefits of heroin use.
You Google that.
Okay.
You might find two or three, but you should probably just Google heroin
use and get the full picture, you know, but you're absolutely right.
People type in what they want to see.
They miss all the results.
They don't.
And that's how everyone's living their life.
On a positive note, on a very positive note, before we move to the movie corner,
um, you're going to talk about the Steve Wilco show being renewed for season 17.
The what show?
What I saw right before I logged in this morning, I was like, I wonder if there's
any Hollywood news I can talk about.
Steve Wilcox was Jerry Springer's bald bodyguard who got his own spin -off show
when I was a kid and I just look now and it got renewed for season 17.
Jesus Christ.
Good for you, Steve Wilcox.
Um, I was going to talk, this is something that'll be out at some point.
I don't know when, but my buddy Shane Torres, who's a very, very, very funny
comic, uh, he's have a great bit about Guy Fieri, like where you're talking
about how everybody hates Guy Fieri and he would then list all the humanitarian
things Guy Fieri has done and then like, Oh, but you hate him because he's
got flames on his shirt.
He's very funny.
I saw that.
Um, by the way, women pronounce it Guy Fieri, all of the, all of them do it.
And I want to be like, and that is a, I want to walk out when someone does that.
I know it's the correct pronunciation.
I don't care.
Um, anyway, I went down to, to watch Shane tape as our special this past weekend.
It was amazing.
It was so funny.
I watched both tapings.
I laughed equally through both seeing the same material twice.
I laughed equally as hard.
Uh, he was awesome.
I was so happy for him.
So proud of him.
Bert Kreischer was there.
Uh, I got to, I hadn't seen Bert in a while.
I got to hang with Bert and just talk about like the hang you need when all of
this kind of shit is driving you crazy.
And you just meet up with a guy like Bert and it's just pure laughter.
We're going to just drink.
We're not going to talk about any heavy shit.
You know what I mean?
Like, uh, it was, it was just an awesome, it was awesome.
It was an awesome experience and I really had a good time and I want everybody to
watch Shane's special when it comes out.
I'll watch it.
Yeah.
And then I was, uh, I got this, I have so many South by Southwest stories.
Do we have time?
I guess we have time.
I mean, go for it.
Well, we're going to review this on the show, I'm sure at some point, but I was
at South by Southwest and I got to go to the premiere of Evil Dead Rise.
Very exciting.
I don't want to say anything about the movie, but I am very excited to review it.
Okay.
Very, very excited to review it.
Sam Raimi.
Well, you can tell us you loved it, Joe.
That's fine.
You're allowed to say Evil Dead Rise is the best horror movie I've seen in years.
Mom, me.
For that kind of horror movie.
You know what I mean?
This is not a, you know, speak no evil, you know, or something like that where
it's like about the, you know, you know, nihilistic, you know, you know, the,
the, the family nihilistic view of the family, you know what I mean?
It's not that kind of thing.
Um, it's an Evil Dead movie.
It's got its own thing that it does.
I was underwhelmed by the trailers.
I wasn't excited.
Yeah.
Uh, I wanted to see it enough that when I got the chance to go see this, I didn't
realize it was the premiere.
I just thought it was being a screening being hosted by Bruce Campbell.
Right.
Um, I wanted to see it enough that I went, but I, I was uninterested
enough because of the trailers that I almost didn't go.
And I was like, ah, you should go just go.
I get there.
I realized, holy shit, it's the premiere.
Um, and it wasn't like I got invited or something.
We just had platinum passes at South by Southwest.
And if you got in line early enough, you could go like that was it.
So we went and me and my friend, JT Haberstadt, um, who's also a funny comic.
Um, anyway, it's for Pepitone, correct?
Yes.
All the time.
Saw him open for, um, and dude, just see it, just see it.
I'm not going to say anything else.
It is the best horror movie I've seen in years and it is fucking intense.
Like it made the remake look like peewees playhouse and the remake
was pretty goddamn intense.
This was like, I was like, holy shit.
The theater was going crazy.
It was so fun, man.
Everybody was screaming and cheering and it was awesome.
I can't wait.
Did you stay after when the guy yelled this movie fucking sucks?
I was there.
Yes.
I'll Bruce Campbell, tell him to get the fuck out.
Sam Raimi, I'm not exaggerating, did not say one word during the Q and
a afterwards he let and neither did Bruce Campbell, except for when
he was addressed with something.
Uh, uh, but Sam Raimi literally didn't speak once and it made me
admire Sam Raimi even more.
Cause I was like, he knows like, he's like, this is this guy's moment.
This is this director's moment.
Here's the, some of the cast is here.
It's their time, man.
I'm not, I don't got to sit here and talk about, well, when we created
the franchise and all that shit, he was, he just was like, yeah, you guys got it.
Like it was an awesome, awesome experience.
Also standing in line to get into a movie and being like, did we get here early
enough, are we going to get in?
Like, where are we going to sit when we get inside, like scrambling to find good.
It made it all so exciting.
I was like, I feel like a kid again.
Like I'm going to a movie.
This is awesome.
So it was a great experience.
It was a great experience.
Um, I would say you, it's something you need to, you need to see, uh, it re on
many levels re, uh, invigorated my hope in horror cinema, especially when I found
it after they did get fucked up by the pandemic and they, it fucked up their
production and they still, you know, for a while now on the show, we've been kind
of giving a past and saying like, well, the pandemic clearly fucked this up.
It was supposed to be better and this, that, and the other thing.
But this, when they said like, yeah, we were like, kind of like almost on filming
and then the pandemic happened and we had to shoot the entire last part with
distancing and all that, the fact that it came out as good as it did.
Well, I'm just, I'm so impressed by it.
Like I just, it was awesome and it was fucking scary.
It was genuinely scary.
So, um, see it, see it.
I can't recommend it highly enough and we'll review it when we review it.
I'm pumped.
I think it comes out end of the month, maybe April.
I'm not sure.
I'm definitely going to see it again.
Love it.
Um, and then what else you do down there?
Stand up.
I did stand up.
That was awesome.
Did a show with Freddie Gibbs, the rapper.
He was awesome.
Uh, did a spot at Rogan's new club.
That was really cool.
Did the Creek in the cave.
My friend Rebecca's club did my hour there, which was great.
Did the sandwich summit where we hang out and talk to other sandwich
makers, Pepitone and Caitlin Palufo sat in on that, uh, with, with me
and a bunch of sandwich people.
It was great.
Went met Saul Chappelle down there, which was great.
Went to a party that Chappelle.
I don't know what it was, but red man jumped on stage and just
did a fucking impromptu set.
It was insane.
That video went viral.
Two videos from South by went viral, red man and Bruce Campbell.
And I was at both things.
I saw both in real time happen.
So, uh, it was just a great, great time.
So Shane Gillis hung out with him a lot.
Uh, tone bell hung out with him.
I saw a lot of comics hung out a lot.
Had a great time with Pepitone.
Um, uh, saw some old friends.
What a wonderful time in Austin.
I really had a nice time down there.
Never been down there.
Is it, is it, can you get into things or is it too packed?
Well, you got to get a festival pass.
Right.
And then there's like tiers of the pass you can get in different versions.
If you perform at it, they give you a platinum pass, which is the highest pass.
Yeah.
So you can go to anything, but you still, unless you got a hook up at the
venue or something, you still have to wait in the line and all that, you know?
There's so much stuff going on.
Um, it's kind of, it's overwhelming, but you and I should go to Austin sometime.
Walsh, we would have the time of our lives.
And I know a lot of people down there and a lot of cool places we can go.
And we'd have a lot of pod down there.
I love Austin.
Let's do it, baby.
All right.
Um, let's get to that movie corn.
I'll keep mine short because we, I went, I talked a lot here.
You're fine, baby.
Uh, I gotta talk about a picture called once upon a time in America.
Oh boy.
Yep.
This is such an overrated movie.
It is when you look on letterbox, when you look on IMDb, whatever, it is always up
there near it's in the top hundred, at least, uh, when people talk about the
great gangster movies, it's always on that list, but what's interesting is that
it's, it's place seems to be kind of slipping.
It's not like people amongst our generation are not talking about it a lot.
The previous ones loved it.
A lot of that is because it was Sergio Leone's Irishman.
It was his kind of last, uh, epic film he's done once upon a time in the
West and then good, the bad and the ugly and all that.
And didn't it take him like 10 years to make it or something like that?
Yeah, it was like 12 years between the, his previous movie and this one came
out in 1984 and I saw some heavily edited version when I was a kid and just
remember being bored to tears by the thing.
And as an adult, I felt the same.
It's got, it's got a shortcut of it.
Like, you know, um, a little over two hours that everyone agrees makes
no sense and it's terrible.
It's got a much longer cut.
That's about four hours.
That is the most easily available cut at the moment.
And then Leone had some five hour cut that he always wanted to get released,
but no, it never came out.
So this movie, what's weird, the biggest issues that has are pacing.
It's a four hour movie that will dive into subplots for 40 minutes that never
come back, but then abandon the stories you do care about to the extent that
it's not even really clear.
Um, it's these Jewish gangsters played by De Niro, James Woods, uh, you
know, Burt Young, all these people.
No one seems Jewish.
William Forsythe, um, playing a Jewish person.
Exactly.
You know, like it's, it, I'm not saying, Oh, all Jewish people have to be
like this or whatever, but I'm saying it's a big stretch when you're having
everyone play a Jewish person and no one seems like they've met a Jewish person.
Well, maybe you don't get an ICI German looking man to play a Jewish person.
William Forsythe is as waspy as it gets.
Forsythe looks, he either plays white trash or like a Nazi and he's in
here playing a Jewish guy.
It's crazy, but, um, the it's got, it's got highlights, you know, there's
cool stuff in the movie, but for the most part, it's this endless story of De
Niro is tormented by his guilt cause he got his buddies killed and it's this
thing that spans, you know, 50 years of his life, it is sort of similar in that
way to the Irishman and then that it's about guilt and an old man looking back
on and having regrets and, uh, the De Niro character is obsessed with opium.
He spends all his time in this opium den trying to forget the past.
And it ends with this very haunting shot of him with a big smile on his
face, you know, as all these horrors in his life pass him by, there's good stuff
in it to Niro, you know, forget the, the de aging process they did in the
Irishman, this movie, if he's playing 20 years old, he's got brown hair.
If he's playing 60 years old, they put three streaks of gray in it.
And there's very little else done.
They're just like, you get it.
Um, so it's, there's a lot that confused me about it.
There's a centerpiece of this movie where they go to see Joe Pesci and
you're like, here we go.
And Joe Pesci is playing like an asshole and he sets himself up
as being this big adversary.
And Pesci had been in raging bull.
You know, he was an actor at this point.
He never comes back.
He's got a big intro scene and then he never comes back.
They bring in Danny, Danny Aiello, who's a cop and they want to fuck with him
because he's fucking with their business.
So they swap babies.
He's got a baby in the nursery.
So Aiello gets home, takes his baby's diaper off.
He goes, Oh, I love my beautiful boy.
I love having a beautiful son.
Yeah.
All right.
They take the diaper off.
The camera zooms in on the baby's vagina.
Zooms in.
And then Aiello goes, Oh, what's that?
What is that?
It's a baby pussy.
This is a 20 minute sequence.
That's it's like something out of a dirty Mr.
Bean he's freaking out that they swapped his baby.
And you're like, all right, this is sort of amusing, I guess, despite
the vagina closeup, but why is it here?
Why is it in this movie?
Um, I don't know, man.
I don't know what to tell you.
Is it better than most movies?
Yeah.
It's got incredible cinematography.
It is Sergio Leone.
There's a lot of great stuff.
You know, almost every actor in the film, but man, it's a missed opportunity.
And I do not know how it got its reputation, but I'm glad to see
it kind of slipping over time.
Joe.
Well, I'll stay on theme with things that are too long and not that good.
Yeah.
Talking about your penis.
I went, uh, it was a mix.
It was a compliment.
Yeah.
I went about four episodes into history of the world.
Part two last night.
Joe's been telling me about this.
It's hard to even believe what I'm hearing.
Look, I actually thought the trailer was, was, was kind of funny.
Like I was like, all right.
There's like, there's some funny parts in there.
Um, I know some of the people involved in this thing.
I respect them.
Uh, some of them I would even say are I'm friendly with.
Nick Kroll is, it seems like it's his baby.
He's the EP.
He's in every single sketch in it.
Um, he seems to be, to have taken on the Mel Brooks role.
In this whole thing.
Uh, you know, I re I really respect Nick a lot, like, um, and you know,
this is a gargantuan thing they did was like, so I'm sure it wasn't easy.
Uh, you know, my, my, my concerns started to rise about, about whether or
not it would be good when I started, you know, you see a trailer or two and
you're like, okay, this does look funny, but this is like a cool kid's thing.
Like, it's like a who's who every fucking scene has three people in it.
That would be notable cameos, you know?
Then I was reading about it on IMDB and you see the writer's room and the
writer's room is like 10, 12 people who are already pretty established, you know?
And I'm like, all right, so no Brooks, like it's part of this, but this is
not Mel Brooks's thing and that's not me saying I think Mel Brooks necessarily
should have been at the head of this thing.
Uh, no Brooks in recent years is not, you know, his later work was not great.
And he's 90.
Yeah.
And despite my admiration for the man, but, uh, so, so, so by the time you
watch it, or I like the time I watched it, I was like, this is kind of like
what is happening now.
It's, it's basically fan fiction as a tribute to a thing that people love.
Uh, and we all wanted to see history of the world part two when it was teased
at the end of the first movie and we never got it.
So here we are.
We get it.
Why this thing is like an eight episode or 10 episode series.
I have no fucking idea.
It is way too big and way too much.
You think it's going to be.
Okay.
I guess they're just going to jump around like through the entire, in all of
history and just do cover everything because there's not going to be a part
three and then no, there are running sketches that come back throughout
episodes that they go back to, which.
So tell them about the Kama Sutra.
No, so I'll get to it.
Which makes no sense.
You're like, just, just, just pick the stuff that's funny and just go with it.
Like, and make it tight, even two hour thing out of this.
Like, but now it's just, I knew we were in real deep trouble.
The first sketch is about the civil war.
Ike Barinholtz, by the way, is all over this thing.
He's, he's the second next to Kroll.
He's the other lead.
No disrespect to Ike Barinholtz.
I don't understand how this guy has the kind of weight he has.
Nobody knows who Ike Barinholtz is.
And I don't say that as a diss, like, but he is not a famous guy.
So to be given the helm of projects, like I just don't understand, like
it's, it's very confusing to me.
Joey, it baffles me as well.
I figure he must be super charming or something, but basically it is
just a star fucking culture out here.
And it doesn't matter how big a star.
Like he, he was on the Mindy project.
He's an actor, like he was in blockers and stuff, but he is a guy who like,
even inside comedy people, I'm including myself who feel like
they know everything about comedy.
It would be hard for me to name three Ike Barinholtz films, but
he's hanging in there, man.
He's got a good agent or something.
It's, you know, I haven't seen anything like this since the kid from the office.
Krasinsk.
No, no, no, no.
No, because they weren't hitting home runs.
BJ Novak.
Yeah.
Novak was the other one.
I was like, yeah, like good for him.
But I'm like, what the, how the fuck does he have this much sway?
This is weird.
Anyway, whatever.
A lot of people, the hype machine is, is their skill more than their
writing and, and they can really make that work for them.
I mean, there are people who just make whole careers out of
believing their own shit.
You know, it works for people.
The first sketch is, is about the Civil War.
It stars like Barinholtz and it's, it's fine.
It's, it's, it's not great, but it's, it's not like offensively bad.
Then you hit the second sketch starring a guy we know, Kumail Nanjiani.
And I was like, my buddy Parvesh is the other guy who I do know, but I haven't
seen the sketch, just a picture of it.
And he's pitching the Kama Sutra.
It's Kumail pitching the Kama Sutra.
And you're like, oh, this is kind of funny.
And like, he's doing like, he's doing like almost like a wedding planner energy.
And you're like, oh, this is going to be funny.
And then the gag is the book is called the Kama Sutra, and it's
about melding soup with sex.
And it's just bad, like bad, lowbrow dick joke after bad, lowbrow dick joke.
Like, you know, like this isn't a joke, but it's literally stuff along the lines
of like, and in this one, you can really clam or chowder if you get what I mean.
Like, it's like literally jokes that like that.
And I'm like, what the fuck is this?
Like, this is, this is a bad pun or play on words.
I don't even know which that would fall under.
And I was like, and like, it's like dick jokes.
This is weird.
Then the third sketch happens.
And the third sketch is about the Russian, my, you know, the, the, the
Romanovs and Russian migration or the Jewish migration and, and, and, and
Stalin coming into power and all that stuff.
And this thing starts and Kroll comes in and I'm like, and he comes in and
he's like, his name is Schmuck, which I thought was funny.
And I'm like, okay, this kind of feels like a Mel Brooks thing.
And then it just isn't funny anymore.
And it, it then goes into the Romanov family led by Danny DeVito and their
henchmen, Rasputin played by Johnny Knoxville, who appears and disappears
by farting upon which the joke is made, Rasputin.
We're in trouble here.
People were in trouble.
This is sketch three.
I'll tell you why we're in trouble.
Tell you why we're in trouble.
Why didn't they say ass be tootin?
It would have made me almost as mad.
All right.
I'm just wondering, but I wonder, was it discussed in the
room? I'd like to know.
But just by this part in this thing, it's just like every fucking thing in
this, like Nick Kroll walks in, the vendors are all being played by different
like sort of notable cameos, like Guy Branham, I guess, you know, I like it,
but I think he was a writer on it.
So I don't even know if he's supposed to be a cameo or not, but he plays a
part in it.
But my point is, is every single part you got Johnny Knoxville playing
Rasputin, you're like, what, like, guys, why is every role in this crammed
with somebody that I might recognize?
It's too much.
And it's not what Mel Brooks would do.
Mel Brooks had a crew of players.
He had a, he had a, what's that called when you have a repertoire?
Yeah.
And he used them and they were great.
And like, and what, and like, this is just like, it's, it felt star fuckery.
It just felt, I don't know.
There's a joke at the beginning of that sketch where there's a vendor selling
bot seeds because you can't sell, you can't grow a Russian bot without seeds.
I texted Pat last night and said, I wouldn't pitch that fucking joke 15
minutes into the first day of a writing room brainstorm.
This thing made it to the final cut of episode one.
Like, like insane to me.
Some of the bits in this.
And I just kept watching the second episode.
I was excited because I saw that Richard Kind was in it and they do a curb
parody, which has been done many, many, many, many times.
So they've got JB Smoove in it.
It's the story of Jesus and it's a parody of curb.
They've got JB Smoove in it as one of the disciples.
And I'm like, oh, this is going to be funny.
And then he's waiting to meet with Judas.
And I'm like, oh my God, Larry, David's going to be Judas.
This is going to be great.
And it's not, it's Nick Kroll in the Larry David role, but he's not doing a Larry
David impression, which I know Nick could do.
So you're like, I don't understand.
Like what were you trying to get Larry David, but you couldn't.
And if you couldn't then don't do the, that's the thing Richard Kind is in.
And they don't even really set Richard Kind up as like the funny cousin, like on
It just starts to get fucking confusing.
Then they go back to the story of Jesus in later episodes.
And at that point you're off the curb bit.
It it's just, it just doesn't make any sense.
I don't understand why.
And this is not a shot at this production.
I think probably what happened in this production is you got 10 writers who
have a lot of writing experience and a lot of celebrity, quite frankly,
in a room with Mel Brooks.
Mel Brooks is obviously going to have the weight that he is going to throw around.
Yeah.
You've got, there's an excessive amount of fucks and dick jokes in this thing.
Which is not like Mel Brooks at all.
So you've got like modern writers who are trying to make it edgy and like very
Seth Rogan -y up against like Mel Brooks who's, who's injecting, I assume the like
old school traditional Mel Brooks, it just doesn't work.
It's a, it's a, it's not a good recipe for anything.
It doesn't make any sense.
Um, it's bloated.
It's too big.
It's too fucking long.
Like everything else, this fucking sit town does anymore.
They, it can never just be enough.
It's got to be the most and it's got to be so indulgent and so high profile at
the cost of the product itself.
Um, and, and then that's where you end up.
Much to my surprise, the one of the, there were two sketches that really made me
laugh.
Josh Gad was one as Shakespeare, where it was Shakespeare's writing room.
Yeah.
And, uh, that was funny.
Like Josh Gad playing Shakespeare, like, and like being the classic guy who's
running the writing room and shitting on everybody and, um, Lauren Lapkit,
Lap, Laura Lapkis, Lauren.
Yep.
She plays, by the way, Pat, there's no payoff for this bit.
She comes in dressed as a guy and she keeps going, I'm a man.
I have a, I'm a man.
See, like, and it's, it's clearly like, oh, she's a woman pretending to be a
man, obviously Pat, they never pay it off.
There's no, there's no explanation.
Why are you doing a Shakespeare and love parody in 2023?
Doesn't make any sense.
Oh, Walsh.
Can I tell you one of the jokes from the sketch that I said was one
of the only funny sketches?
Shakespeare likes, is Shakespeare in love with the idea?
Yeah.
It's this kind of shit.
So, which I feel like is either somebody trying to be Mel Brooks or Mel Brooks
being like, doing like a thing he would have done in 86.
Right.
Um, anyway.
Is Mel Brooks in the show?
Um, aside from the de -aging bit they do with him at the beginning, cold
open of the first episode, he has not returned to know he, he narrates, he
narrates, he doesn't narrate the sketches.
He just reads the title.
So he'll be like the life of Jesus.
And then it starts.
Anyway, um, um, I don't like that movie history of the world part one.
So I knew this wasn't going to be up my alley really, but.
Well, even the movie, it's like the first act in, in Rome is great.
And then after that, you're like, who cares?
Yeah.
You know, but, um, except for the, it's good to be a king line, but, um, it's,
it's, it's, um, it's, um, what's it called?
Oh, but that sketch is pretty funny.
Like with Shakespeare being a dick and it's actually built on a
thing that you kind of are aware.
I mean, not that the other sketches aren't, but.
You know, there's a whole thing with Jack Black where he's playing
Stalin, but he's like the laughing stock of the Russians.
And I'm just like, I don't understand if that really happened to Stalin,
but that's not how anybody remembers Stalin.
So why are, why are we doing this bit?
Like, I just don't get it.
And then the other really, the funniest sketch in the whole thing was
Barinholtz played Alexander Graham Bell.
And it's them inventing the phone, him inventing the phone and testing
it for the first time.
And Sam, um, what's his name for him?
I think you should leave the kid that was in the wolf werewolf movie.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, witherspoon.
What's his name?
Worthington Sam Worthington.
You don't know what I'm talking about.
I do know who you're talking about.
He plays, he plays like a guy that.
Yeah.
He plays a guy that works for bell and he prank calls him from the other room.
And it's the first prank call ever.
Yeah.
And Alexander Graham Bell is like, it's just very funny.
Cause he's like, he's like, you can't be my mother.
My mother is dead.
And he's like, and he's like, if you're my mother, what's your last name?
And Sam is like bell and Barrow, it's like that confirms it.
It must be my mother, you know, it's very funny.
And then Sam is like, show me that Dick and he gets them to send
them a Dick pic with the phone.
And it's a funny sketch.
It's a very, I think you should leave style sketch, but that's when
I realized I think they're letting people come into this thing, like movie
43 style and just write their own thing.
Right.
Jack Black as Stalin has like three musical numbers.
Uh -huh.
And I'm like, I think they're letting these guys come in and be like, here's
my idea, like, like an SNL thing.
We're going to bring you into the writer's room.
We want you to pitch something.
Let's figure out what would work great for you because that entire sketch,
I'm like, this is a fucking, I think you should leave sketch.
So Sam Richardson is his Richardson.
Yes.
So anyway, um, yeah, he's great at it.
He's very, very funny at it.
Um, but that's, there's a kind of funny thing with Seth Rogen is Noah.
You know, it's not without its merits.
It's not like, like crawl will have its moments where it's like, that's kind
of funny, you know, like, but it just all seems.
Uninspired.
Like there are stuff where there are sketches where I'm watching Nick
Crow and I'm going, I know he could do something different here.
I know he's capable of it and he's not doing it.
And I wonder if it's because he's like, just uninspired or underwear.
I don't know.
I can't speak for the guy.
I can't speak for anybody.
Or maybe it was a great show and the network fucked it up.
I don't fucking know, but.
You never know.
I mean, it might, it might be that Mel Brooks is in the writing room.
I mean, who knows that can be annoying too, when you're trying to appease some
guy and it's, well, you know, I'm the one who created this.
So, you know, who knows?
Well, Mel Brooks has historically said, no pun intended has
historically said to people like.
Well, of course that's the right, right idea because I'm a genius.
Like he said that to Cronenberg, I think when they were doing
the fly or whatever, you know, I've heard he's pretty difficult.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
And it's also his last hurrah probably, you know, so I can't have, I don't know.
Anyway, that's my only movie corner.
I talked long enough about that.
Jesus Christ.
All right.
Well, we might as well just get to the fog, you know?
Yes.
I rewatched the fog and basically the premise is this here's something
interesting I noticed about the fog on this viewing the story that John
Housman is telling at the beginning, the ghost story about the ship
crashing into the Bay and blah, blah, blah.
Um, he's saying tomorrow will be the hundredth anniversary of this event.
And that's why all the ghosts are coming back to town.
Yes.
The movie starts John Housman telling this story then on April 20th, 420.
The movie is called the fog and carpenter, a self -proclaimed pothead.
Oh, well, that's, I'm sure that's an inside joke.
It made me like it a little more.
Um, but yeah, the, the gist is the fog is coming to this small town in the
fog is like ghost pirates, um, who are coming to sort of reclaim their treasure.
Well, seek their revenge, right?
Because they were a boat of, uh, tilt your mic down a little bit too.
I don't know what happens with this mic, why it keeps tilting upwards.
I stay back just cause I have a tendency to pop.
Um, yeah, they, they were a leopard, they were, they were, uh, ref, they were
people that were struck in with leprosy that had a lot of money that offered the
town a great sum of money to allow them to build a leopard colony, uh, a mile or
two away from that, from the town, the sleepy town, the town, uh, and it was an
lead by a priest, uh, sabotage the crew, uh, let a fire that drew them into the
rocks instead of to safety to dock the boat because they were so disgusted by
having a leopard colony on their grounds.
Uh, and now a hundred years later, they're back to reclaim or to take their revenge
in the novelization and they have to take six lives because six people sabotaged
them a hundred years prior in the novelization, they make it very clear
that every victim of each of the six is a descendant of one of the original six.
They only make it clear in the movie that how how Brooke is a
descendant of one of them.
His grandfather was the priest and he's himself as a priest, uh, which is
confusing because how does a priest have, I just realized that as I'm talking,
maybe his grandfather wasn't a priest.
He just was trying to build a church.
I don't know.
Anyway, um, this movie, first of all, I got to get the 4k.
I have it on DVD from 10 years ago.
Um, I watched a review of the 4k.
The kid who reviewed it on YouTube was like, this is the second best looking of
the John Carpenter 4k restorations.
This movie truly benefit the thing.
He said Prince of darkness was the best looking one of my
least favorite of his movie.
Me too.
Uh, he said, he said, because of the amount of black in this movie, uh, he
was like, this is, this truly benefits from the 4k and I was like, yeah, I
believe it when I see it and then watching the DVD like five minutes and I
was like, I got to get the 4k.
I can't see a goddamn thing.
Yeah.
No, the, I had just gotten the 4k.
The, the picture is the selling point.
It's absolutely incredible.
Like a lot of these for whatever, whatever, excuse me, whatever reason,
the 4k line seems to do the best stuff with, uh, 80s movies.
It's like, cause they were all shot on 35 millimeter film, but they're
not so ancient that the prints are damaged.
And since they're making these 4k discs off the Prince, um, these 80s
movies just wind up looking fucking incredible.
I mean, this, this one really does.
I agree.
Um, but onto the movie itself.
Yeah.
Uh, let me start by saying, you know, the premise in the plot.
Let me start by saying, in my opinion, this is Carpenter in.
He is in his top form here.
I mean, this is, you've got Carpenter right after Halloween,
still working with Debra Hill.
Uh, Jamie Lee Curtis, he's married to Barbeau.
He's telling a ghost story.
It's true horror.
Uh, Tom Atkins, he's got the pull to get Tom Atkins in this thing.
Janet Lee, John Housman, as I complained about history of the world, filling out
all these small parts with notable people.
Uh, I think that was an example of not doing it well or doing it for
cache or, or doing it more for, for clicks rather this to me was doing it for cache.
Like, is there any better cold opening idea to a horror movie than having
John Housman telling a ghost story to children around a campfire right away?
You're pulled in.
You're like, here we go.
This is all going to be awesome.
I'm going to say this though, real bizarre that this British storyteller
is taking a bunch of young boys out to tell them stories.
Also, who is he?
Who is he in relation to the town, the town storyteller?
It's, I think it's supposed to be, I didn't think it was weird
because when I was a kid, I was in Cub Scouts.
I felt like it was Cub Scouts stuff.
Like I felt like it was like a, a scouting thing or something.
But, um, but, and it's taken me until this watch to truly enjoy the movie
to the cause I always was disappointed watching it prior.
I always thought like it was going to be the, the fog lands and it's
going to be a bloodbath and that's not what it is, uh, Carpenter in fact
said in an interview when a great interview, I think it's the one, I think
it might be the one where they're like, he's on Dick Cavett with King and.
Yeah, everybody.
I think that's, I don't remember anyway, but he said this was an,
originally it was a children's movie.
He wanted to make like a fun kids, like ghost story.
And the studio was like, no, no, no, you're going to make an R rated
horror movie and we're going to, you know, so he adulted it up.
But, well, I watched some of the supplements on here.
There's a bunch on the, on the 4k.
I mean, basically he said, I sat down and watched kind of the first cut of this
movie and I was devastated because I knew I had a movie that did not work in any way.
So they had to reshoot roughly a third of the movie.
A lot of that was adding in gore and stuff, although it still doesn't feel
like a gory movie to me at all.
But, um, by today's standards, this would be a kids movie.
Yeah.
It'd be more like scary stories to tell in the dark or something like that.
But, uh, yeah, I mean, look for me, it's about the visuals.
It's about the vibes.
It's about like kind of that, that spooky old fashioned lighthouse
kind of ghost story fun.
Um, but I did, I never liked this movie when I was a kid and I don't like it now.
It's not that I, it's not that I hate it.
Um, it's an enjoyable way to spend 90 minutes.
I just, Carpenter's stuff for me is always massive hit me, like the
thing or a pretty big miss.
And, and to me, he's about 50, 50.
Um, I think he's got more misses than people give him credit for.
Uh, and the fog is just like the story's not there, you know, like it's
as if you look at it as a slasher where the fog is Jason or something, I guess
maybe then it just kind of works like that.
But the plot of needing to kill six people and that this one's number three
or whatever, it just really feels convoluted to me and it did not work.
That's, that's interesting.
I, I disagree.
I felt like it was a airtight story.
I felt like it was simple.
Just this terrible thing happened.
They come back to get their revenge.
They take six for the six that wronged them.
I thought that all made perfect sense and was super airtight.
I loved it.
This is everything I loved as a kid about horror.
Uh, and as an adult now, I, I, I'm very excited to purchase the 4k and it also
reframed the way I look at the carpenter movies that I don't like.
I'm like, maybe I do need to give Prince of darkness another chance.
Um, you know, I, I feel like this outside of the thing, this is him and his best.
This is the best direction he's done.
Halloween obviously is very well put together, but Halloween from a directing
standpoint is a little, a little more of a run and gun indie, you know, in the
way that you love reservoir dogs.
This to me is way more in the way that you would love the pulp fiction or something.
This is a guy that's got some money now.
He's got a budget to work with and he utilizes it very well.
I really love the first 20 minutes where like all the weird stuff around
town is happening.
I think that's beautifully directed, beautifully shot, super effective.
I just, I don't know.
It's something about me.
A pirate ghost doesn't scare me.
Never will.
Maybe it's cause they were the villains in Scooby -Doo or something so often, but
it's just kind of like, all right, I don't care about this.
Um, and the characters, I feel the same, you know, they got, you got barbo,
um, kind of confined to one set for most of it as like the radio DJ.
You got Holbrooke, you got like, oh yeah, you got, uh, Curtis and Atkins is kind
of like, they're, they're doing a meet cute.
She's a hitchhiker.
They got a nice little chemistry, but I'm not like loving any of these people.
You know, I, I don't know.
There's something about it that just doesn't click into that.
Above average territory for me.
I see it more as an average eighties horror movie, if I'm being honest.
Um, with some perks for sure.
Well, don't refer to Curtis's breasts that way.
That's not very nice.
Perkers, I call them, uh, by the way, Jamie Lee Curtis winning best supporting
actress for everything everywhere all at once is one of the most baffling awards
the Oscars has ever done.
And this is one of the strangest, uh, award shows ever.
I mean, they just keep making bigger and bigger mistakes with each passing year,
but Jamie Lee Curtis, so you get a movie.
That's a breakthrough for being about Asian people.
We're awarding the old white lady who is playing a woman with hot dog fingers.
Um, Jamie Lee Curtis has been better in every movie she's been in.
I felt like that was, I felt like that was like, isn't it weird to see
Jamie Lee Curtis not hot, like, like, you know what I mean?
Like I thought she was good at it and she's funny.
Like, but I'm like best act.
What?
That's why I just can't get over it.
Yeah.
It was really strange.
Uh, that, that whole crew at the Oscars, the three of them hearing when they
mentioned their, I'm like, Oh, for Christ sakes guys, can you please with this?
It's like, I know you weren't on top for the entirety of the last 40 years, but
you had a really good career and the way you're acting is gross.
Uh, I don't know what to tell you.
Like I never, yeah, as we've said privately and now we'll say publicly, I
never thought I'd have, I would say I've had enough of short round.
Yeah.
It happened quick and Fraser, Fraser with that speech.
Oh my God.
Um, yeah.
So I'm looking at Carpenter's IMDB before we wrap up here.
Yeah.
Uh, this is right in the sweet spot.
He got, you got Halloween, you got Assault on Precinct 13, then
Halloween, then someone's watching me, which is where he met Barbeau.
And she said it was the best ever TV movie script she ever read.
Then you got the fog, then you got escape from New York, right?
Then you got the next thing he directs is Prince of darkness.
This, this, so, so I'm, I'm, I'm on the right track here.
I w I want to rewatch Prince of darkness and see, okay, maybe I missed out because
I know people that love that fucking move.
They love it over the pandemic.
It did nothing at all for me.
Um, but yeah, they do.
It's got its fans for sure.
And it's interesting.
Then you jump to they live.
Great.
And this is a sort of different, uh, side of him.
Now you get into the more 80, you know, we're already in the eighties,
but you get into the eighties, more eighties vibe stuff.
You got, they live.
Why is big trouble and little China not on here?
Is this just writer credits?
Oh, I'm a writer.
Could have an actor because carpenters in the fog too.
He didn't write trouble and little China.
Well, anyway, you got, they live then big trouble, little China, which are
like the more fun versions of eighties carpenter, uh, certainly less dark.
I didn't hear Christine in there either.
Well, cause he, why the hell is director not showing up on
goddamn IMDb Jesus Christ.
Everything is so stupidly complicated.
All right.
They live.
Oh boy.
Seems like the thing wasn't on there either.
Okay.
The fog escape from New York, the thing, Christine star, man.
Yeah, that's a run big trouble and little China Prince of darkness.
They live guy was batten fucking thousand for a minute there.
Memoirs of an invisible, terrible body bags fun, but not great in the mouth of
madness and almost flawless run from it's a good run up through and including
94 that started in like 74 74 is dark star, then assault on precinct 13, then
Halloween, his Elvis movie is in there.
Someone's watching me great with Kurt Russell.
It's great movie.
Is star man any good as a kid?
I hated it.
Cause it was too like drama focused versus like, I thought he was going
to have like powers or something.
I guess he does, but I love star man.
Uh, yeah, I do.
I like star man a lot.
Been a while.
Then after that though, is where you run into trouble village of the
dam to escape from LA vampires, ghosts of Mars, ghosts of Mars, maybe a low.
It, it is then the ward, which the ward at least is a sort of return to form,
even though it kind of sucks.
Never saw the ward.
Starring one Amber heard.
Oh, okay.
Uh, so anyway, I never saw the that.
And I also never saw Joe Dante's, uh, the whole, I bought that on blind faith.
Cause I was like, it's Dante.
It's got good reviews.
It's a horror movie starring kids.
It takes place in the suburbs.
This has to be good.
Yeah.
Uh, I think I watched it once and then immediately threw it into a bin.
I respect Dante, but I was like, I can't, I got limited shelf space here.
Yeah.
I just sold my, uh, blue ray of it for $30.
So it must be out of print.
Oh, well I got my blue ray somewhere.
I'll sell it.
I think I paid 399 for it.
All right, folks, that's the show.
We'll be back next time with a knock at the cabin and, uh, something else.
We're not sure yet what, but, uh, probably a classic.
And then next month, I think we'll get into, uh, what's that evil dad, evil
dad, I think scream six, probably.
Right.
Definitely.
I'm seeing that this weekend.
I'm pumped, pumped.
So, um, we'll be back.
We'll, oh, plugs.
Well, no, we don't plug on the second.
We plug on the first and third.
All right.
I'm not going to plug.
We'll see you next time, and we'll see you in hell.